<jobs>
  
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Product Designer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[83799505]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[10/31/2021 06:09:29 UTC]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></company>
    <remote><![CDATA[false]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY, USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[New York]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[New York]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[United States]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><br>As a Senior Product Designer, you will drive design from early-stage feature discovery through usability testing, final delivery, launch, and full-stage life cycle of improving the product experience. Comfortability with an agile, sprint-based workflow, and a passion for working with product teams to develop use-cases and high-level requirements will be required.<br></p>
<h4>Responsibilities:</h4>
<ul>
<li>Utilize user-centered research methodologies to define and visualize product-related hypotheses and recommendations.</li>
<li>Leverage research findings to identify actionable values, and use them to inform design decisions.</li>
<li>Facilitate workshops, broad stakeholder ideation, build shared understanding and consensus, and help develop use cases and high-level requirements.</li>
<li>Produce storyboards, user flows, journey maps, and wireframes that effectively communicate detailed user actions.</li>
<li>Participate in usability research and synthesize feedback into iterative design enhancements.</li>
<li>Prototype design solutions that meet measurable business goals and user requirements.</li>
<li>Deliver meticulous, high-fidelity production design deliverables to engineering teams, and contribute to a component-based design system.</li>
</ul>
<h4>Your Expertise</h4>
<ul>
<li>8+ years of experience as a user-experience designer working in FinTech, or a consumer-focused technology.</li>
<li>Proficiency in a variety of digital product design/prototyping tools, including Figma, Sketch, and Adobe Creative Suite.</li>
<li>A portfolio demonstrating strong UX and UI design solutions to real-world business cases.</li>
<li>Mastery of best-practices for user experience design, including usability principles, user research methodology, testing techniques (A/B, Multi-Variant), design theory, and interaction design.</li>
<li>Excellent communication, facilitation, interpersonal and analytical skills including the ability to break down complex problems and clearly communicate with diverse, multi-disciplinary teams.</li>
<li>Passionate about opportunities to constantly improve user experiences, and aptitude for big thinking.</li>
<li>Ability to work proactively and efficiently in a fast-paced, occasionally ambiguous working environment. </li>
<li>Bachelor’s degree in design, human-computer interaction (HCI), or equivalent professional experience.</li>
</ul>
<h4>Your Perks:</h4>
<p>We benefit from the great work our employees do each day. That is why we are committed to providing a variety of awesome benefits to help them live their best lives.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<strong>Competitive salary </strong>because we value your experience and expertise</li>
<li>
<strong>Unlimited vacation / sick days </strong>because everyone deserves time for R&R</li>
<li>
<strong>Employer</strong> <strong>contribution towards health coverage </strong>(including vision & dental) because your physical health and well-being is important to us </li>
<li>
<strong>Various fringe benefits</strong> such as 401k, Parental Leave, FSA/HSA, and Employee Assistance Programs because health coverage is more than just choosing your yearly plan </li>
<li>
<strong>Flexible work environment</strong> because we are a geographically dispersed team and we believe in balance</li>
<li>
<strong>Pet insurance</strong> because all of your beloved family members should have coverage too</li>
<li>
<strong>Weekly lunch stipend </strong>because there is such a thing as a free lunch! </li>
<li>
<strong>A close-knit team </strong>of enthusiastic, collegial and driven people to work alongside in a highly meritocratic environment because teamwork makes the dreamwork</li>
</ul>
<p></p>
<ul></ul>
<figure><iframe style="width: 500px;height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/o92zit2jRO0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[Full Time]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockfi/jobs/5539024002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/job/logo/83799505/blockfi-logo-512x512.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/jobs/83799505-senior-product-designer-at-blockfi]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockfi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[Thu, 16 Sep 2021 05:48:49 UTC]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[Thu, 16 Sep 2021 21:31:16 UTC]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7eefa976-25ba-4497-9343-24e88aecb41f]]></employer_id>
    <taxonomies_category><![CDATA[UX / UI Design,Engineering And Tech]]></taxonomies_category>
    <featured><![CDATA[false]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[UX / UI Design]]></category>
  </job>
  
</jobs>
