<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[VP of Customer Service]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Strike]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://beta.strike.me/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Strike&#39;s mission is to build a more connected financial world.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strike allows users to send and receive money anywhere, instantly, with no fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strike is built on top of the Bitcoin network - the largest global, interoperable and open payments standard. Strike believes that open payment networks enable universal participation in the financial system, ushering in a new digital economy with truly borderless money transfers. Strike leverages Bitcoin’s open payment network to offer users the first global peer-to-peer payments app and a novel bitcoin-native neobanking experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Role:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strike is looking for an experienced Customer Service leader to establish a vision, design excellence in service delivery, grow a team and execute in a fast-paced environment. Strike is expanding internationally and this is an opportunity to take ownership of key functions in the CS department at a high growth fintech company. Join as a key member of the senior leadership team that will bring Bitcoin payments to the world. The ideal candidate should have experience hiring and developing top-tier talent, scaling support operations during hypergrowth, managing key stakeholder relationships, and executing on plans that deliver amazing customer experiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive service delivery, workforce management, and operational excellence for the customer service team as Strike scales globally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage in vendor outsourcing negotiations to scale the customer service operation globally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work alongside user experience and product to make decisions around planning and implementing new channels for support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Oversee support operation and ensure quality, productivity, and success objectives and key results are met&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive a roadmap of initiatives to deliver operational excellence in partnership with key cross-functional stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the delivery of data driven insights and reporting on the health of the support operation to leadership and key stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;10+ years of proven track record building, leading and scaling operations or support teams, preferably in fintech or financial services, with understanding of card services, disputes, fraud, compliance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated success hiring and developing high performing leaders and their respective teams across multiple functional areas and locations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Devotion to setting and achieving extremely high performance and quality targets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding communicator and influencer with experience driving stakeholder relationships&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience scaling multi-lingual, multi-channel support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://beta.strike.me/jobs?gh_jid=4004927004&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/712431/strike.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[strike@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[28384812-e332-465c-ba22-66f5df8ede20]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Strike]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Consensys]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.consensys.net]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States, Seattle, San Francisco, New York, London, Australia, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About ConsenSys&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At ConsenSys we have a vision of a world where data sovereignty and financial well-being is accessible to every person and organization. We believe Ethereum and decentralized protocol technology is a more trustworthy and equitable foundation for how we create and share value across the web. On this trusted, open source foundation, we can accelerate the world’s transition to a universally accessible network of distributed participants where transparency, security and freedom are fundamental.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our product suite, composed of Truffle, Infura, Quorum, Codefi, MetaMask, and Diligence, serves millions of users, supports billions of blockchain-based queries for our clients, and has handled billions of dollars in digital assets. As the leading Ethereum software company, ConsenSys enables developers, enterprises, and people worldwide to build next-generation applications, launch modern financial infrastructure, and access the decentralized web. To learn more about ConsenSys, and explore our products and solutions, visit &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://consensys.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;http://consensys.net/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The trust and transparency that blockchain delivers has the potential to change the way the world works.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role is a Sr. Software Engineer working on Quorum Blockchain Service, delivering an enterprise-grade consortium blockchain as a PaaS offering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Quorum Blockchain Service is a fully managed ledger service that gives users the ability to grow and operate blockchain networks at scale in Azure. It provides unified control for both infrastructure management as well as blockchain network governance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;These capabilities require almost no administration, allowing you to focus on app development and business logic rather than allocating time and resources to managing virtual machines and infrastructure. In addition, you can continue to develop your application with the open-source tools and platform of your choice to deliver your solutions without having to learn new skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The team is searching for a highly motivated engineer who will join us in making blockchain technology broadly available to enterprise customers and our partners who serve them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The team is looking for an experienced Software Engineer with full stack experience who can drive evolving our architecture to scale with the reliability, performance, and features required to support the needs of a growing customer base. Our team works in an agile environment where each team member will have opportunities to innovate, contribute, and collaborate towards the mission of the team. As a Principal Engineer, you will get exciting opportunities to work on cutting-edge technologies across a variety of platforms and help to build out a services platform for a variety of future products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In this role, you will be executing on a strategy for delivering permissioned blockchains at scale. You will be working with ConsenSys Quorum and Azure technologies to deliver Quorum Blockchain Service and related capabilities. You will be working on projects and cross team initiatives for which you will have to be proficient at creating and maintaining warm and productive working relationships with other teams. Additionally, you will mentor other team members to design and deliver world class solutions that our customers will love.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Required qualifications:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;7+ years’ experience building and shipping production grade software or services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BS/MS in Computer Science or equivalent or 8+ years of industry experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience owning services in production&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Preferred qualifications:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience developing with or on Ethereum or ConsenSys Quorum&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A strong technical background and solid foundation in software engineering principles and architecture design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent customer and partner focus; able to understand their needs through a data driven approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exceptional problem solving, analytical, and communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building out cloud native microservices architectures, especially on Azure or AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience contributing to open source software, especially in the Ethereum ecosystem&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience participating in an on call rotation as a developer on call for incident response&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with any/all of the following technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;C# and ASP.NET core&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;TypeScript and NodeJS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Golang&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ethereum smart contract development with Solidity and/or Viper&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SQLServer or other similar RDBMS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Azure Active Directory and/or other OIDC-capable identity management systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Infrastructure as Code and related tooling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Terraform&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SaltStack&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Docker&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kubernetes &amp;amp; Kustomize&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Azure ARM Templates &amp;amp; Bicep&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CloudFormation templates&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/PTVt2eg0FTA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://consensys.net/open-roles/gh_jid?gh_jid=3714164&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/341584/consensys.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[consensys@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[1036a9a0-3cf5-4e0b-bfa9-5c096c0d3a02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Consensys]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Backend Developer (Go, Solidity)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitfury.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Moscow, Moscow, Russia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;div id=&quot;header&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at Bitfury:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is a leading emerging technologies company. &amp;nbsp;At Bitfury, you can build the solutions of the future, with the most significant technologies of the millennium, in a modern and flexible workplace. We work a bit faster, and a bit smarter, so we can make the world a bit better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of Working at Bitfury:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Experiences &amp;amp; Global Impacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is an international company with 200+ team members in more than 16 countries. No matter your assignment, your work will support global technology initiatives and best-in-class security operations in North America, Asia and Europe, as well as help us fulfil our mission to make the world more trusted and secure.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building the Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe big data, artificial intelligence, blockchain technology, tokenized economies and cryptocurrencies are the future of our digital, global economy. Bitfury is building this future through our products that offer digitised security, asset management, government services and more. We consider ourselves first and foremost a technology company. We are a diversified organisation, with operations across multiple facets of the AI, blockchain, and digital currency sectors. If you are passionate about emerging technologies, you can build your future at Bitfury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Your Career&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is growing fast and looking for the next generation of leaders and entrepreneurs to help us. At Bitfury, you will be expected to create the future – not just execute it. If you are a self-starter, driven and collaborative team member, you can create a dynamic future for yourself and your career at Bitfury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modern Workplace with Intelligent Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury lets you work in the way you need to work to make your work faster, smarter and better. We will give you the resources you need to succeed – competitive pay and benefits, educational support, intellectual challenges, professional advancement, personal accommodations including remote work, and more. We pride ourselves on being less bureaucratic and a lot more impactful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start-up Culture with Established Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with the world’s leading experts and engineers, you will have the opportunity at Bitfury to pursue results that will power your success as well as lead to the adoption of game-changing technologies. Our teams work every day to make the impossible possible, to change the game, to be agile and effective, and most of all – to empower the rest of the world to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ersonal and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rofessional&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;haracteristics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We at Bitfury ensure our team members possess the ability to think out of the box and make the impossible possible. We are self-motivated and result-oriented, and we have an “owner of the company” mindset. We are constantly self-educating and developing. We are able to work in a team and collaborate. We have a “do good” mindset and are not afraid to dream big. And of course, we always deliver in time what we promised and with extreme attention to detail — because if we are not able to do the little things right, we will never be able to do big things right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clarity is an exciting new data oriented decentralised crypto protocol designed to enhance safety and maximise inclusion for the decentralised economy. This is a rare chance to join a greenfield project that has backing from established players within the industry at the pre-launch phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Senior backend developer will join a team of Blockchain developers working closely with the tech lead and product lead to design and implement a market-leading data protocol based on crypto/blockchain tech.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties and responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with development teams and product managers to ideate software solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency coding using Golang, must submit work example&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design client-side and server-side architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build the front-end of applications through appealing visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write effective REST APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write technical documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing efficient, scalable, robust, and maintainable code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing unit and end-to-end test scripts for required modules/packages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technologies you will be using:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cosmos SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solidity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Golang, Protobuf&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database: MongoDB, MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Source control: Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of backend development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in smart contract development, Cosmos SDK and Solidity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and interest in crypto projects covering areas such as DeFi, NFTs, and DAOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An analytical mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having good knowledge of Algorithms, Data structures, and Networking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a collaborative team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear and concise written and oral English communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An excellent team player and humble&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having good problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would be a plus:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slightly obsessed crypto nerd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on decentralized protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/DtkFJoj24rE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitfury/jobs/5763848002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145862/bitfury.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitfury@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bff43dfe-8ac3-4757-8a78-7559c9e9e327]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Lead Account Managers]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Latoken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote Worldwide]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong><strong>LATOKEN exchange has 2 million accounts including 900k+ users of our Android app rated 4.4 by 25+ thousands of reviews. We leverage the next tech to make account opening as easy as Instagram. The technology and our Olympic sports culture can make us the first billion users digital wallet needed to free people to manage their financial life.</strong></strong></p><p><strong><strong>Today, is a great moment to join us as crypto is expanding into mainstream financial market and <a>ex CFO of JP Morgan joined</a> our advisory board and <a>2 presidents joined us</a> in Davos.</strong></strong></p><p><a>Here is our backlog.</a><strong><br><br>Unit:</strong> Growth Managers<br><strong>Role:  </strong>Lead Account Managers<br><strong><strong>Role Mission: </strong></strong>Token adoption through listings &amp; co-marketing activities.<br><br><br><br><strong>Main performance number:</strong> Traders growth<br><strong>Second performance number:</strong> Revenue growth<br><strong>Third performance number:</strong> Co-marketing budget received<br><br><strong>Functions:</strong></p><ul><li>Top liquidity: Maximize number of tokens where we are #1 market in CMC token profile.</li><li>EO Launch: Setup and launch the IEOs.</li><li>Co-Marketing: Upsell co-marketing activities to projects in your portfolio.</li><li>Swap: Conduct swaps.</li><li>Manage team: Control HR and performance of the team.</li><li>Client management: Build strong relationships with and serve our B2B clients.</li><li>Analytics: Analyse success cases and good and bad standing.</li><li>Execution: Workflow management (work on CRM / ClickUp tasks).</li></ul><p><br><strong>Requirement skills and experience:</strong></p><ul><li>2+ years of account management or B2B sales experience in the field of fintech, crypto and investment banking.</li><li>2+ years experience in the crypto industry.</li><li>Experience in business development.</li><li>Problem-solving skills, result-oriented, strong work ethics.</li><li>Fluent English.</li><li>Will be a strong plus: Experience as a trader in banking or finance.</li><li>Experience with marketing. Graduated from a top university. Participant in the regional level of the olympiad or other relevant competitions. Additional language (Turkish, Hindi, Korean, Portuguese, Spanish, German).<br><br><strong>Why LATOKEN:</strong></li><ul><li><strong>Build the future</strong>. Level up the financial system. Put it at fingertips, so everybody can use the money to build and be a stakeholder of the future.</li><li><strong>Culture. </strong>Level up your and our culture until we and the world have advancement in culture deserving be spread with our products. We call it visionary doers culture.</li><li><strong>Raise the bar. </strong>Any hire raises our bar, and you will be the bar raiser for us and newcomers.</li><li><strong>Be stakeholder. </strong>You build a product helping people's success. People pay for it and you get a stake of these future payments as a LATOKEN shareholder.</li><li><strong>Lead.</strong> We are the largest in the world "IPO" platform for digital assets.</li></ul><p><strong>Feel a great fit - apply now </strong>or forward to a great candidate.</p></ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ikbGulIPQs0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.breezy.hr/p/72f7f49b6d2f01-lead-account-managers/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/178323/latoken.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[latoken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[ad8a3cbd-f1ed-4400-b372-af94f5f06cb4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Latoken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Applied Researcher - Cryptography]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Consensys]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.consensys.net]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States, Europe, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At ConsenSys we have a vision of a world where data sovereignty and financial well-being is accessible to every person and organization. We believe Ethereum and decentralized protocol technology is a more trustworthy and equitable foundation for how we create and share value across the web. On this trusted, open source foundation, we can accelerate the world’s transition to a universally accessible network of distributed participants where transparency, security and freedom are fundamental.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our product suite, composed of Truffle, Infura, Quorum, Codefi, MetaMask, and Diligence, serves millions of users, supports billions of blockchain-based queries for our clients, and has handled billions of dollars in digital assets. As the leading Ethereum software company, ConsenSys enables developers, enterprises, and people worldwide to build next-generation applications, launch modern financial infrastructure, and access the decentralized web. To learn more about ConsenSys, and explore our products and solutions, visit &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://consensys.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;http://consensys.net/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join ConsenSys?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote first.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; You’ll be joining a team based all over the world. Providing the unique opportunity to work with people from many different countries and cultures. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Want to work remotely? Go ahead. Or pop into one of our offices? We’ve got you covered in NYC, DC, Dublin, London, Paris, Brisbane and Hong Kong.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible working arrangements.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; You can create your own journey with flexible schedules and locations. We believe everyone has the right to control their own freedom. Our people can make their own schedule, own their own time, and we encourage you to travel and work from anywhere in the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous learning and opportunities.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; You’ll be constantly exposed to new concepts, ideas and frameworks from your peers and as you work on different projects — challenging you to stay at the top of your game. To support your development we pay for you to learn by offering unlimited access to Coursera, a platform with thousands of courses for you to learn whatever you want, and acquire new skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unlimited vacation/holidays. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We value downtime to recharge and reset, ensuring everyone at ConsenSys has work/life balance. Company-wide we participate in “zero productivity” days every quarter to take a break from work, shut down, and sit back and relax.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the most recognized tech companies in the blockchain ecosystem globally.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Work experience at ConsenSys is a tremendous reference for your future career. You’ll join a network of entrepreneurs and technologists that reaches the edge of our ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About R&amp;amp;D at ConsenSys&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The R&amp;amp;D team at ConsenSys is in charge of investigating and researching key technologies for the development of ConsenSys products and technologies. Its applied researchers and research engineers work in multiple technologies such as cryptography, formal methods and distributed systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will participate in the research, definition and implementation of a solution to scale Ethereum through a zero-knowledge virtual machine. You will participate in all aspects of the system, with a focus on the compiler and the EVM (Ethereum Virtual Machine).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with designing and implementing complex systems, preferably in Go or Rust&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable operating in an Agile environment&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborative by nature; willing to give and receive feedback&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding we are a globally distributed, remote-first team; Comfortable with handling uncertainty and ambiguity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Don&#39;t meet all the requirements? Don&#39;t sweat it. We’re passionate about building a diverse team of humans and as such, if you think you&#39;ve got what it takes for our chaotic-but-fun, remote-friendly, start-up environment—apply anyway. While we have a pretty good idea of what we need, we&#39;re ready for you to challenge our thinking on who needs to be in this role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is an equal opportunity employer. We encourage people from all backgrounds to apply. We are committed to ensuring that our technology is made available and accessible to everyone. All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, national origin, ancestry, sex, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age, genetic information, religion, disability, medical condition, pregnancy, marital status, family status, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is aware of fraudulent recruitment practices and we encourage all applicants to review our best practices to protect yourself which can be found &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consensys.net/careers/best-practices-to-avoid-recruitment-fraud/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/PTVt2eg0FTA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://consensys.net/open-roles/gh_jid?gh_jid=3744316&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/341584/consensys.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[consensys@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[1036a9a0-3cf5-4e0b-bfa9-5c096c0d3a02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Consensys]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[HR Business Partner]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Xfers]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.xfers.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About Fazz Financial Group </b></div><div>Founded in 2016, Fazz Financial is a digital financial services group based in Southeast Asia. It is the Holding Group of over 10 FinTech startups includes PayFazz, Xfers, Modal Rakyat; dedicated to enabling financial access for everyone, particularly the “unbankable” which make up over 70% of the region’s population. </div><div>Its flagship product PayFazz - a mobile app that provides digital banking services in rural Indonesia, is serving 50 million users via 500,000 agents. Leveraging FinTech, it provides a diverse range of financial services for consumers, SMEs, and corporates. </div><div>Xfers is our payment processing gateway offering credit card processing and Internet banking transfers that aims to simplify and redefine the process of collecting and receiving bank transfer and credit card payments in both Singapore and Indonesia. </div><div>Headquartered in Singapore and Indonesia, the Group has 600 staff spread across regional offices in Malaysia, Taiwan, and Vietnam. As a local startup born and bred in Southeast Asia, Fazz Financial was the first Indonesian startup to be seeded by Y Combinator, and is backed by both global and local investors including Insignia Venture Partners, B Capital, BRI Ventures, and others.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b>About the role and team</b></div><div>To support FAZZ's next stage of growth &amp; expansion, we are looking to bring on an HR Business Partner to support our business. Partnering with business leaders, managers &amp; employees, you will drive organisation development, workforce planning, performance  &amp; engagement to ensure that the team members in this unit are well supported &amp; set up for success.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Collaborate with our people team across the center of exellanceto roll out relevant programmes &amp; policies.</li><li>Collaborate with leadership team and fellow people team members to design and implement  employee processes and create experiences that are a reflection of our FAZZ culture, values &amp; mission.</li><li>Embed and embody our company's mission, vision, core values and culture in across our regional offices and in so doing, continuously ensure employee engagement and wellbeing.</li><li>Partner and advise our leaders and managers on all things people-related, such as performance management &amp; coaching, employee relations, leveling processes, and organizational development, workforce planning, learning &amp; development.</li><li>Advise and consult management on FAZZ HR policies and programs, in collaboration with fellow people team members and in-house counsel as necessary.</li><br/>What we are looking for in you<br/><li>Background of 3+ years as an HR business partner, preferably with a mix of experience in fast-growing technology companies and more established organizations</li><li>Experience implementing people programs including performance coaching, employee relations, compensation review process, HR compliance, and employee development/growth</li><li>Experience working with both technical and non-technical client groups and a deep understanding of the challenges within each group</li><li>A clear, approachable, and friendly communication style and strong customer service orientation</li><li>Strong analytical and project management skills, proven ability to design clear processes, and a very detail-oriented yet flexible approach to problem solving</li><li>Proven ability to influence across diverse groups and levels</li><div>We love reviewing all the applications we receive, but unfortunately, we may not be able to get back to everyone individually.&nbsp; If we’d like to move forward with your application, we’ll definitely be in touch!</div><div><br></div><div>Xfers is an equal opportunity employer. Individuals seeking employment at Xfers will be considered without regard to race, religion, national origin, age, sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, sexual orientation, marital status, medical condition, ancestry, physical or mental disability, or any other characteristic protected by applicable laws. </div><div><br></div><div>By submitting your application, you agree that Xfers may collect your personal data for recruiting, regional organization planning, and related purposes.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/xfers/3ab51a2b-501a-407e-bb3d-fa6d9bed8885/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/597930/xfers_logo1.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[xfers@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b0a8343f-a5d7-46f6-beef-6fa07262d235]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Xfers]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Development Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Energi Core Ltd]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.energi.world]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Global - Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Energi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Energi (NRG) is a next-generation Proof of Stake (PoS) cryptocurrency, combining Ethereum-compatible smart contracts with on-chain governance, a self-funding treasury, and a layer 2 masternode network, enabling powerful DeFi applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a fully remote company with no fixed headquarters. The team is spread throughout the Americas, Europe, Africa, Asia, and Oceania. With more than 90 contributors, the team forms a well-linked network across a variety of locations, lifestyles, and backgrounds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Energi&#39;s culture is driven by integrity, strategic thinking, leadership, and the shared desire to perform at our peak. While our differences make us adaptable and versatile, it&#39;s our shared values that give us the strength and drive to become the cryptocurrency for world consciousness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in It for You?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work flexible hours from anywhere and be part of a team that is driven by strong values and a clear shared vision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Directly shape the future of a completely new model for cryptocurrency and blockchain applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Challenge your skills and push your creative limits working with the latest blockchain technologies &amp;amp; systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Play an active role in one of the most significant technological innovations in human history.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Receive a competitive salary paid in a combination of BTC and NRG.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’re looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a full-time high-level Business Development Specialist, who has experience doing high level sales to VCs, or for IPOs and such! We are dynamic and growing tremendously fast, and need a steady supply of top talents across all departments at Energi.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;To learn more please visit: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.energi.world/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://www.energi.world/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You must have connections with the top investment firms, VC, hedge funds within the Crypto space&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with the product team to develop and operationalize programs for ads, campaigns, and other promotional partnerships&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build relationships in the crypto space globally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Learn from potential collaborations and existing ones what their needs are, stay up-to-date with the latest trends, and work together with Energi products to communicate and analyze the feasibility of these.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of the blockchain ecosystem&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of the Crypto products and at least 3 years of experience working within the crypto space.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work autonomously, be proactive, prioritize, communicate, and function in a diverse team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent interpersonal, verbal, and written English communication skills, including the ability to speak to different constituencies such as business development, communications, and engineering&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Must have strong sales skills and good public persona/presentation, as they will be responsible for building and maintaining relationships with other projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of other languages&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with blockchain companies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with a fully remote and decentralized team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role is not open to 3rd party organizations or agencies. Any candidates sent will be considered free of any charges&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Energi is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, pregnancy, disability, age, veteran status, or other characteristics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/8QUIHRakeHo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/energicorelimited/jobs/4248369004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/479023/energi-core-ltd-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[energi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5be3229a-46ba-477a-9178-2772ea9250e4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Energi Core Ltd]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Sales Engineer - APAC]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Digital Assets Holding]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://digitalasset.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[APAC]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Digital Asset&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset helps companies of all sizes and across industries get distributed applications to market faster, and stay there longer. At the core of our service offering is DAML (daml.com), the open source and platform-independent smart contract framework that enables developers to write an application once and deploy it anywhere. Today, we work with some of the largest companies in the world to harness the transformative power of smart contracts - a component of the distributed ledger technology (DLT) stack - and change the way applications are developed, deployed and used to solve real-world business challenges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset is a global company with offices in New York, London, Budapest, Zurich, Hong Kong, and Sydney.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As we grow our team, we will maintain the dynamic, collaborative and pragmatic way of working that has grounded our efforts from the beginning.&amp;nbsp; If you seek to develop solutions others have yet to contemplate, this opportunity may be right for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Technical Sales Engineers (TSE) will work closely with the regional Sales Associates and Directors to help clients identify and develop business cases across industry sectors in the APAC region. The TSEs play a critical part in demonstrating and educating clients in the depth of the company’s core products and services and how they can be applied to create new value or business opportunities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with sales team to identify client’s&amp;nbsp; business problems, understand how their processes and systems work today, and then demonstrate how our technology &amp;amp; products can be leveraged to minimize pain points&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist clients in understanding our tech infrastructure and tooling, and help plan interfaces and integrations to the existing technologies within their infrastructure platforms&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Rapidly develop full stack prototypes of identified business cases that provide the critical tangible proof to clients of the unique value that can be created&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deliver our value prop and USP to a variety of audiences, developers, architects to C-Level executives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Play vital role in sales process from discovery to deal closure by owning all technical aspects&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collect, collate &amp;amp; summarize client&amp;nbsp; feedback to product team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in establishing industry presence, at relevant forums, meetups,&amp;nbsp; associations and conferences&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Criteria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong hands-on software engineer on a large-scale project in a production environment; proficient in one or more programming languages e.g. Java, Python, TypeScript, JavaScript (Haskell &amp;amp; functional language will be advantageous but not a must)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience in a senior technical role and/or industry or tech-sales experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience successfully collaborating with others in a dynamic environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable leading customer / developer learning sessions (in-person and remotely)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Self-motivated with a proven track record of supporting technology evaluations and hands on developing prototypes for demanding customers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to adapt to the dynamic atmosphere of a growing Fintech startup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong presentation skills and be able to communicate complex concepts professionally in written responses to emails and patiently train external parties on our tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of infrastructure and how to deploy and run server based software packages in restricted client environments as well as public / private cloud environments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A degree in Computer Science or the equivalent is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of traditional and emerging technologies in data persistence and distribution stack is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect With Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a rare opportunity to help define an industry and join a dynamic team of technology innovators.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, national origin, sex, religion, sexual orientation, age, disability, citizenship status, veteran status or any other basis protected by applicable law. If and as required by applicable law, all persons hired to work at Digital Asset will be required to verify identity and eligibility to work in the location for which they have an offer to work and to complete the necessary employment eligibility verification documents upon hire. Applicants with disabilities who require accommodation should contact &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:recruiting@digitalasset.com&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;recruiting@digitalasset.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As part of our commitment to equal opportunity, Digital Asset believes that all employees should receive equal pay for equal work and is committed to this principle in its pay structure. DA also offers family-friendly benefits in addition to flexible work arrangements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/digitalasset/jobs/3757075?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/289153/digital-asset-holdings-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[digitalassets@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b9e3329f-7812-4695-a1f7-5b094cbac58f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Digital Assets Holding]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Receptionist & Administration Assistant]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKEx]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.okex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;About Us&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKEx is a world-leading cryptocurrency exchange, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology. We provide hundreds of token &amp;amp; futures trading pairs to help traders to optimize their strategy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are also one of the top digital asset exchanges by trading volume, serving millions of users in over 100 countries. OKEX derivatives remains a top-notch venue globally and has a daily volume of approximately $4 billion and is widely recognized as the golden standard of crypto exchange. We believe the blockchain technology will eliminate barriers to transactions, increase the efficiency of transactions across society, and eventually have a significant impact on the global economy. We strive to achieve something that changes the world and never stop to innovate and improve on our customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work scope :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Front of office, greet &amp;amp; welcome visitor, office maintenance, meeting room booking, manage vendor and handle office expenses payment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report &amp;amp; work closely with the Office Manager on managing office daily administrative matters which include facilities, company asset and office supplies procurement, fixed assets management, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Liaise with landlord’s management office.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Handle employees’ leave management, assist in onboarding and offboarding and handle employees’ queries on office administration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the Office Manager to organize internal activities and employees’ welfares&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in handling business travels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ad-hoc duties as and when assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ideal candidate : &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years administration working experience in fast pace company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with Chinese culture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient PC knowledge in MS Office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good at communication, willing to interact with internally and understand their needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent computer skills and knowledge in MS Office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient in spoken and written Mandarin &amp;amp; English is a MUST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent, attentive to details and willing to learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Immediate Available is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/x9kSkBMcOuo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okex/jobs/4872080003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175406/okex.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bcbc2afc-a2fd-45d8-bba3-e7ce4b53b3d8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKEx]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Administrative / Office Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Producer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://mythical.games/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;We are Mythical Games. A fully funded startup innovating at the intersection of video games and blockchain. Our goal is to lead the industry with the launch of exceptional video game experiences that leverage Blockchain Technology, while also providing a platform of robust tools that will allow any other game developer to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a highly-organized Senior Producer with exceptional communication skills and proven game production experience. In this role, you will be responsible for owning multiple features in development, partnering with external development resources, internal stakeholders, the platform team, and various other internal or external resources involved in the publishing efforts for the Blankos franchise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will own the production schedule for gameplay features, establish timelines and coordinate the workload required to achieve milestones, as well as be responsible for identifying risks, providing mitigation plans, and regularly communicating development status to internal stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strong problem-solving skills, the ability to establish clarity from ambiguity, facilitation of collaboration with remote resources, a team first attitude, and maintaining a friendly, supportive, creative environment are all essential to your success.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with stakeholders and resources to define gameplay feature requirements, determine resource needs, and create/maintain production schedules for development, launch, and ongoing maintenance phases.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being an ambassador and controller of quality for the player experience of core gameplay.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being aware of current gameplay trends, the content and landscape in gaming today, and an having awareness of data and metrics to inform decision making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Regularly communicate project and milestone, status, risks, and opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Actively manage risk by proactively identifying mitigation strategies, gaining alignment on solutions, and executing.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with internal and external teams to guide features and content from concept to implementation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Day to day creation and communication of tasks, priorities, and deadlines for internal resources and external development teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that project goals, objectives, milestones, and deliverables are fully understood, communicated and achieved.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Facilitate healthy collaboration, strong communication, effective process, and accountability across all individuals and teams supporting the franchise.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of game production experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven results managing ambiguous situations and driving towards clarity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of orchestrating work across various creative and technical resources on complex software development and publishing projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working closely with design teams to conceptualize an idea or feature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building gameplay systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with leadership and resources to align priorities and develop realistic plans to deliver on schedules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing continuous improvement to process and tools, to support increased collaboration and efficiency&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to set and manage stakeholder expectations amidst competing priorities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert project and people management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of various project management tools and methodologies, paired with the experience to know when and why to leverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable in a highly dynamic, fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized, flexible and able to work with multiple stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A passion for games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team values diversity and believes that it strengthens our games, products, and communities. We strongly encourage POC, folks with disabilities, those belonging to the LGBTQIA+ communities, and folks across all gender identities to apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We offer our team benefits such as (but not limited to) high-quality Vision, Dental, and Health Care, generous Parental Leave, and Unlimited PTO to ensure that they actually take time off without the stress of needing to accrue time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you need assistance around accommodations due to a disability, please reach out to accessibility@mythical.games. We’ll be with you as soon as possible; our goal is to ensure an accessible and equitable interview process for everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Zfsp0FQ5X8s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/mythicalgames/jobs/4815669003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/351124/Mythical-Logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[info@mythical.games]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[541f8953-1749-4738-90d8-efd04dd286d1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer, C++ (Trading Strategy)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[DRW]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://drw.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRW &lt;/strong&gt;is a technology-driven, diversified principal trading firm. We trade our own capital at our own risk, across a broad range of asset classes, instruments and strategies, in financial markets around the world. As the markets have evolved over the past 25 years, so has DRW – maximizing opportunities to include real estate, cryptoassets and venture capital. With over 1,200 employees at our Chicago headquarters and offices around the world, we work together to solve complex problems, challenge consensus and deliver meaningful results. It’s a place of high expectations, deep curiosity and thoughtful collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DRW is looking for an exceptional &lt;strong&gt;Software Engineer &lt;/strong&gt;to join one of our trading desks in Singapore.&amp;nbsp; You will work directly with experienced traders, quantitative researchers, and technologists to design, develop, deploy, and test customized software solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;What we’re looking for:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-6 years professional programming experience and proficiency in C++, preferably within the trading industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in mathematics, physics, engineering, computer science or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience exploring large datasets and applying data analysis to obtain actionable insights&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working familiarity with quantitative strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Formulate and apply mathematical modeling, quantitative methods, and automated techniques to identify and capture trading opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A proven track record of working independently with minimal oversight and driving projects and initiatives to completion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for trading markets and willingness to learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Possess strong analytical, mathematical and quantitative skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create practical solutions to problems presented in the trading environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Nice to haves: &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on a trading team within financial services or another latency-sensitive business that involves solving complex and novel problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort with multiple programming languages, particularly including Java and Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For more information about DRW&#39;s processing activities and our use of job applicants&#39; data, please view our Privacy Notice at &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;California residents, please review the&amp;nbsp;California Privacy Notice&amp;nbsp;for information about certain legal rights at&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#LI-BM1&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MdwEImeQcx8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/drweng/jobs/3761425?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145892/drw.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[drw@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bf32acf8-cf47-410b-aa59-74974c4d6afd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[DRW]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager - Scrum Master]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Akuna Capital]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://akunacapital.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Chicago, IL]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Akuna:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Akuna Capital is an innovative trading firm with a strong focus on collaboration, cutting-edge technology, data driven solutions and automation. We specialize in providing liquidity as an options market-maker – meaning we are committed to providing competitive quotes that we are willing to both buy and sell. To do this successfully we design and implement our own low latency technologies, trading strategies and mathematical models.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Founding Partners, including Akuna’s CEO Andrew Killion, first conceptualized Akuna in their hometown of Sydney. They opened the firm’s first office in 2011 in the heart of the derivatives industry and the options capital of the world – Chicago. Today, Akuna is proud to operate from additional offices in Sydney, Shanghai, and Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;What you’ll do as a Senior Project Manager - Scrum Master at Akuna:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Akuna Capital is looking for a Senior Project Manager to support both software development teams and cross-team projects. Our Project Management team is responsible for overseeing multiple projects at once, driving timelines, motivating our teams, managing dependencies, and helping achieve successful project execution. This role will allow you to manage new projects from conception to delivery and be an integral part of delivering cutting-edge solutions across the firm. The ideal candidate will have no problem diving in headfirst and holding employees accountable to their commitments, responsibilities, and deadlines. In this role, you will:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;1&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Facilitate daily stand-ups and Scrum/Kanban meetings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;2&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Create and maintain project plans and other project documentation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;3&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Provide regular status updates to management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Lead retrospective meetings and ensure teams continually learn and improve.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Drive the OKR process for key teams and projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Collaborate with multiple teams to understand the business problems and changing priorities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Grow, coach, and mentor developers on project management methodology best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Demonstrate leadership skills across the global Project Management team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Qualities that make great candidates:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;1&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;5+ years&#39; experience leading development teams through the software development lifecycle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;2&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Organized with the ability to manage multiple concurrent projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;3&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Familiarity with OKRs and Agile processes and best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Ability to discern when teams need more process and when they need less process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;5&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Highly collaborative in nature, with excellent written and verbal communication skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;5&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Team leadership experience is ideal, but not required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;5&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Familiarity with collaboration tools such as Jira, Confluence, Gitlab, or MS Project is strongly preferred, but not required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;5&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Familiarity with the trading domain and finance is strongly preferred, but not required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-leveltext=&quot;&quot; data-font=&quot;Symbol&quot; data-listid=&quot;4&quot; data-aria-posinset=&quot;5&quot; data-aria-level=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-contrast=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree or equivalent is required, PMP certification a plus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-ccp-props=&quot;{&amp;quot;134233279&amp;quot;:true,&amp;quot;201341983&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;335551550&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335551620&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;335559739&amp;quot;:200,&amp;quot;335559740&amp;quot;:276}&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/_tT7wJWEWy8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.akunacapital.com/job-details?gh_jid=3760159&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/195886/akuna.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[akiuna@crypto-careerrs.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b05d9bd-e49a-47fe-8b17-9f153850eba3]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Akuna Capital]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Engineer (data application)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Crypto.com</strong></p><p>Crypto.com was founded in 2016, Crypto.com today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest-growing crypto app, along with the Crypto.com Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the Crypto.com Exchange and Crypto.com Defi Wallet. Recently launched, Crypto.com NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment, and sports.</p><p>Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy, and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, ISO27001:2013, and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks.</p><p>With over 2,600 people in offices across the Americas, Europe, and Asia, Crypto.com is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a href="https://crypto.com" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com</a></p><p><br></p><p><strong>Job Responsibilities:</strong></p><p>1. Sorted out the company's business sector and data status quo, and designed data warehouse model schemes;</p><p>2. Analyze problems in the field of data life cycle management, formulate improvement plans for data quality, data standards, metadata, data models, etc., and coordinate with cross-departments to promote implementation;</p><p>3. Responsible for the data application and product requirements of the company's business sector; Complete the development and implementation of basic data, index, and label system; and output overall data services.</p><p>1. Bachelor degree or above, major in computer, software engineering, mathematics; at least 3 years experience in data development;</p><p>2. Experience in large-scale enterprise data warehouse construction, data index system sorting, and project implementation;</p><p>3. Familiar with DAMA, DCMM, etc., have a deep understanding of data model, data standard, data quality, metadata, data architecture, and other fields;</p><p>4. Master SQL development, familiar with PostgreSQL, MySQL, and other databases, as well as big data ecological components such as Hadoop, Spark, and Flink;</p><p>5. Experience in real-time warehouse design and development is preferred</p><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing a brand new product from scratch alongside with a talented team</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/639A687697/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Index Research Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://coindesk.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About CoinDesk Indices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinDesk Indices are the industry standard for institutional single- and multi-asset benchmarks for crypto assets. The flagship CoinDesk Bitcoin Price Index (XBX) has been in operation continuously since 2014. Financial institutions rely on the XBX and other CoinDesk Indices products to benchmark billions of dollars in assets under management and to price hundreds of millions in over-the-counter transactions, daily.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;CoinDesk Indices is seeking a Senior Index Research Analyst to join the research group in designing indexes and to provide thought leadership to expand the world’s leading cryptocurrency index offering of industry benchmarks and market indexes for index-linked products.&amp;nbsp; The Head of Index Research will collaborate with internal and external partners to create new index strategies and educational content to support clients and investors. Ideally, candidates will have research experience from indexing, banking, asset management or investment consulting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with a group of research analysts and index developers to create index methodologies and related educational content.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Publish white papers on cryptocurrency indexes and applications in multi-asset class portfolios.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Liaise with internal and external partners in the process of innovating, analyzing and developing new index methodologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Educate on applying cryptocurrency concepts in traditional portfolio frameworks and instruct on similarities and differences of the new technology and well known assets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years experience in financial industry; specific knowledge of cryptocurrency, alternatives, and/or indexing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Undergraduate degree in quantitative or financial field such as finance, accounting, economics, mathematics, computer science, physics or engineering&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience backtesting models and publishing research with supporting results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Must be curious, a methodical thinker, and data-driven in analysis approach&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have a strong understanding of portfolio construction and asset allocation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong communication skills with the ability to simplify complicated concepts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;MBA and/or CFA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep technical knowledge of blockchain protocols and smart contracts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of Experience with Python and other programming.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep technical knowledge of blockchain protocols and smart contracts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EQUAL OPPORTUNITY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In an effort to attract, retain, develop and promote the most qualified individuals, CoinDesk is committed to treating all applicants and employees in a nondiscriminatory manner with respect to the terms and conditions of employment, without regard to race, color, religion or belief, sex, national or ethnic origin, ancestry, age, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status/service, physical or mental disability, or any other classification protected by applicable law. This mandate governs all aspects of employment, including recruitment, selection, promotion, training, education, social and recreation programs, compensation, discipline, termination and access to benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For more information on our DEI initiatives, please visit: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/dei/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://www.coindesk.com/dei/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACCOMMODATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinDesk is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the application process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:accommodations@coindesk.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accomodations@coindesk.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVID-19 VACCINATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;COVID-19 vaccination is required for all employees whose position is based out of the NYC office. However, CoinDesk will consider accommodations for disability- and religious-based reasons on a case by case basis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; (edited)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/coindesk/jobs/5787115002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145913/coindesk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coindesk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[459b477b-1ae2-43d1-a1a8-7a40fbe3f487]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Marketing Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.elliptic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Company description</strong></p><p>As digital assets and cryptocurrency become more widely adopted every day, businesses rely on Elliptic for key data insights to give them an edge in the market. Our unique data set allows customers to see market moves before they happen, driving business decision-making. Our products are used by the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, financial institutions and government agencies, responsible for billions of dollars worth of transactions every single week.</p><p>Elliptic is backed by some of the top VCs: SoftBank Vision Fund, Octopus Ventures, Evolution Equity Partners, Digital Currency Group, Albion VC, SBI Group, Santander, Wells Fargo, and more, and our global team is based predominantly in the UK, USA, Singapore and Tokyo.</p><p>To achieve our mission, we depend on our incredible team of Elliptites. <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/life-at-elliptic" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Our values</a> are reflected in everything we do and every decision we make, both internally and outwardly to our customers. We actively encourage Elliptities to challenge the status quo and allow the freedom to innovate and learn every day. We encourage new ideas and learning, whether that’s through collaboration, our curiosity sessions, or utilising your professional development budget - personal growth is important to us all.</p><p><strong>The impact you will have:</strong></p><p>Product Marketing acts as storytellers for the business, responsible for value proposition development, marketing content creation, messaging, and inbound/outbound marketing for all of Elliptic’s offerings across regions and client segments. You will be responsible for bringing our products to market, empowering our customers with features that make their work in crypto safer.</p><p><strong>What you will do:</strong></p><ul> <li>Support the Director of Product Marketing in the creation and execution of go-to-market, route-to-market, and competitive plans</li> <li>Work with the Product Marketing group to develop messaging for Elliptic’s offerings, including defining customer challenges, resulting customer benefits, and product value proposition</li> <li>Collaborate with Product and Marketing teams to develop product positioning and messaging that resonates with out target buyer personas</li> <li>Manage senior stakeholders from across the business with data-driven commercial strategies, championing the work that we do and challenging where necessary</li> <li>Contribute to the daily execution of managing product/domain strategy, including communication, knowledge sharing, reporting, and managing expectations</li> <li>Create product content such as case studies, videos, website pages, blogs, and landing pages. Partner with other teams to create assets that can be used to drive demand and lead generation through all marketing channels</li> <li>Be the expert on our customers, who they are, how they buy and their key buying criteria. Build and maintain knowledge of our competitive environment and how they are positioned</li> <li>Be a champion for digital delivery, drive internal adoption of multimedia as the primary channel for content marketing</li> </ul><p><strong>Our ideal candidate has:</strong></p> <ul> <li>3-5 years in B2B Product Marketing, preferably within financial services or Fintech</li> <li>BA/BS degree or equivalent practical experience</li> <li>Critical thinker with outstanding written, data analysis, communication, presentation, and delivery skills</li> <li>Ability to handle multiple projects, prioritize, and meet deadlines</li> <li>A self-starter who truly enjoys learning from customers and colleagues about how Elliptic products are being used and how they can be improved</li> <li>Creative, but also process-driven, relying on data to make decision</li> <li>Strong experience with marketing automation tools (ideally HubSpot)</li> <li>An interest in cryptocurrency, blockchain and related technologies</li> </ul><ul> <li>Competitive salary</li> <li>25 days holiday, health insurance, pension plan and EMI options</li> <li>Career development plan &amp; personal training budget</li> <li>Fortnightly team lunches, snacks and drinks in the office, and quarterly team events</li> <li>Collaborative, flexible and friendly environment with options for remote working</li> <li>Being part of a business with a purpose, and the opportunity to work with a passionate team of mission-driven people who’ll stretch and challenge you</li> </ul><p>We know Diversity and Inclusion is much deeper than just hiring, but it’s important for us to mention it here. We welcome and embrace individuals of all backgrounds and identities at Elliptic, and this is an ongoing priority for us. We know incredible people don’t all think in the same way. We want to be challenged every day. We believe our diverse team of individuals underpins this by bringing creative thinking and innovation to Elliptic every day. We are committed to creating a diverse, inclusive and equitable workplace, so we welcome applications from everyone, even if you may not think you fit all of the requirements of our roles. We foster an environment of psychological safety, where everyone feels comfortable to bring their whole self to work.</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ebOLNjlYiNg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/elliptic/j/E01B001D50/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145877/elliptic.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[elliptic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[fefe721f-d5ba-4eb0-9b9b-f4156a27cb2b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Content Coordinator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Miami, Florida, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Crypto.com</strong></p><p>Founded in 2016, Crypto.com today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest growing crypto app, along with the Crypto.com Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the Crypto.com Exchange and Crypto.com DeFi Wallet. Recently launched, Crypto.com NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment and sports.</p><p>Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, CCSS Level 3, ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks.</p>With over 2,600 people in offices across the Americas, Europe and Asia, Crypto.com is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a href="https://crypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com<br><br></a><br><strong>In this role, you will:</strong><br><ul> <li>Copywriting and editing content for landing pages, email marketing campaigns and social media</li> <li>Liaising with clients, partners and cross functional departments and teams to obtain and/or create assets for use across digital channels</li> <li>Liaising with internal and external teams to make sure content is distributed to all necessary stakeholders for marketing and promotional purposes</li> <li>Checking content for accuracy, consistency and quality as appropriate/necessary</li> <li>Conducting research for use in creative content</li> <li>Establishing and maintaining a database of creative assets</li> <li> Establishing and maintaining a drop-focused content calendar for social media</li> <li>Drafting, designing and publishing social media content as appropriate/assigned</li> <li>Drafting and designing blog content as appropriate/assigned</li> <li>Creating internal and external-facing business development material, marketing templates, user guides, etc.</li> <li> Assisting the Editor and Creative Producer with special projects, as needed.</li> </ul><br><ul> <li>Possess a background in journalism or editorial content marketing; professional experience with social media (particularly Instagram); knowledge of SEO a plus; experience with Photoshop a plus; multilingual a plus.</li> <li>Must have a writing portfolio or links to articles, blog posts, press releases and familiarity with AP style</li> <li>Experience and/or interest in the cryptocurrency/NFT space preferred</li> </ul><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1.</li> <li>Be the owner of your own learning curve.</li> <li>The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing a brand new product from scratch alongside with a talented team</li> </ul><p><a href="https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/646166D282/apply/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external"><br></a></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/4829A11B4F/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[PMO Project Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[r3]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.r3.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We are looking for Project Managers&nbsp;to join an amazing group of technologists, industry experts and thought leaders who&nbsp;will bring high quality project delivery expertise and discipline to&nbsp;R3.&nbsp;As part of the Project Management Office you&nbsp;will apply&nbsp;best&nbsp;practices,&nbsp;continuously think about how we can improve our technical and engineering project delivery&nbsp;and work closely with our internal technical teams to ensure that we are&nbsp;delivering software to the expected time, quality and budget.&nbsp;You&nbsp;are knowledgeable in mainstream project management approaches with a particular specialisation in Agile delivery. You are comfortable working autonomously&nbsp;within these approaches.</div><div><br></div><div>You will have extensive software development project management experience and exhibit a natural passion for getting the most out of the teams you work with. This will complement your strong organisational skills and attention to detail. You will have a strong sense of foresight for potential challenges and risks and devise plans to address and mitigate these, both around&nbsp;the implemented&nbsp;engineering processes and&nbsp;the&nbsp;delivery&nbsp;'machinery'.&nbsp;You&nbsp;will contribute to the success of our software products by choreographing scheduled and adhoc meetings and retrospectives, maintaining documentation relating to project delivery processes and contributing to the day-to-day positivity within R3. You will have a methodical and fastidious attitude to software delivery by capturing, tracking and driving actions across the delivery teams to a successful conclusion, keeping fast-moving situations under control and using the right combination of project delivery techniques to suit.</div><div><br></div><div>You will have experience working in firms where releases, software development lifecycles and speed-to-market are the back-bone of your work.&nbsp;You&nbsp;will want to delight your colleagues by helping provide them with a high quality project delivery experience.&nbsp;The majority of your project delivery experience will be from working in Agile environments where project managers, product managers and engineers work closely together.&nbsp;</div><br/>Responsibilities: <br/><li>Take ownership of local and regional project deliveries applying appropriate project control techniques.</li><li>Apply robust and appropriate project planning to capture and track activities so technical project teams can work as efficiently and effectively as possible.</li><li>Communicate to internal and external stakeholders using a variety of techniques appropriately tailored to the audience.</li><li>Produce, validate and publish accurate project reports on a regular and timely basis.</li><li>Display flexibility under changing priorities and actively collaborate with R3 teams to achieve common objectives.</li><li>Identify opportunities for efficiency and development process improvements including but not limited to the use of off-the-shelf tooling and the adoption of best practices.</li><br/>Competencies: <br/><li>A deep understanding of project management principles, particularly Agile methodologies, most likely obtained through a combination of academic study and professional experience</li><li>5-8 years experience delivering enterprise software product/platform - End to End practical knowledge of software delivery lifecycle</li><li>Excellent communication skills written and oral</li><li>Jira experience is a must (Jira administration optional)</li><li>Stakeholder Management, Risk Management</li><li>Comfortable and able to work under pressure</li><div><br></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//player.vimeo.com/video/374680693" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/r3.com/8da473c9-20a4-4ab6-84d2-045d10f9ced7/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145208/r3_logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[r3@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[18dbe364-74c1-4303-b076-66cd4e239ce3]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[r3]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Summer 2022 Internship (London)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The engineering team at Chainalysis is inspired by solving the hardest technical challenges and creating products that build trust in cryptocurrencies. We’re a global organization with teams in Denmark, the USA and the UK who thrive on the challenging work we do and doing it with other exceptionally talented teammates. Our industry changes every day and our job is to build a flexible platform that will allow us to adapt to those rapid changes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Software Engineering Interns at Chainalysis participate in as many real-life responsibilities with our full-time engineering teams as possible! You&#39;ll learn&amp;nbsp; innovative methodologies while contributing to projects that have a lasting impact on our products, databases, and teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;At the end of your internship&lt;/strong&gt;,&lt;strong&gt; you’ll know you were successful if you achieved the following…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developed meaningful relationships within and outside of our engineering team that will persist long after your internship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learned best-in-class software engineering practices, skills, and approaches to problem-solving that prepare you for your career in technology.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contributed to our groundbreaking technologies and made contributions that ultimately become a part of our products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coursework in Computer Science, Information Systems, Cybersecurity, Mathematics or related technical field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&#39;re comfortable coding in at least one or more programming languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The tech startup landscape interests you as a career path and you enjoy fast-paced environments working on difficult problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&#39;re graduating between December 2022 and June 2023.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for cryptocurrency and/or blockchain technology helps, but isn&#39;t required!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is a paid internship for Summer 2022 in our beautiful London office. We are accepting applications and extending offers on a rolling basis. Please email universityrecruiting@chainalysis.com if you have any questions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yNpNz-FvSYQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5790028002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[PMO Lead - COO Office]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Assist COO, serving as a trusted advisor and leading PMO, to coordinate cross-functional teams with structured thinking, problem identification &amp; solving, initiatives design and action implementation;</li><li>Serve as liaison between staff, executives, senior leaders, and CEO, regarding company strategy, culture, employee well-being, business development and planning;</li><li>Perform in-depth analysis and drive stakeholder reporting, including content development &amp; consolidation, narrative, data crunching and presentation preparation, to facilitate business decision making, strategic planning, leadership meetings and broader communications;</li><li>Closely monitor blockchain/ crypto/ fintech industry trends, portfolio company performance and ecosystem dynamics with regular updates to COO &amp; operations team, supported with deep insights &amp; implications;</li><li>Independently steer various projects &amp; company priorities and build consensus with senior leadership across the organization;</li><li>Manage any other ad-hoc tasks/projects where necessary;</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>High integrity, proactive and self-motivated;</li><li>Passionate about blockchain/cryptocurrencies and desire to leverage capital and technology to change the world;</li><li>3-5 years of past relevant work experience in fintech/ blockchain companies, professional service firms or other PMO related roles, with solid experience in managing complex business priorities and projects;</li><li>Solid written, analytical and presentation skills;</li><li>Work well as a team player;</li><li>Detail-oriented, well-organized, able to work under pressure and deliver on time;</li><li>Excellent communication and interpersonal skills;</li><li>Preferably located in UTC+8 or other APAC timezones</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/05fa2521-4c0a-42bd-b226-69885cbe87bb/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Rust Developer (Solana)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Rarible]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://rarible.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Rarible</b></div><div><br></div><div>Rarible is a creator-centric NFT marketplace with a community governance model. We are a #1 ranked marketplace in the world, having exceeded $40 million USD in monthly trading volume. Rarible reached over 10x growth in the past 3 months, and is expanding rapidly! In addition, Rarible is releasing the Rarible Protocol which allows developers, other marketplaces, and partners to easily mint NFTs and to share NFT inventory with a decentralized order book.</div><div><br></div><div>Join our decentralized, motivated and fully remote team building the NFT marketplace of the future.</div><div><br></div><br/>Who you are:<br/><li>You are a code wizard who loves to design abstract technical solutions and implement them.</li><li>You are relentlessly curious and love to tinker in new technologies. You pick them up fast and believe in pushing quick, iterative prototypes like any lean startup.</li><li>You eat, sleep and breath defi. From the memes, to the exist projects and industry concepts you know it all.</li><li>You closely follow the blockchain and defi space and are intellectually fueled by the innovations in the space.</li><li>You are used to being an individual contributor.</li><li>You prefer being quick to being a perfectionist.</li><br/>Required Background/Skills:<br/><li>You have 5+ years of technical experience.</li><li>You are highly experienced in Rust.</li><li>You are comfortable creating at least simple front-ends for interacting with your Solana apps.</li><li>You have a deep understanding of the blockchain and cryptocurrency space and smart contract systems, specifically having a deep understanding of Solana.</li><br/>Preferred Qualifications:<br/><li>Individuals with backgrounds in technical solutions for finance, trade engines, or who have worked on defi or dapp products previously</li><br/>What do we offer<br/><li>📍&nbsp;Working for a rapidly expanding global startup</li><li>📍 Mentorship, training and career progression plans with leadership focused on developing the teams</li><li>📍 Team that cares about products and working conditions</li><li>📍 Flexible Hours start of the working day&nbsp;</li><li>📍 Full-time, paid vacations remote first with relocation packages available, hardware and software support&nbsp;</li><li>📍 Attractive package to include base equity and/or tokens, equity as well as health benefits&nbsp;</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/Rarible/a05429ef-92e3-4f1c-b806-cbb8e79c0f5f/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/811040/rarible-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[rarible@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3d836c10-c446-4ef5-94c0-abd3afb18693]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Rarible]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Substrate Builders Program Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.parity.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berlin, Germany]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Role: Manager Position&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mentor / Supervisor: Santiago Balaguer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Location: Berlin / Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Job Description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Ecosystem Success team at Parity focuses on supporting external development teams building solutions with and for the Substrate and Polkadot ecosystems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Substrate is a blockchain-building framework that makes it easy to create a custom blockchain optimized for any use case. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Substrate blockchains are natively compatible with Polkadot, a Level-0 blockchain solution that enables diverse blockchains &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to interoperate seamlessly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The overall objective of the Ecosystem Success team is to improve both platforms, increase engineering capabilities and accelerate adoption of both Substrate and Polkadot. Therefore, in this role you will work hand in hand with the different engineering and business teams in the Substrate ecosystem, gathering feedback and sharing technical insights to inspire and inform the best developer groups worldwide about the potential of building cutting-edge blockchains with Substrate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Substrate Builders Program Manager plays a vital role in our company, as well as in the Substrate and Polkadot Ecosystems. You will work in close contact with critical teams in the ecosystem to help them develop bleeding-edge blockchain projects. We are looking for a talented individual with the right mix of entrepreneurial instinct, technical and blockchain knowledge, and project management skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support running the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://substrate.io/ecosystem/substrate-builders-program/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Substrate Builders Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, from managing team evaluations, leading the continuous engagement for support, and helping teams to ensure a successful product launch.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Take ownership of the support stream for specific teams in the ecosystem: managing project roadmaps and steering the needs of a fast-growing ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help to set up and monitor metrics to determine the performance of the Substrate Builders Program, with a strong focus on improving scalability in the future.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be creative and use your knowledge to define new support initiatives that improve the program continuously.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead the overall adoption of Substrate and Polkadot by sharing best practices, helping to focus on goals and ensuring ecosystem teams are able to execute accordingly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Qualification and Skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep technical understanding of blockchain technologies and online ecosystems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with building ecosystems, ideally on a technical or blockchain-related product.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong program management skills and ability to address multiple projects in parallel, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;managing competing interests and aligning various parties on a common goal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent interpersonal, verbal, and written communication skills, including speaking to business development and technical teams internally and externally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work autonomously, be proactive, prioritise, communicate, and function in a small team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nice-to-haves&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with a blockchain programming language.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passion for working on and sharing knowledge of new technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Benefits&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working at Parity means focusing on the stuff that counts: building the most cutting-edge technology for the future web. Our teams enjoy a high degree of trust, freedom and autonomy to achieve that goal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will understand blockchain technology and business development and have a skill set transferable to many jobs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Because we value initiative and learning, we&#39;ve defined a generous personal budget to attend conferences or skills courses of your choosing. We think you know what&#39;s best for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Parity is a diverse company with people from various countries, and we will support you with German or English language courses where needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Not all of us who collaborate work in the same place. Bringing the team together is something we value greatly, so we regularly go on team retreats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;To see how we use your data, please see our Applicant Notice: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.parity.io/applicant-notice/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://www.parity.io/applicant-notice/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LZd6z7HiTLw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/parity/jobs/4878912003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/378609/parity.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[parity@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6edef434-1785-497e-a19b-ce6d949ad50a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Substrate Builders Program Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.parity.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berlin, Germany]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Role: Junior Position&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mentor / Supervisor: Santiago Balaguer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Location: Berlin / Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Job Description&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Ecosystem Success team at Parity focuses on supporting external development teams building solutions with and for the Substrate and Polkadot ecosystems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Substrate is a blockchain-building framework that makes it easy to create a custom blockchain optimized for any use case. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Substrate blockchains are natively compatible with Polkadot, a Level-0 blockchain solution that enables diverse blockchains &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to interoperate seamlessly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The overall objective of the Ecosystem Success team is to improve both platforms, increase engineering capabilities and accelerate the adoption of both Substrate and Polkadot. Therefore, in this role, you will work hand in hand with the different engineering and business teams in the Substrate ecosystem, gathering feedback and sharing technical insights to inspire and inform the best developer groups worldwide about the potential of building cutting-edge blockchains with Substrate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As an Ecosystem Success Associate, you will be a crucial player in managing the most cutting-edge projects in the Substrate and Polkadot ecosystems. At the same time, you will have opportunities to deepen your blockchain skills and propose innovative solutions to the way we operate. We are looking for a talented individual with the right mix of entrepreneurial instinct, the desire for learning, and aspiration to build the Web 3.0.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support in the Substrate Builders Program execution, from managing team selection to leading successful ecosystem projects development and product launch support.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure all Substrate Builders Program-related processes are followed and working correctly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help monitor and improve the program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead the Substrate Builders Program projects’ reporting and help optimize our response times.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Aid the overall adoption of Substrate and Polkadot by analyzing and sharing best practices with different teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help coordinate support services from external providers and evaluate the ongoing services for efficiency as a basis for future decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Qualification and Skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent interpersonal, verbal, and written communication skills, including speaking to business development and technical teams internally and externally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work autonomously, be proactive, prioritise, communicate, and function in a small team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong skills in structuring projects, managing competing interests, and aligning various parties on a common goal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Basic knowledge of blockchain technology and blockchain ecosystems with a strong desire to learn more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nice-to-haves&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience and/or understanding of a programming language.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passion for working on and sharing knowledge of new technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Benefits&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working at Parity means focusing on the stuff that counts: building the most cutting-edge technology for the future web. Our teams enjoy a high degree of trust, freedom, and autonomy to achieve that goal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will gain a deep understanding of blockchain technology and business development and develop a skill set transferable to many jobs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Because we value initiative and learning, we&#39;ve defined a generous personal budget to attend conferences or skills courses of your choosing. We think you know what&#39;s best for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Parity is a diverse company with people from various countries, and we will support you with German or English language courses where needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Not all of us who collaborate work in the same place. Bringing the team together is something we value greatly, so we regularly go on team retreats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;To see how we use your data, please see our Applicant Notice: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.parity.io/applicant-notice/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://www.parity.io/applicant-notice/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LZd6z7HiTLw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/parity/jobs/4878921003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/378609/parity.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[parity@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6edef434-1785-497e-a19b-ce6d949ad50a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Manager of Content Marketing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://blockfi.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi’s mission is to provide liquidity, transparency and efficiency to digital financial markets by creating products that meet the needs of consumers and corporations across the globe. We build bridges between traditional finance and digital markets that enable growth for all participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re a team of builders and strivers, proud to champion financial inclusivity and offer economic opportunities around the globe. We provide the same inclusivity to our team members. BlockFi is a place where diversity is celebrated, individuality is recognized, and every single team member is valued. We are changing the status quo to be the first financial company that people love, and we rely on our people to make it happen!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is seeking a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Manager of Content Marketing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to join our growing team!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Your Team &amp;amp; Role&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The BlockFi marketing team is looking for a Senior Manager of Content Marketing to support our growing crypto platform. The role will focus on establishing our content strategy, writing and editing key narratives, developing thought leadership and other content to drive awareness and growth of BlockFi. It is a highly cross-functional role partnering with many teams to develop, launch, and scale our content marketing strategy across a portfolio of products. Content Marketing partners with Creative, Analytics, Performance Marketing, Design, Communications, and Product Marketing to develop compelling content that informs and inspires current and prospective clients.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a high impact role to shape and elevate our brand, capture top of funnel interest, and drive product adoption globally. Your colleagues at BlockFi are pragmatic problem solvers that are excited to tackle the most interesting challenges in the Crypto-FinTech arena.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish and drive the content marketing strategy for consumers (clients)&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own content marketing roadmap and build key narratives for BlockFi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and influence content activation plans with Creative, Social Media, SEO, Comms, and web team to deliver business impact for our brand and portfolio of products.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own and maintain key content channels including the company blog and newsletter by managing the content calendar, developing content, and measuring results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with founders and other key leaders to develop thought leadership articles and papers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deliver detailed content marketing analysis which includes actionable insights to adjust our strategy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Expertise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are a self starter and a solid track record of leadership and influencing skills in a fast-paced environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ambitious, and bar-raiser to improve the quality of output for you and your team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;7+ years of content or digital marketing with an emphasis on strategy, editorial, and execution ownership.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep portfolio of published written and multimedia content that inspires and breaks through the noise.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with cross-functional teams and managing stakeholders, creative partners, contractors, and vendors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Solid knowledge and experience driving end to end content marketing campaigns -- from defining the strategy and objectives to identifying a core insight, to developing the core KPIs and content, to executing the campaigns and measuring results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing content writers, budgets, and content development processes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent analytical and problem solving skills. You can wield data and use it to inform your decision making and developing your KPIS.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Organized and coordinated project management skills -- you have a track record of managing multiple projects and making clear trade off decisions, and executing in a fast-paced environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written, verbal, and interpersonal communication skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience developing fintech or crypto messaging is preferred.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Perks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We benefit from the great work our employees do each day. That is why we are committed to providing a variety of awesome benefits to help them live their best lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive salary &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because we value your experience and expertise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unlimited vacation / sick days b&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ecause everyone deserves time for R&amp;amp;R&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employer&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;contribution towards health coverage &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(including vision &amp;amp; dental) because your physical health and well-being is important to us&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Various fringe benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; such as 401k, Parental Leave, FSA/HSA, and Employee Assistance Programs because health coverage is more than just choosing your yearly plan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible work environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; because we are a geographically dispersed team and we believe in balance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pet insurance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; because all of your beloved family members should have coverage too&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly lunch stipend &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because there is such a thing as a free lunch!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A close-knit team &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;of enthusiastic, collegial and driven people to work alongside in a highly meritocratic environment because teamwork makes the dreamwork&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi has experienced incredible growth since our launch in August 2017. Our client base has grown to more than 225,000 (and counting), and the company now boasts more than $15 billion in assets on our platform. We recently completed a Series D funding round placing the company&#39;s valuation at $3 billion, and our team now has more than 500 people worldwide. We have established ourselves as a crypto market leader, and as we expand our product suite and geographic footprint, we expect our addressable market to grow exponentially.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi&#39;s leadership team has decades of experience in the traditional financial services and banking world, and we take a conservative approach to regulation that will position us well for sustainable long-term growth and expansion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team is comprised of highly motivated professionals from diverse backgrounds. We are aiming to become the leading lender in crypto and are poised to redefine the global financial ecosystem for the better. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is one of the first companies to ever offer crypto-backed loans and the only company whose founding team has an institutional understanding of the debt capital markets and regulatory landscape in the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$100 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series A, B, and C funding led by Valar Ventures with participation from Susquehanna, Winklevoss Capital, Fidelity, Galaxy Digital, Akuna Capital, and Morgan Creek&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$350 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series D funding led by Bain Capital Ventures, partners of DST Global, Pomp Investments and Tiger Global&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are moving quickly and have already deployed substantial capital into the space, proving our ability to execute and capture customer demand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For information about how we&amp;nbsp;collect, use, or otherwise handle your Personal Information, please see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a class=&quot;c-link&quot; href=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-stringify-link=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; data-sk=&quot;tooltip_parent&quot;&gt;Privacy&amp;nbsp;Policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/o92zit2jRO0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockfi/jobs/5743271002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/553492/blockfi-logo-512x512.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockfi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7eefa976-25ba-4497-9343-24e88aecb41f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[(Junior) Software Developer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOTA Foundation]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.iota.org]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berlin]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The IOTA Foundation is a not-for-profit organization established in 2017 and headquartered in Berlin, Germany. The Foundation’s mission is to drive the development and standardization of new distributed ledger technologies (DLTs) that enable permissionless innovation ecosystems. To realize this potential the IOTA Foundation is actively building a collaborative of developers, start-ups, private enterprises, and government, civil society and academic institutions. </span><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Concretely, we engage in engineering, research and community organizing efforts around the IOTA Tangle – a new generation of DLT specifically designed to be the open and free trust layer for the Internet-of-Things (IoT).</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Mission: </span></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">As a <span style="font-weight: bold;">Software Developer</span>, you will work closely together with project teams to design, develop, maintain and test production ready IOTA-based solutions (e.g. tools and platforms implementation or other products/services for private and public partners in public and private funded large projects). </span><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">You will support the development of next generation DLT-based solutions including decentralized digital identities, tokenization and smart contracts in various infrastructure domains including mobility, smart energy, smart e-health, smart cities etc.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #1d1c1d;">Candidates must be located in Germany.</span></span></span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Responsibilities:</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;">Support in designing and developing IOTA software components</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;">Deliver working solution based on project requirements and scope together with your team</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;">Assist in integrating front- and backend of the develop solutions</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;">Document the developed solution</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;">Utilize best practice implementation, build best practice know-how through close interaction with other SW Engineers</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;">Participate in and help transform cutting-edge research into practical software products</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;">Implement software development best practices and collaborate with other software projects in open source DLT space</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;">Requirements:</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;">Your Personality</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Self-driven individual who takes responsibility for projects from their inception</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Ability, desire, and dedication to pick up new platforms or technologies as well as improve in existing ones</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;">Your  Expertise</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Native German skills</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="color: #222222;">You have a basic understanding of the  </span><a href="https://legacy.docs.iota.org/docs/getting-started/1.1/the-tangle/overview" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">IOTA Tangle Technology</a><span style="color: #222222;"> and already tried some of our </span><a href="https://client-lib.docs.iota.org/docs/libraries/nodejs/examples" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">demo projects</a></span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Basic experience in one of the following programming languages: Javascript, Typescript. Rust will be considered a plus</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">You study computer science (or similar technical subject of study)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">At least upper-intermediate level of English language profession (oral and written) </span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Basic skills with office products (docs, spreadsheets, presentations) </span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Experience with React (Frontend) or NodeJS (backend) is a plus</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;">What we offer</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The opportunity to work with the brightest minds in the industry</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">To make a true difference </span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Culture of trust, empowerment and constructive feedback</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">A flexible and agile organization with a flat hierarchy.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The unique combination of foundation and startup </span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;">The IOTA Foundation is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity and are committed to creating an inclusive environment for all employees.</span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LVY9DzwyzdU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://iota.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=187&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180020/iota.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iota@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[89e42fc6-4d4d-416c-82b4-a1443bc5e101]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOTA Foundation]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Junior Visual Designer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Wintermute]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.wintermute-trading.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Wintermute</b></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">&nbsp;</b></div><div>Wintermute is a hyper-growth fintech startup and one of the largest players in the global digital asset markets. We provide liquidity algorithmically across most cryptocurrency exchanges and trading platforms, as well as support high profile blockchain projects and traditional financial institutions moving into crypto.</div><div><br></div><div>Culturally, we combine the best traits of both trading companies and technology startups. As a trading company, we manage hundreds of millions in assets, trade more than $5B+/day across dozens of trading platforms and are highly profitable in doing so. As a technology startup, we build, innovate and move incredibly fast, we create best-in-class liquidity products that create more efficient markets. We believe that traditional finance has to change and we are on a mission to define and build the decentralized future of finance.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Wintermute is a hyper-growth highly profitable proprietary trading business. We are backed by top tier global venture capital investors such as&nbsp;<a href="https://medium.com/lightspeed-venture-partners/wintermute-makes-sure-you-dont-get-ripped-off-when-you-buy-crypto-63aa96dcb983">Lightspeed</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://panteracapital.com/">Pantera Capital</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.sinoglobalcapital.com/">Sino Global Capital</a>,&nbsp;<a href="http://blockchain.com/">Blockchain.com</a>&nbsp;Ventures, Avon Ventures by&nbsp;<a href="https://www.fidelity.com/">Fidelity Investments</a>,&nbsp;<a href="https://defialliance.co/">DeFi Alliance</a>&nbsp;and others. Learn more about our team and culture on our website and Evgeny’s post&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/EvgenyGaevoy/status/1380121973058076672">here.</a></div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 18px"><b>Working at Wintermute </b></span></div><div><br></div><div>In this role you will working with visual design lead on various aspects of Wintermute client-facing products, as well as the brand identity. You will use your energy, creativity and impeccable taste to create designs across different domains - from professional digital user interfaces to social media memes to occasional print. You’ll work with the visual design lead to execute on the creative direction, contribute to the design system and brand identity and develop new ideas. You will be learning about the dynamic space that crypto is, and will enjoy being at the heart of the evolving blockchain space.</div><br/>Responsibilities <br/><li><b>Digital User Interface Design</b></li><li>Create visual identity for financial user interfaces</li><li>Contribute to and expand the distinctive Wintermute style and design system</li><div><br></div><li><b>Brand Assets&nbsp;</b></li><li>Implement and maintain brand library, including internal and external assets, style, templates, typography, etc</li><li>Propose and execute on creative ideas to take brand identity further</li><div><br></div><li><b>Marketing and Social Media</b></li><li>Create visuals and videos for social media, press releases, etc</li><li>Design digital and physical marketing asset</li><div><br></div><li><b>Collaboration</b></li><li>Work closely with design, marketing and product teams to enhance and reinforce Wintermute brand identity</li><div><br></div><div>But most importantly, all employees can shape and develop their roles. There's no limit set by the company. </div><br/>Hard Requirements <br/><li>Bachelor’s degree in Design, Art or equivalent</li><li>Experience in visual and / or motion design, ideally as part of integrated design and product teams</li><li>Portfolio demonstrating creativity and quality of execution</li><li>Proficiency in Adobe Suite</li><li>Excellent sense of humour</li><br/>Preferred Requirements <br/><li>Strong personal interest in or experience with crypto and / or NFTs</li><li>Experience with generative design</li><li>Experience with Figma</li><li>Experience in data visualisation / infographics</li><div><br></div><br/>Wintermute offer <br/><li>A unique opportunity to work on very interesting projects, get the level of responsibility and ownership that would be unlikely at any other firm</li><li>Great company culture: informal, non-hierarchical, ambitious, highly professional yet collaborative and entrepreneurial&nbsp;</li><li>A cool office in central London with a sci-fi touch</li><li>We support significant flexibility in regards to working from home and working hours; however, we require hard/smart work and &gt;60% work from the office; we are unable to accept remote candidates</li><li>Weekly team events, such as team lunches, team dinners, team board games and Dota playing sessions; these are not obligatory in any sense, but this is what we like to do</li><li>Aligned incentive structure: on top of competitive pay, a significant part of your compensation is performance-based variable pay with unlimited upside</li><li>We offer standard perks too, like pension, private health insurance, free food and office gym, but that’s probably not the right reason to join us</li><li>We offer UK work permits and help in relocation</li><br/>Write to us if <br/><li>You love applying your creativity to various domains - from user interfaces, to print, to digital art objects</li><li>You are determined, ambitious yet humble, willing to work hard and learn on the way</li><li>You like meritocracy and being judged by what you deliver</li><li>You have an entrepreneurial mindset versus 9-to-5 mentality</li><li>You are prepared to work non-standard working hours (since we are a high-growth startup operating in the 24/7 crypto world)</li><li>You like working in the team environment (not fully remote)</li><br/>Tips for a successful application <br/><li>This is a London based role</li><li>Do some research: look at our website and social media channels</li><li>If you don't have an obviously matching experience or skills, make sure you state very clearly what you can bring or how your experience is relevant.</li><li>Prepare to be tested on your hard skills required for this job. We do not care as much about your credentials (university or prior employer), but we care a lot about your knowledge and ability to get things done.</li><li>Unfortunately, we won't be able to proceed if you simply press "submit button"; we do promise to reply to everyone who puts time and effort in making the application relevant!</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/wintermute-trading/d645e8fa-3207-4eb7-aada-8e1e705a4143/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637352/wintermute-trading.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[wintermute@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b33e8b5-6d52-4368-8eea-e8c0ac3382ff]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Wintermute]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Project Manager - Hydra]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOHK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://iohk.io]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>IO Global is searching for a Project Manager to join its Hydra team. Hydra is Cardano’s layer-2 protocol solution, designed to make our network faster and cheaper. We invented this leading-edge blockchain technology to improve our network. As the person managing the delivery of this project, you will have strong project management skills and the ability to lead cross-functional teams to deliver projects on time and within budget. </p> <p>This is a varied role requiring C-level status reporting and a significant amount of hands-on report collation and the chasing down of issues and actions across all levels of the organisation.</p><p><strong>Your mission </strong></p><ul> <li>Leading the planning and implementation of projects</li> <li>Facilitating the definition of project scope, goals, and deliverables</li> <li>Defining tasks and resource requirements</li> <li>Developing full-scale project plans</li> <li>Assembling and coordinating staff</li> <li>Managing the budget</li> <li>Helping the lead software development manager to manage the allocation of resources, and to plan and schedule timelines</li> <li>Tracking deliverables using the appropriate tools</li> <li>Defining, implementing, and tracking quality assurance across the project with the test and quality coordinator</li> <li>Working closely with project stakeholders and coordinating cross-functional activity to ensure that projects are of the defined scope and delivered on time</li> <li>Monitoring and reporting on progress to all stakeholders</li> <li>Collating and presenting reports on progress, problems, and solutions </li> <li>C-level status reporting </li> <li>Chasing down issues and actions across all levels of the organisation</li> <li>Scheduling and chairing weekly operational and stakeholder meetings, and making sure minutes are kept</li> <li>Managing the Raid log of risks, actions, issues, and decisions, and updating it with all project actions </li> <li>Coordinating with individuals and teams on the status of all items. </li> </ul><p><strong>Your expertise  </strong></p> <ul> <li>Qualification in project management or equivalent (CAPM or PMP preferred)</li> <li>Experience (or willingness to be trained) in Jira and scrum</li> <li>Knowledge of the theoretical and practical aspects of project management</li> <li>Familiarity with project management techniques, tools, and software</li> <li>Experience in people management, strategic planning, and risk and change management</li> <li>Strong record of delivering software projects</li> <li>Knowledge and understanding of the systems development life cycle</li> <li>Experience in project management and blockchain development experience would be desirable. </li> </ul><p><strong>Location</strong></p><p>IOG is a fully distributed organization and therefore this is a remote position. Due to team distribution we are ideally searching for someone in a European timezone.  </p><p><strong>All Colleagues</strong></p><ul> <li>Flexible schedule</li> <li>Remote work - ability to work anywhere</li> <li>Laptop reimbursement</li> <li>New starter package to buy hardware essentials (headphones, monitor, etc)</li> <li>Learning &amp; Development opportunities</li> <li>Competitive PTO and Sick Leave plan</li> </ul><p><strong>US Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits coverage through Anthem with 100% premium cost covered by IO Global for the employee and dependents</li> <li>Health Savings Account</li> <li>Life Insurance</li> </ul><p><strong>UK Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Monthly Health Stipend to use towards any wellness or medical coverage/service</li> <li>Pension</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EM-XkuQdUq8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/io-global/j/B5D7DC44BB/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143583/iohk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iohk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b89f946-6d3b-434f-aa32-f0e84ecb2992]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOHK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer - Backend]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Salt]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://saltlending.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Company&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SALT is the pioneer of crypto-backed lending and offers crypto-focused financial services for individuals and businesses. Our mission is to build products that increase access to financial opportunities and give people more control over their ability to generate wealth long term. Committed to fostering adoption of blockchain technology, we’re working to bridge cryptocurrency with traditional finance. With an emphasis on security and customer service, we provide the technology, infrastructure, and tools that make it easy for crypto holders, businesses, banks, and governments across the globe to participate in the blockchain economy. SALT operates a blockchain-based platform that facilitates the issuance of consumer and commercial asset-backed loans secured with cryptocurrency and provides asset management services. The platform is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Salt Blockchain Inc. SALT is a remote first organization with a dynamic workforce. For more information, please visit saltlending.com.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are passionate about what we do and seek others that are excited to be in this cutting-edge space!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Position&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Software Engineering team at SALT has an opportunity for a Senior Backend Software Engineer, working on key areas of the system, such as blockchain monitoring, risk mitigation, transaction processing, loan management, and other ad hoc reports as required by management. The Senior Software Engineer will primarily be responsible for writing and maintaining code in our backend services that directly interface with cryptocurrency blockchains. This position requires a motivated self-learner who is willing to learn from our team while also taking the initiative to expand the team’s knowledge base of cryptocurrency technologies and business opportunities. If you have Fullstack experience, then that’s a plus!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This position will work remotely from anywhere in the U.S. &amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;What you’ll be doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and maintain web services to support the automation and scaling of our business using Node with TypeScript, and Rust&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design scalable systems in a micro-service architecture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Articulate a long term vision for maintaining and scaling our backend systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor builds and facilitate deployments in AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate closely on agile teams of designers, developers, and product managers to build new features and applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write automated tests and leverage type checkers for maximal reliability&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist the engineering team to improve standards, tooling, and processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Research and educate the team on new technologies and approaches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Consistently document development reasoning and procedures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mentor engineers on development techniques and trade-offs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;What we are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of experience in software engineering&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with typed-functional programming languages (Typescript, Rust, Haskell)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building and maintaining scalable systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with relational databases such as PostgreSQL or MySQL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work and communicate in a remote environment&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interest in helping to develop less experienced team members&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Respect for quality assurance and the ability to write robust integration and unit tests&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent problem-solving and time-management abilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to define problems, collect data, establish facts, and draw valid conclusions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to establish and maintain cooperative and positive working relationships&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Organized, detail-oriented, diplomatic, analytical, proactive, self motivated, dependable, and driven by excellence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Even-tempered and able to balance multiple tasks in accordance with changing deadlines and priorities in a fast-paced environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work sensitively and effectively with individuals of diverse backgrounds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’d be thrilled with (nice-to-haves):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with typed-functional programming languages - i.e. Typescript, Rust, Haskell&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with Node and the Express framework&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with with cloud hosting technology, especially AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with cryptographic primitives like hashing and public-key cryptography&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Basic understanding of Bitcoin and Ethereum: general concepts, scripting, smart contracts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work Remotely:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;no commute/traffic, enjoy more flexibility and improved work/life balance, live where you want anywhere within the U.S. and work where you want - comfort of your home, favorite coffee shop, the beautiful outdoors - you pick!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health Insurance &amp;amp; Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;medical, dental and vision health insurance with options for the company to pay 100% of the monthly premiums for employees and all their eligible dependents, health care and dependent care flexible spending account options, virtual health options, robust 24/7 employee assistance program, and company-paid short-term and long-term disability insurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paid Time Off:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;12 company paid holidays and unlimited paid time off - work hard / play hard!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Retirement Savings:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;401(k) with company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Company Equity:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;receive grant of company stock options - build and share in our success!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perks &amp;amp; Recognition Program:&lt;/strong&gt; monthly allowance to spend on gift cards, Visa/Mastercard prepaid cards, donation to charities, use to recognize / gift to others, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Work Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;monthly stipend to use towards home internet, cell phone, and work supplies expenses. A generous payment to use towards your home office set up, in addition to a company-provided tech package - laptop, mouse, keyboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matching Gifts Program:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;company match of your charitable contributions - we support the causes important to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Great Culture:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;partner with an engaged, collaborative team and enjoy our informal culture and fun virtual events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Privacy Policy:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Please review our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://saltlending.com/privacy-policy/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Recruitment Privacy Policy.&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;Your privacy is important to us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/saltlending/jobs/5788628002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/142025/salt.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[salt@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[cdde14b6-345a-4b6a-b17d-e800f51b5eef]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Salt]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Go to Market Manager - Freelance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[SettleMint]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://settlemint.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">SettleMint eliminates complexity in Enterprise blockchain development, deployment and integration. Our low-code Blockchain Platform as a Service (BPaaS) is recognised by Gartner and Everest Group as a leading technological solution for blockchain application development globally. Using our BPaaS solution enables our customers, to rapidly integrate blockchain into their digital transformation projects, to rapidly move from a blockchain concept to a fully integrated solution.</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>About SettleMint organisation and team:</strong><br />SettleMint has offices in Belgium, UAE, India and Singapore. A culturally diverse team with deep industry experience in developing innovative and scalable blockchain developer tools. The team includes industry leading thinkers and doers who strive to extend SettleMint’s product leadership, bound together by the ambition to accelerate blockchain adoption globally. In addition to our in-house team, we work hand-in-hand with leading systems integrators active in the blockchain space to deliver end-to-end solutions to customers. We are currently a team of over 50 and are growing our engineering, solution architecture, client success and sales teams.</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>What’s the opportunity? </strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">One of SettleMint’s flagship products is Databroker.global, a blockchain-supported decentralized data marketplace where buyers and sellers exchange data on a peer-to-peer basis. The data exchanged are put to use towards improving operational efficiencies, capturing new markets, and driving better decision making across industries and the public sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">We are looking for an innovative, detail-oriented Go To Market Manager with strong business acumen for a 5-month mission where you will be leading the go-to-market of a data marketplace for the IOT sector.  </p>
<p dir="ltr">In this pivotal role, you will be reporting directly to the head of marketing and become a key member of the project team. Your mission will be to take ownership and be responsible for the set up and the execution of the platform strategy, which includes the design and management of online and social campaigns, the set up of an industry segmentation, the development of customer personas and the orchestration of content marketing campaigns. Also, the monitoring and reporting of the campaign, the identification and resolution of issues, as well as adhering to contract specifications will be part of your responsibilities. </p>
<p dir="ltr">To be successful in this role, you should be an experienced and versatile project manager with excellent technical skills and sound knowledge of growth hacking techniques, as well as strong interpersonal and communication skills.</p>
<p><br /></p><p><h2>Requirements:</h2></p><ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">3-5 years minimum experience in digital project management, with an expertise in go-to-market strategies, preferably in a start up environment where you had to make it happen.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">An analytical mindset, you are comfortable working with Google Analytics or other reporting tools. You know what a market segmentation is and you are able to connect qualitative and quantitative data analysis and link them into a go-to-market strategy. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Tech savvy with a knowledge of growth hacking and SEO tools (Phantombuster, Sales Navigator, Lusha, Semrush…) ideally experienced with an integrated solution like Hubspot (another one is also ok).  </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Able to work independently or as part of a team and you have a high sense of ownership. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">The ability to dream big but realize that achieving great goals often requires small operational steps that you will be happy to undertake.  </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Motivated to train yourself and curious to learn, you are eager to engage in a learning path where you will be continuously auto-challenging yourself, taking lessons from successes and failures. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">You are proficient in Word, PowerPoint and at least one CMS platform that you have used extensively in the past. Familiarity with Hubspot is a plus, but not absolutely required.  </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">An international experience in Africa is a plus.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Interest for new technologies in general and Blockchain in particular is definitely an asset.</p></li></ul>
<p><br /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Language: </strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Fluent (spoken and written) in English plus one other European language.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Employment Terms:</strong></p>
<ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Freelancer for 2 to 3 days a week based in Belgium</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Potential start early February 2022</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">5 months contract to start with, potential to extend beyond if needed. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Remote to start, reporting to Belgium HQ</p></li></ul>
<p><br /></p>
<p dir="ltr">STRICTLY NO AGENCIES</p>
<p><br /></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/CSVAjHkzW-M" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.settlemint.com/o/go-to-market-manager-freelance/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/430042/SettleMint-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[settlemint@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d53ddeff-9d6a-4af9-b60f-79aaa263e2e3]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[SettleMint]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Data Analyst (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://swissborg.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Lisbon]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We are SwissBorg, a FinTech startup headquartered in Lausanne, Switzerland.</div><div><br></div><div>Our flagship product, the SwissBorg app, offers over 550,000+ users the best price and liquidity across 16 fiat and 17 cryptos, as well as giving them the opportunity to earn passive income with our Smart Yield account. Our community is growing fast, with over $1.5 billion in assets under management, a weekly volume of over 250 million, and over 18,000 Premium users.</div><div><br></div><div>This is just the start in our mission to democratise wealth management by building products that allow individuals to manage their crypto assets at the touch of a finger. Whether you’re in Andorra or Zimbabwe, whether your portfolio is worth one dollar or a million, SwissBorg gives you the best tools to learn about digital currencies and manage your wealth.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to join a team of revolutionaries on a mission to decentralise nations? We want to hear from you!</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Mission:</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Within the Data team and working closely with the Marketing team, to be the reference person who monitors, analyses and assists in the optimisation of the marketing campaigns performed by the campaign managers. In addition, the Marketing Data Analyst will be in charge of proposing and developing the growth experiment based on the knowledge she/he will have acquired from the data.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><i><b>Please note this is a fully remote role for a candidate who can be based anywhere in European timezone. </b></i></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 15px">#LI-Remote</span></div><br/>What you might be doing:<br/><li>In close collaboration with the marketing and data team, monitor, analyse and lead the experiments performed</li><li>Develop a thorough understanding of our various acquisition and retention channels based on the data recorded</li><li>Perform exploratory analysis to discover new areas of opportunity, generate hypotheses and quickly assess the potential benefits of a given opportunity</li><li>Help execute projects to obtain information that leads to growth</li><li>Monitor, optimise and report on marketing and growth measures and split test results</li><li>Make recommendations based on analysis and test results</li><li>Develop frameworks, models, tools and processes to ensure that analytical knowledge can be integrated into all key decision making within the marketing team</li><li>Analyse and develop customised reports to provide the Marketing team with KPIs and key information about our various channels</li><li>Develop the framework and knowledge within the marketing team by aggregating all the knowledge and results obtained from past experiments and data</li><br/>What you might bring:<br/><li>2+ years of experience in a growth analytics role</li><li>MSc in a technical discipline or business preferred&nbsp;</li><li>Excellent analytical and problem-solving skills</li><li>Ability to collect, organise, analyse and disseminate large amounts of information with attention to detail and accuracy while adapting to the individual</li><li>Strong knowledge of statistics, including design of experiments for optimisation, statistical significance, confidence intervals and predictive analysis techniques</li><li>Experience with data extraction using SQL&nbsp;</li><li>Advanced expertise with the most common analysis tools, including Google Analytics, Google Data Studio and Google Sheet</li><li>Ease in the creation of dashboards adapted to the different interlocutors and excellent reporting skills with a concise and clear style</li><li>Strong interest in marketing, digital marketing and proactive monitoring of the rapid evolution of these fields</li><li>Must be independent, organised and detail-oriented, as well as have the ability to multi-task and work effectively in a fast-paced environment</li><li>Coding skills is a plus (Python)</li><li>Experience in product and marketing analysis tools such as Adjust, Mixpanel and Metabase a great plus</li><li>Team player, excellent communication skills, positive attitude and good work ethic. You bring creative solutions to difficult problems</li><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Why you should apply: </b></div><div><br></div><div>- Freedom to build the company of your dreams</div><div>- Learn with (super cool) experts in finance, engineering, AI, psychology and business</div><div>- CHSB bonus based on our meritocratic system</div><div>- We'll provide you with a MacBook and a cutting edge tech stack to help you do your best work</div><div>- Flexible work hours</div><div>- Annual team retreats with colleagues around the world</div><div>- Continuous learning and development opportunities</div><div><br></div><div>Oh and are you planning on having a kid? That’s great! We have a bunch of those: you’ll get time off to enjoy that (other) adventure!&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><i>At SwissBorg, we embrace diversity. We strongly believe that getting to the best outcomes requires different perspectives and backgrounds. We’re committed to openness, curiosity and creating an inclusive culture as we know that diverse teams build better products and generate better ideas. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status.</i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/02lonwc5XE4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/swissborg/0ac57c7e-f544-4237-8f7c-44ab6a47d906/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/440178/Swissborg-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[swissborg@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f4703261-2e7b-4b75-af19-fbdfc5e62c02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Institutional Support Analyst -  Prime Operations]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re Coinbase. We’re the world’s most trusted way to join the crypto revolution, serving more than 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/our-mission-strategy-and-culture-18a92a3bb0fa&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web 3.0 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve got good vibes. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As an Institutional Support Analyst, you’ll join a high performing team of hardworking support professionals whose performance is critical to Coinbase achieving its mission. You will serve as a subject matter specialist for Coinbase’s institutional suite of products (Prime, Custody), providing premier service and support to our most valued clients and coverage team. Diligent, insightful, and have a bias towards action, you will play a crucial role in the success of the Client Services organization as we help build the cryptoeconomy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serve as a domain specialist across multiple channels, supporting our highest value customers and institutions on Coinbase’s institutional products (including Prime and Custody)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide white glove support to our highest priority global clients through phone, email and video calls in an articulate and insightful manner&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Make informed, data-driven decisions through a detailed understanding of metrics and the business&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serve as a key member in the team strategy of crafting a global 24x7 operating model for Prime Broker support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive impactful changes across workflows and tools by partnering with the sales, engineering, and product teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Continuously make valuable contributions through effective project management, conclusive prioritization, and efficient execution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Set a high bar for support analysts within the organization by setting an example through performance and work ethic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Operationalize new and existing policies, processes, and procedures related to the Client Services scope&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate prospect and client demo calls, serving as subject matter specialist on product features and answering technical cryptocurrency related questions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serve as the voice of the customer to internal teams including Advocacy, Engineering and Product when surfacing bugs, incidents, and product feedback&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in a weekend on-call rotation and serve as an escalation point for high priority requests or complex investigations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we look for in you (ie. job requirements):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Motivated by Coinbase’s mission and creating a seamless, scalable support experience for our global customer base&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with high priority clients, compliance, product support, payments, fraud, or other relevant operational domains&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of cryptocurrency, global financial markets, and/or trading platforms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum of 2 years of relevant experience in financial services, technology and/or customer support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with different channels of support, including voice, e-mail and/or chat&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Must work in a defined shift, as required by the business. Weekend support is required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fantastic communication skills in order to operate across multiple departments, stakeholders, and clients&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible and adaptable to meet the evolving needs of a high-growth and fast paced organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Travel requirements up to 20% to Coinbase offices and client locations (depending on business need)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in API support or FIX support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency in one or more of the following languages: French,&amp;nbsp; German,&amp;nbsp; Spanish or another language&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Notice for Colorado applicants as required by sb19-085 (8-5-20). Target annual salary for this role performed in Colorado, is $65,450 + target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ID: P37608&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations@ coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Please contact accommodations@ coinbase.com for additional information or to request accommodations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3772510?gh_jid=3772510&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of Events Marketing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BitGo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.bitgo.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitGo is the leader in custody and security solutions with over $64B in assets under custody. Founded in 2013, BitGo is the first digital asset company to focus exclusively on serving institutional clients. In 2018, it launched BitGo Trust Company, the first qualified custodian purpose-built for storing digital assets and established BitGo New York Trust in 2021. BitGo also offers market leading trading, lending, and borrowing services and supports over 400 digital assets on its platform. BitGo provides the security and operational backbone for more than 500 institutional clients in 50 countries, including many of the world’s top cryptocurrency exchanges and platforms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re hiring an&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Events Marketing Director&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; who will &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;own the event strategy and execution for conferences and events in the Blockchain/Crypto space globally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide vision and strategy for BitGo’s&amp;nbsp; global execution of conferences and events that supports key business objectives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Sponsor Third-Party Conferences: Plan and execute third-party conference sponsorships end-to-end that allows for an engaging on-site presence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with our Brand Design Team on event promotion and space designs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support our executive team on preparing for events&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Explore new channels and events for engaging with the broader crypto market and deliver recommendations to executive leadership&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Marketing, Sales and Product&amp;nbsp; to ensure events are in line with business goals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track and report event KPIs including Marketing Engaged Leads, Trials, and Attendee demographics, tools &amp;amp; technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Frequently travel (worldwide)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5-8 years of experience in a relevant role and are comfortable managing stakeholder expectations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong public speaking and networking skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills. Must have the ability to effectively connect with internal and external stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong strategic thinking skills. Must have the ability to identify and solve problems by consulting with key stakeholders, predicting metrics, and sharing data-driven recommendations to executive leadership.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enjoy attending conferences and technical events&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analytical and data-driven mindset. Must have the ability to set goals, execute and measure the results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Join BitGo?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Disrupting an industry takes vision, innovation, passion, technical chops, drive to deliver, collaboration, and execution. Join a team of great people who strive for excellence and personify our corporate values of ownership, craftsmanship, and open communication. We are looking for new colleagues who bring innovative ways of thinking and problem solving, and who want risks to be part of the team that changes the world’s financial markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the benefits of working at BitGo:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive base salary, bonus and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% company paid health insurance for employee, partner and dependents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 5% 401k company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave, paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free custom lunches, dinners and snacks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer equipment and workplace furniture to suit your needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great colleagues and inspiring startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Benefits may vary based on location&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrencies are the most disruptive change the financial services industry has seen in years. Join us and you’ll be able to look back and say you were part of the team that transformed investing.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yGR7NLjXslU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitgo/jobs/5791735002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175514/birgo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitgo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b720d671-6d88-4863-a59d-ea5d1c6feea8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BitGo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
