<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Trust & Security]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York; Portland, Oregon; Chicago, Illinois; Los Angeles, California; San Francisco, California; Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is a crypto exchange and custodian that allows customers to buy, sell, store, and earn more than 30 cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, bitcoin cash, ether, litecoin, and Zcash. Gemini is a New York trust company that is subject to the capital reserve requirements, cybersecurity requirements, and banking compliance standards set forth by the New York State Department of Financial Services and the New York Banking Law. Gemini was founded in 2014 by twin brothers Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss to empower the individual through crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto is about giving you greater choice, independence, and opportunity. We are here to help you on your journey. We build crypto products that are simple, elegant, and secure. Whether you are an individual or an institution, we want to help you buy, sell, and store your bitcoin and cryptocurrency. Crypto is not just a technology, it&#39;s a movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Department: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engineering&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is regulated and licensed like a bank, but it’s run like a tech startup, and engineering is the core of the company.&amp;nbsp; There’s a wide range of tough problems to solve at Gemini – from properly securing hundreds of millions of dollars worth of customer funds, to developing innovative new blockchain products, to finding new techniques to combat fraud, to shaving microseconds off our API response times, and everything in between.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;All of Gemini’s engineers are able to work across the software platform, not just on their own specialization or subteam. We value a thoughtful, collaborative software development process, coupled with a pragmatic approach to problem solving and delivering software.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Senior Software Engineer for Trust &amp;amp; Safety&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As an engineer on our backend team, you’ll architect and solve complex problems that will directly influence the direction of the digital asset space. There’s a wide range of problems to solve at Gemini – from properly securing millions of dollars worth of customer funds, to developing innovative new blockchain products, to shaving microseconds off our API response times. We have a strong culture of code reviews, and a focus on security, with the end goal of writing and shipping high-quality code by getting things right the first time. We want to continue building the best product we can as we scale and grow our business. If you get excited about solving technical challenges that directly impact our customers, clients, and the rest of the Gemini team, we’d love to hear from you.&amp;nbsp; This role can be based in any of our New York, Chicago, San Francisco, or Portland, Oregon offices as well as remotely in the United States&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop new products and product features on the Gemini platform, as part of a tight knit team of two to eight developers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write automated tests and work with our QA team to ensure the operation and correctness of new product features.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide technical input and knowledge to the planning, design, and requirements process for new products and features.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Review other software engineers’ code for correctness, style, and information security concerns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Improve the performance, maintainability, and operations of the Gemini code base by engaging in occasional refactoring and upgrade projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support your team’s production software by responding to an occasional alert or bug report.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 6 years of software engineering experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Advanced proficiency in at least one language. We use mostly Scala, Java and C++ on our backend and Typescript on the frontend – it’s great if you’re comfortable in those or if you’re willing to learn.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to work closely across teams and manage dependencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A customer- and product-focused mindset, with the ability to make well-reasoned tradeoffs between speed and quality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to adapt and handle multiple competing priorities in collaboration with peers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with fraud detection and ML systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work experience or knowledge of the finance industry, payments, trading and/or exchange systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-DA1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/70jrfYSxKC4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3134120&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Genesis Global Trading]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://genesistrading.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City, New York, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p><br></p><h3>About Genesis</h3><p>Genesis is a global leader in institutional digital asset markets. We provide a single point of access for digital asset trading, derivatives, borrowing, lending, custody and prime brokerage services.</p><p>Genesis facilitates billions in trades, loans and transactions on a monthly basis. We have a proven track record driving results for some of the largest digital asset-focused hedge funds, quant funds, family offices, VC’s, market makers and exchanges.</p><p><br></p><h3>Join Our Team</h3><p>Genesis is expanding to solve some of the toughest challenges in digital asset financial markets.</p><p><br></p><h3>About This Role – Technical Project Manager</h3><p>Genesis Trading is seeking a Technical Project Manager with experience managing software and infrastructure related technology projects. The Technical Project Manager will translate requirements into project planning materials used to ensure accountability and delivery of critical technology projects. Leading projects through their entire lifecycle, including defining goals, developing timelines, tracking milestones, managing engineer time, identifying risks, and coordinating with related teams are essential to the success of this role.</p><h3><br></h3><h3>Primary Responsibilities</h3><ul> 						<li>Develop and maintain projects plans for software and infrastructure projects</li> <li>Coordinate across various teams of stakeholders to ensure successful project delivery</li> </ul><p><br></p><h3>Requirements</h3><ul> <li>B.S. degree in Computer Science or related area</li> <li>2+ years of project or program management experience working with engineering teams</li> <li>Experience managing software and infrastructure projects</li> <li>Experience with project management planning tools (i.e. JIRA, spreadsheets, Gantt charts)</li> <li>Ability to describe detailed problems with clarity and accuracy</li> <li>Ability to handle competing priorities and to work effectively in a fast-paced environment</li> <li>Strong organizational and time management skills</li> </ul><p><br></p><h3>Personal Attributes</h3><ul> <li>Strong interpersonal and communication skills</li> <li>Self-starter yet knows when to ask for help and works great in a team</li> <li>Strives to simultaneously achieve high-velocity and high-quality output</li> <li>Willingness and ability to meet aggressive deadlines</li> <li>Thrives in a dynamic and high-pressured environment</li> <li>Proven troubleshooting and problem-solving skills</li> </ul><p><br></p><h3>Benefits</h3><ul> <li>Comprehensive health, vision, dental and FSA benefits</li> <li>Flexible time off</li> </ul><p><br></p><h3>Why Genesis</h3><p>Genesis is dedicated to creating best-in-class infrastructure for institutional investors, developing advanced products that lower barriers, increase profitability and broaden access. Our team has decades of experience at top Wall Street investment banks and Silicon Valley technology firms, and includes leading experts in blockchain, distributed computing, cryptography and cybersecurity.</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Digital Asset Ecosystem</strong></p><p>Genesis operates at the heart of the digital asset ecosystem:</p><p>→ We are a subsidiary of Digital Currency Group (DCG), the largest investor in the bitcoin and blockchain space.</p><p>→ We have an unparalleled global network at the intersection of data, finance and technology.</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Accelerating Momentum</strong></p><p>Our addressable market is expanding rapidly as new institutional investors enter the space. Recent results include:</p><p>→ 300%+ Y/Y trading volume growth</p><p>→ 400%+ Y/Y loan origination growth</p><p>→ 300%+ Y/Y active loan growth</p><p>→ 150%+ Q/Q derivatives transaction growth</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Diversity And Inclusion</strong></p><p>Genesis invests in creating a welcoming environment where everyone can feel supported and connected at work.</p><p>→ We help employees develop a deep understanding of the problems we’re trying to solve.</p><p>→ We thrive on ideas driven by a broad range of perspectives.</p><p>→ We believe diverse teams lead to better products and bigger outcomes.</p><p><br></p><p><em>We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.</em></p><p>Requirements</p><p>Benefits</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/genesistrading/j/4457BFD983/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/393086/genesistrading.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[genesis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c9bd0dc3-d1d2-4216-adf4-36b49462bc09]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Genesis Global Trading]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Axoni]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://axoni.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Axoni is building the next generation of capital markets technology. Our solutions are used by the world’s leading banks, asset managers, hedge funds, and infrastructure providers. Our diverse team focuses every day on our goal of building products that will change and improve how our clients and the markets will interact.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are seeking talented, motivated professionals that want to be part of this once-in-a-career opportunity to not only see, but also drive the incredible changes coming to global capital markets. We are building a culture where our team feels valued and everyone is given an opportunity to grow and succeed. We try to live by our Core Values and demonstrate what we believe represent the kind of company we are working to build. These Values are: Delivery is everything; Choose Kindness; Be better every day.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Responsibilities:</b> Build and deploy the core technology underpinning blockchain networks on a wide variety of projects from the development of our core software, to API servers, database integrations, and measuring and</div><div>improving network performance. This role has heavy emphasis on clean software development, algorithm design, as well as the development of scalable high-throughput systems.</div><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Master’s degree in Computer Science, Electrical Engineering, or a related field plus 1 year of experience in the job offered, software engineering, or a related occupation. </li><div><br></div><li>Prior experience must include 1 year of experience in writing large scale, high quality, high-reliability, well tested code using either Go, C++, Java, or a comparable compiled programming language; 1 year of experience working with SQL or NoSQL databases; 1 year of experience with a scripting language such as JavaScript (<a href="http://node.js/">Node.js</a>), Python or Bash; and 1 year of experience working in Unix/Linux environments and with CI/CD tools such as Jenkins.</li><div>Individuals seeking employment at Axoni are considered without regards to race, color, religion, national origin, age, sex, marital status, ancestry, physical or mental disability, veteran status, gender identity, or sexual orientation. You are being given the opportunity to provide the following information in order to help us comply with federal and state Equal Employment Opportunity/Affirmative Action record keeping, reporting, and other legal requirements.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xO7B4WYKVZE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axoni/98270bd7-c474-466b-8894-783d57031d80/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145318/axoni.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axoni@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b96c34e0-5c46-4ec2-8e42-397e29857c6f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Axoni]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Procurement Coordinator (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitfury.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Toronto, Ontario, Canada]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;div id=&quot;header&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at Bitfury:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is a leading emerging technologies company. &amp;nbsp;At Bitfury, you can build the solutions of the future, with the most significant technologies of the millennium, in a modern and flexible workplace. We work a bit faster, and a bit smarter, so we can make the world a bit better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of Working at Bitfury:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Experiences &amp;amp; Global Impacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is an international company with 200+ team members in more than 16 countries. No matter your assignment, your work will support global technology initiatives and best-in-class security operations in North America, Asia and Europe, as well as help us fulfil our mission to make the world more trusted and secure.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building the Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe big data, artificial intelligence, blockchain technology, tokenized economies and cryptocurrencies are the future of our digital, global economy. Bitfury is building this future through our products that offer digitised security, asset management, government services and more. We consider ourselves first and foremost a technology company. We are a diversified organisation, with operations across multiple facets of the AI, blockchain, and digital currency sectors. If you are passionate about emerging technologies, you can build your future at Bitfury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Your Career&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is growing fast and looking for the next generation of leaders and entrepreneurs to help us. At Bitfury, you will be expected to create the future – not just execute it. If you are a self-starter, driven and collaborative team member, you can create a dynamic future for yourself and your career at Bitfury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modern Workplace with Intelligent Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury lets you work in the way you need to work to make your work faster, smarter and better. We will give you the resources you need to succeed – competitive pay and benefits, educational support, intellectual challenges, professional advancement, personal accommodations including remote work, and more. We pride ourselves on being less bureaucratic and a lot more impactful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start-up Culture with Established Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with the world’s leading experts and engineers, you will have the opportunity at Bitfury to pursue results that will power your success as well as lead to the adoption of game-changing technologies. Our teams work every day to make the impossible possible, to change the game, to be agile and effective, and most of all – to empower the rest of the world to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ersonal and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rofessional&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;haracteristics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We at Bitfury ensure our team members possess the ability to think out of the box and make the impossible possible. We are self-motivated and result-oriented, and we have an “owner of the company” mindset. We are constantly self-educating and developing. We are able to work in a team and collaborate. We have a “do good” mindset and are not afraid to dream big. And of course, we always deliver in time what we promised and with extreme attention to detail — because if we are not able to do the little things right, we will never be able to do big things right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role consists in optimisation of daily power procurement processes and support in identifying, securing power procurement contracts for the development of Bitfury’s data centers in Norway/Sweden and Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties and responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permanent review of Company’s current contract prices;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identification of market opportunities and potential new suppliers, execute contract re-negotiations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define tactics and methods:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define and refine electricity purchase tactics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refine methids of electricity cost reporting and analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop tactics and methods implementation plan (e.g. propose additional electricity suppliers);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop hedging policy (electricity and certificates):
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform historical price analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare risk profile assessment and proposal for hedging portfolio content, including time horizons. PPA opportunity mapping;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing hedging instructions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing hedging plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily power procurement (EU, North America)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support with search for new promising sites for future Data Centers with cheap energy and available power.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support with paper work, managing external consultants and/or subcontractors (certified estimates for applications, preliminary design, etc), upon request;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span lang=&quot;EN-US&quot;&gt;Specific knowledge, skills and abilities: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Must:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-year minimum experience in the power sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of power market structures, rules and ancillary services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding the power generation, transmission and distribution mechanisms as physically, as commercially.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to breakdown and model grid tariffs and ancillary services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial mindset and ability to work autonomously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As-a-plus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of Bitcoin blockchain and mining economics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Power trading experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong network across power generating companies in Europe and North America.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/DtkFJoj24rE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitfury/jobs/5793858002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145862/bitfury.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitfury@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bff43dfe-8ac3-4757-8a78-7559c9e9e327]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Delivery Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Uphold]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://uphold.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Braga]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span>About Uphold</span></p>
<p><span>Uphold is an easy-to-use investments and payments app. Specialising in digital assets, we serve more than 7 million customers in 150 countries. We open around 15,000 accounts a day and provide consumers with a more versatile and cost-effective home for their daily financial lives. For businesses, we provide regulated infrastructure to connect crypto with fiat currencies. Today, we support 51 digital assets, 28 national currencies, four precious metals and fractional U.S. equities. </span></p>
<p><span>Uphold’s unique trading experience - ‘Anything-to-Anything’ - allows customers to trade directly between any supported asset or currency in one step - physical gold to Bitcoin, for example - saving both time and money. Uphold supports financial inclusion by enabling customers virtually anywhere to open an account in less than 5 minutes and to invest with no minimum amounts. Customers can send money to virtually anyone with an email address free of charge. </span></p>
<p><span>To learn more, please visit </span><a href="https://uphold.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span>https://uphold.com</span></a></p>
<p><span>If you’re a Rockstar and this sounds interesting and challenging, we want to hear from you. Apply here!</span></p>
<p><br><span>The opportunity: </span></p>
<p><span>Uphold is looking for a Delivery Manager to join our Engineering team. This is an incredibly exciting opportunity where you will plan and oversee projects within Uphold. You'll coordinate people and processes to deliver projects on time, within budget and with desired outcomes aligned to OKRs.</span></p>
<p><br><span>What you’ll be doing primarily:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Work with the Chief Delivery Officer to evangelize and put into operation delivery and project management processes internally.</span></li>
<li><span>Work with the Project Managers, Product Managers, Owners and others to help define the roadmap for any given product or initiative.</span></li>
<li><span>Predict resources needed to reach objectives and manage resources effectively and efficiently.</span></li>
<li><span>Identifying areas of the organisation in need of improvement and helping drive that transformation.</span></li>
<li><span>Championing Uphold vision through leadership, advocacy, and action, as we fight to improve the company in many areas.</span></li>
<li><span>Moving the organisation to clear ´sunset´ delivery dates so that multiple functions can be properly coordinated to ensure effective product launches.</span></li>
<li><span>Provide project updates consistently to various stakeholders about strategy, adjustments, and progress.</span></li>
<li><span>Utilize industry best practices, techniques, and standards throughout the entire project execution.</span></li>
<li><span>Collaborate with leadership and cross-functional teams to deliver the projects.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br><span>Required qualifications:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>BS/MS in computer science, design, business or equivalent experience.</span></li>
<li><span>Comfort working in an agile, fast-moving, iterative software development process.</span></li>
<li><span>Be smart, analytical and creative problem solver.</span></li>
<li><span>Proven ability to solve problems creatively.</span></li>
<li><span>Proven ability to complete projects according to outlined scope, budget, and timeline.</span></li>
<li><span>Ability to be highly effective in a remote-first environment.</span></li>
<li><span>Significant experience in leading software teams.</span></li>
<li><span>Excitement to act as a team lead with significant ownership of the group’s efforts.</span></li>
<li><span>Effective communication skills; a positive, team player.</span></li>
<li><span>Fluent written and oral English skills.</span></li>
<li><span>Not be afraid of experimenting with alternative solutions to problems.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br><span>Bonus if you have:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Fluency in cryptocurrencies or other digital assets as they are core to our business.</span></li>
<li><span>Community talks, certifications, and/or blog posts on your interests and research.</span></li>
<li><span>Open source project contributions of any kind, such as tools developed to solve specific problems you’ve had or fixing issues on existing projects.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span>Importantly, if you’re looking for a senior role with us, you will have achieved many of the things above while also providing mentorship to others, and have engaged in public speaking opportunities.</span></p>
<p><br><span>What we have to offer you:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>An amazing work environment in a company that continues to grow, driven by extraordinary and passionate people that keep up innovating and challenging more each day.</span></li>
<li><span>An international team, in a cutting edge field, working on the most fascinating projects.</span></li>
<li><span>Growth and career opportunities, and the chance to be proactive and creative.</span></li>
<li><span>A flexible and enthusiastic work environment that offers you snacks, a lot of coffee and other great benefits.</span></li>
<li><span>Open and transparent culture - we get together on a weekly basis to share updates, strategic plans, and engage with each other informally over food and drinks.</span></li>
<li><span>Interesting events that keep you connected with the team and celebrate our success.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span>Be part of a great company that is revolutionizing the financial services. Apply now!</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><br><span>EEOC Employer</span></p>
<p><span>We're proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer and we celebrate our employees' differences, including race, color, religion, gender identity, national origin, age, military service eligibility, veteran status, sexual orientation, marital status, disability, and any other protected classes. Difference makes us stronger and better - together.</span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/UpvIJLUizB8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://uphold.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=311&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144414/uphold.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[uphold@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[8acc9c28-72bb-41e4-9d28-123751dcb8ad]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Uphold]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sales Manager - Crypto / Blockchain / Fin Tech]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Latoken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, GB - Remote OK]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>LATOKEN exchange has 2 million accounts including 900k+ users of our Android app rated 4.4 by 25+ thousands of reviews. We leverage the next tech to make account opening as easy as Instagram. The technology and our Olympic sports culture can make us the first billion users digital wallet needed to free people to manage their financial life. Today, is a great moment to join us as crypto is expanding into mainstream financial market and <a>ex CFO of JP Morgan joined</a> our advisory board and <a>2 presidents joined us</a> in Davos.<br><br>For the past 3 years we have been developing our own blockchain (called “Lachain”) and we are now building the DeFi ecosystem based on it (including DEX, dApp, IDO, NFT etc) and launched our <a>mainnet</a>. <a>Here is our backlog.</a></p><p><strong>Mission:</strong> Paid top token listings with a co-marketing budget.</p><p><strong>Mission description: </strong><strong>Story</strong>: LATOKEN users need top token listings on the platform to trade and invest their funds. <strong>Key PROBLEM's</strong>: Make 2 paid Listings within 1st month. <strong>How</strong>: List tokens from your own CRM pipeline, agents, and own search. <strong>Constraints</strong>: Focus on paid listings &amp; strong token trader community. <br><br><strong>Main performance number:</strong> Listings revenue<br><strong>Second performance number:</strong> Listing trading fees<br><strong>Third performance number:</strong> New Listing clients<br><br><strong>Functions:</strong><br>• Sourcing : Hunt and list top promising projects to list with us before any other exchange.<br>• Clients : Build relationship with clients. Make first approach, learn their needs and pains, and show the value of LATOKEN exchange.<br>• Deals : Increase listing and trading fees revenue by winning IEO/Listing deals.<br>• Product : Participate in custdev, detect clients' pains, reasons of rejections, formulates hypothesis and implement the changes to improve our products.<br>• Team : Grow your team of top-performing sales managers to increase sales revenue.<br>• Workflow : Keep everything well organised and follow company's workflow.<br>• Training : Grow your sales skills through workshops and ghost calls of your senior buddy.<br><br><strong>Requirement skills and experience:</strong><br></p><p>2+ years in B2B sales or busdev for investment / fintech products or services.Experience in investments/fintech is a strong plus. Personal experience with cryptocurrencies &amp; blockchain tokens.Demand the highest standards for clear and MECE-defined roles and OKRs.Fluent English.SQL queries / Python skills as a plus.</p><p><br><br></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ikbGulIPQs0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.breezy.hr/p/b655caf1ad7901-sales-manager-crypto-blockchain-fin-tech/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/178323/latoken.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[latoken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[ad8a3cbd-f1ed-4400-b372-af94f5f06cb4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Latoken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[DataOps Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Akuna Capital]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://akunacapital.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sydney, NSW]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Akuna:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Akuna Capital is an innovative trading firm with a strong focus on collaboration, cutting-edge technology, data driven solutions and automation. We specialize in providing liquidity as an options market maker – meaning we are committed to providing competitive quotes that we are willing to both buy and sell. To do this successfully we design and implement our own low latency technologies, trading strategies and mathematical models. At Akuna we have a flat structure, where the best idea wins.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Founding Partners, including our CEO Andrew Killion, first conceptualized Akuna in their hometown of Sydney. They opened our first office in 2011 in Chicago, the heart of the derivatives &amp;amp; options industry. &amp;nbsp;Akuna then expanded to Sydney in 2018 to be the center of our Asian trading operations, and in 2021 moved to our new Barangaroo waterfront office. We are currently trading HK, Korea, cryptocurrencies and US night markets and are excited for expansions into all the major Asian exchanges. We also have offices in Shanghai and Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Akuna, we believe that the people are the center of everything we do. Our Sydney office has a start-up feel with less than 200 people, which means you really get to know the team! We run social poker competitions, office happy hours, have a fully stacked breakfast and snack room, host social events, go on company trips, have social clubs, and offer great training with our Akuna University. We are expanding rapidly and looking for the best talent to join us on this journey. If you enjoy being part of smart, driven teams with real challenges to solve- this could be the place for you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll do as a&amp;nbsp;DataOps&amp;nbsp;Engineer on the Data Engineering team at Akuna:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a data-driven organization! We&#39;re looking for a DataOps Engineer to take our data platform to the next level. At Akuna, we believe that our data provides a key competitive advantage and is a critical part to the success of our business. Our Data Team is composed of world class talent and runs our infrastructure and build exceptional management and monitoring tooling. Our data platform extends globally and must support ingestion, processing sand access to complex datasets for a wide range of streaming and batch use cases. To support it we build, deploy and monitor the platform in efficient and highly automated ways, building on the best frameworks and technologies available.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In this role, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work within&amp;nbsp;the&amp;nbsp;global&amp;nbsp;data team, using your expertise to build highly automated provisioning, monitoring and operational capabilities for data at&amp;nbsp;Akuna&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the ongoing growth, design and expansion of our data platform across a wide variety of data sources, enabling large scale support across an array of streaming, near real-time and research&amp;nbsp;workflows&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Operate the data platform to ensure key SLAs are managed across a wide range of producers and&amp;nbsp;consumers&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and run essential monitoring infrastructure supporting many of the most important data pipelines at the&amp;nbsp;firm&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the Data Infrastructure team to coordinate high quality data platform releases into our hybrid cloud&amp;nbsp;architecture&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce clean, well-tested, and documented code with a clear design to support mission critical&amp;nbsp;applications&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenge the status quo and help push our organization forward, as we grow beyond the limits of our current tech&amp;nbsp;stack&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Report directly into our Data Team Lead who is based in Sydney&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualities that make great candidates:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/MS/PhD in Computer Science, Engineering or equivalent technical field&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of professional experience developing and operating automation, monitoring and management&amp;nbsp;solutions&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior hands-on experience with data platforms and technologies such as Kafka, Delta Lake, Spark, Elastic Search&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior hands-on experience with observability and monitoring tools (Prometheus, Grafana, ELK stack&amp;nbsp;etc)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience with a leading cloud provider (AWS, Azure, Google Cloud Platform)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of at least one programming language (Java, Python, C++, Scala, Go, etc.) – Java, Scala experience is a plus&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with containerization and container orchestration technologies, like Docker, Kubernetes, and Argo is a plus&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated and willing to take ownership of high-impact projects upon&amp;nbsp;arrival&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on, collaborative working style, with the ability to build relationships with multiple&amp;nbsp;teams&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience using software engineering best practices like Continuous Integration / Deployment to deliver complex software projects&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/_tT7wJWEWy8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.akunacapital.com/job-details?gh_jid=3785474&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/195886/akuna.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[akiuna@crypto-careerrs.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b05d9bd-e49a-47fe-8b17-9f153850eba3]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Akuna Capital]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[VP Distribution]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[ADDX]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://addx.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>Who are we?</b></div><div>Here at ADDX, we believe in a future where everybody can access financial ecosystems easily, fairly, and safely. That is why we’ve built the world’s first fully regulated platform for digital securities, licensed by the Monetary Authority of Singapore.</div><div><br></div><div>In 2021, we raised USD 50 million in Series A funding led by Japan Investment Corporation and Development Bank of Japan. Among other esteemed investors, we are backed by Singapore Exchange and Heliconia, a subsidiary of Temasek.</div><div><br></div><div>We have gone through a total re-brand and promise this to be an exciting time. An integral part of a fast-growing team enabling investments in unicorns, pre-IPO companies, and hedge funds, your role is to innovate and discover new solutions.</div><div><br></div><div>If you believe in a future of fair financial markets, just like we do, we’ve been waiting for you at ADDX.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Who are we looking for?</b></div><div><br></div><div>Named the Most Innovative Fintech by Global Brands, we are redefining private market investing and are looking for&nbsp;an VP distributor to join our Growth team.</div><div><br></div><div>You will be responsible for building a B-to-B business by pitching to and collaborating with Financial Institution strategic partners.</div><br/>Responsibility<br/><li>Analyze the unique needs of Financial Institution strategic partners, effectively pitch the benefits of collaborating with ADDX accordingly</li><li>Support the Head of Distribution and Partnerships with driving outreach to financial institutions (including asset managers and private banks)</li><li>Develop and execute strategic plans to achieve business-to-business sales targets and expand the customer base</li><li>Build and maintain strong, long-lasting investor relationships</li><li>Effectively communicate the value proposition through proposals, presentations and any content format required</li><li>Contribute to overall platform marketing effort and position ADDX as the platform of choice for accessing capital markets more efficiently&nbsp;</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Entrepreneurial mindset, creative strategist, solution-driven, and proven experience in institutional sales</li><li>Strong professional network and market knowledge&nbsp;</li><li>Excellent interpersonal and communication skills&nbsp;</li><li>More than 10 years of experience in institutional sales (preference for global markets or asset manager)</li><div>Due to our limited capacity, we regret that only shortlisted candidates will be notified. </div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/7ErT7T4wgYI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/addx/221827e2-e96c-4e66-a6ec-f0b0a3626234/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/413784/addx-istox-logo.jpeg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[addx@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b82fa9b1-c059-434f-82d6-6cb949f49699]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[ADDX]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Manager - Social Media]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">About Celsius Network</span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>Celsius addresses the financial needs of today’s consumers worldwide through a democratized reward income and lending platform accessible via a mobile app. With a mission to put unparalleled economic freedom in the hands of the people, and a core belief that financial services should only do what is in the best interests of the community, Celsius is a modern platform where membership provides access to curated financial services that are not available through traditional financial institutions. Crypto holders can earn high-yield compounding interest by transferring coins to their Celsius Wallet and can borrow fiat currency against their crypto collateral at the lowest interest rates in the space.  </span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span>The Celsius team is committed to doing good and doing well. We believe in the power of disruption and the importance of decentralization to create a new system that acts in the best interest of everyone. Each member of our team brings something unique and innovative to the table, but the common thread that links us together is our passion for blockchain, equality, and leading the next financial revolution that changes the equation to bring power back to the people. </span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">Marketing Manager - Social Media</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>Responsibilities:</span></p>
<ul>
<li>
<ul>
<li>
<ul>
<li><span>Manage social media strategy across TW, IG, FB and others</span></li>
<li><span>Drive growth in community, engagement of community and positive sentiment of community through these channels</span></li>
<li><span>Own and drive proactive content calendar that aligns with company and marketing themes</span></li>
<li><span>Develop a metrics and measurement plan to understand effectiveness</span></li>
<li><span>Partner with other channels to build a holistic picture of the customer experience with Celsius</span></li>
<li><span>Create innovative content formats independently and in collaboration with creative team</span><span></span></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li><span>Requirements</span>
<ul>
<li><span>Experience developing content and creative for social media</span></li>
<li><span>Experience developing a proactive content strategy and calendar for social media</span></li>
<li><span>Extremely organized, can manage multiple projects and workstreams simultaneously</span></li>
<li><span>Strong communicator and strong copywriting skills</span></li>
<li><span>Ability to develop creative independently from creative team</span></li>
<li><span>Experience collaborating with cross-functional teams such as legal and creative</span></li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xW6QWaNfysw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=501&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/731816/celsius_network.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celsius@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5fa72b05-b42d-48a9-806e-c3fdccb06776]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, Sanctions Compliance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Circle]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.circle.com/de/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Chicago - will also consider remote in US]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Circle is a global financial technology firm that enables businesses of all sizes to harness the power of digital currency and public blockchains for payments, commerce and financial applications worldwide. Circle platforms and products provide a suite of internet-native financial services for payments, treasury infrastructure and capital formation. Circle is also a principal developer of USD Coin (USDC), which has become the fastest growing dollar digital currency in the world. USDC has grown to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;over 40 billion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in circulation and supported over&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; $1.3 trillion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in transactions in the past year. Circle’s payments and treasury infrastructure services available through the Circle Account and APIs helps bridge the legacy financial system and digital currency and blockchain based finance.&amp;nbsp; Circle’s SeedInvest service brings internet-native fundraising and capital formation to startups and growth companies.&amp;nbsp; Combined, Circle’s suite of services helps companies to participate in a more open, global and inclusive financial system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be part of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;With the mission “To raise global economic prosperity through the frictionless exchange of financial value,” Circle was founded on the belief that the internet, blockchains and digital currency will rewire the global economic system, creating a fundamentally more open, inclusive, efficient and integrated world economy.&amp;nbsp; We envision a global economy where people and businesses everywhere can more freely connect and transact with each other with new technologies for digital money and internet-native finance. We believe such a system can raise prosperity for people and companies everywhere. Our mission is powered by the values we espouse and which we expect all Circlers to respect. We are Multistakeholder, serving the needs of our customers, our shareholders, our employees and families, our local communities and our world. Furthermore, we are also Mindful, Driven by Excellence, and High Integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be responsible for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role will oversee the development and management of Circle’s Global Sanctions Compliance Program. As a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; key leader within the second line of defense Compliance team, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you will be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;responsible for developing and implementing the requirements and standards for Circle’s Sanctions programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will work with the business and compliance/risk peers to provide timely guidance and advice and ensure that the relevant controls are in place and maintained to comply with the relevant regulations in all the jurisdictions in which Circle operates. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will be responsible for establishing internal strategies, policies, procedures, processes related to monitoring and fostering awareness of sanctions regulatory requirements including assessing related sanctions risk exposure, overseeing the quality of sanctions control processes and setting global standards to manage and mitigate those sanctions risks and protect the business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are seeking someone with a demonstrated history of successfully owning and managing large, complex program areas and engaging with cross-functional teams, and numerous stakeholders, directly and through influence. The ideal candidate has extensive experience managing sanctions compliance programs in large scale financial services/Fintech companies, including leveraging technological solutions to solving compliance issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll work on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the end-to-end global Sanctions program and strategy, including the development of policies, standards, and other procedural or guidance materials.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide day-to-day guidance for designing global sanctions screening platforms and controls for Circle’s services and all applicable global sanctions regulations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Plan, design, develop and test configurations for Sanction screening applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform data analysis, design business requirements, understand emerging issues, perform estimation and verify implementation of new features and enhancements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify, assess, and advise on compliance risks and control &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;enhancements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to a variety of stakeholders and customers &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to mitigate risks related to AML and Sanctions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide advice to the businesses on an ongoing basis on new business initiatives, new products, and customer-related matters with respect to applicability of policies, resolution of potential red flags or other compliance escalations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Research, analyze and provide recommended remediation efforts on Action Plans for matters that present sanctions and/or reputational risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Oversee control assessments and support the completion of company-wide Sanctions Risk Assessments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Staying current on key Sanctions regulatory changes, key enforcement actions and related industry trends.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist regional Heads of Compliance in ensuring that all regulatory processes are scalable and remain compliant.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop, monitor and report on a suite of KPIs / KRIs for various internal fora including Executive Leadership and Board-level reporting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate closely with the Compliance Operations team to operationalize the Sanctions Compliance program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work closely with Legal, Product and other internal stakeholders to support license application processes across multiple regions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Present to regulators, examiners and auditors performing reviews of the Compliance program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will aspire to our four core values:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multistakeholder - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you have dedication and commitment to our customers, shareholders, employees and families and local communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mindful - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek to be respectful, an active listener and to pay attention to detail.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driven by Excellence - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you are driven by our mission and our passion for customer success which means you relentlessly pursue excellence, that you do not tolerate mediocrity and you work intensely to achieve your goals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Integrity - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek open and honest communication, and you hold yourself to very high moral and ethical standards.&amp;nbsp; You reject manipulation, dishonesty and intolerance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll bring to Circle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;12+ years of relevant experience in compliance with deep specialization in managing Sanctions programs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of experience managing teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Compliance experience in either banking, consulting, or cryptocurrency required. Experience in RegTech or Fintech companies is preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven experience with regulatory exams and presenting to examiners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Extensive knowledge of and experience with OFAC, UN, and other Global Sanctions regulatory guidance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing the configuration and performance of client and transaction sanction screening systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with client screening and associated alert reviews&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working hands-on with other cross-functional team leaders, such as lawyers, engineers, product managers, data analysts, operations analysts in improving compliance processes and systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience and comfort working in an ever changing industry and the flexibility to quickly react to changing demands&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency in Google Suite, Slack and Apple MacOS preferred.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience/familiarity with Slack, Apple MacOS and GSuite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;equal opportunity employer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and value diversity at Circle. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/KEvenCaIq70" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/circle/jobs/5806257002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143132/circle.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[circle@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[e4722b14-c590-4410-b876-45bc581c49c8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Circle]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[French Senior KYC Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://swissborg.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Lisbon]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We are SwissBorg, a FinTech startup headquartered in Lausanne, Switzerland.</div><div><br></div><div>Our flagship product, the SwissBorg app, offers over 550,000+ users the best price and liquidity across 16 fiat and 17 cryptos, as well as giving them the opportunity to earn passive income with our Smart Yield account. Our community is growing fast, with over $1.5 billion in assets under management, a weekly volume of over 250 million, and over 18,000 Premium users.</div><div><br></div><div>This is just the start in our mission to democratise wealth management by building products that allow individuals to manage their crypto assets at the touch of a finger. Whether you’re in Andorra or Zimbabwe, whether your portfolio is worth one dollar or a million, SwissBorg gives you the best tools to learn about digital currencies and manage your wealth.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to join a team of revolutionaries on a mission to decentralise nations? We want to hear from you!</div><div><br></div><div>Mission:</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Due to the growth of our business, SwissBorg is offering an opportunity for a Senior KYC analyst to join our team in Lisbon. If you are motivated, creative and want to learn more about the new financial era, this is your chance to apply!</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The successful candidate should be hard working and decisive with a capacity to manage a diverse Legal and Administrative workload. You will work in a dynamic ambiance and under the guidance of our Compliance officer.</span></div><br/>What you might be doing:<br/><li>Perform the due diligence on new users, requesting the KYC information, documentation, review and verification of received documentation and making an analytical risk assessment for new users</li><li>Prepare KYC checklists and arrange for review</li><li>Analysis of accounts and user information during review</li><li>Investigate high risk users and reporting where necessary, including Politically Exposed Persons, and obtaining all necessary documentation to complete the user file</li><li>Communicate effectively and efficiently with relevant internal and external parties to obtain KYC documents</li><li>Work on specific projects which may rise from time to time</li><br/>What you might bring:<br/><li>Bachelor degree in law or business administration or country equivalent in a related discipline together with equivalent working experience</li><li>1-2 years of experience in similar position</li><li>Bilingual in English and French</li><li>Strong research and analytical skills</li><li>Sound knowledge of and /or experience in working with FATF Recommendations (Anti-Money Laundering, Countering Terrorism Financing)</li><li>Ability to work on multiple tasks independently with minimal supervision</li><li>Excellent organizational skills required for handling a high volume of work with attention to detail</li><li>Good understanding of Blockchain ecosystem is an advantage</li><li>Experience with AML monitoring and screening is an advantage</li><br/>What you can expect:<br/><li>Competitive salary</li><li>25 days of holidays</li><li>Meal allowance</li><li>Accident insurance</li><li>Employee premium account</li><li>Hybrid work environment</li><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Why you should apply: </b></div><div><br></div><div>- Freedom to build the company of your dreams</div><div>- Learn with (super cool) experts in finance, engineering, AI, psychology and business</div><div>- CHSB bonus based on our meritocratic system</div><div>- We'll provide you with a MacBook and a cutting edge tech stack to help you do your best work</div><div>- Flexible work hours</div><div>- Annual team retreats with colleagues around the world</div><div>- Continuous learning and development opportunities</div><div><br></div><div>Oh and are you planning on having a kid? That’s great! We have a bunch of those: you’ll get time off to enjoy that (other) adventure!&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><i>At SwissBorg, we embrace diversity. We strongly believe that getting to the best outcomes requires different perspectives and backgrounds. We’re committed to openness, curiosity and creating an inclusive culture as we know that diverse teams build better products and generate better ideas. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status.</i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/02lonwc5XE4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/swissborg/7b7b5346-d32c-41eb-bc06-f64b928303c8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/440178/Swissborg-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[swissborg@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f4703261-2e7b-4b75-af19-fbdfc5e62c02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Program Manager Supply Chain - PSG]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOHK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://iohk.io]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>IO Global is looking for a Program Manager to join their Professional Services Group. As Program Manager, you will manage the delivery of client engagements such as solution implementation, workshops, consulting engagements, and the development of software enhancements or bug fixes.  You will have strong project and program management skills and the ability to lead cross-project and functional teams to deliver projects on time and within budget.  Equally importantly, you must demonstrate the proven ability to set, align, and manage customer expectations while delivering your projects and programs with high customer satisfaction.  </p><p>As part of the Professional Services Group, you will work every day to apply blockchain technologies to solve emerging real world problems. You will bridge the gap between real life problems and tip of the spear technology. If you are curious about how this new industry will shape the world, you are in the right place!</p><p><strong>Your mission</strong> </p><ul> <li>Lead the planning and implementation of front office projects</li> <li>Decide on suitable strategies and objectives</li> <li>Be the escalation point of contact for the project team with IOHK clients and external stakeholders</li> <li>Work closely with the Project Managers and Account General Manager to ensure client satisfaction</li> <li>Careful expectation management of internal and external stakeholders</li> <li>Act as an advocate for both the client and IOHK</li> <li>Formulate, organize and monitor inter-connected projects</li> <li>Manage program budget</li> <li>Assess program performance and aim to maximize ROI</li> <li>Assist PS leadership with project and program resource allocation</li> <li>Assist PS leadership with scheduling project and program timelines</li> <li>Prepare program reports</li> <li>Apply change, risk, and resource management</li> <li>Lead and evaluate project managers and other staff</li> <li>Coordinate closely with the IOHK PMO on best practices and alignment with best practices.</li> </ul><p><strong>Your expertise  </strong></p> <ul> <li>Proven experience as a Program Manager or other delivery management position</li> <li>Thorough understanding of project/program management techniques and methods</li> <li>Outstanding leadership and organizational skills</li> <li>Client facing front office project management experience</li> <li>Enterprise project management</li> <li>Ability to set priorities and expectations</li> <li>Qualification in project management or equivalent</li> <li>Knowledge of both theoretical and practical aspects of project management</li> <li>Knowledge of project management techniques and tools</li> <li>Direct work experience in project management capacity</li> <li>Proven experience in people management</li> <li>Proven experience in strategic planning</li> <li>Proven experience in risk management</li> <li>Proven experience in change management</li> <li>Proficiency in project management software (JIRA/Atlassian)</li> <li>Strong experience in delivering Software projects</li> <li>Understanding of digital ledger technology is a plus.</li> </ul><p><strong>Location</strong></p><p>IOG is a fully distributed organization and therefore this is a remote position. Due to team distribution we are ideally searching for someone in a US or European timezone.  </p><p><strong>All Colleagues</strong></p><ul> <li>Flexible schedule</li> <li>Remote work - ability to work anywhere</li> <li>Laptop reimbursement</li> <li>New starter package to buy hardware essentials (headphones, monitor, etc)</li> <li>Learning &amp; Development opportunities</li> <li>Competitive PTO and Sick Leave plan</li> </ul><p><strong>US Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits coverage through Anthem with 100% premium cost covered by IO Global for the employee and dependents</li> <li>Health Savings Account</li> <li>Life Insurance</li> </ul><p><strong>UK Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Monthly Health Stipend to use towards any wellness or medical coverage/service</li> <li>Pension</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EM-XkuQdUq8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/io-global/j/14588E77CE/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143583/iohk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iohk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b89f946-6d3b-434f-aa32-f0e84ecb2992]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOHK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sr. Cybersecurity Penetration Test & Threat Hunting (Ethical Hacker)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchains]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.blockchains.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;h3&gt;OUR VISION&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchains is committed to protecting and empowering individuals through the development of applications, services, and ecosystems designed to change the way people interact with technology, infrastructure, and each other. Software solutions in development by Blockchains focus on preparing the world for the next phase of the internet’s evolution – Web 3.0 – with an emphasis on digital identity, digital asset custody, IoT, and a stable means of digital payment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchains is dedicated to innovation, and its efforts do not stop at software. Blockchains envisions a world transformed by blockchain technology, in which digital- and real-world interactions are interwoven. Blockchains plans to build out a real-life sandbox in northern Nevada, where it, along with other like-minded companies and individuals, can come together to innovate and collaborate to create a better future for all.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Sr. Cybersecurity Penetration Test &amp;amp; Threat Hunter, you will work with a talented group of IT, Cybersecurity, &amp;amp; GRC professionals.&amp;nbsp; You will be part of a global organization responsible for providing the complete attacker perspective, developing Cybersecurity Testing standards, vulnerability management, Threat Hunting, and executing various security tests and risk assessments on newly developed products, software, applications, networks, and systems across the Company.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential functions include, but are not limited to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing security testing results and vulnerability assessment reports to key stakeholders, primarily to the VP IT/Cybersecurity and the Risk Advisory Council.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing Security testing and threat hunting technical standards and supporting programs and processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducting continuous analysis of security threat information (viruses, malicious code, potential backdoors, industry events, hackers, zero-day exploits, OEM weaknesses, IDS/IPS, and SIEM alerting) proactively assessing and investigating emerging threats and potential impact to Blockchains Inc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assessing the applicability of threat and vulnerability feeds, rating the risk, and communicating to appropriate parties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recommending corrective actions to mitigate security threats and risks to Blockchains Inc. products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Producing reports to demonstrate assessment coverage and remediation effectiveness and working with the Product engineers, IT, &amp;amp; Cybersecurity teams to ensure corrective actions are implemented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifying&amp;nbsp;internal and external threats could divulge vulnerabilities that would lead to the misappropriation of customer or company information.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifying and developing new tools, tactics, and procedures for changing threat scenarios.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing trend and research analysis techniques to identify new detection methods for new and evolving attack vectors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working directly with technical staff and leadership to promptly assess and implement mitigating controls to new attack vectors and a constantly changing threat landscape.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identifying, evaluating, and communicating new and ongoing security threats to senior management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicating and influencing technical (especially security) and business issues and/or solutions to multiple organizational levels internally and externally.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED TO SUCCEED&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To ensure success, you must have a passion for all things Cybersecurity and be detailed-oriented.&amp;nbsp; You are a diligent worker who is equally technical and business-minded.&amp;nbsp; You are knowledgeable in taking a risk-based approach to prioritize efforts.&amp;nbsp; You can work with numerous cross-functional teams in a fast-paced, growing company.&amp;nbsp; Strong verbal and written communication skills.&amp;nbsp; Experience in blockchain technologies is preferred.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competencies &amp;amp; Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expert knowledge with many different tools of the trade to include: Metasploit, Nmap, Nessus, burp suite, Accunetix, Qualys, Core Impact, IDAPro, Fiddler, Wireshark, Netcat, OWASP Zap, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and experience with Red, Blue, and Purple teams and activities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with diverse IT products, architectures, and enterprise IT data centers, large-scale transaction processing environments, external hosted services, and cloud computing environments. Extensive knowledge and experience with physical and virtual server configurations and implementations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with perimeter technologies (e.g., router, firewalls, proxies, WAF’s, and intrusion detection) and vulnerability management tools (i.e., vulnerability scanners, file integrity monitoring, configuration monitoring).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of configuration management, change control, risk assessments, exception management, and security baselines and frameworks (e.g., CIS Baselines &amp;amp; NIST CFS).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of and experience with MITRE ATT&amp;amp;CK and the Penetration Testing Execution Standard (PTES).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience applying Common Weakness Enumeration (CWE), Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS), Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVS and Open Web Application Security Project (OWASP)) processes and remediation recommendations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong technical skills and hands-on experience assessing threats to multiple operating system platforms, database, and application servers, custom, and off-the-shelf applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with static code analysis and capabilities of tools such as GitHub, GitLab, Veracode, Coverity, IBM App Scan, and HP Fortify.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in advising on network segmentation, network ACLs, and protocols such as DNS, HTTP/S, TCP, UDP, TLS, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;YOUR EDUCATION AND EXPERIENCE&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A minimum of eight years of relevant cybersecurity, penetration testing, IT (systems/network) work experience with a bachelor’s degree in computer science, computer engineering, cybersecurity, or a related field. A minimum of five years of hands-on Penetration testing or Ethical Hacking, vulnerability management, and threat hunting experience. Leadership and mentoring skills will be necessary to provide support and constructive performance feedback: significant IT &amp;amp; Cybersecurity domain knowledge and experience managing IT &amp;amp; Cybersecurity projects.&amp;nbsp; Experience with DevSecOps is highly desired. You must be a self-starter and team player with the ability to work independently with limited supervision. Experience with HIPAA, PCI, ISO, NIST, and other compliance standards and frameworks is desired. Experience with banking regulations and their implementation and controls to remediate findings related to these regulations. Excellent writing and verbal communication skills, interpersonal and presentation skills, and the proven ability to influence and communicate effectively. You must be flexible and manage multiple tasks and priorities on very tight deadlines. Demonstrated understanding of corporate protocol, maintained a high level of discretion and confidentiality. This position also requires you to have a deep understanding of practices relating to IT standards such as NIST CSF, SP 800-53 R5 AND 800-37 R2, ISO/IEC 27001, ISO 22237, SOC2/SOC3, and CCSS (Cryptocurrency Security Standard).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Blockchains, Inc. (“Blockchains”) is proud to be a diverse workforce, and we are committed to inclusion and diversity to ensure equal opportunity for all applicants. Blockchains provides equal employment opportunities to all employees and applicants regardless of race, color, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity and/or expression, national origin, age, marital status, physical or mental disability, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by federal, state, or local laws.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;When you apply to a job on this site, the personal data contained in your application will be collected by Blockchains, Inc. (“Controller”), which is located at 610 Waltham Way, Sparks, NV 89437 and can be contacted by emailing privacy@blockchains.com. Controller’s data protection officer is Edward O&#39;Connor, who can be contacted at privacy@blockchains.com. Your personal data will be processed for the purposes of managing Controller’s recruitment related activities, which include setting up and conducting interviews and tests for applicants, evaluating and assessing the results thereto, and as is otherwise needed in the recruitment and hiring processes. Such processing is legally permissible under Art. 6(1)(f) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation) as necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Controller, which are the solicitation, evaluation, and selection of applicants for employment.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Your personal data will be shared with Greenhouse Software, Inc., a cloud services provider located in the United States of America and engaged by Controller to help manage its recruitment and hiring process on Controller’s behalf. Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, your personal data will be transferred to the United States once you submit it through this site. Because the European Union Commission has determined that United States data privacy laws do not ensure an adequate level of protection for personal data collected from EU data subjects, the transfer will be subject to appropriate additional safeguards under [either the standard contractual clauses or the Privacy Shield]. You can obtain a copy of the standard contractual clauses by contacting us at privacy@blockchains.com.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Your personal data will be retained by Controller as long as Controller determines it is necessary to evaluate your application for employment. &amp;nbsp;Under the GDPR, you have the right to request access to your personal data, to request that your personal data be rectified or erased, and to request that processing of your personal data be restricted. You also have to right to data portability. In addition, you may lodge a complaint with an EU supervisory authority.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.blockchains.com/careers/job/?gh_jid=5806959002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145209/blockchains-logo-card.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchains@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[2789f1a5-7917-494f-8f0c-6aa29463a8b8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchains]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior People Partner]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Cape Town, Western Cape, South Africa, Johannesburg, Gauteng, South Africa]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior People Partner - Product &amp;amp; Engineering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cape Town/Jo&#39;burg, South Africa&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Together, we are upgrading the world of work to unleash the potential within and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Upgrading the entire planet to a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;new financial system&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is a challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;working together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with unusual skill, focus and determination. We’re changing the financial landscape, and to do so,&amp;nbsp; we need the best team on board for our mission. In short, to achieve our goals, we need people with exceptional talent. As simple as that.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A bit about us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We make it &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;safe and easy &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to buy, store and learn about cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We currently have over 5 million customers across 40 countries&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are Series B funded, backed by Balderton Capital and the Naspers Group&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our platform has processed over $14&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;billion dollars &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;since we’ve launched&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re proud to be &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;one of the world’s most international cryptocurrency teams&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; from 43 different nationalities — working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria and Singapore&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This role in a nutshell:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Every day, the People team strives to create the best place to work for mission-driven people. As a key part of our business, our team makes sure that Luno attracts, hires and retains the best talent. The team consists of superstars who maintain their networks in specific industries, and because they are immersed in the talent pool, our team is able to connect with the brightest candidates who are excited about our vision. We see ourselves as the culture guardians, and strive to deliver the best possible employee experience to all Lunauts. Onboarding our monthly group of Newnauts, encouraging continuous skills development and personal growth, and partnering with our people leaders to achieve their goals, are just a few of the things we do to make coming in to work the highlight of your day. You will be focussing on Engineering &amp;amp; Product in your role (30% of our Lunauts).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will be part of Sarah Robertson&#39;s team, meet her&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/sarah-robertson-78b285ab/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your mission will involve:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying your in-depth understanding of the employee life cycle and ensuring innovative problem solving is implemented, in partnership with management and internal stakeholders (onboarding, setting new starters up for success, development, moves, offboarding)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitating positive employee relations and the development of high performing teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Actively working towards improving employee engagement, in partnership with management, employees and stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Supporting your business units with change management and company wide initiatives such as performance management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal candidate will have:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A Bachelor’s degree in HR or a related discipline, and you have practically applied this knowledge in the workplace&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience scaling (technology) companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum of 6 years&#39; experience in a HR Generalist role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A calm and approachable attitude and the ability to adapt your interpersonal style as required.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great attention to detail and giving consistent, pragmatic and fair advice .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven experience in providing guidance and support with regards to employee relations and the application of South African Labour Law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to coach and advise managers on effective leadership behaviours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with people analytics, process improvements and policy development.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with Engineering and/or Product teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Behaviour Competencies &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;p-rich_text_list p-rich_text_list__bullet&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;unordered-list&quot; data-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong data-stringify-type=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Team Working:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;They support others and show respect and positive regard for them in social situations. Puts people first, working effectively with individuals and teams and customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong data-stringify-type=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Influencing and Persuading:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Communicates and networks effectively. Successfully persuades and influences others. Relates to others in a confident and relaxed manner.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong data-stringify-type=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Analytical Thinking:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Provides evidence of clear analytical thinking. Gets to the heart of complex problems and issues. Applies own expertise effectively. Quickly learns new technology. Communicating well in writing and can explain complex technical analysis to a non-technical audience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong data-stringify-type=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Planning and Organising:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Plans ahead and works in a systematic and organised way. Follows directions and procedures. Delivers within the agreed time frames.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In your first six months, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with management across the entire employee journey, including setting new starters up for success, engagement action plans, feedback mechanisms, performance management, effective leave management, wellbeing and recognition initiatives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support, and be involved in the wider People Team’s roadmap of projects as part of our mission to upgrade the world of work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Life at Luno&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Like the majority of the companies, Luno is currently working remotely to keep our employees safe, which means you will not be physically, but virtually onboarded for now!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Live long and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;prosper. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve got you covered with excellent private medical insurance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;maternity / paternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and even (yes, you are reading it correctly) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;paw-ternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for your furry friend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Annual Inspiration Day... like that pottery course you’ve always been meaning to do!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;diverse team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; of hardworking, ambitious and friendly people on something that will truly revolutionise the financial world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a social bunch of people, we have virtual quarterly activities and drinks Fridays for whoever wants to join!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We have &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;virtual cooking, dancing, drawing and house planting classes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; hosted by our Lunauts to break up your day and work that other part of your brain.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not negatively discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3790392?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[IT Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Washington, DC]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Corporate Technology team at Chainalysis is responsible for the devices, infrastructure and services that employees rely on.&amp;nbsp; This job involves managing hundreds of devices, Identity and Access Management and services such as GSuite, Slack, Zoom, and Atlassian among others.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The IT Associate will help the company by enabling our teams to maintain their best performance.&amp;nbsp; You will be the face of the team, interacting with and advising our customers on their technical needs and mishaps in person at our NYC HQ.&amp;nbsp; You’ll be hands on with some of the best in class technology within the office and online.&amp;nbsp; Your friendly demeanor and attitude will help ensure that all our customers leave satisfied with your assistance!&amp;nbsp; This role will be the face of the IT organization within our HQ and the first point of contact for any in-office gremlins.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have improved the daily efficiency of our customers by providing top level service&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You took ownership of the NYC office space and ensured operational excellence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Solved many IT Challenges to unblock the productivity of our technology customers and partners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Implemented security team recommendations and best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assisted with the automation of qualifying tasks and support requests&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participated in the creation and optimization of processes and policies to best support our customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Developed key working relationships to help achieve outstanding outcomes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Documented processes and procedures for your team and customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Few years of experience in a similar role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in managing a variety of SaaS applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working within a cloud environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in Mac OS and Mac hardware troubleshooting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in basic network troubleshooting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have a positive outlook and an optimistic mindset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Keen to working with others in a collaborative fashion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong communicator in English, both written and verbally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;#LI-DM1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yNpNz-FvSYQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5802583002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Trust and Safety Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinlist]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://coinlist.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[U.S. (Remote OK)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinList, one of the fastest-growing crypto financial platforms, is where the world’s best crypto projects build their communities, and early adopters can invest in and trade top-tier digital assets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to accelerate the advancement of blockchain technology by finding the best emerging blockchain projects and helping them succeed. CoinList has become the global leader in new token issuance, helping blue chip projects like Filecoin, Solana, Celo, Algorand, Dapper, and others raise over $800 million and connect with hundreds of thousands of new token holders. And we now support the full lifecycle of a crypto investment, from token sales through token distribution, trading, lending, and crypto-specific services such as staking and access to decentralized-finance opportunities. CoinList users trade and store Bitcoin, Ether, and many other popular crypto assets through our full-service exchange, CoinList Pro, mobile apps, and CoinList.co, while also getting exclusive access to the best new tokens before they list on other exchanges. Our customers include validators, miners, founders, CEOs, crypto funds, bitcoin OGs, as well as a broad array of crypto enthusiasts. Unlike other centralized crypto finance platforms, we&#39;re not here to just build a bank or a brokerage. We&#39;re building the platform for people who are passionate about moving crypto forward, and we’re just getting started.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you&#39;re interested in investigating trends, patterns, fraud detection/prevention and enjoy working through complex cases, please read on. We&#39;re also interested in speaking with fast learners, those who are driven and analytically minded and interested in joining a fast-growing startup.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re excited about cryptocurrency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. CoinList’s mission is to help the best crypto companies succeed by serving as a trusted advisor in the space.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re entrepreneurial&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. This role is autonomous - you’re excited about proposing and testing ideas based on issues and opportunities you see.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re a problem solver.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; You’ll have (often ambiguous) responsibilities and are comfortable navigating to find the best solution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re curious&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. You want to understand how things work and like to question things, and can synthesize the ideas concisely. You learn quickly and like picking up new skills on the fly. You aren’t intimidated by complex problems and enjoy solving them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re a proven operator&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. You have proven experience managing a high volume of users/customers while adhering to specific procedures.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’re collaborative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. You take pride in being a great resource to peers and partner to stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Conduct investigations into various customer issues including account takeovers, phishing, cryptocurrency thefts, and more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Respond to and resolve complex user issues related to fraud, user safety, and risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with third-party vendors to perform takedowns of phishing and other malicious sites.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work closely with cross-functional teams such as Compliance Analysts, Onboarding Associates, and Support teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must-Have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attention to detail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong organizational skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to manage multiple projects at the same time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Structured thinking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable diving into technical concepts, navigating backend products, and working with data and spreadsheets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to adapt to evolving requirements and changes as the company grows.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice To Have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fluency with a second language.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve worked on or have thought about Internet-based risk, abuse, fraud, data protection, or security.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in a customer-facing role related to operations, fraud, or trust &amp;amp; safety.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/coinlist/jobs/5807077002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145375/CoinList.jpeg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinlist@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[53dcfcc4-4b3a-448c-81ad-47bdcbb7143e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinlist]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Communications Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Circle]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.circle.com/de/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Boston - will also consider remote in US]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Circle is a global financial technology firm that enables businesses of all sizes to harness the power of digital currency and public blockchains for payments, commerce and financial applications worldwide. Circle platforms and products provide a suite of internet-native financial services for payments, treasury infrastructure and capital formation. Circle is also a principal developer of USD Coin (USDC), which has become the fastest growing dollar digital currency in the world. USDC has grown to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;over 40 billion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in circulation and supported over&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; $1.3 trillion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in transactions in the past year. Circle’s payments and treasury infrastructure services available through the Circle Account and APIs helps bridge the legacy financial system and digital currency and blockchain based finance.&amp;nbsp; Circle’s SeedInvest service brings internet-native fundraising and capital formation to startups and growth companies.&amp;nbsp; Combined, Circle’s suite of services helps companies to participate in a more open, global and inclusive financial system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be part of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;With the mission “To raise global economic prosperity through the frictionless exchange of financial value,” Circle was founded on the belief that the internet, blockchains and digital currency will rewire the global economic system, creating a fundamentally more open, inclusive, efficient and integrated world economy.&amp;nbsp; We envision a global economy where people and businesses everywhere can more freely connect and transact with each other with new technologies for digital money and internet-native finance. We believe such a system can raise prosperity for people and companies everywhere. Our mission is powered by the values we espouse and which we expect all Circlers to respect. We are Multistakeholder, serving the needs of our customers, our shareholders, our employees and families, our local communities and our world. Furthermore, we are also Mindful, Driven by Excellence, and High Integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Communications Specialist, you will play a key role in ensuring successful execution of our communication strategy. In this role you will learn from a growing, world-class communications team, have the opportunity to put new skills into practice and help keep the team on the rails. You will collaborate closely with the broader policy, strategy and communications organization as well as marketing, legal, compliance and finance. Your primary responsibility will be keeping the team accountable to on-time delivery of deadlines and opportunities and keeping the engine running to bring our strategy to life. This role will report to the VP of Communications and support the entire Communications team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll work on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Media list development and management.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mining news for trends, hooks and insights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinating the speaker’s bureau and media trackers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Measurement and share of voice analysis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Trade media outreach.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drafting press releases and related external content.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Running the Circle News employee slack channel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Policy research and insights.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;EveryoneSocial employee advocacy program support.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Customer story management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Circle Impact and rolling out our CSR initiatives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will aspire to our four core values:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multistakeholder - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you have dedication and commitment to our customers, shareholders, employees and families and local communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mindful - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek to be respectful, an active listener and to pay attention to detail.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driven by Excellence - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you are driven by our mission and our passion for customer success which means you relentlessly pursue excellence, that you do not tolerate mediocrity and you work intensely to achieve your goals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Integrity - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek open and honest communication, and you hold yourself to very high moral and ethical standards.&amp;nbsp; You reject manipulation, dishonesty and intolerance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll bring to Circle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree in journalism, communications, public relations or related field&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Documented experience in a Communications role via internship or part-time assignment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Baseline PR knowledge and experience - how to write a release, how to build relationships with media and exposure to building and executing against a communication plan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding writing and verbal communication skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Appetite for learning, growth and career development.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Get it done attitude with ability to pivot fast, go with the flow and take on new challenges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A foundational understanding of markets, finance, banking, and economics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A deep interest in crypto and blockchain infrastructure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency in Google Suite, Slack and Apple MacOS preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;equal opportunity employer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and value diversity at Circle. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/KEvenCaIq70" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/circle/jobs/5776376002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143132/circle.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[circle@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[e4722b14-c590-4410-b876-45bc581c49c8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Circle]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Fund Accountant]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Republic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://republic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Boston, MA / Houston, TX / New York, NY / US Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 11pt">Republic</b><span style="font-size: 11pt"> is a financial technology firm that allows everyone to invest in private markets. Republic operates several distinct business lines including a retail investment platform, a private capital division, and a blockchain advisory practice. The Republic ecosystem has deployed over $700 million in investments, has supported over 600 companies, and is comprised of a community of over 1.5M users across 100 countries. Republic is backed by dozens of leading investment firms and financial institutions and its affiliated entities have co-invested with the best names in venture and private equity. Founded in 2016, Republic is headquartered in New York City with offices worldwide.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Republic Capital is the institutional arm of Republic that invests in early and growth-stage technology companies. Since its founding in 2019, Republic Capital has grown to nearly $1 billion in assets under management and built a portfolio of increasingly dominant companies in areas such as FinTech, E-commerce, New Space, and Digital Assets.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We are looking for a Fund Accountant to join the Capital team. The right person is highly effective, engaged, organized, and detail oriented. You will work closely with the existing Investor Relations team and cross functionally with Finance to analyze our growing portfolio and ensure seamless distributions back to our investors.</span></div><br/>What you'll do<br/><li>Shadow Accounting OR Full NAV Reconciliation</li><li>Reconcile all portfolio and cash activity to source data</li><li>Ensure fund expenses are accrued timely and in accordance with GAAP</li><li>Review investor allocations and ensure fee/allocations are booked accurately</li><li>Review Fund Admin prepared quarterly net asset value reporting</li><li>Liaise with fund administrator as they prepare the YE AFS</li><li>Liaise with auditors to ensure completion of audits by SEC/External/Internal Deadlines</li><li>SPV quarterly reconciliations</li><li>Audit our records for completeness and accuracy of all SPVs / Vehicles that will be doing distributions.</li><br/>What we're looking for:<br/><li>6-8 years of fund or partnership accounting CPA preferred</li><li>Experience in both venture capital and crypto preferred</li><li>Experience managing multiple projects, engagements and teams&nbsp;</li><li>All around team player, that is willing to “roll up your sleeves” whenever <a href="http://needed.Ownership">needed.Ownership</a> and accountability</li><li>Highly organized and extremely detail oriented</li><li>Strong analytical skills</li><li>Excellent written and verbal communication skills</li><li>Comfortable working in several technologies platforms including, Google Suite, Microsoft Office, Salesforce, and more</li><li>Demonstrated ability to handle multiple tasks with accuracy and precision</li><li>Comfortable working in a high-stakes, fast-paced environment.</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Qy1lzYTV6Uc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/republic/04508eb3-e84f-41b7-8b72-f083661b797f/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/211719/Republic.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[republic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b024f433-5745-442c-98f6-a3b65ac4a9b0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Republic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Equity Compensation Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City, New York | Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; at Chainalysis is dedicated to enabling growth, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;building an inclusive environment, and providing the benefits and perks that help our employees balance work, life, and happiness. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our job is to make sure Chainalysis has the right talent and framework in place to grow both quickly and thoughtfully.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Equity Compensation Manager will play a pivotal role on the Compensation team and the broader People Team. The person in this role will lead the development, implementation, and continuous improvement of our equity compensation strategy. You will partner closely with Legal, Finance, and People Operations to ensure our equity programs are structured to help us attract and retain top talent while running smoothly from start to finish. We measure success in this role by your ability to effectively manage the program from design to implementation and administration, assess competitive equity compensation trends, make recommendations in line with our business and talent growth strategies, and improve related communications and education for our current and potential employees.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve improved existing and developed new equity compensation guidelines and processes that help us effectively grow and scale across the globe&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve improved the accuracy and timeliness of our equity plan administration and related transactions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve created educational opportunities for current and potential employees that explain the value and potential of being a Chainalysis employee and shareholder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve built and/or implemented robust modeling tools supported by dynamic data that enable us to make better equity compensation decisions faster&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing and administering equity compensation programs pre- and post-IPO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience forecasting and managing equity budgets with exceptional modeling skills (primarily using Google Sheets and Excel)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong grasp of equity market trends and experience in benchmarking equity programs and policies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable making data-backed recommendations using various external and internal sources&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiar with global equity compensation regulations, including tax implications and plan registration requirements&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience clearly communicating complex equity concepts to all levels of the organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience preparing equity and executive compensation materials for the Board&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable working through ambiguity and change as we grow and develop our total compensation programs in line with evolving business goals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to build credibility with business leaders and cross-functional teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with Carta and other equity administration platforms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working knowledge of / experience working with Workday a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in a high-growth tech company preferred&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-YT1 #LI-Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/Gcv0hp5.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;108&quot; height=&quot;139&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yNpNz-FvSYQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5810431002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Customer Support Representative - Singapore]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[f2pool & stakefish]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://stake.fish/en/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>We are looking for a passionate Customer Service Manager to provide excellent customer service and to promote this idea throughout the organization. The goal is to keep the department running in an efficient manner, to increase customer satisfaction, loyalty, and retention, and to meet their expectations.</p><p><br></p><h3>In this role, you will<br> </h3><ul> <li>Be familiar with Company's platform and be up-to-date on general market conditions</li> <li>Handle customer issues through live chat and other online tools</li> <li>Update our internal databases with information about technical issues and useful discussions with customers</li> <li>Inform customers about new features and functionalities.Gather customer feedback and share with our Product, Sales, and Marketing teams</li> <li>Provide proper solutions to customer issues within reasonable time limits</li> <li>Maintain a positive, empathetic, and professional attitude toward customers at all times. and flexible to work on various work shifts</li> <li>Diligently and effectively manage and follow up the inquiries/complaints of the current/prospective clients</li> <li>Continuously seek improvement to enhance team’s performance and work efficiency</li> </ul><ul> <li>Diploma and above in any discipline, fresh graduates are welcome to apply</li> <li>Excellent communication and problem-solving skills and Multi-tasking abilities</li> <li>Proficient in English &amp; Chinese in communication and writing</li> <li>Team player, who is committed and self-driven, with the ability to respond positively to a client's request for assistance</li> <li>Positive about the crypto industry</li> </ul><ul><li>The applicants based in Singapore will be more considered for this position</li></ul><p><br></p><p>If those describe you, this is the right opportunity for you!</p><p><br></p><h3>Why are we awesome you ask?</h3><p>We are a truly global team! We can work from wherever we want. We have a collective mission, to provide meaningful services and bring a unique value to users within the crypto space.</p><p>We are looking for fun, curious, and committed individuals to swim with us!</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/stakefish/j/BB28AEF1A8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/732239/f2pool_stakefish.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[f2pool@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[33981a68-3968-406e-a0b6-0c8956f5810a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[f2pool & stakefish]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Manager Team Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[UK]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing. We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual, and we want to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno welcomes crypto lovers and crypto newbies. You - just like everyone in the world - are on your own unique crypto-learning journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a mission-driven cryptocurrency company that is building more open and equal access to the future of money. You don’t have to know lots about crypto to be interested in joining us, you just have to feel that upgrading the world to a fairer financial system matters, and that you’d like to be part of this global change. We’re a passionate and committed team taking on a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;working together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with unusual skill, focus and determination. We need the best team on board for our mission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If that sounds like a culture you’d thrive in, then we are excited to hear from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role in a nutshell:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a product manager who appreciates the beauty in the mechanics of each &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;product feature&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. You&#39;ll ensure the voice of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;our customers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is represented in our product strategy. Along with our talented team of Lunauts, you&#39;ll be responsible for designing and delivering our product roadmap. You get to work in a dynamic and fast-paced environment, where ownership is key.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;ll work with cross-functional pods to help scale Luno to the next level. This role will be part of the Product team that is headed up by&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Alex, Luno’s VP of Product, meet him&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/alex-koller-2171b143/&quot;&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In your first six months, you will&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Complete your onboarding program. After getting comfortable with the basics, you&#39;ll start learning our patterns in a safe, easy-to-follow way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understand Luno’s product roadmap and vision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Meet the wider team and work closely with Product Owners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;After completing the onboarding program, you&#39;ll begin your journey contributing to your pod&#39;s success. You&#39;ll help plan the next quarter&#39;s objectives and key results (OKRs) and will begin working on our product roadmap. We succeed as a team, so we will provide you with regular feedback from your manager and peers and will encourage you to do the same.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’d like you to have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have at least 4 years experience as a Product Manager or Product Owner&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You take control and exercise leadership to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;lead change&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; by initiating action, giving direction and taking responsibility to ensure delivery of objectives/goals/tasks/projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are great in prioritising, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;planning and organising&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; your day and can manage your time efficiently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working as a team comes naturally to you – it’s all about driving cooperation and teamwork to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;deliver results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will be the one raising your hand when it comes to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;creative and critical thinking&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and solution-driven ideas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In order to excel in your role, a great eye for detail is inevitable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nothing holds you back, you have a positive and friendly disposition, with a ‘can do’ attitude&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with cryptocurrencies is highly advantageous&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Life at Luno&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you’re looking to work on something truly global and disruptive with a forward-thinking and ambitious team that highly values diversity, teamwork, and the continuous quest for excellence, then this is an opportunity for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Like the majority of the companies, Luno is currently working remotely to keep our employees safe, which means you will not be physically, but virtually onboarded for now!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Live long and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;prosper. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve got you covered with excellent private medical insurance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;ll be able to continuously &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;up-skill&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; yourself with access to free courses on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Udemy and Codecademy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For the crypto fans among you (should be everyone!), &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;you&#39;ll pay 0 fees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with Luno from the day you start&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;maternity / paternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; leave.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An annual &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;inspiration day&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, over and above your annual and public holiday leave... for that pottery course you’ve always been meaning to do!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; globally diverse team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; of hardworking, ambitious and friendly people on something that will truly revolutionise the financial world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We have &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;virtual cooking, dancing, drawing and house planting classes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; hosted by our Lunauts to break up your day and work that other part of your brain.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work is important, but&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; your mental health should always take priority&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. At Luno, we do everything we can to make sure you lead a healthy and happy life. That&#39;s why Luno gives you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; free access to Headspace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; – a full library of guided meditations, sleep stories, and music.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not negatively discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3793574?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Social Media Manager, NFT]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,400+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b>About the Role</b></div><div><br></div><div>Kraken is looking for a Social Media Manager to establish a social media presence for Kraken’s consumer NFT product. Owning the creation, execution, and growth of our NFT channels, the Social Media Manager interacts with existing and potential customers through timely, dynamic, interactive, and engaging social content.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>You will design social media content and develop social relations to grow product awareness, acquire new customers, and drive traffic/conversion. This role involves working in a dynamic, fast-paced and feedback-driven environment to solve complex business problems where you will be given the opportunity to add value from day one.</div><div><br></div><br/>Responsibilities <br/><li>Execute and optimize NFT social media strategy across Kraken’s social channels.</li><li>Determine new social media channel opportunities and test for effectiveness.</li><li>Oversee social research, planning, calendaring, creative development, publishing, moderation, and reporting.</li><li>Understand historical narratives in the crypto space and observe current industry events.</li><li>Monitor crypto and NFT trends to identify engagement opportunities.&nbsp;</li><li>Grow our presence in the NFT community by engaging NFT fanatics &amp; Gen Z audiences.</li><li>Curate, write, schedule, and interact with social media posts related to our NFT product.</li><li>Interface with and Support, Growth, Product, Brand, and Comms teams.</li><li>Maintain social media tracking, data presentation, and perform optimizations.</li><li>Experiment with ideas to boost audience engagement and promote Kraken in the NFT space.</li><li>Identify target audience and develop tactics to engage existing clients and acquire new Kraken clients.</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>2-4 years of hands-on social media marketing and community management experience.</li><li>Expert at best practices for the top social media platforms – like Twitter, Tik Tok, Discord.&nbsp;</li><li>You intimately understand NFT terminology and culture.</li><li>You live and breathe on social – understanding how the NFTs work and how to integrate crypto and mainstream trends into content seamlessly.</li><li>Ability to transform highly technical crypto and NFT terminologies into concise social media copy.</li><li>Proficiency in social media publishing, listening and measurement tools.</li><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</b></div><div><br></div><div><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link"><b>Follow us on Twitter</b></a></div><div><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link"><b>Catch up on our blog</b></a></div><div><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link"><b>Follow us on LinkedIn</b></a></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/d9a8281e-729a-4228-a831-ead1dfbbf153/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crypto Partnerships Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://blockchain.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, San Francisco, Miami, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain is the world&#39;s leading software platform for digital assets. Founded in 2011, we provide the world’s largest and most trusted production blockchain platform, powering more than 80 million wallets. Together with our platform of liquidity and execution services, we share the passion to build an open, accessible and fair financial future, one piece of software at a time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for an experienced partnerships professional to help lead our efforts in crypto and ecosystem partnerships for Blockchain.com. This person will be instrumental in defining how Blockchain.com partners with the crypto communities and help expand our role within the ecosystem. The Crypto Partnerships Lead will take a long view of building out deep relationships while finding new opportunities for Blockchain.com to partner. As a key member of the Partnerships team, this person will play a significant role in driving the growth of Blockchain.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define and drive Blockchain.com’s partnership strategy with crypto projects, dapps, and crypto communities more broadly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Operationalize and scale up our asset listing strategy working across legal, product, engineering, and marketing; conduct research, analysis, and diligence on crypto projects and build recommendations based on analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build strategic relationships with DeFi protocols and DEX to identify potential opportunities across Blockchain.com retail and institutional products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create platform strategy for establishing Blockchain.com as preferred wallet and exchange partner for projects and Dapps in the ecosystem&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify new products, verticals, or strategic opportunities for Blockchain.com and turn ideas into products and services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Cultivate and build lasting relationships with developers, entrepreneurs, and leaders in the ecosystem and establish Blockchain.com’s role as the go-to partner in the ecosystem&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive all aspects of deal cycle from sourcing, diligence, negotiating, closing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work closely with external and internal teams to launch and ensure successful launches&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong understanding of crypto and blockchain ecosystems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;8+ years BD or partnerships experience overall with 2+ years experience in crypto preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A proven track record of leading and closing impactful partnerships in a product-centric environment with significant internal and external dependencies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience negotiating commercial deals with organizations of all sizes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team player with strong interpersonal skills, ability to interact effectively with partners and colleagues from various cultural backgrounds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Highly organized, analytical thinker who thrives in a fast-paced, high growth environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Master’s or equivalent degree in finance or engineering&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;COMPENSATION &amp;amp; PERKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Unlimited vacation policy; work hard and take time when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Apple equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Full-time salary based on experience and meaningful equity in an industry-leading company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Make a difference: we’re not just another crypto company: we’re the financial system for the internet and changing the future of finance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you apply to a job on this site, the personal data contained in your application will be collected by one or more of the following subsidiaries of Blockchain Luxembourg S.A (each, a “Controller”):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain Access UK Ltd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain (GB) Limited&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain (US), Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain (LT), UAB&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may contact our Data Protection Officer by email at&amp;nbsp;dpo@blockchain.com. Your personal data will be processed for the purposes of managing Controller’s recruitment related activities, which include setting up and conducting interviews and tests for applicants, evaluating and assessing the results thereto, and as is otherwise needed in the recruitment and hiring processes. Such processing is legally permissible under Art. 6(1)(f) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation) as necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Controller, which are the solicitation, evaluation, and selection of applicants for employment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your personal data will be shared with Greenhouse Software, Inc., a cloud services provider located in the United States of America and engaged by Controller to help manage its recruitment and hiring process on Controller’s behalf.&amp;nbsp; Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, your personal data will be transferred to the United States once you submit it through this site. Because the European Union Commission has determined that United States data privacy laws do not ensure an adequate level of protection for personal data collected from EU data subjects, the transfer will be subject to appropriate additional safeguards under the standard contractual clauses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your personal data will be retained by Controller as long as Controller determines it is necessary to evaluate your application for employment.&amp;nbsp; Under the GDPR, you have the right to request access to your personal data, to request that your personal data be rectified or erased, and to request that processing of your personal data be restricted. You also have to right to data portability. In addition, you may lodge a complaint with an EU supervisory authority.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain/jobs/3795735?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180745/blockchaininc.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchaininc@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5457bd3d-b464-4d43-bfd6-5c9d9e62930e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Junior IT Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Keyrock]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.keyrock.eu/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keyrock is expanding!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Keyrock was founded in 2017 and has quickly grown from 3 to over 50 people today. As an industry recognized liquidity provider and market maker, Keyrock is a leading European creator of algorithmic trading technology in the digital asset space. With VC backing and a constantly expanding global client base, Keyrock is one of Belgium’s fastest-growing fintech companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;We’re currently active on over 80 exchanges and count numerous marketplaces and asset issuers among our clients, including some of the best-known companies in the crypto space.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Keyrock&#39;s beating heart is its technical team filled with software engineers, digital scientists and PhDs, who themselves are supported by university professors, industry-leading experts and a strong management team. Over the years Keyrock has become a company that is both idealistic and practical.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;A system administrator with a proven track record in ensuring cybersecurity and providing end-user desktop IT support. You will take ownership and single-handedly and independently oversee IT Risk Management, information security, local area networks, manage our equipment and act as local IT Help-desk but most importantly - you will be building and co-creating Keyrock.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;For this particular position we require that the candidate is based in Brussels or close vicinity that enables regular physical presence in our office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background and experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Hands-on experience in ensuring cybersecurity&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;At least 1 year of hands-on experience working in an end-user desktop support role or computer operations environment required (equivalent of Tier 1 and 2 support level)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Experience in Linux and bash scripting&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Experience in network administration&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Good knowledge of and passion for the entire IT landscape&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Basic coding skills and willingness to learn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What would be a strong plus:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Experience with Atlassian Suite and project management systems (like Shortcut, formerly Clubhouse)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Familiarity with ISO27001 and ISO27002 Standards&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Familiarity with regulatory requirements for IT environment for financial institution&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competences and personality:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Disciplined with strong organisational skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Strong problem-solving skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills, fluent business-level English&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Ability to deal with ambiguity and a fast-paced environment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Good adaptability to change&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Motivated and eager to learn&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Good analytical skills and ability to effectively draw conclusions and act in accordance with data-based evidence&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Self-starter willing to take ownership for their work&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Ensuring best in class end-user desktop support&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Manage local area networks&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Driving creation and implementation of internal IT policy&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Ensure bullet-proof IT Security&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Active directory and access architecture and management&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Managing IT equipment and software upgrades for all our hybrid workforce&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Ensuring optimal software and hardware environment for our operations to be performed both physically in the office in Belgium and by our remote workforce&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our recruitment philosophy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;We believe the most important aspect of our recruitment process is self-awareness: we are looking for people who have a clear understanding of themselves and what they are looking for in their professional career. That means that we expect to work with people who not only have the right skills, but who have also made the conscious decision to look for a company in our industry and with our characteristics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;A competitive salary package, including benefits that you choose and manage according to your needs and those of your family (car/bike, meal vouchers, phone and internet subscription, health insurance, 25 days off, etc.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Complete autonomy in your time management thanks to flexible working hours and the opportunity to work remotely&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The freedom to create your own entrepreneurial experience by being part of a team of people in search of excellence who all receive stock options from the first year&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;A ton of fun in a thriving and multicultural environment, with colleagues enjoying regular team building activities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Keyrock offers you both a career and a large range of benefits that we will gladly discuss in the course of the application process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;As an employer we are committed to build an inclusive, diverse and non-discriminating work environment. We welcome employees of all backgrounds, ethnicities, genders, creed and sexual orientation. We hire, reward and promote entirely based on merit and performance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://keyrock.freshteam.com/jobs/dQS8YU0vCL7B/junior-it-manager?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/831880/keyrock-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[keyrock@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5b5712b4-ea1b-4843-8efd-ea04303877b0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Keyrock]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior System Engineer (DevOps)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re Coinbase. We’re the world’s most trusted way to join the crypto revolution, serving more than 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/our-mission-strategy-and-culture-18a92a3bb0fa&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web 3.0 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve got good vibes. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are searching for a DevOps Engineer with strong networking experience to help the IT organization move to a more software defined networking model.&amp;nbsp; You’ll partner closely with our networking and system engineering teams to bring more infrastructure as code principles to the support of our global networks, which include Wifi services, VPN technologies, and AWS services.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with the Coinbase Infrastructure team to support and extend existing ci/cd frameworks to support IT services, including enterprise network platforms&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with security and compliance to build surveillance tooling into deployment pipelines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide automation support to streamline operational IT support and operational workflows&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with other engineering teams to streamline deployment, connectivity, security and compliance within IT supported infrastructure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in on call to support the AWS service deployment pipeline&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we look for in you (ie. job requirements):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years experience supporting network infrastructure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years experience automating cloud infrastructure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable scripting in several languages (Bash, Python, Ruby, Go, etc)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with LAN and WAN concepts and configuration, including, switching, routing,&amp;nbsp; firewalls and advanced VPC concepts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience supporting AWS services and ci/cd workflows using terraform or equivalent framework&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrable troubleshooting methodologies and root cause analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expertise with Linux, Bash, Ruby, Python and/or Go&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expertise automating EC2 with terraform or similar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong network security fundamentals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing and leveraging log aggregation&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in a highly regulated environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in a fast-paced, high-growth company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in a Remote-first IT environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ID: P29544&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Notice for Colorado applicants as required by sb19-085 (8-5-20). Target annual salary for this role performed in Colorado, is $&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;188,275&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; + target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations@ coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Please contact accommodations@ coinbase.com for additional information or to request accommodations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3718039?gh_jid=3718039&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Staking]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 15px;">About Celsius Network</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;">Celsius addresses the financial needs of today’s consumers worldwide through a democratized interest income and lending platform accessible via a mobile app. With a mission to put unparalleled economic freedom in the hands of the people, and a core belief that financial services should only do what is in the best interests of the community, Celsius is a modern platform where membership provides access to curated financial services that are not available through traditional financial institutions. Crypto holders can earn high-yield compounding interest by transferring coins to their Celsius Wallet and can borrow fiat currency against their crypto collateral at the lowest interest rates in the space.  </span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;">The Celsius team is committed to doing good and doing well. We believe in the power of disruption and the importance of decentralization to create a new system that acts in the best interest of everyone. Each member of our team brings something unique and innovative to the table, but the common thread that links us together is our passion for blockchain, equality, and leading the next financial revolution that changes the equation to bring power back to the people. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"> </span></p>
<p>The Head of Staking will be responsible for managing all of Celsius staking activities.<span>  </span>Responsibilities include:</p>
<ul>
<li>Responsible for evaluating, selecting, and overusing the implementation of all technical staking options including in-house and vendor solutions.</li>
<li>Work closely with custody partners (GK8 and Fireblocks) to make sure their roadmap is aligned with staking needs</li>
<li>Identify new staking opportunities (coins) and work with coins-in side of the business to ensure that those coins are listed</li>
<li>Manage a team of one or two staking specialists who will be responsible for a staking activities (deployment/withdrawals, etc)</li>
<li>Work close with product team to develop direct-staking strategy</li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span>Requirements include:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>At least three years experience operating a commercial staking business</span></li>
<li><span>Five years experience evaluating vendors for IT infrastructure services and negotiating contracts</span></li>
<li><span>Five years manage teams doing IT infrastructure deployments</span></li>
</ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xW6QWaNfysw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=506&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/731816/celsius_network.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celsius@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5fa72b05-b42d-48a9-806e-c3fdccb06776]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Human Resources/Talent Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Nifty's]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://niftys.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT NIFTY’S, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nifty&#39;s is the eco-friendly home for NFTs (non-fungible tokens) from your favorite brands and creators on the blockchain. Nifty&#39;s, based in Miami FL, brings together premium publishers, brands and creators with collectors, curators and the communities of fans that will emerge around them. Offering an easy-to-use interface, the innovative platform will allow members to collect, discover, and curate the most important digital art and other collectibles from across the rapidly expanding NFT universe. Nifty&#39;s will provide creators with a premium, powerful, flexible and safe platform to launch their NFTs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FUNCTION&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for a Human Resources /Talent Manager to join our fully remote based team. You will help us grow our team and help shape the culture of Nifty&#39;s as we grow.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role will recruit top talent, build a recruitment pipeline and support the development of various human resources programs that will fuel engagement and relationships with the Nifty’s team. This is a unique position where you will have the opportunity to make a huge impact in&amp;nbsp; shaping the growth and success of the company by hiring the best talent.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES &amp;amp; DELIVERABLES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manages the talent acquisition process, to include recruitment, interviewing, and hiring of&amp;nbsp;qualified job applicants, collaborates with departmental managers to understand skills and competencies required for openings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partners with HR leadership on recruitment initiatives and drives the creation and delivery of retention efforts, and monitors for success.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure a high level of candidate engagement and positive candidate experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate the on-boarding process, including data entry into HRIS systems. Participate in new hire orientation; assisting with orienting new employees to the culture of the company, programs, and philosophy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Contributes to the development, and support of HR dashboard, monitoring of HR metrics and analysis of trends. Identifies root causes and takes proactive remedial action and partners with program leadership to implement appropriate course of action.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provides day-to-day performance management guidance to management (e.g., coaching, counseling, career development, disciplinary actions).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Works closely with management and employees to improve work relationships, build morale, and increase productivity and retention.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provides HR policy guidance and interpretation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Performs onboarding and offboarding activities as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develops contract terms for new hires, promotions and transfers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participates in evaluation and monitoring of training programs to ensure success. Follows up to ensure training objectives are met.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of experience in Human Resources, 3 years experience Human Resources Management/Leadership role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3 + years of recruiting experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with applicant tracking systems required- knowledge of Greenhouse ATS plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent active listening, influence, written/verbal communication and conflict management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Thorough understanding of HR practices, including employment law and regulations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An ability to work independently and proactively with minimal direction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working at a start-up a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Other things to note:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nifty’s, Inc. strives to be a best-in-class and equal opportunity employer.  All qualified applicants &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, religion, color, national origin, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, age, status as a protected veteran, among other &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;things, or status as a qualified individual with disability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This job posting highlights the most critical responsibilities and requirements of the job. Other duties may be assigned as needed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nifty&#39;s, Inc. Privacy Policy can be found here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://niftys.com/privacy-policy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://niftys.com/privacy-policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/niftysinc/jobs/4283318004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/943210/niftys.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alexander+niftysinc@cryptocareers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6167914b-84e3-41bb-934a-cdb803281ce7]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Nifty's]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
