<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Energi Core Ltd]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.energi.world]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Global - Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Energi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Energi (NRG) is a next-generation Proof of Stake (PoS) cryptocurrency, combining Ethereum-compatible smart contracts with on-chain governance, a self-funding treasury, and a layer 2 masternode network, enabling powerful DeFi applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a fully remote company with no fixed headquarters. The team is spread throughout the Americas, Europe, Africa, Asia, and Oceania. With more than 90 contributors, the team forms a well-linked network across a variety of locations, lifestyles, and backgrounds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Energi&#39;s culture is driven by integrity, strategic thinking, leadership, and the shared desire to perform at our peak. While our differences make us adaptable and versatile, it&#39;s our shared values that give us the strength and drive to become the cryptocurrency for world consciousness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in It for You?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work flexible hours from anywhere and be part of a team that is driven by strong values and a clear shared vision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Directly shape the future of a completely new model for cryptocurrency and blockchain applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Challenge your skills and push your creative limits working with the latest blockchain technologies &amp;amp; systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Play an active role in one of the most significant technological innovations in human history.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Receive a competitive salary paid in a combination of BTC and NRG.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’re looking for&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a detail-oriented full-stack web developer to drive our website and web app development.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;To be an ideal candidate, you should be comfortable using front end technologies fused with blockchain plugins such as Metamask and web3 to develop robust and efficient web apps and dApps.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You Will Do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work alongside graphic and UX designers to implement web design features&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop dApps on the Energi network&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write effective APIs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure responsiveness of applications across all platforms and devices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;See through projects from conception to finished products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Organize technical documentation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Maintain the existing ecosystem to the highest degree of quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven experience as a Full Stack Developer or similar role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency with JavaScript frameworks such as AngularJS, React, Amber and Gatsby&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with blockchain technology (web3, infura, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with server-side languages such as Python, Golang and PHP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of database technologies such as MySQL, Oracle, and MongoDB&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent organizational skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An analytical mind&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attention to detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good problem-solving skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Self-driven with the ability to deliver results with minimal supervision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fluent English communicator&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passionate and up-to-date on the rapidly changing world of blockchain technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Values aligned with the Energi culture and values&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong organizational and project management skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role is not open to 3rd party organizations or agencies. Any candidates sent will be considered free of any charges&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Energi is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, pregnancy, disability, age, veteran status, or other characteristics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8QUIHRakeHo&t=2s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/energicorelimited/jobs/4029914004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/479023/energi-core-ltd-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[energi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5be3229a-46ba-477a-9178-2772ea9250e4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Energi Core Ltd]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Development & Strategic Partnerships]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Securitize]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://securitize.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span>Securitize is the global fintech pioneer that provides investors with access to invest in and trade private securities while also helping companies raise the capital they need to grow. </span></p>
<p><span>Recognized as a top 50 blockchain company in the world, we are the industry-leading and the first end-to-end digital securities issuance and compliance platform operating on the blockchain.</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span>We just received $48m in Series B from Wall Street &amp; venture capital funding from top investors to aggressively expand our teams across New York, Miami, San Francisco, and remote offices. We are a global team made up of top blockchain and financial industry talent based around the world, based in Tel Aviv, Buenos Aires, Tokyo, New York, and San Francisco. We’re backed by leading financial institutions and blockchain investors, including Morgan Stanley, Blockchain Capital, MUFG, Sumitomo Mitsui Trust Bank, Sony Finance, Banco Santander, and Coinbase.</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span>We are seeking an accomplished <span style="font-weight: bold;">Strategic Business Development</span> leader to own and drive the strategy and execution of portions of our holistic partnerships approach and broader company approach. This is a senior role that will report to the CEO and spearhead key business efforts with the focus on the developing new relationships with key clients in the ecosystem. </span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span>The successful candidate will be responsible for formulating, sourcing, negotiating, and launching important strategic partnerships to support and accelerate the Company’s growth. This is a key hire that would have broad latitude on defining and executing on our strategy for key investors. You will own the end-to-end deal process from ideation to post-launch success and will work collaboratively across product, sales, strategy, and operations. </span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span>Responsibilities:</span></span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<ul>
<li><span> </span><span>Monitor the competitive landscape to help identify and prioritize opportunities to accelerate our strategy, including through tracking of external parties, cultivating relevant companies and experts, and interaction with other sources of opportunities.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><span>Full ownership and management of deals from research, outreach, negotiation, and launch.</span></li>
<li><span>Collaborate with leadership to develop strategic plan to maximize partnership opportunities.</span></li>
<li><span>Build and foster strong relationships with key external partners to accelerate customer adoption and long-term client or investor satisfaction.</span></li>
<li><span>Source, negotiate, and close multifaceted complex partnership deals that support and accelerate the company goals.</span></li>
<li><span>Launch partnerships with a focus on results/impact while ensuring a delightful user experience.</span></li>
<li><span>Work cross-functionally with Product Management, Engineering, Legal, Marketing, and Sales and other internal organizations across Securitize to identify areas of impact, prioritize key initiatives, and execute.</span></li>
<li><span>Conduct and manage due diligence as a leader in M&amp;A activity; assist with negotiations, deal closure and execution/integration.</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><span> </span><span>Evaluate proposals and negotiate the terms of partnership agreements to deliver on expected outcomes for company’s growth &amp; success.</span></li>
<li><span> </span><span>Routinely represent the organization to financial and operational partners, including financial institutions, investors, auditors, lawyers, partners, and board members.</span></li>
<li><span> </span><span>Maintaining strong understanding of client business and strategy, economic models, financial results, industry trends, and operational developments.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span>Requirements:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Must have 8-10+ years of professional experience in product partnerships, business development, account management, strategic partnerships, or similar roles within a rapidly scaling and/or enterprise company. </span></li>
<li><span>Experience in financial sector, fintech, and/or identity industries strongly preferred. </span></li>
<li><span>A strong attention to detail along with a keen eye for the big picture. </span></li>
<li><span>Requires a growth mindset individual that can drive multiple projects simultaneously through excellent time management, planning and organizational skills.</span></li>
<li><span>Exceptional communication and presentation skills. </span></li>
<li><span>Demonstrated ability to collaboratively influence gaining broad stakeholder support when developing, implementing, and promoting strategies, initiatives, projects, and new ventures in a shared leadership environment.</span></li>
<li><span>A firm but fair negotiator with a great demeanor and partner-facing attitude.</span></li>
<li><span>You are reliable, helpful, honest, and efficient.</span></li>
<li><span>Proven track record of negotiating complex deals and driving most aspects of the legal process.</span></li>
<li><span>Sharp strategic thinker who can design and execute on a vision.</span></li>
<li><span>History of running quickly with little supervision.</span></li>
<li><span>Ability to adapt to and lead through fast-paced, high-growth, uncertain environments.</span></li>
</ul>
<p> </p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span>Join an awesome company entering a hyper-growth phase</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Unlimited Paid Time Off</span></li>
<li><span>Bonus program </span></li>
<li><span>Remote work environment</span></li>
<li><span>Company paid professional development </span></li>
<li><span>100% Medical/dental/vision insurance</span></li>
<li><span>401K</span></li>
</ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-7Nr4euKbfk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://securitize.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=38&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/294965/seciritize.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[securitize@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6fa7bf1d-9e9f-4ac1-9f2a-f1de480d8620]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Securitize]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Associate Account Executive (AUS)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sydney, Australia | Melbourne, Australia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our sales team is made up of expert storytellers and problem-solvers and we’re obsessed with expanding cryptocurrency markets and helping customers track and prevent fraud and abuse. Our goal is to make sure both public sector agencies, cryptocurrency businesses and financial institutions see the value of implementing our solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Account Executive for A&amp;amp;Z can quickly establish trust within strategic customers and they are an expert at navigating complex sales cycles. We measure success by new business and account expansion revenue.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;exceeded your quota and substantially increased our foothold in the A&amp;amp;Z market through strategic and relentless prospecting and developing your sales pipeline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve helped us develop compelling product positioning and messaging specific to market trends, competitive drivers, region-specific sales channels, and more&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your relationships with customers are built on trust and transparency resulting in network referrals that ultimately build Chainalysis’ brand awareness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve created and executed go-to-market plans that have resulted in predictable and increasing quarterly forecasts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve built a diverse pipeline of opportunities resulting in consistent and accurate forecasting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have managed and structured our relationships with the local resellers and distributors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have relationships across departments at Chainalysis allowing you to provide expert advice to prospects related to technical concepts, product roadmaps, solutions implementations, training, and more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;B2B SaaS sales mostly focused on the Cryptocurrency industry in A&amp;amp;Z&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;B2B SaaS sales across different verticals including Financial Institutions and Cyber security&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Both written and spoken fluency in English for the purposes of communicating with Chainalysis’ offices around the world and with customers in A&amp;amp;Z&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience leading the entire sales process from discovery calls to contract negotiation to closing deals&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience dealing with resellers &amp;amp; Distributors to extend our reach in the local market.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience dealing with blockchain use cases&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-RS1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yNpNz-FvSYQ&t=6s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5713287002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Investment Associate/Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Pantera Capital]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.panteracapital.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Pantera Capital (<a href="http://www.panteracapital.com/">www.panteracapital.com</a>) is one of the oldest and largest institutional investors in blockchain and cryptocurrencies. Pantera Capital is hiring an analyst or associate to focus on early-stage investment opportunities in venture capital and ICOs. As a junior member on the investment team, you will learn about both the venture capital and hedge fund industries, meet inspiring entrepreneurs and get exposure to cutting-edge technologies and products. We are looking for someone who is able to start immediately.&nbsp;</div><br/>The primary responsibilities of the associate can be broken down into four areas:<br/><li>Sourcing - proactively identifying new investment opportunities and qualifying inbound leads for the firm by meeting with entrepreneurs.</li><li>Deal Diligence - helping the team evaluate new investment opportunities through market research, product reviews, competitive analysis, metrics analysis, customer/user reviews and technical diligence.</li><li>Portfolio Work - collaborating with the team to support the Pantera Capital portfolio.</li><li>Ecosystem building - being an active contributor to the blockchain/cryptocurrencies community by organizing activities, participating in local events and looking for ways to help make the Pantera team stronger.</li><br/><br/><li>Passion for blockchain/cryptocurrencies</li><li>1–4 years of relevant work experience in venture capital, investment banking, consulting, tech, or a startup</li><li>Native understanding of blockchain technology, experience reviewing white papers or crypto projects strongly preferred</li><li>Strong written and analytical skills for deal analysis and internal reporting</li><li>Strong interpersonal skills</li><li>History of being proactive within previous roles</li><li>An ability to work well within a team and be self-guided on a day-to-day basis</li><li>Technical background or experience in data science&nbsp;a plus</li><div>Our process starts with having candidates answer one question by video recording. From the initial submissions we will select a smaller group for telephone interviews. From there a set of finalists will be asked to submit a written piece and join us for in-person or virtual meetings</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=N0d45K1SH4Q" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/panteracapital/07a7dc4a-2811-44ac-a915-25b25b7838e7/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145535/pantera_capital.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[pantera@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[39ddee3c-0f1b-4fd8-9347-b2206455a7c1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Pantera Capital]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Center Facilities Technician]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ankr]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ankr.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Cumberland, Kentucky, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p><strong>About ANKR</strong><br></p><p>Ankr provides Web3 infrastructure for easy, accessible and affordable deployment of blockchain nodes, API’s, decentralized staking infrastructure and Layer 2 scaling solutions, designed to lower the entry barrier for everyday people, enterprises, and developers to contribute to blockchain ecosystems. </p><p>Check us out at <a href="https://www.ankr.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://www.ankr.com/</a></p><p>Ankr was founded in 2017 in Berkeley, California. Its founding team and headquarters are based in San Francisco. Ankr’s distributed team of 50+ people operates from offices in San Francisco, Shanghai, Moscow, and Amsterdam.</p><p>Joining our operations team means that you will be at the forefront of all we do, maintaining critical facilities infrastructure as part of a close-knit team delivering best in class service. </p><p>The Data Center Facilities Technician will be responsible for performing repairs, corrective maintenance, and complex installations, training can be provided. </p><p><br></p><p><strong>What we are looking for in a Data Center Facilities Technician:</strong></p><ul> <li>Performs site inspections and monitors the building and alarms</li> <li>You will be responsible for performing preventative maintenance on site infrastructure (e.g. maintenance of primary infrastructures)</li> <li>Undertakes repairs and corrective maintenance</li> <li>Assists in coordinating critical infrastructure</li> <li>You are responsible for completion of site logs and data gathering for permits, such as MOPs and scripts</li> <li>You are expected to respond to all on-site incidents and take action as required</li> <li>May instruct on-site staff during simple incidents</li> <li>Completes complex work requests and circuit installations</li> <li>Effectively collaborates with internal and external departments</li> <li>Provides input to your peers for complex / critical maintenance activities</li> <li>Works through issues in a confident, positive way; is able to influence without authority</li> <li>Carries out more complex infrastructure projects</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>High School Diploma</li> <li>Able to perform all essential job functions, including walking, standing, bending, stooping, climbing, lifting and manual dexterity, with or without reasonable accommodation</li> <li>Ability to work days/nights/weekends/holidays, if needed and/or required</li> </ul>ANKR is an equal opportunity employer. All applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, religion, color, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, status as a protected veteran, or status as a qualified individual with disability.<p>Benefits</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/ankr/j/2F4F9696C4/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/746707/ankr-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ankr@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3b58522a-6fba-41ac-b017-94bbed42523c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ankr]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Content Media Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.axiomzen.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote or Vancouver, BC]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 16px">More than just an exciting new product in the tech space, NBA Top Shot is a fast-growing part of the general fan experience. This is a responsibility we relish. Given NBA Top Shot’s integral role in the NBA and WNBA landscapes, we want to continue to establish ourselves as world-class authorities on the sport.</span></div><div><br></div><div>As we raise the bar higher and higher for what sports collectibles can be in the 21st century, we’re hiring a <b>Basketball Operations, Media Lead</b>. This individual, in addition to having an expert-level knowledge of basketball past and present, will ensure that we are optimizing and getting the absolute most out of the video and photo assets that make our Moments special.</div><div><br></div><div>This individual will not only leverage their knowledge of the game but their experience editing captivating videos and photos to make sure that the Moments that arrive on our platform are as polished, refined and compelling as possible. This role will report to the Head of Basketball Operations of NBA Top Shot.</div><br/>What we’ll accomplish together:<br/><li>Thoroughly monitor and discuss all live NBA and WNBA content (as well as historical archives) with the goal of identifying candidate plays that would resonate with Top Shot collectors.</li><li>Provide editorial guidance and feedback in the video cutting process for highlights that appear in the product, with the goal of sufficiently capturing the excitement of the chosen play.</li><li>Scour available photo databases for thumbnail images that capture the context of and provide additional value to the Moments, while working within the framework defined by our relationship with company partners.</li><li>Edit, refine and polish the media assets to be included in the render of potential Moments based on the feedback of key stakeholders.</li><li>Work closely with marketing and creative teams to ensure that the most compelling and captivating aspects of our content are identified and made available to be featured in promotional campaigns.</li><br/>A little about you:<br/><li>You live and breathe basketball with expert-level knowledge of the sport, past and present. You’re comfortable and familiar with the names and faces of all current NBA and WNBA rosters, with a solid grasp of past personnel and the pertinent historical context of each league.</li><li>You not only appreciate the game on a personal level but understand modern-day fandom, new media and the role that a product like NBA Top Shot can play in shaping basketball culture.</li><li>You have a keen eye for compelling video content and an intimate understanding of the editing process.</li><li>You have first-hand experience editing photos for publication either online or in print.</li><li>You understand the visceral impact that compelling media has on viewers and embrace the challenge of making captivating, beautiful content.</li><div>Please include any sample work that you are able to share with your application. If you aren't able to add it to your application, please be prepared to share it during the interview process </div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div><b>More about Dapper Labs:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Dapper Labs is the world's first blockchain entertainment company. We are the creators of industry-leading experiences including CryptoKitties and NBA Top Shot, as well as Dapper Wallet, the simplest way to manage your assets and use the blockchain. We are also the original developers behind Flow, a new decentralized blockchain designed from the ground up for scalability and ease of use.</div><div><br></div><div>Our mission at Dapper Labs is to make the world a more open, empowering, and enjoyable place through consumer adoption of decentralized technologies. We have raised over $600M from leading VCs including Fred Wilson (USV) and Chris Dixon as well as Venrock, Samsung, Google Ventures, Coatue, NBA players, and global artists, among others. Dapper Labs partners include the NBA and NBPA, the NFL-PA, Ubisoft, Warner Music, Turner, Dr. Seuss, Genies, and the UFC, as well as 100+ others.</div><div><br></div><div>Visit our website to learn even more about Dapper Labs, including <a href="https://www.dapperlabs.com/careers#benefits" class="postings-link">information about benefits and perks</a>.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Vvp75OCtwa0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axiomzen/a5a8da61-8540-4a4b-a82f-24ba44460cb7/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194192/axiomzen1.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axiomzen@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5da21464-b527-48a0-a501-0b4f2e445537]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Regulatory Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[NEAR]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://nearprotocol.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Zug, Switzerland]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;NEAR Foundation is hiring a Regulatory Specialist, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;who can contribute with strong domain expertise excelling in a startup environment. Our offer is to become part of a group of high-performing pioneers at the forefront of digital technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ll:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Take responsibility for regulatory aspects of the blockchain industry developments in various jurisdictions around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Contribute to the NEAR Foundation’s regulatory strategy, applicable standards and guidelines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate and submit responses to relevant industry working groups with regards to regulations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Maintain regulatory documentation up to date for worldwide regulatory purposes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assess regulatory changes and support respective activities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish and update internal procedures to enable up to date and consistent output, as well as efficient workflow within the NEAR Foundation teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Master’s degree in law from a Swiss University or equivalent EU or USA University law degree&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least five years of relevant experience, thereof at least two years of experience working in the blockchain industry&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent knowledge of the applicable fintech and blockchain regulations in major jurisdictions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Independent, reliable and communicative personality who can deliver high-quality work even under pressure and handle several projects simultaneously&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Adaptive, critical and outside the box thinking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enjoy the challenges the new digital asset world provides&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exact and diligent working style&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Skilled at interdisciplinary collaboration with experts from various fields&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fluency in the English language mandatory, German and any other language an advantage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We value:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ECOSYSTEM-FIRST: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;always put the health and success of the ecosystem above any individual&#39;s interest.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;OPENNESS: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;operate transparently and consistently share knowledge to build open communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;PRAGMATISM OVER PERFECTION: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;find the right solution not the ideal solution and beat dogmatism by openly considering all ideas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;MAKE IT FEEL SIMPLE: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;strive to make the complex feel simple so the technology is accessible to all.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;GROW CONSTANTLY: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;learn, improve and fail productively so the project and community are always becoming more effective.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;About the NEAR Foundation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://near.org/blog/what-the-near-foundation-does/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;NEAR Foundation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is a nonprofit, non-beneficiary foundation based in Switzerland which supports community-driven innovation and the Open Web with a specific focus on the NEAR platform. The Foundation distributes grant funding into the NEAR ecosystem, coordinates governance among participants, educates people about the protocol and ensures that relationships among the community members are as strong and sustainable as the apps they build. It seeks to combine the inclusive care of a community-driven NGO with the at-scale effectiveness of a Silicon Valley startup.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-hOWM-o7N5k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/near/jobs/5712437002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/291590/near-protocol-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[near@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[968fe95d-e05d-452b-ab80-880386c33b67]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[NEAR]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Flipside Crypto]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://flipsidecrypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Boston, MA - Remote OK]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Senior Data Analyst</strong></p><p>The Data Analytics Team at Flipside Crypto is looking for a Senior Data Analyst to help us build out our suite of analytics products.</p><p>As a Senior Data Analyst at Flipside Crypto, you will serve in a highly cross functional role and be responsible for creating detailed analytics product specifications and metric definitions for customers, as well as partnering with engineering and data science teams to deliver reports, data models and data visualizations.</p><p>As a Senior Data Analyst at Flipside Crypto, you will:</p><p></p><ul><li>Write SQL or other querying code to extract and manipulate data from database systems to create reports and data visualizations using proprietary Flipside applications</li><li>Partner with Product and Data Science to design and define analytics product specifications</li><li>Create compelling data visualizations that convey clear insights to users </li><li>Ensure accuracy of data results and analytic methods through testing and validation of underlying report data and coordinate closely with Data Product on issue resolution</li><li>Learn about the top Blockchains and Protocols in order to model a data framework needed to do proper analysis of their use cases.</li><li>Become an expert on customer blockchain projects and serve as the main point of contact for data questions as well as mentor other analysts</li><li>Help build data models that are in line with analytics product specifications in Python and in SQL</li><li>Work with Blockchain Communities on Discord in order to gather insights as well as give support</li><li>Mentor more junior analysts on the team for learning and guidance on best practices</li></ul><p></p><p>You are a fit if:</p><ul><li>You possess a strong analytical background that includes 7+ years of experience working with complex data sets</li><li>You are have experience working with and are a subject matter expert with Blockchain Data</li><li>You are comfortable creating your own intermediary tables and thrive in ambiguity</li><li>You have experience with creating data visualizations to convey meaning to customers and telling a compelling narrative</li><li>You are self directed and capable of driving projects forward to meet deadlines</li><li>You have great communication skills (verbal and written) and are able to present your ideas to a wide audience</li><li>You have a strong background in writing SQL (Snowflake)</li><li>Are familiar using ETL pipelining tools like DBT</li><li>You have an analytical mindset with a great statistics background</li><li>You have some programming experience with Python</li></ul><p></p><p>About Flipside:</p><p>Flipside Crypto empowers crypto communities to create and share data-driven insights on the projects they care most about. Flipside powers Community-Enabled Analytics, which uses a bounty program to incentivize on-demand insights based on feedback from the protocol and community participants. CEA provides fully pre-modeled and labeled data, a SQL interface for data queries. Community members can use our dashboard and visualization tools to easily share insights, or leverage auto-generated API endpoints to build whatever they can imagine.</p><p>Flipside customers include FLOW, NEAR, Terra, Algorand, CELO, Compound, Alchemix and many others. Flipside Crypto is led by a team of experienced technology entrepreneurs with multiple exits; it’s backed by Galaxy Digital Ventures, True Ventures, Founder Collective, Coinbase Ventures, Digital Currency Group, Avon Ventures (a venture capital fund affiliated with FMR LLC, the parent company of Fidelity Investments) and other investors.</p><p></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4oOcum2vCVo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://flipsidecrypto.breezy.hr/p/1c4816f56e94-senior-data-analyst/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/371352/flipside_crypto.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[flipsidecrypto@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9fd60574-03dd-4ff7-969f-631367694cbd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Flipside Crypto]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Recruiting Coordinator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York; Portland, Oregon; Chicago, Illinois; Los Angeles, California; San Francisco, Cal]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is a crypto exchange and custodian that allows customers to buy, sell, store, and earn more than 30 cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, bitcoin cash, ether, litecoin, and Zcash. Gemini is a New York trust company that is subject to the capital reserve requirements, cybersecurity requirements, and banking compliance standards set forth by the New York State Department of Financial Services and the New York Banking Law. Gemini was founded in 2014 by twin brothers Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss to empower the individual through crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto is about giving you greater choice, independence, and opportunity. We are here to help you on your journey. We build crypto products that are simple, elegant, and secure. Whether you are an individual or an institution, we want to help you buy, sell, and store your bitcoin and cryptocurrency. Crypto is not just a technology, it&#39;s a movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;empower the individual &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;and that includes giving our employees flexibility of choice — our Office Optional Policy allows employees to choose to work from one of our physical locations or from home. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Select roles that are location-specific will still be eligible for flexible schedules.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Department: &lt;/strong&gt;Talent Acquisition&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The People Team at Gemini are thought partners, business influencers, and ambassadors for Gemini&#39;s company values. Our collaborative team is comprised of recruiters, program managers, and human resources specialists. As a member of the People Team, you’ll be on the ground floor of a quickly growing organization, with the opportunity to create best-in-class processes and programs that find, grow, and retain amazing talent at Gemini.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role: &lt;/strong&gt;Recruiting Coordinator&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Recruiting Coordinator, you&#39;ll play a large role in contributing to the Talent Acquisition team&#39;s success in hiring and retaining amazing talent at Gemini. You&#39;ll be responsible for providing support to many aspects of the recruitment lifecycle with a primary focus on the coordination of interviews. In this role, you will report to the Senior Manager, Recruiting Strategy &amp;amp; Operations and global Talent Acquisition team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support Talent Acquisition team with scheduling and coordination interviews -- both in-person and by phone/video&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Recruiters and Hiring Managers to document, enter, and update interview processes in our Applicant Tracking System, Greenhouse&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with Hiring Managers and Interviewers to run an efficient and seamless interview process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Maintain data accuracy within Greenhouse, and coordinate with Talent Acquisition team to ensure information on candidates and requisitions is up to date&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist with the implementation and integration of recruiting-related tools/platforms (e.g. LinkedIn Recruiter, Greenhouse, Entelo, Stack Overflow)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track and process invoicing for recruitment agencies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Process background checks for new hires&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help organize and maintain confidential filing systems for employee files&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with team to document Recruiting Coordinator processes; help train and onboard new team members&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in ad-hoc projects&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree in human resource management or business-related area&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;1+ years of experience related to several aspects of HR, including talent acquisition and HR generalist duties&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Applicant Tracking Systems (We use Greenhouse!)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency with Google Suite (Gmail, Google Calendar, Drive, Sheets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exceptional administrative skills, including organization, high attention to detail, proactive communication, and responsiveness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated judgment and ability to deal with confidential and sensitive matters effectively&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to respond to changing situations in a flexible manner and reprioritize accordingly to meet immediate needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to identify areas for process improvement and give recommendations for how to improve&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-EP1&lt;br&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=70jrfYSxKC4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3676413&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Support Content Editor]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Cape Town]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Together, we&#39;re upgrading the world of work to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Upgrading the entire planet to a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;new financial system&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is a challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;working together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with unusual skill, focus and determination. We’re changing the financial landscape, and to do so,&amp;nbsp; we need the best team on board for our mission. In short, to achieve our goals, we need people with exceptional talent. As simple as that.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We make it safe and easy to buy, store and learn about cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We currently have over 9 million customers across 40 countries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re part of the Digital Currency Group, a group of companies driving progress in the cryptocurrency and blockchain space that includes Grayscale, Genesis, Coindesk and Foundry Services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our platform has processed over $17 billion to date.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re proud to be one of the world’s most international cryptocurrency teams from 43 different nationalities — working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria and Singapore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little about the Customer Success team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Customer Success team is responsible for delivering service support to Luno’s 8 million customers across the globe.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a global team with team members in the US (soon), Europe, South East Asia and South Africa.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This team is passionate about delivering fantastic customer support experiences that build customer loyalty and love for Luno.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This team is made up of leaders and specialists in the areas of workforce management, customer success service operations, quality management, customer service measurement, training, continuous improvement, programme management, customer experience design and content, to name a few.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We will be 250+ passionate global Lunauts in this team by the end of 2021.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role in a nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ll be creating and managing customer-facing support content and communication across various channels, ensuring that our customers are given the best experience they can possibly get on their cryptocurrency journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ll report into André, the Manager Support Content, Customer Support Experience Design and Internal Communications. Meet him&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.linkedin.com/in/andre-wessels/&quot;&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your mission will involve&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working closely with the Support Content Manager and the Customer Success (CS) Internal Content Team to align on customer-facing communication.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Creating support content (written and video content) that will be used to assist and support our customers, through various channels including help centre content, automated customer communication, live chat and social media. Example of help centre content (written and video) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.luno.com/help/articles/425889692295723&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital copywriting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Being involved in projects launching across Luno and developing localised support content for new and existing customers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working closely with the CS Internal Content Team to identify content needs based on feedback from the CS Quality Assurance team, by conducting root-cause analyses, and by analysing data and metrics pertaining to Luno’s customer support.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identifying opportunities to improve content performance and usability, as well as content development processes and tools.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Delivering and implementing end to end processes including writing, editing, publishing, analysis and reporting of external support content to all relevant stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensuring all content is in line with Luno’s brand guidelines and tone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal candidate will have the following essentials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 6 months of working experience in Customer Support.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have a solid understanding of Customer Support processes and policies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent natural writing skills and the ability to simplify complex concepts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have basic to good HTML experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A good communicator.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in a similar role or a proven track record in Customer Support.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have a willingness to build upon your current knowledge of cryptocurrencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good listening and organisational skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to multitask with the best and work on different projects at the same time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A proactive mindset.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p1&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Life at Luno&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you’re looking to work on something truly global and disruptive with a forward-thinking and ambitious team that highly values diversity, teamwork, and the continuous quest for excellence, then this is an opportunity for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Like the majority of the companies, Luno is currently working remotely to keep our employees safe, which means you will not be physically, but virtually onboarded for now!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;ll be able to continuously upskill yourself with access to free courses on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Udemy, Coursera and CodeAcademy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Live long and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; prosper. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve got you covered with excellent private medical insurance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For the crypto fans among you (should be everyone!), you&#39;ll pay &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;0 fees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with Luno from the day you start.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;maternity / paternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and even (yes, you are reading it correctly) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;paw-ternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for your furry friend..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Annual Inspiration Day...for that pottery course you’ve always been meaning to do!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;diverse team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; of hardworking, ambitious and friendly people on something that will truly revolutionise the financial world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work is important, but&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; your mental health should always take priority&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. At Luno, we do everything we can to make sure you lead a healthy and happy life. That&#39;s why Luno gives you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; free access to Headspace&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; – a full library of guided meditations, sleep stories, and music.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p1&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3670702?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Android Developer (Remote - Work from Anywhere)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Xapo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://xapo.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xapo is an international fintech startup on a mission to protect and grow its clients’ life savings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re a fully distributed team that works remotely from 50+ countries around the world. We may come from many different cultures and backgrounds, but it’s our values, our resourcefulness, and our drive that makes us Xapiens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We work hard, think globally, and inspire each other to grow every day. If you’re the best at what you do and share our passion, we want you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us, wherever you are, and help us build a digital bank worthy of the digital age at Xapo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ANDROID DEVELOPER&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Although we are headquartered in Gibraltar, this is a full time, 100% remote position. Work from anywhere!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our tech stack includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% Kotlin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Architecture components&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;RxJava, Coroutines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Dagger, Koin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kotlin Multiplatform&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Compose&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Xapo we are building truly cross functional teams with full ownership of design, architecture, build and&amp;nbsp; test. You will collaborate closely with your fellow team members from the product, backend, design and QA communities of practice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As Android Developer, you will be responsible for building components of our mobile app &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;that will enable users all over the world to send, spend, save, and receive money and Bitcoin safely and globally. The impact of what you will help develop at Xapo will help people protect their life savings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you are a passionate, enthusiastic engineer interested in revolutionizing banking, join us!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years experience in Android development.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in Kotlin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with code sharing, pull requests and code reviews (Git).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with teams in an agile environment (Jira).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passion for clean code where re-usability, testability and readability are a must (SOLID).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with the tech stack described above.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great communication skills in English.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in CI/CD, Gradle and static code quality analytics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in UI tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in Kotlin Multiplatform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in material design and animations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience or willing to learn some Swift&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Open source contributions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A dedicated workspace.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A reliable internet connection with the fastest speed possible in your area.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Devices and other essential equipment that meet minimal technical specifications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Alignment with Our Values.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why work for Xapo?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;IMPACT GLOBALLY, WORK REMOTELY.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Shape the Future: Improve lives through cutting-edge technology, work 100% remotely from anywhere in the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own Your Success: Receive $80k to $100k depending on skills and experience, enjoy an autonomous work culture and flexible hours, apply your expertise to meaningful work every day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expect Excellence: Collaborate, learn, and grow with a high-performance team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY WORK FOR XAPO?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPACT GLOBALLY, WORK REMOTELY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shape the Future: Improve lives through cutting-edge technology, work 100% remotely from anywhere in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own Your Success: Receive attractive remuneration, enjoy an autonomous work culture and flexible hours, apply your expertise to meaningful work every day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expect Excellence: Collaborate, learn, and grow with a high-performance team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT XAPO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We founded Xapo to address two of the biggest issues with Bitcoin adoption: accessibility and security. In a matter of years, we developed an industry-leading platform that introduced cryptocurrency into the daily lives of millions worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, we’re bringing our expertise to all facets of our users’ finances. Because no matter who we are or where we’re from, we all deserve more options, more control, and more peace of mind where our money is concerned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re an Equal Opportunity Employer – we believe that diversity is critical to our success as a global company. An inclusive workplace is the foundation of Xapo – it allows us to create products that cater to clients around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/xapo61/jobs/4820797003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175504/xapo500x500.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[xapo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f1ade05b-4c67-4366-b825-57e86b9f373d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Xapo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Engineer - Market Intelligence]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.elliptic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>As digital assets and cryptocurrency become more widely adopted every day, businesses rely on Elliptic for key data insights to give them an edge in the market. Our unique data set allows customers to see market moves before they happen, driving business decision-making. Our products are used by the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, financial institutions and government agencies, responsible for billions of dollars worth of transactions every single week.</p> <p>Elliptic is backed by some of the top VCs: SoftBank Vision Fund, Octopus Ventures, Evolution Equity Partners, Digital Currency Group, Albion VC, SBI Group, Santander, Wells Fargo, and more, and our global team is based predominantly in the UK, USA, Singapore and Tokyo.</p> <p>To achieve our mission, we depend on our incredible team of Elliptites. <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/life-at-elliptic" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Our values</a> are reflected in everything we do and every decision we make, both internally and outwardly to our customers. We actively encourage Elliptities to challenge the status quo and allow the freedom to innovate and learn every day. We encourage new ideas and learning, whether that’s through collaboration, our curiosity sessions, or utilising your professional development budget - personal growth is important to us all.</p><p><strong>The Impact you will have <br></strong></p><p>This role will be part of a small, dedicated Market Intelligence business unit within the wider Elliptic team. This is an ideal role for a data engineer excited by the chance to discover a brand new product space inside an existing scaleup. The team will act like a startup inside a scaleup and move fast so this is an opportunity to have an outsized impact in a small ambitious team and to work truly cross-functionally at pace.</p><p><strong>What’s the role?</strong></p><p>Elliptic is looking for a Data Engineer to join our product-engineering organisation who can help drive forward our support for new blockchains.</p><p>We want a data engineer who is comfortable with working in a ‘scrappy’ startup way and flexible enough to change gear. The role is quickly discovering value in our dataset and exposing this to our customers for a ‘good enough’ (vs perfect) MVP. We want engineers with a strong customer orientation, huge determination in problem-solving to bust through any challenges our MVP build may bring, and happy to work in a self-directed, proactive way. </p><p>We are looking for somebody who always tackles the biggest risk first, who brings new ideas and approaches to development, who makes decisions with data, and who loves solving customer-centric problems.</p><p><strong>What will you do?</strong></p><ul> <li>Take pleasure from clean code and see writing tests as core to software engineering </li> <li>Use data to make decisions about what to build and how to iterate</li> <li>Measure their successes with usage data rather than release milestones</li> <li>Are not afraid to fail, experiment often and learn quickly</li> <li>Are keen to learn new technologies and challenge existing tools, methodologies, processes</li> <li>Ship code to production every day</li> </ul><p>In a typical week you will:</p><ul> <li>Work in a fast, lean, Agile environment with minimal process overheads</li> <li>Develop new features for our big data MVP </li> <li>Review the code of your peers, and test that it works</li> <li>Participate in various “chapter” debates about new ideas and interesting tech</li> <li>Support your software on production</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>2+ years of experience in Apache Spark or any other big data processing tool</li> <li>Design, build, test and debug batch and streaming data pipelines capable of processing large volumes of data.</li> <li>Experience performance tuning queries and data models to produce the best execution plan</li> <li>Experience with Data Lake implementations and design patterns</li> <li>A strong understanding of the Big Data ecosystem</li> <li>A strong coding background in either Scala, Java or Python</li> <li>Bonus: someone with the desire to learn and code in Scala</li> </ul><p><strong>Bonus Points for:</strong></p><ul> <li>Experience in other Big Data Technologies (Hadoop, Presto, Kafka, Hive, Flink, etc…)</li> <li>Experience with AWS Big Data tools such as Kinesis, Glue, Athena and EMR</li> <li>Has experience working with Data Science teams</li> <li>Confident working with SQL</li> <li>HODLs some crypto</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>Share Options</li> <li>Holiday - 25 days + public holidays + additional day for your birthday</li> <li>Private Health Insurance - we use Vitality!</li> <li>Work Pension Scheme</li> <li>Quarterly full-day off-sites &amp; annual company 3-day offsite</li> <li>$1000 Personal training budget &amp; LinkedIn Learning subscription</li> <li>£500 Home office allowance</li> <li>Enhanced parental leave; we provide eligible employees, regardless of gender or whether they become a parent by birth or adoption, 16 weeks fully-paid leave and job-protected leave</li> <li>Full access to Spill Mental Health Support</li> <li>Our offices provide all of the amenities you could need</li> <li>Work with top of the range equipment - MacBook Pro and any other equipment you need</li> </ul><p>We know Diversity and Inclusion is much deeper than just hiring, but it’s important for us to mention it here. We welcome and embrace individuals of all backgrounds and identities at Elliptic, and this is an ongoing priority for us. We know incredible people don’t all think in the same way. We want to be challenged every day. We believe our diverse team of individuals underpins this by bringing creative thinking and innovation to Elliptic every day. We are committed to creating a diverse, inclusive and equitable workplace, so we welcome applications from everyone, even if you may not think you fit all of the requirements of our roles. We foster an environment of psychological safety, where everyone feels comfortable to bring their whole self to work.<br></p> <p>No recruitment agencies!</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ebOLNjlYiNg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/elliptic/j/3DC1739087/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145877/elliptic.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[elliptic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[fefe721f-d5ba-4eb0-9b9b-f4156a27cb2b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
