<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Growth Manager (Remote Ireland)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.bitfinex.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The Marketing Growth Manager will support all areas of the marketing department and the head of marketing to launch campaigns, market existing products and meet marketing KPIs and growth targets that are met for the year. This will be a fully autonomous role and the ability to seek opportunities and build campaigns from the ground up is essential.</p>
<p dir="ltr">From determining positioning, competitive analysis, feature prioritization and external communications, you help shape the voice of Bitfinex and our suite of products to help us grow our user base. This means you work with a cross-functional team across Business Development, legal, Developers, Web Design, product development, engineering and more. In this role, you'll be involved with product marketing strategy from beginning to end.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Demonstrable experience in a wide range of digital marketing including marketing database management, content creation, email marketing, social media, display advertising campaigns and events promotion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Highly creative with experience in identifying target audiences and devising digital campaigns that engage, inform, and motivate our audience of cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p>
<p><br /><br /></p><h3 dir="ltr">Currently looking for:</h3>
<p><br /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Bitfinex Marketing Growth Manager (Remote)</strong></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">​<strong>Job description</strong></h3>
<p><br /></p><ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Supporting the central marketing team with their day to day operational marketing activities</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Working closely with the marketing manager to identify new opportunities to market Bitfinex. You will take ownership of campaigns to meet our marketing objectives for the year as well as your own targets</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Strong analytical skills to identify areas of opportunity and improvement across our website and products</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Supporting the growth of other key teams within Bitfinex by developing new campaigns to promote product launches</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Research and create engaging content that also supports the growth of our SEO strategy</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Work with the design teams to create effective campaigns on both social media, email and at events. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Come up with new and innovative campaigns and take ownership of each campaign from start to finish once agreed with the marketing manager. Campaigns will include, email marketing, influencer outreach, content marketing and community engagement.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">A creative thinker, able to come up with innovative new ideas and solutions.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Ability to work to tight deadlines </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Pro-active in their approach so opportunities can be spotted and fast action can be taken to take an idea to market</p></li></ul><p><h2>Requirements:</h2></p><ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">MANDATORY EXPERIENCE in these sectors or similar industries: Crypto, Financial, Medical/Pharma, Cannabis, eSports and Gambling or other regulated environments.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Motivated team player who actively seeks challenging projects and proactively shares experiences and knowledge towards the team’s goals.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Good understanding of multichannel marketing and how users interact with each channel</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience in using data, research and customer feedback to improve a campaign to inform future activities</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience in planning and developing digital marketing campaigns from start to finish working with a number of teams to ensure a marketing campaign is ready for project launch</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience using a number of email marketing solutions</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Work closely with the marketing manager and social media strategist to enhance and maintain the company's social media presence</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Be able to write captivating copy to engage existing users and attract new users to the website</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Google certification would be an advantage</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Knowledge of the cryptocurrency industry and trading would be an advantage but not necessary</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Work to strict deadlines for project launches and experience using project management tools such as Asana. </p></li></ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fx7gryqZwzw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://bitfinex.recruitee.com/o/marketing-growth-manager-remote-ireland/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/227432/Bitfinex_Long_Logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ricardo.pinheiro@bitfinex.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[a48bec57-75b8-41d5-9cff-1828d315ba59]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Partner Engineer/Solution Architect]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://protocol.ai/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Ecosystem]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs makes breakthroughs in computing technology to push humanity forward. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how things work. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Partner Engineers/Solution Architects have the challenging and exciting task of working on complex problems in an environment defined by curiosity, passion, and a love for open source. This will be an opportunity to work directly on our projects including IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Ecosystem ⇄ Outercore</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Outercore, the subsidiary that represents grants, accelerators, and special projects at Protocol Labs is looking for a Partner Engineer to help us build the future of p2p distributed networks. If you’re excited about the promise of Filecoin, Libp2p, IPFS, and you want to work closely with the people who use our technology every day, this role may be for you.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Everything Outercore does is open source and we encourage everyone to work out in the open. We’re comfortable sharing unfinished work and trying out new things. The goal is to come up with solutions the entire ecosystem can benefit from.</span></div><br/>A Partner Engineer will team up with any company in the ecosystem of their choosing. Afterwards they will ensure:<br/><li>The company in the ecosystem is able to use Filecoin, Libp2p, IPFS, and the FVM to help achieve business goals.</li><li>Any learnings they discover along the way will be brought back to the Filecoin, Libp2p, IPFS, and FVM contributors.</li><li>A Partner Engineer when necessary will take charge and lead the projects to improve protocols and applications.</li><li>Build great software that other companies and individuals will use to achieve their goals.</li><li>Help us grow this Filecoin ecosystem to its full potential.</li><br/>What we're looking for:<br/><li>You enjoy embedding with new teams and learning about their companies and users.</li><li>You’re great at keeping track of feedback and helping other team members understand the problems that need to be solved.</li><li>You know how to unblock progress and create temporary solutions for difficult problems.</li><li>You have some interest in IPFS and Filecoin, if you do not have any interest, you should be genuinely curious about what those technologies are and hope to develop an interest. We will ask what content addressing is!</li><li>You’re familiar with open source work and the Go programming language or you are someone who is willing to pick the language up and you have the foundation to do so.</li><li>You have a B.Sc. in Computer Science or a related field. A degree is not required but a lot of what we do requires a computer science foundation.</li><div><b style="font-size: 18px">What’s it like to work at Protocol Labs?</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs mission is to improve humanity’s most important technology, the Internet. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how it works. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Our projects include IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As a distributed team, we hire anywhere in the world, and at various levels of experience (entry, senior, staff). We look for people with unique perspectives and diverse backgrounds.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We have a great benefits package, including parental leave, contributions to your retirement, competitive pay, and unlimited time off. For <a href="http://U.S.-based">U.S.-based</a> employees, we also provide platinum-level health, dental, and vision coverage for you and your family.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">What’s it like to work at Protocol Labs?</span></b></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs mission is to improve humanity’s most important technology, the Internet. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how it works. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Our projects include IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As a distributed team, we hire anywhere in the world, and at various levels of experience (entry, senior, staff). We look for people with unique perspectives and diverse backgrounds.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We have a great benefits package, including parental leave, contributions to your retirement, competitive pay, and unlimited time off. For U.S.-based employees, we also provide platinum-level health, dental, and vision coverage for you and your family.</span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EClPAFPeXIQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/protocol/0ddaf1df-805f-4772-bca0-aadff729b1e6/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/207125/protocol_loabs.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[protocollabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c4028873-6454-47fc-a65d-6c6d1ed8cb1f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineering Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.elliptic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Company description:</strong></p><p>As digital assets and cryptocurrency become more widely adopted every day,, our products are essential to ensure cryptocurrency is safe and accessible to all.  Our solutions help to prevent financial crime and allow cryptocurrencies to be used for good. Our products are used by some of the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, financial institutions and government agencies to screen over $1 billion of transactions every single week.  </p> <p>Elliptic is backed by some of the top VCs: SBI Group, Albion VC, Octopus Ventures, SignalFire, Paladin Capital, Santander InnoVentures, and Digital Currency Group, and we have grown globally with teams in the UK, USA, Singapore and Tokyo. </p> <p>To achieve our mission, we depend on our incredible team of Elliptites.  <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/life-at-elliptic" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Our values</a> are reflected in everything we do and every decision we make, both internally and outwardly to our customers.  We actively encourage Elliptities to challenge the status quo and allow the freedom to innovate and learn every day.  We encourage new ideas and learning, whether that’s through collaboration, our curiosity sessions, or utilising your professional development budget - personal growth is important to us all.  </p><p><strong>Do you want to be part of the future of value transfer?  Are you excited about solving problems that have never been solved before?  Do you take pride in empowering teams top build market leading products?</strong><br></p><p><strong>The impact you will have:</strong></p><p>You will be managing engineers and data scientists across several cross functional teams - giving them the support and guidance they need to grow along with the space they need to make decisions and own their own functional area.</p><p>Your contributions will shape the future of Elliptic and the crypto ecosystem.</p><p><strong>How you will grow:</strong></p><ul> <li>Supported by an industry leading engineering and data science teams, built around a culture of trust and failing fast, you will be challenged on a daily basis to move outside your comfort zone</li> <li>You will learn from a pool of highly experienced peers, in a rapidly growing engineering leadership function</li> <li>You have a generous personal development budget and the time and space to grow. Depending on how you learn, there are many options open:<ul> <li>Attend conferences</li> <li>Complete industry certifications</li> <li>Undertake training in technical and/or leadership spaces</li> <li>Have the time and space to try new tech with your team</li> <li>Participate in company hack days</li> </ul> </li> </ul><p><strong>What you will do in a typical week:</strong></p><ul> <li>Strategise on the future of engineering at Elliptic with your peers across the organisation</li> <li>Support your engineers and data scientists, emparting experience from your own experience and current best practices</li> <li>Help establishing a healthy culture embodying the company values to ensuring that expectations are set and work is delivered</li> <li>Promote knowledge sharing forums across engineering to ensure best practices exist and no silos build up</li> <li>Make it your business to know about each person in your organisation, what they want and how best they can develop</li> <li>Stay current, always maintaining a working understanding of what each of your teams are doing, so you are effectively able to support and represent them across the business.</li> </ul><p><strong>You will be a great fit here if you:</strong></p><ul> <li>Build strong teams around an environment of trust and empowerment</li> <li>Celebrate failure and share learnings widely</li> <li>Care deeply about the individuals on your teams and are rewarded by their growth</li> <li>Have strong opinions about engineering management best practices, and relish the debate about what works in given situations</li> <li>Are able to build lasting personal relationships atop a foundation of trust, vulnerability and openness</li> <li>Use data to make decisions, to understand what is slowing your teams down, what they need to succeed</li> <li>Are not afraid to fail, experiment often and learn quickly</li> <li>Are keen to learn new technologies and challenge existing tools, methodologies, processes</li> </ul> <p><strong>Our ideal candidate is:</strong></p><ul> <li>Experienced working within a fast-paced data environment</li> <li>Passionate about investing in individuals and supporting them to grow and succeed</li> <li>Experienced in leading several teams across diverse functional areas</li> <li>An accomplished line manager who has a track record of investing in individuals and seeing them succeed</li> <li>An engineer at heart who can still be hands on when they need to</li> </ul> <p><strong>Bonus Points for:</strong></p><ul> <li>Worked with data scientists in the past</li> <li>Enjoys discussing about data science, as well as engineering</li> <li>Understands the basics of crypto, and is interested in learning more</li> <li>Has gone through this scaling phase before, at any time in their career</li> <li>Has put together training and development plans for teams</li> </ul><ul> <li>Competitive salary</li> <li>26 days holiday + Bank Holidays</li> <li>Private health insurance and wellness program</li> <li>Pension plan</li> <li>EMI options</li> <li>Enhanced parental leave</li> <li>Career development plan &amp; personal training budget of $1000 per year plus LinkedIn Learning subscription</li> <li>Regular team events, including lunches, socials and quarterly team events</li> <li>Home office allowance</li> <li>All of the equipment you need to be successful</li> <li>Collaborative, flexible and friendly environment, with a truly hybrid working policy</li> </ul> <p>We know Diversity and Inclusion is much deeper than just hiring, but it’s important for us to mention it here.  We welcome and embrace individuals of all backgrounds and identities at Elliptic, and this is an ongoing priority for us.  We know incredible people don’t all think in the same way.  We want to be challenged every day.  We believe our diverse team of individuals underpins this by bringing creative thinking and innovation to Elliptic every day.  We are committed to creating a diverse, inclusive and equitable workplace, so we welcome applications from everyone, even if you may not think you fit all of the requirements of our roles.  We foster an environment of psychological safety, where everyone feels comfortable to bring their whole self to work. </p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ebOLNjlYiNg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/elliptic/j/F423DA54C2/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145877/elliptic.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[elliptic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[fefe721f-d5ba-4eb0-9b9b-f4156a27cb2b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[HR Coordinator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Strike]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://beta.strike.me/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Strike&#39;s mission is to build a more connected financial world.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strike allows users to send and receive money anywhere, instantly, with no fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strike is built on top of the Bitcoin network - the largest global, interoperable and open payments standard. Strike believes that open payment networks enable universal participation in the financial system, ushering in a new digital economy with truly borderless money transfers. Strike leverages Bitcoin’s open payment network to offer users the first global peer-to-peer payments app and a novel bitcoin-native neobanking experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Role:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strike is looking for an individual who can manage a high number of HR related processes simultaneously and flawlessly. The ideal candidate should be able to maintain HR systems that serve Strike Team Members, as well as answer benefits and almost any other employment-related questions with a smile while ensuring legal compliance.&lt;br&gt;The desired candidate will possess an acute proclivity for speed and be date-driven for completing tasks and reporting back to stakeholders and other team-members with haste.&lt;br&gt;The ideal candidate will possess excellent analytical, critical thinking, and writing skills and be able to thrive in a high case volume environment. The ideal candidate should thrive working in an ambitious startup environment and be excited about Strike’s mission and potential. You must be comfortable with a team-first approach in a remote work environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act as an administrator on our HRIS &amp;amp; Payroll system to field requests from Team Members regarding payroll-related questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain digital and electronic records of employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate leave of absences and maintain records of time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become fluent in the mechanics of the medical insurance programs to answer Team Member questions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform I-9 verification checks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform reference checks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Serve as a point of contact with benefit vendors and administrators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain our Learning Management System&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate training sessions and seminars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must be able handle sensitive information and must maintain the highest ethical standards&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Candidates who have performed this role will certainly be considered; however, being familiar with benefits and broad HR requirements is sufficient&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and exceptional organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being a customer-oriented team-player striving to please&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to take ownership of work products and consistently deliver results in a high-volume environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to respect deadlines in a fast paced environment and deliver constant and accurate reports to stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not make hiring decisions based on educational history whatsoever. Our Founder is a college dropout. We employ high school dropouts, PHD candidates and everything in-between. We do not hire credentials. We simply hire talented, passionate individuals who are excited to be a part of our team.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://strike.me/jobs?gh_jid=4308620004&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/712431/strike.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[strike@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[28384812-e332-465c-ba22-66f5df8ede20]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Strike]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineering Manager, Protocol]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://uniswap.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>The Uniswap Protocol is the largest decentralized trading and automated market making protocol (often called a DEX, “Decentralized Exchange”) on Ethereum.</div><div><br></div><div>The Uniswap Labs team was a major contributor to the Uniswap Protocol and now focuses on building a suite of products to support the Uniswap ecosystem. Our team is one of the most impactful in crypto. We are based out of SoHo in New York City with the option to be partially or fully remote depending on the position.</div><div><br></div><div>We're looking for an experienced engineering manager to help us grow our world-class protocol engineering team. You will focus on the people and process of Uniswap Labs engineering so that we can continue to ship great technical work. You're excited to support engineers and help them reach their full potential.</div><div><br></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Directly manage individual contributor engineers</li><li>Ensure the engineering team is able to deliver quality projects at a fast pace</li><li>Provide career growth advice and performance feedback</li><li>Focus on improving team processes</li><li>Recruit and hire new engineers to the team</li><li>Collaborate with product and design to deliver a roadmap</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Experience growing and managing a deeply technical team of engineers</li><li>High emotional intelligence</li><li>Technical knowledge to discuss issues, approaches, and solutions in depth</li><li>Knowledge and passion for software engineering best practices</li><li>Interest in crypto and basic Solidity exposure</li><br/>Nice to Haves<br/><li>Full-time experience in the Web3/crypto space</li><li>Willingness to work out of our NYC office regularly</li><li>Understanding of blockchain architecture</li><li>Previous experience with common dev tools in the space - Solidity, Ethers, etc</li><div>Uniswap Labs welcomes&nbsp;all qualified persons to apply regardless of race, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, disability, age, or veteran status. Compensation will be competitive and commensurate with experience. This is a full time role which includes health insurance and other benefits.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/Uniswap/0616b025-6eb8-43a4-ac1e-49d8cca90013/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/669325/uniswap-uni-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[uniswap@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b488dfbb-84b8-4efa-9d5d-2ced4e25769e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Contracts Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tron]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tron.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contracts Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitTorrent offers a unique and compelling work environment. We are proponents of the open Internet and we serve one of the largest user demographics in history. We take these responsibilities seriously and hire accordingly. We work with only the brightest engineers and the most talented business people we can find. Everyone on our team is here to do meaningful work with broad reaching impact. We have a fun yet challenging work environment that fosters diversity, creativity, and teamwork.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitTorrent’s legal department is looking for a high-performing&amp;nbsp; Contracts Manager to join our team. In this role, you will assume a wide range of responsibilities, all of which will require critical thinking, innovation, and integrity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Contracts Manager is responsible for drafting and negotiating various commercial agreements with BitTorrent’s customers and vendors. We are looking for someone with impeccable attention to detail, high energy, strong project management skills, outstanding oral and written negotiation skills, and a positive attitude.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who you are committed to being:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a positive attitude and ability to work in a fast-paced, high-output, team-oriented, practical environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You demonstrate enthusiasm for solving problems and adding value to the company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are courteous, flexible, highly organized, competent, reliable, proactive and use independent judgment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are committed to your personal growth and development by actively seeking feedback and responding with action&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are open and honest in communications with all stakeholders – legal colleagues, management, customers and others&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are a strong negotiator with a proven track record of success&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can manage highly confidential information with professionalism and unquestionable integrity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll own:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analyze and interpret complex provisions in commercial agreements&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Negotiation (both written and verbal) of complex sales, professional services and data privacy agreements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate with cross-functional teams during contract review, acting as a key contact for the legal department by providing guidance to internal and external customers on commonly requested edits, non-standard terms, policies, questions, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Review and revise complex, non-standard agreements to adhere to BitTorrent’s standard policies and procedures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage workflow for contract review process for a variety of contract types, beginning with receipt of requests for contract creation through routing for signatures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Execute assigned projects as determined by the needs of the legal department&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience you’ll need:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;6+ years of experience managing contracts (including drafting and negotiation) in a corporate environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s Degree with a strong academic record or equivalent work experience required; Master’s Degree or Juris Doctor preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please note: we are looking for someone who is licensed to practice law in the state of California&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage and deliver on a diverse and complex workload while maintaining priorities and proactively anticipating issues; particularly in a fast-paced corporate setting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Must be a creative problem solver and capable project manager with an eye to best practices in legal operations and the ability to balance getting the deal done while protecting the company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in oral negotiations, project management, risk awareness, and issue escalation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong business acumen with the ability to clearly recognize risk elements in business transactions, providing advice to operations teams in carrying out the terms of the contract, as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient in Word and Excel&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with contract databases and integration&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with electronic signature software, e.g., EchoSign, Docusign&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Apply today if this is for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/gU6Jfz2jOHA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/rainberry/jobs/5858318002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180174/300px-Tron_logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tron@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f44423ad-b7da-465f-8880-ebeb8930922a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tron]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Client Services Representative]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[MetalPay]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.metalpay.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Are you looking to be a part of one of the most influential companies in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div>At Metal, we are shaping digital money and revolutionizing the way people transact by building the decentralized financial infrastructure of the future. To date, we have launched and operate Metal Pay (digital banking and crypto wallet) and Proton SDK a distributed ledger for identity and interaction with the card and banking payments settlement layer.</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">As we continue to expand, we are seeking a solutions-oriented Client Services Representative, who is passionate about our customers and loves to innovate customer-centric strategies. The landscape in cryptocurrency is evolving, and this is a chance to help guide our customers on the Metal Pay and Proton products and services as we unlock the future of payments. We’re a lean and collegial team in which every role matters, and you’ll have a big impact on high-stakes decisions, working across the enterprise with Compliance, Community, Marketing, business, and technical teams in pioneering innovative financial services solutions.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">You will have demonstrated the ability to understand key metrics pertaining to basic customer service factors. You will be given ample opportunity to broaden your skills and strengthen your existing talents within and outside the team and must be able to succeed in a high-direction, low-supervision environment.</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Develop and demonstrate a thorough understanding of the market, product, and customer needs</li><li>Process technical and non-technical inquiries from our customers and find ways to decrease ticket processing time</li><li>Assist directly or route customers to the appropriate personnel for assistance</li><li>Ensure customer satisfaction by meeting customer needs in a courteous and timely manner</li><li>Provide excellent customer service through the omnichannel services provided in a timely manner in accordance with SLAs</li><li>Work with the Client Services team to draft and update template responses and Knowledge Base Articles outside of the Community Manager’s scope</li><li>Assist Client Services team to compile data for analytics and trends that lead to operational efficiencies</li><li>Be driven by metrics and key performance indicators to make informed and strategic decisions to achieve your team’s goals and Metal’s mission while maintaining our corporate values</li><li>Participate in cross-functional initiatives working with product managers, Community, and Marketing to design the best customer experience portal as well as in-product (contextual help)</li><li>Assist in developing cross-functional internal stakeholder partnerships between KYC analyst(s), Community Manager, Marketing, and senior management to identify opportunities for process and strategic enhancements</li><li>Analyze customer complaints and provide appropriate corrective actions</li><li>Assist in collecting relevant data for periodic metrics to management</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>2+ years of customer service or customer support experience</li><li>You have a passion for crypto and want to learn more</li><li>Previous experience in personal banking or at Fintech </li><li>Startup experience preferred</li><li>You have experience in email/chat-based customer service channels</li><li>Demonstrated experience working in customer-centric environments and have a passion for customer service excellence</li><li>Strong written and verbal communication skills</li><li>Comfortable working with Google suite (Docs, Sheets, Slides, etc)</li><li>Strong time management skills &amp; analytical skills</li><li><b>Language Requirements - English and German</b></li><li><b>Shift Details: Morning/Day shift (CET timezone) during Weekday and Weekends&nbsp;</b></li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/NL19PxnvygQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/metalpay/ca3ecfea-f72b-475a-ba84-c29c7bdb1fc4/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145800/metal.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[metal@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b7a50291-0f8e-47e0-a91b-6502b21fa6a2]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[MetalPay]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineering Director, Quality Assurance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chronicled]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://chronicled.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Chronicled has established the decentralized MediLedger Network, which connects the pharmaceutical industry and runs mission critical processes. You will be working on the software that connects to and runs the Network. You will be building a cutting-edge platform using the latest technological achievements at the intersection of blockchain, cryptography, distributed computing and network protocols.</div><div><br></div><div><b>The opportunity</b></div><div>As Director of Quality Assurance you will own the overall quality of distributed software that supports mission critical functions of Fortune 100 companies. As a hands-on leader in the organization you will be driving quality efforts, leading by example, coaching peers, and working with a talented team to build an event-driven, enterprise grade solution based on microservices.</div><br/>What you'll do: <br/><li>Own the end-to-end quality of complete enterprise solutions</li><li>Drive a coherent test strategy and comprehensive methodology across multiple application services and engineering teams</li><li>Oversee test planning and execution by leveraging strong project management skills</li><li>Actively participate in design reviews to ensure appropriate test coverage and test methods</li><li>Drive a comprehensive test automation strategy in partnership with the Engineering Teams</li><li>Influence software teams to raise the bar on quality deliverables, and ensure that features and bug fixes come with automated test coverage</li><li>Own, measure and report on security, performance, scalability and resiliency of the software</li><li>Generate coverage metrics, quality reports and trends for Engineering Managers, Executives, Product Team and internal stakeholders</li><li>Hire and develop a world-class QA team</li><li>Evangelize Quality Assurance processes while implementing water tight Quality Control checkpoints</li><br/>What you'll need: <br/><li>Experience in establishing and iteratively improving company-wide processes</li><li>Experience in test automation, performance and resiliency testing</li><li>Proficiency in designing and building world class test automation infrastructure for synchronous and asynchronous APIs, and UI</li><li>Proficiency in project management and designing test plans</li><li>Experience with testing enterprise-grade solutionsFamiliarity with modern technologies such as TypeScript, Java, Postgres, RabbitMQ and React</li><li>Proven work in fast-paced environments </li><li>Experience working with Enterprise Saas solutions </li><li>At least 3 years of experience of management in addition to at least 4 years of hands-on software engineering experience</li><li>Startup experience a plus </li><li>BS in Computer Science or equivalent experience</li><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">At Chronicled we take pride in our Total Rewards Package which is available to all full time Chronicled Employees:</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Competitive Rewards</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: Comprehensive and competitive employment and rewards packages for all employees</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Full benefits</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: Medical, Dental, Vision. 401k</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Equipment</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: Macbook pro and accessories standard issue. </span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Location</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: Centrally located and easily accessible offices in San Francisco and Vancouver with remote employees worldwide!</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Flexibility</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: We believe flexibility comes in multiple forms. Freedom to express yourself with an open startup casual dress code, Flexible schedules. Best of all we have an unlimited vacation policy that allows you to get the rest and relaxation you need to refresh.</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Welcoming Culture</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: We call ourselves a family for a reason. We foster a fun and creative atmosphere where anyone can openly contribute ideas, feel appreciated, and feel empowered to be who they are. Fun is also highly encouraged! </span><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Recognition</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: Respect and prominence due to work contributions, working on cutting edge technology. Our team is celebrated and recognized for their contributions</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Variety:</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt"> Opportunities to experience different job tasks, responsibilities, and project opportunities</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Workload</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: Challenging and fast paced work making a real impact utilizing blockchain technology.</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Work Importance</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: The typical Chronicled team member has a bias for action. We do. We build. We step outside of the scope. We believe we will change the world.</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Control your own Destiny</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: Ability to influence others and control one’s own destiny.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Advancement</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">: Opportunities to get ahead both personally and professionally.</span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/5MArmZpzU68" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/chronicled-2/d08a066b-c21f-476e-8a6a-34295edd662a/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/301749/chronicled.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chronicled@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d44ed840-83fb-4e02-8dd2-2347727f060d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chronicled]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Embedded C Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ava Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.avalabs.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avalanche is an open-source platform for launching decentralized finance applications and enterprise blockchain deployments in one interoperable, highly scalable ecosystem. Developers who build on Avalanche can easily create powerful, reliable, and secure applications and custom blockchain networks with complex rulesets or build on existing private or public subnets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded by the creators of Avalanche, Ava Labs makes it simple to launch finance applications using blockchain technology–with highly scalable and efficient networks, customizable public and private blockchains, the capability to create any digital asset, and more. We are empowering people to build an open, simple, and democratic internet of finance that enables the world to have a more prosperous future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop hardware crypto-wallet integrations across multiple hardware device type(s) in the industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver well-designed, high performing, software for hardware wallet integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Launch new features and new hardware wallet integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the Wallet team, advise, and develop on wallet-specific features&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test, debug, troubleshoot, and deploy solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;WHAT YOU WILL BRING&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with embedded software development in C for Linux or UNIX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Javascript for testing purposes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated strength in debugging, troubleshooting, and testing embedded OS-based software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Established proficiency in cryptographic protocols, signature schemes, ciphers, threat modeling, and security best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with software reverse-engineering or debugging tools, GDB ideal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience on microcontrollers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY AVA LABS?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re a world-class team of experts in computer science, economics, finance, and law with offices in New York City and Miami. We&#39;re passionate individuals creating a frictionless world by redefining the way people build and use finance applications. &lt;/span&gt;The company has received funding from Andreessen Horowitz, Initialized Capital, and Polychain Capital, with angel investments from Balaji Srinivasan and Naval Ravikant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ava Labs is committed to diversity in the workplace and we’re proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. We do not hire on basis of race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, citizenship, age, disability, veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, or any other basis protected by local, state or federal law. All employment is decided on the basis of qualifications, merit, and business need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/mWBzFmzzBAg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/avalabs/jobs/4313185004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/571953/avalabs-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[avalabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[a4029032-6a83-4107-89a8-330ee9cccbd1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ava Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Executive Assistant]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Axoni]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://axoni.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Axoni is building the next generation of capital markets technology. Our solutions are used by the world’s leading banks, asset managers, hedge funds, and infrastructure providers. Our diverse team focuses every day on our goal of building products that will change and improve how our clients and the markets will interact.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are seeking talented, motivated professionals that want to be part of this once-in-a-career opportunity to not only see, but also drive the incredible changes coming to global capital markets. We are building a culture where our team feels valued and everyone is given an opportunity to grow and succeed. We try to live by our Core Values and demonstrate what we believe represent the kind of company we are working to build. These Values are: Delivery is everything; Choose Kindness; Be better every day.</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 15px">Axoni is looking for an Executive Assistant who will support multiple executives at Axoni.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><b>Objectives of this Role</b></div><div>With a primary responsibility of supporting the executives, the EA will work closely with the executive team and other EA(s) to ensure that the executive team’s priorities and needs are met and that operations run smoothly and efficiently&nbsp;. Manage communication between upper management and employees as well as liaising with external executives, clients and vendors&nbsp;. Maintain and refine internal processes on behalf of the executives to ensure&nbsp; company-wide goals and objectives are accomplished&nbsp;</div><br/>As an Executive Assistant, you will:<br/><li>Manage administrative duties for the executives, including meetings, agendas, mail, email, calls, travel arrangements, client management, and other company logistics</li><li>Manage the various calendars with extensive scheduling and conflict resolution&nbsp;</li><li>Act as the gatekeeper to senior executives and prioritize the flow of information and communication&nbsp;</li><li>Arrange, coordinate and manage senior executives’ travel and travel-related activities, including hotel booking, transportation, and meal coordination</li><li>Perform administrative and office support, such as typing, dictation, spreadsheet and presentation creation, faxing, and maintenance of filing system and contact database</li><li>Maintain professionalism and strict confidentiality with all materials, and exercise discretion when interfacing with the business</li><li>Help organize team communications and plan events, both internally and offsite</li><li>Assist with light office responsibilities as needed&nbsp;</li><br/>We're looking for: <br/><li>4+ years experience in administrative role reporting directly to upper management</li><li>Superb written and verbal communication skills</li><li>Strong time-management skills and the ability to organize and coordinate multiple projects at once</li><li>Proficiency in Microsoft Office and other office productivity tools, with aptitude to learn new software and systems</li><li>Flexible team player willing to do what it takes to get the job done; adaptable and enjoys a challenge</li><li>Ability to keep company confidences</li><div>Individuals seeking employment at Axoni are considered without regards to race, color, religion, national origin, age, sex, marital status, ancestry, physical or mental disability, veteran status, gender identity, or sexual orientation. You are being given the opportunity to provide the following information in order to help us comply with federal and state Equal Employment Opportunity/Affirmative Action record keeping, reporting, and other legal requirements.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xO7B4WYKVZE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axoni/29daa31b-c191-4ad1-a747-3ce4712adbb5/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145318/axoni.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axoni@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b96c34e0-5c46-4ec2-8e42-397e29857c6f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Axoni]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Administrative / Office Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Data analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKEx]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.okex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;job-preview__description &quot; data-test-description=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About OKX:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKX is a world-leading digital asset trading platform, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKX provides hundreds of token &amp;amp; futures trading pairs to help traders to optimize their strategy. We are also one of the top digital asset trading platforms by trading volume, serving millions of users in over 100 countries. OKX derivatives remains a top-notch venue globally and has a daily volume of approximately $10 billion and is widely recognized as the golden standard in the industry. We believe the blockchain technology will eliminate barriers to transactions, increase the efficiency of transactions across society, and eventually have a significant impact on the global economy. We strive to make innovative achievements that change the world and never stop to improve on our customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the team/role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Senior Data Analyst to join our Support Product Squad. This role will work closely with the Product, Design, Ops and Engineering teams that are focused on creating a global chatbot led conversational support strategy. This is a very dynamic role in which one day you will find yourself running workshops, defining data requirements and scoping requirements to meet product strategy; another day you might be conducting research, data analysis or transcript reviews.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Converting raw conversational and customer support data into insights that will lead to informed business decisions and high quality product backlog.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating, developing, and applying machine learning approaches to conversational decision making and dialogue management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interpreting data and analysing results using statistical techniques.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducting analysis of operational and conversational data to provide insight into current processes, agent behaviour and automation opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing knowledge graphs to represent customer support topics and improving service scope of chatbots and efficacy of FAQ and self-support content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysing large scale conversational datasets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being comfortable in applying analysis results to multiple global languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Using expert knowledge of state-of-the-art methods and tools to consistently find the most effective, efficient, stable, explainable, and elegant approaches.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use and present research findings in ways that inform and sometimes guide business and product strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A mathematical ability to analyse, model and interpret data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years research and/or work experience with Natural Language Processing (either text or voice)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of NLU (natural language understanding) and NLG (Natural Language Generation) technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong proven problem-solving skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience using open source data, functions and libraries for data science and machine learning is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of creating and maintaining labelled dataset out of unstructured conversational transcripts is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and ability to tell product stories using data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Written and spoken proficiency in multiply languages is a plus with an added advantage if proficient in Mandarin.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/x9kSkBMcOuo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okx/jobs/4936742003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175406/okex.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bcbc2afc-a2fd-45d8-bba3-e7ce4b53b3d8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKEx]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Project Manager (PMO)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOHK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://iohk.io]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>We are searching for an experienced Project Manager to work closely with the Head of Project Management Office operations and senior stakeholders from departments across the business, to set up and execute the delivery of PMO standards.</p> <p>This role is ideal for someone with five or more years of project management experience who wants to develop their skills and experience. It is a great opportunity to support and influence the direction of the PMO standards at IOG as we expand to take on more commercial projects for customers. </p> <p>You will help set up and implement PMO/Project standards, processes and practices according to the project life cycle. You will thrive in an environment where you are the glue that brings a project team together. You will help set the standards for managing projects within IOG and work closely with HR to develop training processes for project managers. You will document and align IOG standards for project management.</p><p><strong>Your mission </strong></p><ul> <li>Set up and implement IOG PMO/Project standards for project management</li> <li>Support the development of the PMO function, specifically Enterprise Reporting Systems and Jira</li> <li>Report on project status across the company</li> <li>Provide management and teams with a consistent and comprehensive view of project status</li> <li>Work with relevant parties to set standards for training project managers within IOG.</li> </ul><p><strong>Your expertise  </strong></p> <ul> <li>Five or more years of experience working in a variety of software development projects with full SDLC</li> <li>Solid understanding of software project delivery and project delivery methodologies</li> <li>The ability to understand the following roles: Product Owner, Project Manager, Scrum Master, Business Analyst</li> <li>The ability to support core PMO functions for an organization; ie, PMO Standards, delivery dashboards, high-level plans (milestones), risks and issues, dependencies, change control, decision logging, resource and project progress status</li> <li>Project management tools such as PMP, PRINCE2 are desirable</li> <li>Expert in Jira and Confluence, Scrum, Kanban</li> <li>Qualified Senior Agile coach to provide training to PM’s and project leaders is desirable</li> <li>Experience in technology, engineering, or business.</li> </ul><p><strong>Location</strong></p><p>IOG is a fully distributed organization and therefore this is a remote position. Due to team distribution we are ideally searching for someone in a UK/ Ireland timezone.  </p><p><strong>All Colleagues</strong></p><ul> <li>Flexible schedule</li> <li>Remote work - ability to work anywhere</li> <li>Laptop reimbursement</li> <li>New starter package to buy hardware essentials (headphones, monitor, etc)</li> <li>Learning &amp; Development Opportunities</li> <li>Competitive PTO and Sick Leave plan</li> </ul><p><strong>US Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits coverage through Anthem with 100% premium cost covered by IO Global for the employee and dependents</li> <li>Health Savings Account</li> <li>Life Insurance</li> </ul><p><strong>UK Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Monthly Health Stipend to use towards any wellness or medical coverage/service</li> <li>Pension</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EM-XkuQdUq8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/io-global/j/0E61B9991F/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143583/iohk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iohk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b89f946-6d3b-434f-aa32-f0e84ecb2992]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOHK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Associate, Communications]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gemini empowers individuals through crypto by providing simple, reliable and secure ways for people to buy, sell and store cryptocurrency. We are a globally regulated cryptocurrency exchange and custodian with a focus on product, security, licensing and compliance.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;In 2020, Gemini launched our full services in the UK - our first international market outside the US - after securing our Electronic Money Institutions license and Cryptoasset registration from the Financial Conduct Authority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cryptocurrency and blockchain technology have the power to transform the world for good. This truth, along with our core values, form the bedrock of our company and culture. At Gemini, no job is too small and no project too big as we endeavour to build the future of money. We are a mission-driven, team-based, inclusive, and determined community of thought leaders who invest in each other and the long game. Join us in our mission!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Department: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marketing and Communications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We believe that the world should know and love Gemini. In Communications, we spend our days crafting the Gemini story and telling it to the people who need to hear it. This team sits between our product and the market, and is a key growth driver for every aspect of the organisation. We have a holistic philosophy that combines data, integrated communications, including owned content, including our blogs and social media, paid content and earned media and all aspects of consumer &amp;amp; customer-facing communications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Role:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gemini is seeking an experienced, hands-on Senior Associate to execute and manage an integrated communications strategy to support our fast-growing retail and institutional offerings in the UK and Europe. In this role you will drive clear media narratives about our products, brand, strategy, and vision, connecting with national and international news agendas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Senior Associate will design and implement campaigns - including overall strategy and tactical plans - with the goal of increasing brand awareness and customer acquisition. You will be a great team player, and will work cross-functionally with teams including business development, strategy, product, engineering, marketing, customer support and communications to ensure that all communications activities align with regulatory requirements, support roadmaps, and advance business objectives.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Communications is a small department, so the successful candidate will be comfortable flexing between strategy and tactical execution and will be required to act nimbly, taking on tasks large and small.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The Senior Associate will report to the Director of Marketing and Communications and help to manage an external agency.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Aligned to Gemini’s business strategy and local market research, help create and implement communications plans to launch new products and services, expand into new markets, and announce partnerships, thought leadership, and other updates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactively develop Gemini’s media commentary programme through designing and executing campaigns, supported by content, that increase our share of voice on relevant industry issues and deliver quality pieces of coverage. Ensure tight coordination with local marketing objectives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help provide day-to-day guidance to the external PR agency, with the direction of the Director of Marketing and Communications. Help ensure agency activities are structured, strategic, and delivered on-time and on-budget.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working with the UK PR agency and Communications team, continue to build Gemini’s media relationships in the region, including through networking and background meetings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Effectively evaluate and manage inbound media requests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate and facilitate media interviews and other interactions with external stakeholders in an appropriate manner.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Prepare spokespeople, providing briefing documents and Gemini messaging, and offering interview techniques.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage a pipeline of high quality events that drive brand awareness and customer acquisition. Secure organic speaking opportunities for business leadership and identify paid event sponsorships and partnerships to promote the Gemini brand.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support Gemini spokespeople to attend events, including helping with networking, media and other practical activities on the ground.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create and run exceptional Gemini-owned events, from live events to virtual webinars, to support business development activities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Successfully deliver on communications objectives relating to major brand and sports partnerships, for example, the Gemini Boat Race.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create and manage a pipeline of target awards, including working cross-functionally to research opportunities and manage submissions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support on defining and evolving the internal communications strategy in the region.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop our social media strategy to increase awareness of our international presence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage, create and write a wide range of communications materials and assets, including press releases, messaging, reactive statements, quotations, talking points, blogs, bylines, Q&amp;amp;As, social media content, presentations, sponsored media ad copy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help measure and demonstrate the effectiveness of Gemini’s communications activities in the region.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor&#39;s degree or equivalent work experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in communications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven ability to develop plans independently and implement them&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects at once while maintaining composure and flexibility under tight deadlines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building strong relationships internally across cross functional teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exceptional writing skills and proven ability to distill complex technical information into media and customer-friendly language&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exemplary professionalism, strong judgment, and discretion, especially when under tight deadlines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing relationships with external agencies/press&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A proven portfolio of media campaigns that have been featured on high quality sites at a national level&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience building and managing comms strategy for the financial services and/or high growth technology industries&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in communications in the regulated finance, tech or fintech space with app and web products desirable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience launching disruptive technology products in a new market&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-ED1&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/70jrfYSxKC4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3862130&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer (Backend), Blockchain OS]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BitGo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.bitgo.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Toronto, Canada Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitGo is the leader in custody and security solutions with over $60B in assets under custody. Founded in 2013, BitGo is the first digital asset company to focus exclusively on serving institutional clients. In 2018, it launched BitGo Trust Company, the first qualified custodian purpose-built for storing digital assets and established BitGo New York Trust in 2021. BitGo also offers market leading trading, lending, and borrowing services and supports over 400 digital assets on its platform. BitGo provides the security and operational backbone for more than 500 institutional clients in 50 countries, including many of the world’s top cryptocurrency exchanges and platforms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitGo is looking for a Senior Software Engineer to join our Blockchain OS team and help us build highly reliable and scalable systems. This role can be worked remotely so long as your home base is metro Toronto, Canada (exceptional candidates outside of Toronto are encouraged to apply).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Capable of designing and implementing full system architectures with an emphasis on redundancy, scalability and durability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with other engineers and take responsibility for all facets of the development process, while actively participating in design and code reviews.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design and build strong, resilient, and robust APIs to power our application services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and coordinate software unit testing and system testing and validation procedures, and documentation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide support and mentor team members to improve overall team velocity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide maintenance support and enhance performance to existing application code&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor and troubleshoot production software issues and provide solutions while being a part of on-call rotation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own functionality and scalability features by taking responsibility from inception to deployment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expose and document functionality to the UI, third-party developers, and our internal and external tooling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Capable of building proofs-of-concept(POC) with fellow engineers and/or stakeholders while ensuring the current milestones are met&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Follow legal policies as directed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Experience&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for teammates who share and practice our values: open communication, transparency, taking ownership, and a high level of craftsmanship. We are looking for coworkers who share our vision and mission: deliver trust in digital assets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum of 5 years in building enterprise level applications on a cross-functional Agile Software Development team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong development experience with any of the JVM languages, preferably Java or Kotlin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building web services, preferably using REST&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Development experience building microservices in Spring&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Asynchronous messaging technologies such as Apache Kafka, JMS&amp;nbsp; or RabbitMQ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience developing SaaS applications in the cloud, preferably AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong relational database experience&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong work ethics and willingness to work hard to achieve employer objectives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong teamwork and communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in an agile development environment with continuous integration and continuous delivery, using tools such as Git, Docker and Kubernetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with production troubleshooting and analysis using log/debugging tools such as Grafana, ELK, Splunk or New Relic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Web technologies e.g. JavaScript / TypeScript / React / Node&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with NoSQL databases, preferably Mongo&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency with IDE-based development, especially in IntelliJ or Eclipse&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of and strong interest in cryptocurrencies and blockchain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Why Join BitGo?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Disrupting an industry takes vision, innovation, passion, technical chops, drive to deliver, collaboration, and execution. Join a team of great people who strive for excellence and personify our corporate values of ownership, craftsmanship, and open communication. We are looking for new colleagues who bring innovative ways of thinking and problem solving, and who want risks to be part of the team that changes the world’s financial markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Here are some of the benefits* of working at BitGo:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive base salary, bonus and stock options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% company paid health insurance for employee, partner and dependents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Up to 4% 401k company match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paid parental leave, Paid vacation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Free custom lunches, dinners and snacks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Computer equipment and workplace furniture to suit your needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great colleagues and inspiring startup environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;*Benefits may vary based on location&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Cryptocurrencies are the most disruptive change the financial services industry has seen in years. Join us and you’ll be able to look back and say you were part of the team that transformed investing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yGR7NLjXslU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitgo/jobs/5872702002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175514/birgo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitgo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b720d671-6d88-4863-a59d-ea5d1c6feea8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BitGo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Social and Community Manager (NFT)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - United Kingdom, London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Manage NFT social account and deliver high quality content to promote NFT drops and updates from platform;</li><li>Design campaigns to drive user growth and engagement, partnering with different stakeholders to run cross campaigns on social media</li><li>Manage Binance NFT community(including telegram, discord but not limited to) to engage and educate users&nbsp;</li><li>Run AMA and online show in community to introduce and promote different NFT drops and educational content</li><li>Plan, develop and deliver high-quality, engaging campaigns to attract new users and boost community engagement</li><li>Work with Angels to collect feedbacks from community to refine service NFT platform offer</li><li>Partner with Binance’s business units and local teams to drive and execute user-growth marketing campaigns for local and global markets.</li><li>Work with Paid MKT team to run ads&nbsp;</li><li>Collect feedbacks and work with product team to optimize platform</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Native or Fluent English language is a MUST</li><li>Would be a bonus if the candidate also has strong written &amp; communication skills in Chinese&nbsp;</li><li>2 - 3 years of experience in digital marketing and community managing related roles in crypto industry&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Highly organised and comfortable working across time zones and multiple projects</li><li>A basic understanding of public relations in general</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/dd061353-35ae-49cc-9a8e-b5e932652f15/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Trading Operation]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://blockchain.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Miami, Remote (US)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p class=&quot;p1&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain.com is the world&#39;s leading software platform for digital assets. Offering the largest production blockchain platform in the world, we share the passion to code, create, and ultimately build an open, accessible and fair financial future, one piece of software at a time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p2&quot;&gt;Head of Trading Operations reporting to the CFO. The head of trading operations will be responsible for the oversight and coordination of all institutional trade and loan processes.&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p3&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Hire and manage global financial operations team&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Responsible for all daily financial operations to ensure settlements of trades and loans&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Designs systems and processes for efficient and accurate financial operations including integration of OMS, PMS, transfer, custody Liasse with client services to ensure there is a transparent and accurate life of a trade or loan&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Reconciliation between exchange/ bank accounts and internal portfolio management system Escalating exceptions and trade breaks where appropriate&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Manage the internal security master to ensure counterparties, instruments, new accounts are setup properly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p2&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;The foremost quality for this position or any position at Blockchain.com is integrity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Finance or Accounting or similar educational background required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Asset management background preferred but not required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li5&quot;&gt;Strong finance background with particular experience in securities trade operations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;10+ years working in industry or financial services with prior experience focusing on trade operations, middle office, and reconciliations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Strong presentation and communication skills when working with internal teams and external vendors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Excellent&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;attention to detail and ability to work as a team to identify process improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Capacity to meet deadlines while maintaining quality standards and effective time management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Ability to work collaboratively with a broad range of business functions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Adapt to a fast-paced continuous learning environment and show a willingness to take on additional responsibility where required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li5&quot;&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li5&quot;&gt;Excellent organization, project management and analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li6&quot;&gt;Demonstrated ability to work autonomously, coordinate the efforts of others and work well with people at a wide range of levels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p8&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPENSATION &amp;amp; PERKS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Unlimited vacation policy; work hard and take time when you need it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Apple equipment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Full-time salary based on experience and meaningful equity in an industry-leading company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li8&quot;&gt;US Benefits: Medical, Dental, Vision, 401K, Flexible Spending Account, Commuter, Life, Short Term &amp;amp; Long Term Disability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p8&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;APPLICATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li3&quot;&gt;Resume/CV and LinkedIn profile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li8&quot;&gt;Your favorite GIF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain/jobs/3882251?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180745/blockchaininc.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchaininc@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5457bd3d-b464-4d43-bfd6-5c9d9e62930e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Trading ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, Compliance Monitoring and Testing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Circle]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.circle.com/de/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Los Angeles - will also consider remote in US]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Circle is a global financial technology firm that enables businesses of all sizes to harness the power of digital currency and public blockchains for payments, commerce and financial applications worldwide. Circle platforms and products provide a suite of internet-native financial services for payments, treasury infrastructure and capital formation. Circle is also a principal developer of USD Coin (USDC), which has become the fastest growing dollar digital currency in the world. USDC has grown to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;over 47 billion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in circulation and supported over&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; $1.6 trillion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in transactions in the past year. Circle’s payments and treasury infrastructure services available through the Circle Account and APIs helps bridge the legacy financial system and digital currency and blockchain based finance.&amp;nbsp; Circle’s SeedInvest service brings internet-native fundraising and capital formation to startups and growth companies.&amp;nbsp; Combined, Circle’s suite of services helps companies to participate in a more open, global and inclusive financial system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be part of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;With the mission “To raise global economic prosperity through the frictionless exchange of financial value,” Circle was founded on the belief that the internet, blockchains and digital currency will rewire the global economic system, creating a fundamentally more open, inclusive, efficient and integrated world economy.&amp;nbsp; We envision a global economy where people and businesses everywhere can more freely connect and transact with each other with new technologies for digital money and internet-native finance. We believe such a system can raise prosperity for people and companies everywhere. Our mission is powered by the values we espouse and which we expect all Circlers to respect. We are Multistakeholder, serving the needs of our customers, our shareholders, our employees and families, our local communities and our world. Furthermore, we are also Mindful, Driven by Excellence, and High Integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be responsible for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As part of the Compliance Programs team, you will help to create a central global function focused on developing a best in class compliance management system, which will support all regional and core compliance team functions. This team is responsible for compliance risk management through a combination of development, assessment and oversight of key compliance programs throughout Circle.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Specifically, as a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; key second line of defense role, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you will be responsible for the development and execution of a risk-based monitoring and testing program to ensure Circle’s compliance with applicable laws, regulations, policies and procedures. This position will work with the business and compliance/risk peers to establish and maintain appropriate testing forums, testing schedules, and status reporting of all testing activity.&amp;nbsp; You will provide oversight and make recommendations that significantly impact Circle’s ability to monitor regulatory compliance programs, minimize operational risk and align with evolving regulatory expectations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll work on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define the strategy and design the program&amp;nbsp; for a risk-based regulatory compliance monitoring &amp;amp; testing framework to provide independent,monitoring and testing of Circle’s Compliance programs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and deliver the annual Compliance Monitoring &amp;amp; Testing plan, ensuring coverage for existing and new regulations, changes to existing regulations and any audit or exam findings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage all daily aspects of Circle’s Compliance Monitoring &amp;amp; Testing Program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and oversee a team of testers who are executing the monitoring and testing program, including priority setting, coaching team members, reviewing workpapers for accuracy, completeness, and conformance with standards and methodology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure second line monitoring reviews are delivered on time and to an appropriate standard of quality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Oversee the tracking of corrective action plans and effectively challenge and manage the satisfactory resolution of issues, including ensuring adequate remediation plans and validation to ensure proper and timely resolution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify, assess, effectively challenge and oversee the satisfactory resolution of issues, including ensuring adequate management remediation plans and validation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with program owners, subject matter experts and all relevant stakeholders to understand requirements (e.g. laws, regulations, guidelines, policies) of compliance, enterprise programs and products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Evaluate design and operating effectiveness of controls, assess identified findings, determine root causes, propose risk ratings in accordance with internal guidelines and standards, and draft recommendations and reports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Document test results, and reporting metrics in GRC Tool and/or central repository.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage the assignment and execution of closure verification testing to ensure testing conforms to guidelines and standards, workpapers are complete and accurate, and the testing is completed in a timely manner.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with the business to strengthen compliance maturity for programs and products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Prepare testing scope, work papers, and reports capturing final results of testing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and document detailed testing scripts covering testing of controls evaluations and testing of transactions to assess adherence to compliance/risk rules.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure testing engagements and other assignments are completed within established timeframes, and/or provide early escalation of anticipated delays to senior management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Execute, organize and prioritize testing in a timely manner ensuring deliverables are achieved. while maintaining accuracy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will aspire to our four core values:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multistakeholder - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you have dedication and commitment to our customers, shareholders, employees and families and local communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mindful - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek to be respectful, an active listener and to pay attention to detail.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driven by Excellence - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you are driven by our mission and our passion for customer success which means you relentlessly pursue excellence, that you do not tolerate mediocrity and you work intensely to achieve your goals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Integrity - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek open and honest communication, and you hold yourself to very high moral and ethical standards.&amp;nbsp; You reject manipulation, dishonesty and intolerance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll bring to Circle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;12+ years relevant experience in compliance, internal audit or related discipline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;7+ years leading and managing a team of direct reports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Detailed knowledge of compliance standards as they relate to OFAC, AML, KYC, Card Brand, money transmission, payments and e-money.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Prior hands-on experience designing and establishing a monitoring and testing role within Compliance Testing or Internal Audit, preferably in a BSA/AML/OFAC capacity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Compliance experience in either banking, consulting, or cryptocurrency required. Experience in RegTech or Fintech preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong communication, planning and project management skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establishes trust and collaboration with cross-functional stakeholders and team members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong attention to detail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent ability to investigate, analyze, and interpret data as well as state and federal regulations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated understanding of and passion for harnessing the power of digital currency and blockchain technology and services built on top of it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working hands-on with other cross-functional team leaders, such as lawyers, engineers, product managers, data analysts, operations analysts in improving compliance processes and systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience and comfort working in an ever-changing industry and the flexibility to quickly react to changing demands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience/familiarity with Slack, Apple MacOS and GSuite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;equal opportunity employer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and value diversity at Circle. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 style=&quot;text-align: right;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/KEvenCaIq70" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/circle/jobs/5875179002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143132/circle.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[circle@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[e4722b14-c590-4410-b876-45bc581c49c8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Circle]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Global Talent Acquisition Specialist - Fintech Start-up]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Australia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>About Crypto.com</p><p>Crypto.com was founded in 2016 on a simple belief: it's a basic human right for everyone to control their money, data and identity. With over 10+ million users on its platform today, Crypto.com provides a powerful alternative to traditional financial services, turning its vision of "cryptocurrency in every wallet" into reality, one customer at a time. Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have  ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance. Crypto.com is headquartered in Singapore with a 3000 strong team. For more information, please visit www.crypto.com.</p><p><br></p><p>About the role</p><p>You will be joining our Recruiting team to supporting our global expansion. In order to place Crypto.com as one of the best place to work in the region, you will work closely with our leadership team, execute our regional talent acquisition strategies and initiatives, from sourcing to onboarding the best talents in this space. Besides the recruitment activity, you will also be responsible for project managing the entire recruiting pipeline for the company. This is an excellent opportunity for someone looking to broaden their recruiting experience and enhance their project management skills in a goal oriented, fast-paced, high growth startup environment.</p><p><br></p><p>Responsibilities</p><ul> <li>Support of Crypto.com’s talent search and engagement strategy, including Employer Branding as well as end-to-end talent acquisition process from sourcing to onboarding</li> <li>Manage company-wide recruitment timeline, and meet the defined hiring KPI and objectives</li> <li>Work with Talent Acquisition team define the profiles and scope of responsibilities for specific roles based on immediate organization needs, as well as design and implement winning sourcing strategies to fill critical positions</li> <li>Successfully manage talent searches on a predefined timeline, set benchmarks and metrics, identify bottlenecks, as well as understand how to prioritize in a fast-paced environment, with tight deadlines</li> <li>Execute and support recruitment and onboarding activities in a timely and effective manner</li> <li>Be an active member of the HR partnership; sharing insights on organizational structure, recruitment strategy and HR plans with management</li> <li>This role will be mainly focusing regional recruitment positions including executive hires and technology hires</li> </ul><ul> <li>BA/BS degree or equivalent practical experience</li> <li>1 year of experience in a recruitment related position</li> <li>Support Talent Acquisition team by successfully managing talent searches on a predefined timeline, set benchmarks and metrics, identify bottlenecks, as well as understand how to prioritize in a fast-paced environment, with tight deadlines</li> <li>Ability to learn about new markets quickly and to run a thorough and high-quality search process, including leadership candidate research, outreach, engagement, evaluation and presentation</li> <li>Good understanding of employment laws and related policies</li> <li>Passionate about Technology, Disruptive models, Organisational Culture, and Talent Management</li> <li>Financial Service hiring experience preferred</li> </ul><ul> <li>Crypto.com provides a great environment and platform for employees to build their career. In this role, you can expect:</li> <li>Unique opportunity to be a part of the digital disruption in cryptocurrency</li> <li>Autonomy in the role and in managing your own portfolio</li> <li>Exposure to the fast-paced world of high-tech start-ups</li> <li>Attractive experience and compensation</li> <li>Working with passionate, smart and driven colleagues in a vibrant environment</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/B8855461AB/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Front-end Developer (React)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Europe]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for experienced Frontend Web Engineer to lead migration of crypto-wallet mobile application on web to join one of our products team.</div><div><br></div><div>Regardless of your role, you'll have massive ownership and freedom and have the opportunity to work with a variety of technologies across the stack (and across blockchains):</div><div>- ReactJS with TypeScript</div><div>- State Management and routing with Redux</div><div>- Chrome Extension development</div><div>- Unit tests with Jest</div><div>- QA Automation with Cypress</div><div>- 3 or more applications from 0 to production</div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li><b>Lead our efforts:</b> You'll be leading the development of our Chrome Extension app, working closely with the team to define the product</li><li><b>New initiatives and products:</b> You will be leading initiatives to add support for other blockchains to Trust Wallet, and to launch new complementary products or infrastructure</li><li><b>Interfacing with users:</b> You will be interfacing directly with end-users and developers building on Trust Wallet. Supporting them and collecting feedback to inform the direction of the product</li><li><b>Team building:</b> You will be working with the team to create and foster a culture of raising the bar with each new hire</li><br/>Qualifications:<br/><li>5+ years full-time experience as a front-end developer</li><li>1+ years full-time experience in a blockchain based project</li><li>Demonstrated interest in open and community-driven platforms</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/aad10883-ca2e-4f6a-b5c5-93c0dcc663cd/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Junior Product Manager (Junior Quant)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As one of the largest and most trusted </span><b style="font-size: 11pt">digital asset platforms</b><span style="font-size: 11pt"> globally, we are empowering people to experience the life-changing potential of crypto.&nbsp;Trusted by over 8 million consumer and pro traders, institutions, and authorities worldwide - our unique combination of products, services, and global expertise is helping tip the scales towards mass crypto adoption.&nbsp;But we’re only just getting started. We want to be pioneers in crypto and add value to the everyday lives of billions. Now is not the time to sit on the sidelines. Join us to bring crypto to the world.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">About the Role</b></div><div><br></div><div>As part of the expansion of the business we are seeking a Junior Product Manager who will be responsible for ensuring that the firm’s products are administered and developed to the highest standards. This will involve working closely with the firm’s management, compliance and technology development functions. This role would allow the successful candidate to work in the heart of an integral part of the wider cryptocurrency ecosystem and drive data standards for the integration of cryptocurrency into the investment portfolios of institutions, corporations and individuals.</div><br/>What you'll do:<br/><li>Quantitatively analyse digital asset markets including cryptos, NFTs, yield, etc.</li><li>Develop new index products including design, testing, and evaluation</li><li>Manage the firm’s existing product suite with focus on robust and reliable processes</li><li>Enhance existing products and grow out the CFB IP stack to include different reference data sources, including on-chain blockchain data</li><li>Maintain and develop Index Metric Analysis</li><li>Collaborate with the firm’s technology development team to specify the build of new technology tools and infrastructure to facilitate product management and development</li><li>Ensure accurate documentation of methodologies and processes required to support new products</li><br/>Who you are:<br/><li>Education (PhD or MSc) from a top tier educational institution in a highly quantitative subject (Maths, Stats, Physics, Computer Science etc)</li><li>1-4 years working experience as a Product Manager or as a Structuring or Quantitative Analyst at a top tier asset management or banking institution.</li><li>Strong numeracy skills and applied knowledge of statistics and econometrics&nbsp;</li><li>Strong written and graphical communication including an ability to articulate mathematical concepts&nbsp;</li><li>Ability to work with and analyse large data sets</li><li>Understanding and practical experience in financial products and structured products</li><li>Understanding of cryptocurrencies and blockchain technology a plus</li><li>Experience gained within an index provider or asset management firm a plus</li><li>Good working knowledge of data software - EXCEL, SQL, Python, Jupyter Notebooks</li><div>Location Tagging: #EU #US #LI-Remote #LI-DP1</div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/05ff5c41-9bb5-4037-9e65-58a76850a455/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crypto Program Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re Coinbase. We’re the world’s most trusted way to join the crypto revolution, serving more than 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/our-mission-strategy-and-culture-18a92a3bb0fa&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web 3.0 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture. We’re a remote-first company looking to hire the absolute best talent all over the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve got positive energy. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for a Crypto Programs Manager to join the Crypto Intelligence Team within the Business Development organization to roll out efficient and repeatable processes, enable cross-functional alignment and collaboration, and deliver initiatives on time through consistent planning and tracking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What you’ll be doing:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work directly with the Manager of the Crypto Intelligence Team and other team members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Utilize professional and crypto experience to collaborate closely with cross-functional teams including Listings, Product Management, Business Development, Data Science, Legal, Compliance, Security and others to implement new crypto-related programs and improve systems and processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish and maintain workflows to support a “Monitoring Command Center” program while identifying scaling vectors and supporting internal adoption across cross-functional partners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support various programs in the crypto asset lifecycle, including but not limited to: asset reviews/re-reviews/prioritizations, Day-1 listings and crowd-fundraising platform product.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Leverage crypto forward knowledge to spin-up pioneering (yet-to-be-defined) programs around DApps, Wallet and NFTs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead efforts to improve data integrity across crypto-programs to measure process performance, and identify process improvement opportunities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate stakeholder alignment to create short-term and long-term program roadmaps to support business needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create executive-facing reports and presentations regarding team KPIs and accomplishments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What we look for in you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years program, project or growth experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor&#39;s degree from an accredited university&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven track record of handling large-scale projects across a variety of cross-functional teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Solutions oriented with a curious &amp;amp; analytical mindset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated data-driven decision making or quantitative analysis skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent communicator who can influence a wide range of partners, facilitate training to large groups, and is comfortable presenting to senior leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working at a tech company or has a track record of quickly ramping up on complex projects/environments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to handle multiple stakeholders and priorities simultaneously&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to thrive in ambiguous environments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven “crypto-forward” knowledge or demonstrated passion/curiosity and ability to ramp into crypto quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Notice for Colorado applicants as required by sb19-085 (8-5-20). Target annual salary for this role performed in Colorado, is &lt;span data-sheets-value=&quot;{&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;:3,&amp;quot;3&amp;quot;:170850}&quot; data-sheets-userformat=&quot;{&amp;quot;2&amp;quot;:21443,&amp;quot;3&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;:2,&amp;quot;2&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;\&amp;quot;$\&amp;quot;#,##0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;3&amp;quot;:1},&amp;quot;4&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;:2,&amp;quot;2&amp;quot;:16770457},&amp;quot;9&amp;quot;:2,&amp;quot;10&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;11&amp;quot;:4,&amp;quot;12&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;15&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Lato&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;17&amp;quot;:1}&quot; data-sheets-formula=&quot;=if(R45C6=0,R6C15*index(&#39;[HIDE]  Constants&#39;!R6C17:R18C17,match(R6C16,&#39;[HIDE]  Constants&#39;!R6C16:R18C16,0)),DGET(IMPORTRANGE(&amp;quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/11NK8Qii7CmiOpX_swzo7Ml0cEWE3j-g8se90PW81hhQ/edit#gid=1563110246&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;Comp 3.0!$B$5:$CH$200&amp;quot;),R47C6,{&amp;quot;lookup&amp;quot;;R42C6&amp;amp;R43C6}))&quot;&gt;$144,500&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;+ target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ID=P32041&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please note that for employees based in the US, Philippines, Canada or Singapore, if your role requires you to be present in a Coinbase office or if you choose to be physically present in a Coinbase office or sponsored location, participate in any in-person gathering (including offsites) or engage in business travel sponsored by Coinbase, you will be required to be fully vaccinated (as defined by applicable law).&amp;nbsp; If you receive an offer, you will receive additional information about the grounds and process for an exemption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations[at]coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3836485?gh_jid=3836485&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Development Lead, Bitria]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York; Portland, Oregon; Chicago, Illinois; Los Angeles, California; San Francisco, California; Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is a crypto exchange and custodian that allows customers to buy, sell, store, and earn more than 30 cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, bitcoin cash, ether, litecoin, and Zcash. Gemini is a New York trust company that is subject to the capital reserve requirements, cybersecurity requirements, and banking compliance standards set forth by the New York State Department of Financial Services and the New York Banking Law. Gemini was founded in 2014 by twin brothers Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss to empower the individual through crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto is about giving you greater choice, independence, and opportunity. We are here to help you on your journey. We build crypto products that are simple, elegant, and secure. Whether you are an individual or an institution, we want to help you buy, sell, and store your bitcoin and cryptocurrency. Crypto is not just a technology, it&#39;s a movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, our mission is to &lt;strong&gt;empower the individual&lt;/strong&gt; and that includes giving our employees flexibility of choice — our Office Optional Policy allows employees to choose to work from one of our physical locations or from home.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select roles that are location-specific will still be eligible for flexible schedules.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Department: Gemini Investment Solutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini Investment Solutions is one of the fastest growing teams at Gemini. We serve as a platform for the institutional investing side of the business and are addressing a multi-trillion dollar market opportunity. Our core team recently joined via strategic acquisition and are positioned to play a critical role in Gemini’s mission with best-in-class technology solutions and investment products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a dynamic group with both entrepreneurial spirit as well as enterprise experience. We have incredibly high aspirations for 2022 and beyond - to build a rocket ship on a rocket ship - and we are looking for like-minded individuals from diverse backgrounds (technology, financial services, fintech, SaaS…) who want to carve new paths and guide the transition from the traditional world to a new more decentralized world where access to digital assets is normalized and ubiquitous.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you fit this mindset and either work with digital assets today or are looking for the right entry point to transition into the space, GIS is a fantastic place to start.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role: Business Development, BITRIA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Transforming finance and empowering the individual through crypto is a deeply human pursuit. In Business Development you’ll be involved in sales strategy and operations, manage the account lifecycle from prospect to close, and partner with our best-in-industry Customer Success team to build long-lasting relationships with customers that range from innovative startups to leading firms. In addition to CS, you’ll partner closely with marketing, product, and leadership to better understand our target market and grow our pool of addressable AUM.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The candidate must have 6+ years experience closing business in either the Asset Management, Fintech, or Enterprise SaaS space. Ideally, this person has experience and a passion for building territories from scratch, rather than upselling existing customers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Promote lead generation activities for both outbound and inbound contacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with other go-to-market teams to organize demand generation activities within your given account list.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Handle customer pitches, company overviews and product demonstrations to prospective clients.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage pipeline reporting and sales forecasting along with&amp;nbsp; other sales operations responsibilities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interact with internal Gemini teams to improve processes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage the due diligence process for GIS prospective and existing clients.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Continually evaluate operational process to identify inefficiencies and develop scalable solutions leveraging product teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;6+ years of experience working within either Financial Services or Enterprise Software Platform sales&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience&amp;nbsp; selling to C-level executives and/or department leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;History of meeting &amp;amp; exceeding quarterly and annual quotas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Success in building a territory by adding new clients, not managing existing accounts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience being part of a collaborative / team selling process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of CRM tools, reports and dashboards&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-EP&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/70jrfYSxKC4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3869396&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Front-End Developer - Remote]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tendermint]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tendermint.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berlin]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About us:&nbsp;</b></div><div><br></div><div>At Tendermint, we empower people to engage with blockchain advancement and uncover new opportunities presented by this cutting-edge technology. Our diverse talent comes from around the world and together, we ignite change, powering the growth of truly innovative ideas and providing access to next-generation financial systems.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>By developing an innovative suite of products that are optimized for ease of use, including Starport and Emeris, we lead the way in building an open decentralized future. We are focused on creating an environment that allows for permissionless innovation, stemming from our legacy as the creators of Cosmos ($ATOM), the world’s largest cross-chain ecosystem that has secured billions of dollars in digital assets.</div><div><br></div><div>Fueling the advancement of blockchain applications through our user-friendly solutions, we connect technology and creativity to deliver a future where global businesses and individuals can benefit from a transparent ecosystem that is sustainable and interconnected.</div><div><br></div><div>Join our rapidly growing international team and play a meaningful role in this exciting industry, positively impacting global collaboration and prosperity.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div><b>How we work:</b></div><div><br></div><div>True to our vision of a Web3 future, we take a decentralized approach in our team. With team members working worldwide from North &amp; South America, Europe, Africa to the Middle East and Asia-Pacific, we focus on talent rather than location. We understand the importance of open communication and collaboration, leveraging the most optimal tools to operate efficiently and run an open-door policy with the leadership team.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>This role is a full-time remote position, and you are free to work from anywhere. The benefits we offer are carefully considered, aimed to facilitate remote working and maintain team welfare. As a team made up of varied backgrounds, cultures and experiences, we believe everyone has a unique way of contributing, and we fully encourage cross-learning.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Due to the nature of a decentralized team, there is a need to align schedules across different time zones. Having a certain level of time flexibility is therefore required during times of 8 am - 12 noon PST but this also means that you have flexibility in your schedule to best suit your lifestyle.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>At the heart of our work ethics, we value diversity, inclusivity, kindness, and respect.</div><div><br></div><div><br></div><br/>What you’ll be doing:<br/><li>Be a part of the front-end web engineering team building Starport, a developer-focused platform for building and launching sovereign blockchains.</li><li>Implement the user interface for the desktop web and mobile web versions of Starport, based on the high-fidelity mockups produced by our design team.</li><li>Design API client-side libraries that will be generated automatically from the source code of the blockchain.</li><li>Maintain a white-label wallet web app template, an integral part of Starport scaffolding.</li><li>Writing unit tests and integration tests for various features of the Starport web application.</li><li>Ensure our web application and components are accessible, responsive, performant, and bug-free for recent versions of web browsers across all popular platforms.</li><li>Ensure the code you write is readable, maintainable with minimal technical debt.</li><div><br></div><br/>We’re looking for someone who has:<br/><li>An exceptional portfolio demonstrating 6+ years of web development experience.</li><li>Mastery in building component-based web apps in JavaScript and TypeScript using Vue (preferred) or React.</li><li>Deep expertise in client-side state management libraries like Vuex, Mobx, or Redux</li><li>Expert understanding of client-side application architecture</li><li>Excellent knowledge of CSS and experience in writing stylesheets with Sass.</li><li>Experience in using communication protocols such as WebSockets and gRPC.</li><li>Proficient understanding of code versioning tools, such as Git.</li><li>Clear and concise written and oral English communication skills.</li><div><br></div><br/>Nice to have:<br/><li>Experience in using cryptocurrencies, wallets, decentralized exchanges, lending protocols, etc.</li><li>Fascination with blockchain technology</li><div><br></div><br/>What we offer:<br/><li>The opportunity to be part of building the future of the Internet</li><li>Flexible work schedule</li><li>Excellent benefits like educational budget, fitness and wellbeing spend</li><li>Flexible PTO</li><li>Healthcare, Dental and Vision insurance 100% covered for employees in the US</li><li>401K Match in the US</li><li>Competitive salary, including equity</li><div>Tendermint in the news:</div><div><br></div><div><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2019/03/17/welcome-to-the-hub-of-all-hubs/" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://techcrunch.com/2019/03/17/welcome-to-the-hub-of-all-hubs/</a></div><div><a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cross-platform-blockchain-project-cosmos-launches-first-hub-after-17-million-ico" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://cointelegraph.com/news/cross-platform-blockchain-project-cosmos-launches-first-hub-after-17-million-ico</a></div><div><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/a-blockchain-to-connect-all-blockchains-cosmos-is-now-officially-live" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://www.coindesk.com/a-blockchain-to-connect-all-blockchains-cosmos-is-now-officially-live</a></div><div><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/how-to-turn-a-17-million-ico-into-104-million-the-cosmos-story" class="postings-link">https://www.coindesk.com/how-to-turn-a-17-million-ico-into-104-million-the-cosmos-story</a></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/oJ4WG3SelT0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/tendermint/2c113947-2109-444e-9da4-6b5da33c7985/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145907/tendermint.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tendermint@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7560c97e-86cc-40b9-b8e0-09ef50cbd9ef]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tendermint]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of Talent]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Immutable]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://immutable.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sydney, Australia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">A bit about us:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Immutable is Sydney based, technology scale-up that focuses on making digital worlds real and is the fastest Australian company in history to reach Unicorn status.&nbsp;We've grown from 40 people to 150 people in 12 months and are looking to add a further 300 people to the Immutable family. </div><div><br></div><div>Due to this growth, we are looking for an experienced Director of Talent who can build our global talent strategy to align with our people vision and culture architecture. Reporting to the Chief People Officer you will play a pivotal role in setting Immutable up for high global growth and expansion.  You will have the opportunity to create and build two new departments (Employee Branding and Talent Programmes) as well as influence and coach the Head of Talent Acquisition and the wider business. </div><br/>You will have the opportunity to:<br/><li>Develop talent programs across EVP/Recruitment, DEI, candidate experience, talent mobility and development that will move the needle on our key metrics around attraction, engagement, performance, development and retention</li><li>Work with finance, people partners and leaders on strategic workforce and talent planning to build a robust and proactive framework</li><li>Manage with our Head of Talent Acquisition on capacity and capability planning to meet our exciting hiring plans</li><li>Provide leadership to our Talent Group (EVP, TA and Talent Programmes) and across the broader people team at Immutable</li><li>Encourage involvement in team strategic activities and programs outside of talent </li><br/>We would love you to have:<br/><li>Experience leading talent functions including broader programs and strategic experience</li><li>Global scaling experience </li><li>Experience working in a fast-paced/high growth environment</li><li>The ability to think strategically and design a compelling strategy that will yield the talent outcomes we need</li><li>Project Management expertise to lead and deliver programs across Talent</li><li>Strong presentation skills </li><li>Exceptional communication skills </li><br/>Some extra skills that would be awesome:<br/><li>Experience scaling a global Talent team in a SaaS or Fin-tech environment</li><br/>Some of the things we can offer you:<br/><li><b>Competitive Salary and Employee Stock Options: </b>Everyone in our team contributes to the success of our game-changing products, which is why we share all our wins company-wide. As we continue to succeed, stock options and a competitive salary mean you get to enjoy the upside!</li><li><b>Flexible working life and $750 WFH set up allowance</b>: Work-life balance is important. Whether you want to work from home or come to our new, shiny, Sydney office the choice is yours. To help you get comfortable working from home we’ll assist with a $750 contribution</li><li><b>Paid Parental Leave:</b> We celebrate our growing Immutable family! 12 weeks equal pay plus an extra 6 weeks for the birthing parent.</li><li><b>Employee Assistance Program</b>: A 24/7 service that includes unlimited counselling for you and your family</li><li><b>EOY and Birthday Leave: </b>You can enjoy 2 additional paid annual leave days at EOY and a paid day off for your birthday</li><li><b>Internet and Phone Allowance:</b> $900 annually to put towards your mobile and internet expenses</li><li><b>Learning and Development:</b> We are dedicated to your professional development. You’ll get access to thousands of online learning courses via Go1, Udemy and Naspers. Immutable will also contribute between $1500-$2000 annually for you to invest in your continued education</li><li><b>Wellness Benefits:</b> Work-life balance and your wellbeing are important to us. We will contribute $1200 annually to put towards anything that contributes to your mental or physical wellbeing</li><li><b>Diversity and Inclusion</b>: We are committed to building a diverse and inclusive community for everyone. We’ve joined the Project F initiative aimed at removing the systemic barriers to achieving gender-balanced technology teams</li><li><b>Personal perks:</b> Perkbox benefits including premium access to Aura, Calm, an online fitness portal and discounts at major retailers</li><li><b>Ideal office location:</b> On-top of the Apple store on King Street, Sydney, CBD</li><li><b>Social events:</b> Fun and regular company events to relax and connect with teammates</li><div><b>Additional Information:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Immutable is committed to building and fostering an inclusive, diverse workplace. We believe in incorporating everyone’s perspectives and experiences as this has been a significant driver in our success so far.</div><div><br></div><div>For this reason, we strongly encourage candidates of all backgrounds to get in touch. Even if you don’t meet all the requirements of a job listing, do yourself (and us) a favour by still applying! It’s highly likely you’ll bring something to the workplace that we haven’t thought of yet, and we would love to hear from you.</div><div><br></div><div><b>We are a 2021 Circle Back Initiative Employer – we commit to respond to every applicant.</b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fT1YFjzry3k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/immutable/bd75d3a7-405e-4a6f-916e-c598853a82bc/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/364981/Immutable.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[immutable@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f8630842-e278-44a1-80ce-2963904a6243]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Immutable]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Controller]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Wyre]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.sendwyre.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>In order to port over the next billion people into a secure and open financial system, you’re going to need a network of applications that connect to the fiat world… Wyre’s APIs make that happen.<br></p><p>Wyre's on a mission to bring crypto to the masses - we're pumped about building the infrastructure that will be used to build the future.</p><p>For visionary developers who want to build the next great crypto company, Wyre is the crypto stack that brings together the most powerful payment APIs in one place. To accomplish this mission, we’ve built a simple set of tools that allows fintech projects to materialize their visions. (1) Our instant Fiat-to-Crypto Checkout gateway is now being used by hundreds of applications (ie. MetaMask, Opera, Ledger) to offer the best way to convert card payments into crypto, and (2) Our flexible APIs (Transfers API, Custody API, Users API), allow projects to build e-wallets, merchant processing services, and money transfer platforms from the ground up.</p><p>As of December 2021, Wyre has raised over $55M in funding and currently is the backbone to over 1,200 partners and 7.6M accounts.</p><ul> <li>Review and analyse trends of expenses, revenues, and losses to identify opportunities to improve performance</li> <li>Review the budget on a monthly basis to ensure the organization is meeting its financial objectives and ensure proper resolution of major variances to budget</li> <li>Provide direction in determining the way financial information will be documented, maintained and reported</li> <li>Manage/contribute to ad-hoc Group Executive Management/Board of Directors requests, due diligence processes</li> <li>Coordinate and direct the preparation of the budget and financial forecasts and report variances</li> <li>Prepare and publish timely monthly financial statements</li> <li>Coordinate the preparation of regulatory reporting</li> <li>Research technical accounting issues for compliance</li> <li>Support month-end and year-end close process</li> <li>Ensure quality control over financial transactions and financial reporting</li> <li>Manage and comply with local, state, and federal government reporting requirements and tax filings</li> <li>Develop and document business processes and accounting policies to maintain and strengthen internal controls</li> <li>Additional controller duties as necessary</li> <li>Maintain efficient accounting and reporting systems and procedures for internal, external and regulatory reporting</li> </ul><ul> <li>University Degree (Master degree in Finance/Accounting preferred)</li> <li>5-10 years financial analysis experience</li> <li>CPA or CMA preferred</li> <li>Must be comfortable interacting at senior level in a culturally diverse environment and have the ability to build effective relationships</li> <li>Thorough knowledge of accounting principles and procedures</li> <li>Experience with creating financial statements</li> <li>Experience with general ledger functions and the month-end/year end close process</li> </ul><p><br><br></p><p>Required Skills</p> <ul> <li>Strong problem solving skills, judgment and attention to detail</li> <li>Excellent accounting software user and administration skills</li> <li>Excellent presentation and highly developed skill of prioritization and timing</li> <li>High energy and creativity, an entrepreneurial spirit and the ability to work autonomously in a fast growth and changing environment</li> </ul><p><br><br></p><ul> <li>An opportunity to build the future and freedom to work wherever you want<br> </li> <li>Health, dental, and vision benefits for you and your family</li> <li>Life insurance and disability benefits</li> <li>Equity options for all full-time employees</li> <li>401(k) plan with corporate matching</li> <li>Unlimited paid time off to relax and recharge</li> <li>Enjoy a highly fulfilling, mission-driven culture</li> <li>You are an owner! We offer stock options to each of our employee</li> <li>Fair pay, no matter where you live along with a competitive benefits package</li> <li>Flexible work hours</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/XF10lmj4V1M" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/wyre/j/0857B8FA61/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/195911/SendWyre-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[wyre@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[819988b2-62bb-4397-8af0-2a6f483e05ef]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Wyre]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Engineer, Commodities Desk]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[DRW]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://drw.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRW&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;is a technology-driven, diversified principal trading firm. We trade our own capital at our own risk, across a broad range of asset classes, instruments and strategies, in financial markets around the world. As the markets have evolved over the past 25 years, so has DRW – maximizing opportunities to include real estate, cryptoassets and venture capital. With over 1,200 employees at our Chicago headquarters and offices around the world, we work together to solve complex problems, challenge consensus and deliver meaningful results. It’s a place of high expectations, deep curiosity and thoughtful collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Data Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; at DRW, you will be part of the agricultural / softs research desk where you will work directly with a team of Analysts and PM’s. The primary objective of the role is to build and maintain a platform that is capable to consolidate and integrate the various existing&amp;nbsp;data&amp;nbsp;sources in the agriculture world: production, exports, cash values and others using structured and non-structured&amp;nbsp;data.&amp;nbsp; A BI reporting tool will be used for the visualization of a large and complex&amp;nbsp;data&amp;nbsp;sets. The developer must be able to translate the workflow to the PM and trading team, as well as being proactive in identifying other related process in research subjective to automation and improvement.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS or MS degree in Computer Science or a related technical field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in ETL/Data&amp;nbsp;Modelling/Business Intelligence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience developing&amp;nbsp;Data&amp;nbsp;pipelines for&amp;nbsp;Data&amp;nbsp;Ingestion or Transformation using Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of SQL experience in PostgreSQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience with schema design and dimensional&amp;nbsp;data&amp;nbsp;modeling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands on design experience with&amp;nbsp;data&amp;nbsp;pipelines joining&amp;nbsp;data&amp;nbsp;between structured and unstructured&amp;nbsp;data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in BI reporting tools like Power BI or Tableau]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience working with large&amp;nbsp;datasets and write complex queries with query/server optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For more information about DRW&#39;s processing activities and our use of job applicants&#39; data, please view our Privacy Notice at &lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;California residents, please review the&amp;nbsp;California Privacy Notice&amp;nbsp;for information about certain legal rights at&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#LI-GV&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MdwEImeQcx8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/drweng/jobs/3888381?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145892/drw.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[drw@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bf32acf8-cf47-410b-aa59-74974c4d6afd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[DRW]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Strategy Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ledger]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ledger.fr/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 10pt">&nbsp;</span><span style="font-size: 11pt">Ledger is a fast-growing leader in cryptocurrency security and infrastructure for blockchain applications.&nbsp;Headquartered in Paris, with offices in multiple countries across Europe, North America and Asia, Ledger has a team of 250 + and an aggressive hiring plan for the next couple of years. (Note that the M&amp;A function is based in London).&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Ledger is well funded with an aggressive growth agenda and a diversifying business model requiring strong strategic analysis in order to maximise the capture of value.&nbsp;&nbsp;In this context of strong growth, LEDGER is looking to grow the strategy team, recruiting for a manager to join the strategy team, based either in London or Paris.</span></div><div><br></div><br/>MAIN RESPONSIBILITIES<br/><li>The strategy manager  will work with the VP of Strategy &amp; M&amp;A and rest of the executive team to identify the highest priority strategic questions for the business, collecting and analysing internal and external data, identifying optimum solutions and working with business leaders to initiate execution.&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><div><br></div><div><b>Specific responsibilities:</b></div><div><br></div><li>Identify, prioritise, structure and lead strategic projects, including group and business unit strategies.</li><li>Work with the M&amp;A team to develop the acquisition or divestment pipeline&nbsp;Take overall responsibility for projects, including a thought leadership role in problem solving and developing recommendations.</li><li>Synthesize inputs to create high quality and concise deliverables, including reports, financial models, presentations, and other outputs to document and communicate findings to the executive <a href="http://committee.Support">c</a>ommittee.</li><li>Support finance on key strategic initiatives including Board strategy materials, investor materials, strategic planning, portfolio reviews</li><li>Plays a critical role in executing complex analytical and problem-solving modules on an individual basis.</li><li>Recruit and manage a high quality team.</li><li>Track the latest developments in the crypto ecosystem to keep Ledger ahead of evolving market demands.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><br/>Profil <br/><li>A total of 4/5 years Strategy Consulting Experience with a Top Tier Strategy Consulting firm</li><li>Strong financial analysis and modelling skills</li><li>Clear written and verbal communication of coherent analytical output to identify trends, develop key insights and required decisions for senior management</li><li>Personal initiative, excellent judgment, and the ambition to independently identify and resolve Ledger’s most important strategic issues</li><li>Curiosity to learn about new technologies and industry trends.</li><div><br></div><div><b>SOFT SKILLS</b></div><li>Familiarity with best practice strategic analysis methodology</li><li>Ability to influence, advise and push back on executives</li><li>&nbsp;Excellent written and verbal communication skills</li><li>Ability to analyze and synthesize, problem solving. </li><li>Fluent English</li><div><br></div><br/>Benefits<br/><li>Competitive remuneration and employee shareholding: access to EQUITY according to the company's current plan&nbsp;</li><li>Relocation assistance if needed</li><li>&nbsp;Strong focus on personal development, including internal and external training and conference attendance</li><li>High performance equipment for your work.</li><li>Aggresive paid-off policy</li><li>Comprehensive health insurance with medical, dental and vision <a href="http://coverage.Annual">coverage.</a></li><li>Annual company outing for Ledger Days; annual parties, snacks and drinks on the premises.</li><li>Employee discount on Ledger products.</li><div>Contract: Permanent </div><div>Location: Paris or London</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt"><i><b>&nbsp;Ledger ensures fairness to all during the hiring process, regardless of gender, ethnicity, religion, sexual orientation, social status, disability or age</b></i></span><span style="font-size: 10pt"><i><b>&nbsp;</b></i></span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/5Ss7xnFP9AM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/ledger/b7511b73-4ff4-4c48-81ed-31fa5854f2ba/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/142943/ledger.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ledger@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[83f3aace-4751-47ca-bbcd-26157dd3bc4a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ledger]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer - Hydra]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOHK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://iohk.io]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Want to work in a cutting-edge, research-driven project with an impact on millions of users?</p> <p>IO Global is searching for a Senior Software Engineer to join the Hydra team and work with us on the next big thing for the Cardano ecosystem. As a vital part of the Basho era, Hydra supports the growth and adoption of Cardano. By increasing the speed of transactions and ensuring low transaction fees, Hydra will be an enabling factor to applications that require these conditions, and it will be off-loading transactions from the main chain. Based on research done at IOG, we are creating the first implementation of the Hydra protocols as a full functionality layer-two solution for Cardano, providing scalability with the same level of security.</p> <p>Within our team of seasoned Haskell engineers, you'll be working on the implementation of a "hydra-node", which is a decentralized, event-sourced backend application acting as a component in a layer 2 stack for the Cardano network. Blockchain interaction (Utxo-based ledger + Plutus scripts in our case), networking, cryptography, APIs, persistence and resilience are some of the topics that engage us.</p> <p>We develop in an agile, amenable, and iterative approach inspired by eXtreme Programming (XP) and its values. Despite (or rather because of) the fact that we all work in a fully remote setting, we communicate daily and prefer working in an ensemble/pair programming setting as much as possible. But we also leave room for some more traditional solo programming with pull requests. Most of the time, we drive our development using end-to-end, integration, unit, and (our favorite) property tests.</p> <p>Although we only use Haskell in this project, extensive knowledge and expertise in it is not required as we try to practice "non-fancy" (aka simple or boring) Haskell. Instead, experience in one or more areas of our domain, seniority in another statically typed or functional programming language, substantial experience in building, delivering, and running distributed systems, as well as willingness to learn are more important to us.</p> <p>We look for someone who shares our values and mentality to create working software in a highly collaborative and iterative way, strives for correctness and simplicity, and appreciates our open discussion culture.</p><p><strong>Your mission </strong></p><p>As a Software Engineer at IOG, you are responsible for writing high-quality code for our products. You have the exciting challenge of working on cutting-edge technology focusing on the market's needs. To support you on this challenge, our product teams have software architects, product managers, and research specialists with whom you must communicate professionally, effectively, and efficiently.</p><p>Your responsibilities</p><ul> <li>Following agile software development and open source best practices</li> <li>Working with teams across multiple time zones in pair- and ensemble-programming sessions, but also independently on software development tasks</li> <li>Contributing to and reviewing software specifications and designs</li> <li>Assuring quality of your code with unit, property, and integration tests</li> <li>Integrating software components and third-party libraries</li> <li>Creating and maintaining continuous integration and deployment workflows </li> <li>Writing documentation and technical user manuals.</li> </ul><p><strong>Your expertise  </strong></p> <ul> <li>A degree in Computer Science is desirable but not essential  </li> <li>Practical experience working in agile  software development projects</li> <li>Minimum of three years experience in a statically typed or functional programming language; Haskell is ideal, but not strictly required</li> <li>An appreciation of the value of test-driven development and formal methods (ie. correctness), and ideally a knowledge of property-based testing</li> <li>Background in working with (UTXO) blockchains, distributed systems/networking, cryptography, or owning open-source projects is beneficial</li> <li>Experience with nix and docker to build and distribute code is beneficial</li> <li>Solid written and spoken communication skills in English.</li> </ul><p><strong>Location</strong></p><p>IOG is a fully distributed organization and therefore this is a remote position. Due to current team distribution, we are looking for someone in a CET, +/- 4 time zone for this role.   </p><p><strong>All Colleagues</strong></p><ul> <li>Flexible schedule</li> <li>Remote work - ability to work anywhere</li> <li>Laptop reimbursement</li> <li>New starter package to buy hardware essentials (headphones, monitor, etc)</li> <li>Learning &amp; Development opportunities</li> <li>Competitive PTO and Sick Leave plan</li> </ul><p><strong>US Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits coverage through Anthem with 100% premium cost covered by IO Global for the employee and dependents</li> <li>Health Savings Account</li> <li>Life Insurance</li> </ul><p><strong>UK Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Monthly Health Stipend to use towards any wellness or medical coverage/service</li> <li>Pension</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EM-XkuQdUq8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/io-global/j/110FE2CF1B/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143583/iohk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iohk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b89f946-6d3b-434f-aa32-f0e84ecb2992]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOHK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxos]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos is on a mission to enable the movement of any asset, any time, in a trustworthy way. Today’s financial infrastructure is archaic, expensive, inefficient and risky - supporting a system that leaves out more people than it lets in. So we’re rebuilding it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a regulated blockchain infrastructure company, we use technology to tokenize, custody, trade, and settle assets for enterprise clients like PayPal, Novi, Bank of America, and Interactive Brokers. Paxos is a top-funded blockchain company, with more than $500 million in total funding from leading investors like OakHC/FT, Founders Fund, PayPal Ventures, and Declaration Partners. Together, we empower today’s financial leaders to build a more open, trusted economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our &lt;strong&gt;Analytics&lt;/strong&gt; team is looking for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Data Analyst&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;to join our small but growing data &amp;amp; analytics team. Data &amp;amp; Analytics is changing the way Paxos operates as a data-driven organization. We’ve just built a new data stack from the ground up and are bringing more insights and intelligence to every decision made at the company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a Senior Data Analyst, you&#39;ll get to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Empower cross-functional partners and stakeholders to make data-driven decisions by delivering high quality analyses, dashboards, reporting &amp;amp; actionable insights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design, build and maintain self-service dashboards - working directly with end-users to ensure our partners and stakeholders have access to the data they need&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design key metrics to track and understand our products’ and functions’ performance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be a mentor and role model for more junior analysts on the team, both technically and professionally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build an understanding of our products, customers and the markets we operate in and proactively combine this with your data expertise to make actionable recommendations to the business&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Conduct one-off analyses and present findings and recommendations to senior leadership&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Document &amp;amp; build processes to share knowledge - from table and column definitions to workflow schedules to codebases&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Seek to scale everything 10x: from automation to writing reusable code&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Immerse yourself in blockchain technology, cryptocurrency for enterprises and investors, our regulation-first approach, and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your experience should include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+&amp;nbsp; years of proven work experience as a data analyst or similar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years of experience writing SQL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated data visualization skills and experience with BI tools (Looker / Tableau)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to simplify complex data and present findings to non-technical audiences&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent program management skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfort working in a tech-driven environment with the ability to coordinate across several stakeholder groups&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You might also have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience with any of the following: Snowflake, DBT, Looker, Python/R/Julia&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with any of: Finance &amp;amp; Accounting, Compliance &amp;amp; Risk, Customer Success &amp;amp; Sales, Financial Markets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience rolling out new functionality to end users in an analytics platform (e.g. new dashboarding solution, data models or other analytical/data/reporting tooling)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll love about Paxos:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paxos has consistently been named as a “Best Place to Work” by BuiltIn and was listed on the 2021 Forbes Fintech 50. All of our employees have significant ownership and impact on our business, as well as benefits like company equity, health insurance, family leave, a $500 quarterly stipend for development, a $500 stipend for home office setup and unlimited PTO. From team product demos and virtual lounge and learns to care packages and an active Slack #shoutouts channel, there are countless opportunities to connect and make your mark. Help us continue to build a new, open financial system from one of our three offices or right from your home!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Company&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/T_B9-TxFIVM&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Life at Paxos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2022/01/12/2021-was-just-the-beginning-paxos-will-accelerate-mainstream-digital-asset-adoption-in-2022/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;2021 Paxos Year in Review&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/29/paxos-raises-300-million-in-series-d-funding-at-2-4-billion-valuation/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Paxos Raises $300M in Series D Funding at 2.4B Valuation&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/23/paxos-national-trust-receives-occ-conditional-approval-for-de-novo-charter/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Paxos National Trust Receives OCC Conditional Approval for De Novo Charter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Customers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2020/10/21/paypal-launches-new-service-enabling-users-to-buy-hold-and-sell-cryptocurrency/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Paxos &amp;amp; PayPal Bring Crypto to Millions of Users&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/10/19/usdp-chosen-for-novi-pilot/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;USDP Stablecoin Chosen for Meta&#39;s Pilot of Novi Digital Wallet&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/12/02/mercadolibre-is-creating-the-biggest-crypto-market-in-latin-america-paxos-powers-the-experience/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Mercado Libre Creating Biggest Crypto Market in LatAm through Paxos&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/13/paxos-supports-interactive-brokers-journey-into-crypto-markets/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Interactive Brokers&#39; Journey into Crypto Markets&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Media&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.builtinnyc.com/2022/01/19/paxos-hiring-400-employees-2022&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Paxos Hiring 400 Employees in 2022&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h5ar-oLO1VY&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Paxos CEO Discusses Crypto, Blockchain and the Future of Finance&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://ca.finance.yahoo.com/video/stablecoin-infrastructure-strategic-national-security-170457903.html?guccounter=1&amp;amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAMFMUTbtU_axK3jgAPcjQwK96cXc7lA7_QZuCuDmtzBiUa6I6LBsac6Omvua-D7-ceIBXkCCGzEq6Z5JbbkCVgYrRYE0u5isY8mBmCAOmb0PvfHSUZrRmIunY_Svm7sse7WKahW2SnsaGVi96_aG3eUJsfDKLjdgVCQ4JgxOVbaP&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Yahoo Finance Interviews Paxos CEO on Testimony to Congress and Stablecoin Infrastructure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://tearsheet.co/sponsored/how-blockchain-can-replatform-the-financial-system-paxos-charles-cascarilla/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Paxos CEO Discusses How Blockchain can Replatform the Financial System&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Recognition&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.builtinnyc.com/companies/best-midsize-places-to-work-nyc-2022?utm_medium=exreferral&amp;amp;utm_source=3punknown&amp;amp;utm_campaign=bptw2022&amp;amp;utm_content=na-wcl#paxos&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BuiltIn NYC Names Paxos a 2022 Best Place to Work&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/fintech/2021/#413b4e2631a6&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Forbes Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 50&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/fintech-250-startups-most-promising/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;CB Insights Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 250 for Crypto Category&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our Paxos team is made up of passionate people from all over the world with different perspectives and experiences. If this opportunity excites you, but your experience doesn’t perfectly match the description…apply! Unique voices help us build a more open, trusted economy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-JC1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com/careers/role/5872071002?gh_jid=5872071002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/215201/paxos.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxos@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c782dc3a-8644-40b8-919b-b98b0cb1b35f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxos]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Junior Financial Crime Investigator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York Metropolitan]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At &lt;strong&gt;Luno&lt;/strong&gt;, we see you as an individual.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Together, we&#39;re upgrading the world of work to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A bit about us:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno means moon in Esperanto, we chose the name because at night, wherever you are in the world, you look up at the same moon. We believe in the power of working together, as one team, across borders, with clear focus and shared purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our popular mobile app and website helps people around the world grow and manage their money using the world&#39;s most mature cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum and USDC. We’ve processed over $21 billion to date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Over 8 million customers across 40 countries have chosen to hold their crypto wallets on Luno because we offer a delightfully simple experience and bank-grade security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re part of the Digital Currency Group, named in 2021 as one of TIME magazine’s 100 Most Influential Companies, in the “Disruptors” category alongside Tesla, AirBnB, SpaceX, Peloton. TIME noted that DCG is “mainstreaming cryptocurrency”.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re proud to be one of the world’s most international cryptocurrency teams, with colleagues from 43 different nationalities working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria, Australia and Singapore. Financial inclusion is part of our mission, but on a deeper level, inclusion is a way of life, and a way of work for us. It is part of who we are as a company, and a group of human individuals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your role in a nutshell:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a financial crime investigator, you’ll be involved in preventing and investigating financial crimes like fraud, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;money laundering and account takeovers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; from occurring on Luno. You will report to our Manager Investigations in South Africa. You’ll also be working closely with other Financial Crime team members to help support cross-department operational initiatives to detect and prevent abuse.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are passionate about cryptocurrencies and their role in the overall fraud and Financial Crime landscape. In your role you will be contributing to setting the standard for Luno’s Financial Crime team in the US.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The team:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to provide an amazing fraud framework and response to our business, partners, and customers in dealing with fraud related matters. We do this by responding to any fraud related incidents swiftly and in a coordinated way. We are the front line of Financial Crime and we ensure that fraud cases are dealt with appropriately and on time.&amp;nbsp; We keep the bad guys out and the good guys in. We operate globally and are centralised in South Africa with regional teams globally..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your mission will involve:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist with comprehensive investigations into &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;fraud, money laundering and account takeovers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to completion;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Conduct root cause analyses of incidents and report them to other business stakeholders;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist with the development of fraud policies, procedures and tools;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactively identify and monitor fraud patterns;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interact with customers to understand unusual account activity;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify areas of improvement in Luno’s products;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with a high degree of independence;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Keep detailed logs of incidents and prepare regular and ad-hoc reports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For this role you will need:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A BA, BSc BComm or other relevant qualification from an accredited college/university&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;1-3 years’ relevant work experience (involving money laundering, fraud and / or account takeovers)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience investigating complex financial crimes within the cryptocurrency/blockchain domain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A can do, get things done attitude&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An existing, valid work permit for the United States, if you’re not a US citizen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Willing to work in the New York metropolitan area and come into the office regularly for the first few months&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attention to detail, strong sense of responsibility and very high level of integrity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to take charge in critical situations and work on resolving problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Entrepreneurial, strong sense of responsibility and very high level of integrity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Solid interpersonal, communication and negotiation skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Friendly, transparent, articulate and driven to succeed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;ll especially get noticed if you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have any additional qualifications, such as CAMS or CFE;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have experience within a Fintech or Regtech environment;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are a veteran of the United States Army;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;em style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;italic&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. You&#39;ll need to hold the legal right to work in the UK already as we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3881040?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior DeFi Associate, Asset & Ecosystem Monitoring]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re Coinbase. We’re the world’s most trusted way to join the crypto revolution, serving more than 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/our-mission-strategy-and-culture-18a92a3bb0fa&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web 3.0 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture. We’re a remote-first company looking to hire the absolute best talent all over the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve got positive energy. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Coinbase Asset &amp;amp; Ecosystem team prides itself on being the compliance force on the front lines of the financial revolution.&amp;nbsp; The Asset &amp;amp; Ecosystem Senior DeFi Associate will be a lead contributor to the design and implementation of a monitoring program to identify and detect risks associated with assets supported across Coinbase platforms. &amp;nbsp; Y&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ou’ll apply your knowledge of data sourcing, analysis, and data visualization to&amp;nbsp; identify risks associated with supported assets. You’ll work collaboratively with the asset addition team, product and business development teams, and other Risk teams to support the enterprise growth strategy, including expansion into new markets and products.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ideal candidate will be a crypto-forward individual with a drive to see beyond the curve, possess a strong knowledge of various crypto protocols and have a natural curiosity to learn more and stay on the edge of innovation.&amp;nbsp; This role will report to the Asset and Ecosystem Monitoring Manager and will be located in the US / remote.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support the design, build and scaling of an asset and ecosystem monitoring program that efficiently and proactively identifies emerging risks related to supported assets and products&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify pertinent open-source and third-party data sources, identifying methods and techniques to derive valuable insights into risk exposures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform data analysis to determine significant risk thresholds to trigger additional action including investigations and escalations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage with product and business teams to identify requirements and objectives&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Stay apprised of changes in the cryptoeconomy including blockchain trends, new network protocol, industry participants, as well as regulatory rule making, guidance, and litigation.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with SMEs to tailor and tune the monitoring program to capture innovation in the crypto ecosystem or changes in the regulatory environment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we look for in you (ie. job requirements):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years of experience in a data analysis or reporting function and 1+ year in crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working knowledge of blockchains, crypto trends, crypto-specific risk typologies, and crypto data providers (open source and proprietary)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Well organized self-starter adept at working autonomously and committed to ongoing learning&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working knowledge of the cryptoeconomy and applicable compliance risks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in data collection, analysis, and dashboard design.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using SQL and other programing language (e.g., Python, R, Scala, or other)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Active collaborator that can build relationships across the organization to support holistic and strategic risk identification and mitigation&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with data collection and analysis to facilitate efficient and effective collaboration with technical and engineering teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree or higher.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working knowledge of Mandarin, Russian, Arabic or Spanish&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CAMS certification&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Notice for Colorado applicants as required by sb19-085 (8-5-20). Target annual salary for this role performed in Colorado, is $113,900 + target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ID: P31979&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please note that for employees based in the US, Philippines, Canada or Singapore, if your role requires you to be present in a Coinbase office or if you choose to be physically present in a Coinbase office or sponsored location, participate in any in-person gathering (including offsites) or engage in business travel sponsored by Coinbase, you will be required to be fully vaccinated (as defined by applicable law).&amp;nbsp; If you receive an offer, you will receive additional information about the grounds and process for an exemption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations[at]coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3879035?gh_jid=3879035&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Community Engagement Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As one of the largest and most trusted </span><b style="font-size: 11pt">digital asset platforms</b><span style="font-size: 11pt"> globally, we are empowering people to experience the life-changing potential of crypto.&nbsp;Trusted by over 8 million consumer and pro traders, institutions, and authorities worldwide - our unique combination of products, services, and global expertise is helping tip the scales towards mass crypto adoption.&nbsp;But we’re only just getting started. We want to be pioneers in crypto and add value to the everyday lives of billions. Now is not the time to sit on the sidelines. Join us to bring crypto to the world.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">About the Role</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our ideal candidate is motivated to provide excellent client support, experienced in interacting with clients on various social media platforms, enjoys getting to the root of issues reported by clients and able to escalate these issues across multiple departments effectively. You should be stress-resistant and able to perform under pressure. Above all, you are passionate about Kraken’s mission to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency and you have a broad knowledge about cryptocurrencies and the industry at large. If our words have struck the right chord with you and you are up for another challenging yet exciting career opportunity, we would like to meet you! Help us continue to define and lead the industry.</div><div><br></div><div>Depending on the particular support situation, there will at times be work needed outside of the core working hours for this position, including mornings, evenings and weekends. You need to work with a large geographically dispersed team consisting of people possessing a broad understanding of and comfort with technology.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>You will provide support and assist clients on various social media platforms (Facebook, Twitter, Reddit and others)</li><li>You will support clients in relation to&nbsp;high&nbsp;touch escalations and platform incidents</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>At least 2 years of relevant experience working with social media management platforms, like Sprout Social</li><li>At least 3 years of relevant experience in financial services, technology and/or customer support</li><li>You are a highly motivated, dedicated teammate with creative ideas to encourage customer loyalty and adoption</li><li>You have strong interpersonal skills and experience building strong internal and external relationships</li><li>You have the energy and patience to work in a dynamic environment and rapidly growing industry</li><li>You are passionate about cryptocurrencies and motivated to accelerate global crypto adoption</li><li>Excellent communication skills</li><li>Team-player who can also work independently</li><div>Location Tagging: #EU #US #APAC #CANADA #LI-Remote #LI-GW1</div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/e3dc3bf1-b9e6-442d-a7cd-0fd278f83ae6/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Designer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gauntlet]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gauntlet.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City / San Francisco / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Gauntlet’s mission is to drive adoption and understanding of the financial systems of the future. Gauntlet is the platform for off-chain intelligence that drives on-chain efficiency in Decentralized Finance (DeFi). We work with protocols to manage risk, improve capital efficiency, and manage incentive spend. We also publish cutting-edge research and aim to take a leading role in defining market risk standards across the industry.</div><div><br></div><div>Gauntlet is building infrastructure that allows us to simulate and stress-test blockchain protocols, contracts, and network interactions at scale over a wide range of market conditions. Our models ingest a wide range of on-chain and off-chain data, and are continuously calibrated to the current crypto market structure so that our recommendations are always up-to-date. These models and infrastructure power our platform that currently manages risk and optimizes incentives for over $40B in assets.</div><div><br></div><div>As Gauntlet’s product designer, you’ll design, prototype, and specify digital solutions that solve some of the biggest, most complicated problems facing DeFi protocols today. You’ll work with product managers to define problems worth solving, you’ll talk to users to understand their needs and experiences, and you’ll collaborate with Gauntlet’s engineers and data scientists to deliver high-quality digital experiences. Gauntlet gathers a wealth of data about the protocols it works with across its all of DeFi. You’ll be passionate about unlocking the value of this data for our DAO’s, Community members, and Protocol team.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>&nbsp;A sample of products and features you will work on:</div><div><br></div><div>* Our Risk Dashboards (<a href="http://gov.gauntlet.network">gov.gauntlet.network</a>)</div><div>* Marketing and sales collateral to help sell our services</div><div>* Our website</div><div>* Driving our brand, logo, design system throughout all of Gauntlet</div><div>* New project work we are just kicking off</div><div><br></div><div>As part of the product team, you’ll work with our PMs (there are only 2 of us right now) and engineers to ship digital products that improve the work lives of millions of truck drivers and managers. You will also work with Growth and leadership and have the opportunity to own our brand and drive it forward.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Distilling problems to their simplest essence, then iteratively designing digital products to solve those issues. Gauntlet believes in fast feedback cycles that start with loose sketches and whiteboard sessions, then moves to wireframes, and finally detailed high-fidelity designs for engineers to execute. You’ll drive these design cycles for the products you work on.</li><li>Developing Gauntlet’s visual product language. You'll design a clear and functional product language that makes Gauntlet easier to learn and use. You will be distilling very technical concepts into easy to understand visualizations that users without deep technical knowledge can understand</li><li>Gathering qualitative and quantitative product insights through user research with Gauntlet’s client’s, DAOs, and protocol teams.&nbsp;</li><br/>Qualifications<br/><li>3+ years of experience as a Product Designer.</li><li>An online portfolio showing off your high-quality product design work. An emphasis on clean user experiences and data-rich experiences is a plus.</li><li>Strong visual design skills. Experience and/or interest in designing reusable, scalable design systems is a plus. Ability to work in a wide range of design tools such as Figma and Balsamiq.</li><li>Experience interacting and communicating with a wide range of stakeholders including customers, users, engineers, and product owners to arrive at desired design solutions.</li><li>Experience with a variety of methodologies for product discovery and user research.</li><br/>Nice to Haves<br/><li>Bachelor’s degree in relevant field.</li><br/>Benefits and Perks<br/><li>Remote first - work from anywhere!</li><li>Regular in-person company retreats and cross-country "office visit" perk</li><li>100% paid medical, dental and vision premiums for employees</li><li>Laptop, monitor, keyboard and mouse setup provided</li><li>$1,000 WFH stipend upon joining</li><li>$100 per month reimbursement for fitness-related expenses</li><li>Monthly reimbursement for home internet, phone, and cellular data</li><li>Unlimited vacation</li><li>100% paid parental leave of 12 weeks</li><li>Fertility benefits</li><li>Opportunity for incentive compensation</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/gauntlet/7271ebf8-8030-4037-a837-167a55da9f10/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637342/gauntlet-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gauntlet@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5a52a20d-0bf4-491e-a6c0-a97d19aee27d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gauntlet]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Blockchain Engineer - Customer Excellence]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BitGo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.bitgo.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitGo is the leader in digital asset financial services, providing institutional investors with liquidity, custody, and security solutions. In 2020, BitGo launched Prime Trading and Lending, as well as BitGo Portfolio and Tax, providing clients with a full-stack solution for digital assets. In 2018, it launched BitGo Trust Company, the first qualified custodian purpose-built for storing digital assets. BitGo processes over 20% of all global Bitcoin transactions, and supports over 400 coins and tokens. BitGo’s customer base includes the world&#39;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges and institutional investors and spans more than 50 countries. BitGo is backed by Goldman Sachs, Craft Ventures, Digital Currency Group, DRW, Galaxy Digital Ventures, Redpoint Ventures, and Valor Equity Partners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitGo is looking for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Software Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to join our blockchain team and help us build a robust and scalable system to integrate new and existing blockchains .This role can be worked remotely so long as your home base is metro San Francisco, Palo Alto, NYC, Austin, Seattle or Toronto, Canada.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work closely with different blockchain experts to improve functionality on a variety of projects for multiple coins&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop enhancements and fix product features&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate closely with the technical support team to detect trends among support tickets to identify common root causes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop tooling to automate the detection and resolution of inconsistencies, as well as automate root cause analysis of issues and inconsistencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead projects and mentor junior developers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Experience:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for teammates who share and practice our values: open communication, transparency, taking ownership and a high level of craftsmanship. We are looking for coworkers who share our vision and mission: deliver trust in digital assets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 5 years of back-end, server-side software development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong programming skills in Javascript &amp;amp; Typescript&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great with unit and functional testing and debugging&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great at providing simple and extensible abstractions to complex systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in Git/GitHub and branching methodologies, code review tools, CI tools, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree in computer science, applied mathematics, or another technical discipline from a top university&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of and strong interest in cryptocurrencies and blockchain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great at algorithm design, problem solving, and complexity analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work independently in a fast-paced environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have been a team lead and mentored junior developers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of and experience working in the blockchain industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with microservices and service-oriented architectures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work full-stack and familiarity with React and Databases (MongoDB)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with Docker and Kubernetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Join BitGo?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Disrupting an industry takes vision, innovation, passion, technical chops, drive to deliver, collaboration, and execution. Join a team of great people who strive for excellence and personify our corporate values of ownership, craftsmanship, and open communication. We are looking for new colleagues who bring innovative ways of thinking and problem solving, and who want risks to be part of the team that changes the world’s financial markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Here are some of the benefits* of working at BitGo:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive base salary, bonus and stock options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% company paid health insurance for employee, partner and dependents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Up to 4% 401k company match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paid parental leave, Paid vacation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Free commuter/parking pass; 5 min from Caltrain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Free custom lunches, dinners and snacks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Computer equipment and workplace furniture to suit your needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great colleagues and inspiring startup environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;*Benefits may vary based on location&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Cryptocurrencies are the most disruptive change the financial services industry has seen in years. Join us and you’ll be able to look back and say you were part of the team that transformed investing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yGR7NLjXslU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitgo/jobs/5893636002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175514/birgo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitgo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b720d671-6d88-4863-a59d-ea5d1c6feea8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BitGo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Community Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Alchemy]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://alchemyapi.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, New York, and Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><a href="https://www.alchemy.com/company" class="postings-link">Our mission</a> is to bring blockchain to a billion people. The Alchemy Platform is a world class developer platform designed to make building on the blockchain easy. We've built leading infrastructure in the space, powering over $45 billion in transactions for tens of millions of users in 99% of countries worldwide. </div><div><br></div><div>The Alchemy team draws from decades of deep expertise in massively scalable infrastructure, AI, and blockchain from leadership roles at leading companies and universities like Google, Microsoft, Facebook, Stanford, and MIT. </div><div><br></div><div>Alchemy recently raised a <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/10/28/aws-for-blockchain-alchemy-boost-valuation-to-3-5b-with-250m-raise/" class="postings-link">Series C</a> led by a16z at a $3.5B valuation, having previously raised from Coatue, Addition, Stanford University, Coinbase, the Chairman of Google, Charles Schwab, and the <a href="https://alchemy.com/company#investors" class="postings-link">founders and executives</a> of leading organizations.</div><div><br></div><div>Alchemy powers the top blockchain companies globally and has been featured in <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/04/28/alchemy-raises-80m-at-a-505m-valuation-to-be-the-aws-for-blockchain/" class="postings-link">TechCrunch</a>, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ninabambysheva/2021/06/08/the-future-of-crypto-and-blockchain-fintech-50-2021/?sh=6791bad153b1" class="postings-link">Forbes</a>, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-21/nfts-mushroom-into-billion-dollar-market-with-help-from-alchemy?srnd=premium" class="postings-link">Bloomberg</a>, and <a href="https://www.alchemy.com/newsroom" class="postings-link">elsewhere</a>.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b>The Opportunity</b></div><div>The Community Manager is the core of Alchemy’s efforts to engage with and invest in the passionate community of developers and creators that use our products. You’ll help drive the growth of our community, developing strategies to drive engagement across social (especially Twitter and discord), virtual gatherings like online tutorials and, and in-person events and dinners. You’ll work hand-in-hand with marketing, communications, developer relations, events, product, and sales teams to make certain business objectives are being met and, critically, that our internal teams understand, hear, and respond to the voice of our community.</div><div><br></div><div>The role requires a passion for our mission — helping creative people bring their ideas to life on Web3 — and a willingness to roll up your sleeves and get your hands dirty. Your ability to authentically communicate as the voice of Alchemy is critical to the success of this role. Startup experience is preferred, knowledge of Web3 and blockchain is a plus.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Responsibilities</b></div><div>Set the tone for engagement with the community across multiple channels</div><div>Engage daily with our community members on Twitter and discord to foster community sentiment and growth</div><div>Support marketing campaigns, giveaways, and other community events</div><div>Develop comprehensive strategies that foster engagement across digital and in-person touch points</div><div>Align community engagement efforts to long-term business goals</div><div>Collect user feedback from the community and share it with internal functional partners</div><div>Act as a source of knowledge, support, and escalation for discord community managers</div><div>Contribute to the learning and success of your team, and the company, by sharing knowledge through mentorship, collaboration, and aiding in documentation</div><div><br></div><div><b>Requirements</b></div><div>2+ years in leadership roles organizing communities</div><div>Impeccable writing skills</div><div>Ability to context switch and manage multiple conversations</div><div>Demonstrable experience using Twitter and discord to foster community</div><div>Experience developing in-person community events, including dinners and larger gatherings</div><div>Creative thinking for deepening community interest</div><div>Excellent people skills</div><div>Interest in technology, blockchain, crypto</div><div>Experience with blockchain a large plus</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/alchemy/79438a1c-c358-41cc-bc42-d45535316e8b/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637333/alchemy-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alchemy@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[2216d58c-1ece-4465-a4f9-6c8eafa52f36]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Alchemy]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Community Management ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
