<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Compliance Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinsquare]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://coinsquare.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Toronto]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Coinsquare is excited to announce an opening for a Compliance Analyst role! This person will support the efforts of maintaining core components of the Compliance program function. As a Compliance Analyst, this person will also help build a data focused approach to Compliance.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities :<br/><li>Creates, maintains, and archives Compliance data and reporting monthly metrics</li><li>Liaises with internal departments to obtain statistical data to maintain and update Compliance reports and databases on a regular basis&nbsp;</li><li>Assists Compliance with administrative functions related to regulatory and corporate compliance program requirements and other ad hoc assigned duties where needed</li><li>Participates in Compliance department investigations and transactions monitoring</li><li>Participates in self-assessment, audit, quality assurance, and regulatory testing exercises</li><li>Completes ad hoc projects or miscellaneous duties as required</li><li>Develops awareness and knowledge of regulatory compliance requirements, developments and industry “best practices” through review of publications, participation in industry associations, employee development initiatives, etc.</li><br/>Key Skills :<br/><li>Bachelor's Degree or equivalent preferred</li><li>3-5 years of relevant experience in financial services</li><li>Business intelligence and project management skills</li><li>Experience performing data collection, research, analysis and administration</li><li>Introductory knowledge of Canadian securities laws and regulations</li><li>Strong attention to detail and accuracyStrong verbal/written communication and organizational skills</li><li>Strong research, problem-solving, and analytical skills</li><li>High level of enthusiasm and desire to learn and progress in skills</li><li>Solid time management skillsSolid interpersonal and team interaction skills</li><li>Previous compliance experience an asset</li><br/>Nice to Have :<br/><li>Completion of Canadian Securities Institute course(s) within 12 months of hire</li><div><b>About Coinsquare</b></div><div><br></div><div>Coinsquare is Canada’s leading and most secure digital asset trading platform for trading Bitcoin, Ethereum, Litecoin and other digital currencies.</div><div><br></div><div>We built the most secure trading platform, and since our founding in 2014 we’ve never lost a coin. We’re FINTRAC regulated as a money services business, meaning we keep all our clients' money in Canada and use bank-level security measures on our platform.</div><div><br></div><div>We’ve raised over $60M to date, growing from one employee in February 2017 to over 100 employees by January of 2019. We’ve been featured in major media outlets across Canada and are always dedicated to bringing digital asset investing to the mainstream through our various operations like digital currency mining, funds, capital markets, and other offerings coming down the pipeline as we grow.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Discover what's possible with digital currency by checking out our trading platform:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Coinsquare for&nbsp;<a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=coinsquare.io.coinsquare">Android</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;<a href="https://itunes.apple.com/ca/app/coinsquare/id1262552870">iOS</a>&nbsp;|&nbsp;<a href="https://coinsquare.io/register">Web</a></div><div><br></div><div>We’re full of bright and diverse thinkers. Team members have equal opportunities to contribute to our success within a scale-up culture that encourages self-starters, transparency and team connectivity.</div><div><br></div><div>Coinsquare is committed to maintaining a diverse work environment where we welcome and encourage candidates of all backgrounds to apply. Should you have any accessibility requirements or concerns regarding the hiring process or employment with us, please notify us so we can provide suitable accommodation.</div><div><br></div><div><i>In order to promote and enhance the security of Coinsquare and our platform, just so you know, anyone receiving a job offer will be required to complete a background check.</i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3iipb_DvFv4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/coinsquare/748737cf-0085-4754-9843-0fbe1db32e5b/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/211877/coinsquare.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinsquare@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[0f495cc1-e746-4a10-8780-0031986d036d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinsquare]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Heartbeat Solution Architect]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Altoros]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.altoros.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[California, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p><strong>Responsibilities</strong><br>Consult customers on designing and developing applications for cloud (cloud-native applications) using your experience with Spring Framework for Java, cloud infrastructures, cloud-native architecture designs, legacy application migrations. Design distributed solutions using experience with Cloud platforms – Cloud Foundry and Kubernetes. Use experience with Internal Architecture of Cloud Foundry VMware Tanzu to develop and support Heartbeat solution and Altoros Tiles (additional components that extend core functionality). Use experience with IFTTT protocol to organize complex remote control of technical devices for our Alarta (covid safety and compliance platform) in order to develop and maintain the system. Travel to various unanticipated client’s worksites. May work remotely from home.<br></p><p><strong>Requirements</strong><br></p><ul> <li>Master’s Degree in Informational Technology, Automatization and Management of Technological Processes and Productions, or equivalent, or related field;</li> <li>2 years of experience as Senior Java Developer, Cloud Solutions Architect, or related occupation;</li> <li>Experience with Spring Framework for Java;</li> <li>Experience with enterprise-scale cloud infrastructures, cloud-native architecture design, legacy application migrations;</li> <li>Experience with Cloud platforms – CloudFoundry and Kubernetes;</li> <li>Experience with Internal Architecture of Cloud Foundry and VMware Tanzu;</li> <li>Experience with IFTTT protocol;</li> <li>Travel to various unanticipated client’s worksites; and</li> <li>May work remotely from home.</li> </ul><p>Worksite: 4900 Hopyard Road, Suite 100, Pleasanton, CA 94588<br>Qualified applicants mail resumes only to Altoros Americas LLC, Attn. HR/CFE, 4900 Hopyard Road, Suite 100, Pleasanton, CA 94588</p><p>Requirements</p><p>Benefits</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JnXjZXKFNYo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/altoros/j/77A1EA4C80/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194210/Altoros_Logo_color_white_bg.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[altoros@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[1f68a1c5-75de-4c13-b070-17adb45bf5d2]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Altoros]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Kiva US Operations Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kiva]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.kiva.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Portland, OR / U.S Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kiva (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://kiva.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;kiva.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;) &lt;/span&gt;is an international nonprofit with a mission to expand financial access to help underserved communities thrive. We run a global marketplace platform to crowdfund microloans for financially excluded entrepreneurs, farmers and students around the world. &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Through Kiva Capital, we serve as a bridge between large scale impact first investors and underserved populations. Our digital identity platform enables borrowers who don’t have a track record with traditional financial institutions to record and verify their financial history and gain access to less costly mainstream financial markets. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our organization combines the culture and technological passion of an internet start-up with the compassion and empathy of a non-profit to create impact and opportunity at global scale. &lt;/span&gt;Since 2005, we have raised more than $1.57 billion in loan capital for 3.9 million borrowers in 98 countries. Our lenders fund over $10 million in loans every month. With offices in San Francisco, Portland, New York, Nairobi, and Bangkok, Kiva&#39;s team includes 100+ employees and 400+ volunteers worldwide. Our team is growing as we pursue exciting new opportunities to create a financially inclusive world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role overview:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Kiva U.S. team provides 0%, no-fee loans of up to $15,000 to entrepreneurs and small businesses in the United States that are typically excluded from formal financing products. With no minimum credit score and an inclusive approach to underwriting, Kiva U.S. extends access to capital to small businesses across the country.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In communities and cities where there is an expressed gap in affordable financing options, Kiva offers a plug-in microlending partnership model for small business support centers, city governments, and community development financial institutions called the Kiva Hubs program. In more than 40 cities like Oakland, New York, Detroit, and Pittsburgh, partners are developing small business ecosystems and deepening their impact by making Kiva loans accessible to the entrepreneurs they serve.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a unique role that gets to play a part in the complete lifecycle of a Kiva US borrower, from application to repayment. As a Kiva US Operations Associate, you will participate in the execution of Kiva’s innovative, social underwriting process, and support our borrowers with their repayments. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In other words, you will be performing the tasks that turn a loan application into capital in an entrepreneur’s hands and then work on ensuring they repay their loan in full so Kiva lenders can support even more borrowers!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will learn the current processes we use to vet borrowers and to manage their delinquency, as well as engage with the larger team in suggesting and executing improvements to our processes and tech infrastructure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Once you’re fully onboarded, a typical day might include approving loan applications reviewed by our underwriting team, answering borrower questions, monitoring loan review and repayment through key metrics, creating repayment reports to be shared with partners, attending team problem-solving sessions on ways to improve the underwriting process and/or strategies to increase repayment, and experimenting with new solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you’re highly analytical, detail oriented, mission driven, and if you’re interested in seeing a fast-growing startup expand and scale, this job is for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At this time, we can only consider applicants with authorization to work in the United States on a permanent, full-time basis; unfortunately we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key responsibilities include:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support the US Credit Operations Manager on the underwriting process for entrepreneurs interested in receiving a loan through Kiva&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead the communications with borrowers in repayment, helping them avoid delinquency or default&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Carry out collections, delinquency, and defaulting processes for repaying borrowers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track and analyze impact and loan fundraising/repayment metrics for both reporting and strategy-informing purposes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create and support projects aimed at improving our operations and at increasing the value we provide to our borrowers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Implement innovative solutions to boost one of the most important metrics of our program: repayment rate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;1-3 years of relevant academic or professional experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong critical thinking and process orientation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attention for detail and ownership of your work&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enjoys completing processes efficiently while maintaining high quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Thorough and organized, responsible and reliable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Highly proactive and able to work independently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage time well and prioritize across competing tasks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Tech-savvy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Spanish is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with Salesforce, Looker, Excel, Google Suite is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passion for social impact and financial inclusion&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An opportunity to improve real lives, solve hard problems, and change the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Friendly, supportive, and adventurous environment with a team of engaged colleagues&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A comprehensive, industry-leading benefits package&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Opportunities to connect with and learn from colleagues and partners around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Salary range for Colorado : $48K - $50K&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A diverse and inclusive workplace where we learn from each other is an integral part of Kiva&#39;s culture. We actively welcome people of different backgrounds, experiences, abilities and perspectives. We are an equal opportunity employer and a great place to work. Join us and help us achieve our mission!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We will only accept applications directly from candidates. Kiva will not be responsible for any recruiting agency fees, absent a formal agreement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IEdy6XHkd9k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/kivaorg/jobs/3665354?gh_jid=3665354&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194099/kiva.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kiva@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[12467ec7-a781-4b48-abdb-bfbbc2a9cc79]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kiva]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Director,  Enterprise Memberships]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[The Block]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.theblockcrypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Founded in 2018 and based in NYC, The Block is the leading research, analysis, and news brand in the digital asset space. The Block's team is spread across 7 timezones, covering the global cryptocurrency space 24/7.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Block delivers deep insight into how the emerging digital assets sector interacts with traditional finance, technology, governments, and markets. We reach hundreds of thousands of technologists, financial market participants, Fortune 500 professionals, global service providers, policymakers, and more through our main website, dedicated Research Portal, podcast, and events. </span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We are currently seeking a Senior Director to join our rapidly growing Revenue team. This role is an enterprise sales position focused on growing new business and current client growth for The Block’s Membership Team.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Meet and exceed team quarterly and annual revenue targets as well as other key performance objectives</li><li>Develop and implement scalable sales processes, key performance indicators (KPIs), and systems to continuously improve the performance of the Membership New Business team</li><li>Partner with Director of Business Development (BDA Leader) to develop robust outbound prospecting and outreach strategies for BDAs and AEs to leverage</li><li>Hire, train, mentor, and motivate a high-performing sales team&nbsp;</li><li>Take full ownership of team effectiveness on all aspects of the sales process including client presentations, proposals, contract negotiations, and final close</li><li>Provide regular and meaningful insights to the Vice President of Memberships, New Business, and other members of the Revenue Leadership team on team performance, market trends, product feature requests, and competition</li><li>Partner with Account Management and Client Services to ensure seamless client delivery in the sales and post-sales process</li><li>Travel as needed to industry events and in-person meetings with prospective clients to assist in the development of key relationships</li><br/>Qualifications <br/><li>Minimum of 8+ years of experience in consultative, enterprise sales with a demonstrated track record of hitting and exceeding revenue targets, preferably in SaaS or B2B sales.&nbsp;</li><li>Experience managing a strategic sale, including selling unbudgeted solutions to multiple executives and decision-makers and creating value in a competitive environment.&nbsp;</li><li>Ability to prospect and manage C-level and senior-level relationships with enterprise organizations.</li><li>An interest in the evolving crypto and digital assets industry</li><li>Propensity to ask probing questions to match the prospect’s challenges with The Block’s services.&nbsp;</li><li>Excellent communication, interpersonal, and presentation skills</li><li>Effective problem solving and time management&nbsp;</li><li>Adaptable to changing startup environment</li><li>Collaborative spirit and results-oriented</li><li>Hit individual goals while staying invested in the team’s larger revenue success</li><li>Working knowledge of CRM platform preferred. </li><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Block is an equal employment opportunity employer.&nbsp; Qualified candidates are considered for employment without regard to race, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, age, military or veteran status, disability, or any other characteristic protected by applicable law.</span></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/theblockcrypto/b896d7d8-a3d7-44f8-9784-d002244e5c44/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/374217/theblock.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[theblock@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[27d78dc7-e726-4a53-af38-f0660605e195]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[The Block]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Jr.  Applications Product Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Axoni]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://axoni.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Axoni is building the next generation of capital markets technology. Our solutions are used by the world’s leading banks, asset managers, hedge funds, and infrastructure providers. Our diverse team focuses every day on our goal of building products that will change and improve how our clients and the markets will interact.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are seeking talented, motivated professionals that want to be part of this once-in-a-career opportunity to not only see, but also drive the incredible changes coming to global capital markets. We are building a culture where our team feels valued and everyone is given an opportunity to grow and succeed. We try to live by our Core Values and demonstrate what we believe represent the kind of company we are working to build. These Values are: Delivery is everything; Choose Kindness; Movements must be shared. </div><div><br></div><div>As a part of the Product team, the <b>Jr. Applications Product Manager</b> will help to build cutting edge products that will define the future of Capital Markets. Partnering with both our Business and Engineering Teams, you will be responsible for tracking market and customer needs, evolving our Application product roadmap, developing and prioritizing new functionality, and managing build to plan. </div><div><br></div><div>You will be at the center of everything we do, driving a technical product from planning to execution throughout the entire product life cycle while bringing standardization across all our initiatives.</div><br/>You will: <br/><li>Collaborate closely with Business, Engineering and Delivery teams to be an integral part of developing and delivering products for enterprise customers</li><li>Analyze workflows and facilitate efficient delivery of software updates</li><li>Perform business analysis and write detailed product requirements as deliverables for implementation</li><li>Work closely with engineers and architects during the implementation phase to ensure a fit for purpose delivery of product features</li><li>Support our Business team during client meetings when detailed product discussions are required</li><li>Provide product updates and technical elaboration based on client requests or cross-team needs</li><br/>You have: <br/><li>2+ years of product management experience</li><li>Experience managing or working on enterprise software products with an understanding of various components of the enterprise software suite</li><li>Ability to think strategically and execute methodically</li><li>Strong verbal and written communication skills across all levels of the organization</li><li>Experience working with Agile/ScrumExperience using task management software including Jira or another similar tool</li><li>Knowledge of enterprise product management preferred</li><li>Experience with data-intensive financial software products a plusKnowledge of UX/UI best practices a plus</li><div>Individuals seeking employment at Axoni are considered without regards to race, color, religion, national origin, age, sex, marital status, ancestry, physical or mental disability, veteran status, gender identity, or sexual orientation. You are being given the opportunity to provide the following information in order to help us comply with federal and state Equal Employment Opportunity/Affirmative Action record keeping, reporting, and other legal requirements.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xO7B4WYKVZE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axoni/9efa74c6-7703-4ba0-b432-a46159071236/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145318/axoni.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axoni@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b96c34e0-5c46-4ec2-8e42-397e29857c6f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Axoni]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Recruiting & People Ops Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[The Block]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.theblockcrypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Founded in 2018 and based in NYC, The Block is the leading research, analysis, and news brand in the digital asset space. The Block's team is spread across 7 timezones, covering the global cryptocurrency space 24/7.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Block delivers deep insight into how the emerging digital assets sector interacts with traditional finance, technology, governments, and markets. We reach hundreds of thousands of technologists, financial market participants, Fortune 500 professionals, global service providers, policymakers, and more through our main website, dedicated Research Portal, podcast, and events.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">In order to meet our goals as an organization we are heavily invested in the employee experience, from first contact in the recruiting process to onboarding to learning &amp; development and everything in between. Reporting directly to the VP, People Operations, you will support the people operations function as we build a best in class sourcing, recruiting and people ops program that sets employees up for long term success.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities Include:<br/><li>Support the recruiting process through interview scheduling and applicant tracking system administration.</li><li>Ensure interviewers are set up for success through clear communication on evaluation metrics in advance of interviews.</li><li>Source candidates for open roles in applicant tracking system to support the recruiting team's effectiveness.&nbsp;</li><li>Assist in onboarding new hires in partnership with the recruiting team and Director, Employee Experience - add to PEO, complete i9, schedule new hire orientations and cohorts, set up welcome meetings, etc.&nbsp;</li><li>Maintain accurate employee files for current and former employees.&nbsp;</li><li>Ad hoc improvement projects to streamline various HR processes as identified by people ops leadership.</li><br/>Qualifications Include:<br/><li>Professional work experience, especially in a support role</li><li>Strong attention to detail</li><li>Excellent written and verbal communication skills&nbsp;</li><li>Comfortable communicating with stakeholders internally and externally at all levels</li><li>Desire to grow a career in people ops / recruitment</li><div><span style="font-size: 14.6667px">The Block is an equal employment opportunity employer.&nbsp; Qualified candidates are considered for employment without regard to race, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, age, military or veteran status, disability, or any other characteristic protected by applicable law.</span></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/theblockcrypto/d5a71f5c-c472-46e9-a93a-51e37f01a5e3/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/374217/theblock.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[theblock@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[27d78dc7-e726-4a53-af38-f0660605e195]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[The Block]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Associate, End User Computing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxful]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://paxful.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Miami, Florida, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Paxful&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxful is the people-powered marketplace for money transfers with anyone, anywhere, at any time. Imagine a world where everyone has equal access to finance, no matter who they are, or where they’re from. We&#39;re building it. Our mission is to empower the forgotten four billion unbanked, so they have control of their money in a way they&#39;ve never had before.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working across three offices in different time zones, the Paxful team serves our amazing community of 4 million strong. We build for people, not profits, and consider ourselves to be everyday heroes who don’t wear capes or masks. That’s why we launched Built with Bitcoin, a charitable initiative that aims to build 100 schools, water facilities, and entrepreneurial incubators in emerging markets all over the world. We want to show that bitcoin can have a positive impact and make real changes in the lives of people everywhere.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;&lt;strong data-stringify-type=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;As a key member of our team, your responsibilities will entail:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;p-rich_text_list p-rich_text_list__bullet&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;unordered-list&quot; data-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-border=&quot;false&quot; data-border-radius-top-cap=&quot;false&quot; data-border-radius-bottom-cap=&quot;false&quot;&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Install and purchase new software and hardware components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Assist with network administration tasks and onboarding/offboarding task for new employees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Manage inventory system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Understand the Security Policies and perform tasks in accordance to these standards.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Manage corporate MDM systems that are in place - Jamf/Intune&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Maintain IT-related documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;&lt;strong data-stringify-type=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;The most important skill and capabilities for this role are:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;p-rich_text_list p-rich_text_list__bullet&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;unordered-list&quot; data-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-border=&quot;false&quot; data-border-radius-top-cap=&quot;false&quot; data-border-radius-bottom-cap=&quot;false&quot;&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;You&#39;re open-minded, ready to learn/grow, have an analytical mindset and able to work independently.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Find feasible solutions to problems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Treat end users with priority and satisfy their computing needs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;You&#39;re proactive and have good communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Skills in Macbook/Windows troubleshooting iw.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Able to reach out to software/hardware vendors/partners if needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;In-depth knowledge of various computer hardware and software technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;&lt;strong data-stringify-type=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Your expected experience:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;p-rich_text_list p-rich_text_list__bullet&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;unordered-list&quot; data-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-border=&quot;false&quot; data-border-radius-top-cap=&quot;false&quot; data-border-radius-bottom-cap=&quot;false&quot;&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Some experience in IT support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Pursuing a degree in computer science or a related field is required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Good verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Have worked in an IT firm previously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Experience in using ticketing systems like JIRA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity &amp;amp; Inclusion at Paxful&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Paxful, we know that a diverse workforce fuels our individual and collective success. We encourage applicants of different backgrounds, cultures, genders, experiences, abilities and perspectives to apply. We are actively working to increase the diversity of experience and perspectives on our team and are looking for someone who can help continue to lead that process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EEOC and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accommodations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxful is committed to diversity in the workplace and we’re proud to be an equal opportunity employer. We do not hire on basis of race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, citizenship, or any other basis protected by local, state or federal law.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re also committed to providing accommodations to people with disabilities. If you need any kind of accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, you can reach out to careers@paxful.com and let us know how we can best help you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other privacy laws may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full Privacy Notice is available at https://paxful.com/privacy-notice. By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JvYoQb4qyg4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/paxful/jobs/4827660003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/353334/paxful-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxful@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[0cd1eea2-97ef-4cc0-9d15-01fa1a8ce9ca]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxful]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Content Marketing Specialist (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Current Media]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://current.us/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote from anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What Is Current?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to enable budget-conscious consumers to earn additional income from their everyday habits. We accomplish this with&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=us.current.android&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; an Android app&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://modephone.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; smartphone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; that pay users to listen to music, charge their phone, play games, complete surveys; and connect them with exclusive deals to save and earn even more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve grown our product by several multiples in 2020: over 200,000 people earn on Current daily, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;we’ve paid out over $1M to people in the last few months&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and are maintaining positive margins at an 8-figure revenue run rate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team of 30 works in several autonomous, cross-functional pods. Each pod has a Product Manager, 3-5 Engineers, a designer, and a QA Engineer rallied around a core part of the product; together they are responsible for defining and achieving a set of OKRs. Our team is distributed across the globe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are rigorously data-driven with our product and engineering decisions, allowing us to prioritize the best outcome for our users while maintaining a sustainable business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About The Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;ll be working closely within the Partner Marketing / Monetization team and reporting to the Senior Product &amp;amp; Lifecycle Marketing Manager, and will be responsible for a wide range of tasks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Set content strategy for digital channels in line with campaign and business goals and translate that strategy into compelling new content (especially blogs) that is engaging, relevant, and on brand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write compelling blog articles based on SEO strategies and trends.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Produce SEO-driven content marketing which ranks well and gets results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work with designers, product, marketing, sales, external influencers, and other industry experts;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Keep up to date on emerging and current content trends and best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Do keyword research, think about content reuse, use data and analytics, and heavily promote content.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Report on sales revenue generated from content marketing effort&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We&#39;d Love To Talk With You If…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Education: B.A. or B.S. in Communications/Journalism/Marketing or equivalent experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years of professional experience in affiliate marketing, SEO optimization, and / or content creation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated excellent communication skills (written and verbal).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Content writing experience.&amp;nbsp; Excellent writer/storyteller and researcher with the ability to adapt to new ideas quickly.&amp;nbsp; Writing samples will be required as part of the interview process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with WordPress or similar content development platforms would be a big plus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SEO content knowledge and experience. You understand fundamental SEO principles and how to optimise content to increase search traffic. You understand what effective content needs in order to deliver traffic and conversions, as well as how to monitor content and report on ranking results.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent keyword research skills: You’ll have experience undertaking keyword research and selecting winning keywords for SEO content work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;re data-driven and have experience monitoring metrics to measure performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Having been a part of a high growth start-up before is a plus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Adept at handling multiple projects simultaneously under pressure to meet deadlines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to self-manage and work in remote work settings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient in English.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Available to work solely or mainly in US Central Time zone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We All Share The Same Core Values&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lead with Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Leadership does not necessarily mean management. Everyone is a leader, no matter the role. Taking pride in your responsibilities, finding &amp;amp; executing solutions is key.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on the ‘Why’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;- The best solutions start with everyone understanding the problem and its impact. We’ve found that if someone understands the ‘why’, they will produce an innovative &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;‘what’ and ‘how’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. If we cannot explain the ‘why’ clearly, we don’t understand the problem ourselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bring a Sense of Humor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Our work environment is a lighthearted &amp;amp; positive place where employees are united by humor and camaraderie; we believe laughter is a great way to uplift employee morale and form bonds with each other.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set New Precedents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - We drive innovation and push boundaries for all company activities while understanding that anything worth doing will have roadblocks. We set a new standard of worth for people’s time, data, and attention while rewarding what most other companies take.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - We won’t thrive without recognizing others’ strengths. Listen and evolve together, helping and supporting each other for the sake of a collective goal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;We Believe In The Following Workplace Norms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Honor Commitments, Your Word Matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Specific, Measurable, Attainable, Relevant &amp;amp; Timely (S.M.A.R.T) Asks &amp;amp; Answers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allow OKRs To Guide Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Individual &amp;amp; Departmental OKRs will largely impact success at Current Mobile.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agree to Disagree &amp;amp; Commit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; -Voice concerns in a respectful &amp;amp; appropriate manner directly to your manager or the Executive Team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assume Positive Intent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Always start from the idea that a person meant well or was doing their best, no matter what they say or do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Are Offering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;***We are a remote-first company so this position is 100% remote from anywhere that can overlap with US CST / EST hours***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participation in the company&#39;s equity &amp;amp; token plan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We pay out individual bonuses every two months in accordance with our bi-monthly OKRs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Health, dental, and vision insurance with employer contribution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with highly curated high-caliber people.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Celebrate employee personal milestones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Remote team-building activities every 6-8 weeks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Virtual happy hours &amp;amp; virtual coffee buddies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bonus.ly - we use bonus.ly as a way to recognize and reward employees for their hard work + commitment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monthly virtual yoga + meditation classes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We follow the “12 PM to 1 PM CST Break” - no meetings during this time to encourage team members to take a break in their workday!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://current.us/jobs/?gh_jid=5722710002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/351812/Current_Media.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[current@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[38be4d80-6e57-4589-a599-b71d9fc28633]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Current Media]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Engineer, CoinDesk Indices]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://coindesk.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About TradeBlock&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;TradeBlock is a wholly owned subsidiary of CoinDesk, servicing financial firms with crypto currency trading technology, institutional-grade market data, as well as blockchain data and analytics. We are a technology company focused on building the future of finance by developing robust data infrastructure for blockchain networks and crypto markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for candidates excited to shape this future by contributing to the crypto and blockchain industries through an industry-leading firm. This full-time role offers a competitive base salary, comprehensive medical/dental/vision benefits, flexible time-off and a rewarding work environment rooted in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/coindesk-way&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The CoinDesk way&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our data engineers build and maintain the technology underpinning our market data and index infrastructure. They are responsible for core software development, data ingestion, transformation and distribution, as well as measuring and improving the performance of our systems. The ideal candidate will have experience in crypto currencies, capital markets and/or FX. Deep Linux and AWS experience is important, as well as experience working with complex data-processing pipelines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage multiple API integrations (REST, Web Socket and FIX)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop scalable and robust architecture for the existing state of our infrastructure as well as its future state while contributing to its maintenance and improvement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write reliable, reusable and efficient code and APIs to support our infrastructure and product requirements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analyze performance and identify bottlenecks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Contribute to the status and health monitoring systems of our infrastructure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide quick responses to production issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Contribute technical input and knowledge to the planning, design, and requirements process of new products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Well versed in Javascript (node.js) and Python.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with large data sets, preferably Redis, and PostgreSQL.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of AWS infrastructure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of Linux.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency with communication APIs (HTTP short and long polling, HTTP streaming, REST, WebSockets).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Preferred&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with C.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with FIX.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years experience with Linux.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years experience with AWS.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years experience with Redis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in crypto currencies, FX, or capital markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Technologies&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;AWS, PostgreSQL, Linux, Redis, Python, Node.js, C/C++, HAProxy, Javascript, Graphite/Grafana, Ansible, Nginx, Python, Django, Git&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EQUAL OPPORTUNITY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In an effort to attract, retain, develop and promote the most qualified individuals, CoinDesk is committed to treating all applicants and employees in a nondiscriminatory manner with respect to the terms and conditions of employment, without regard to race, color, religion or belief, sex, national or ethnic origin, ancestry, age, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status/service, physical or mental disability, or any other classification protected by applicable law. This mandate governs all aspects of employment, including recruitment, selection, promotion, training, education, social and recreation programs, compensation, discipline, termination and access to benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For more information on our DEI initiatives, please visit: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/dei/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://www.coindesk.com/dei/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACCOMMODATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinDesk is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the application process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:accommodations@coindesk.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accomodations@coindesk.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVID-19 VACCINATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;COVID-19 vaccination is required for all employees whose position is based out of the NYC office. However, CoinDesk will consider accommodations for disability- and religious-based reasons on a case by case basis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; (edited)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/coindesk/jobs/5711323002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145913/coindesk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coindesk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[459b477b-1ae2-43d1-a1a8-7a40fbe3f487]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sr. Director, Business Development, RippleX]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;RippleX, the crypto native business unit of Ripple, is looking to bring on board an amazing and dynamic leader who can build and manage a team of professionals to pursue and grow a range of business opportunities in crypto and decentralized technologies. Areas of pursuit include DeFi (decentralized finance), Dapps (decentralized applications), CBDCs, NFTs, Stablcoins, Carbon Credits and more.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The RippleX’s team is extremely active as it is able to leverage the Company’s significant balance sheet to support partnership opportunities, investments, and grants in the developer community and broader crypto partnership ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ideal candidate will be an experienced and dynamic business development leader with a track record of managing high performance business development teams, a proven history of closing first-of-kind deals and building new businesses, and has the foresight to think through how nations, companies, developers, and consumers will adapt to the inevitable shift from centralization to decentralization. That is the scope of the opportunity. Come join us if you see it too, and know how to get it done.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU’LL DO:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Set the direction, strategy and priorities for RippleX Business Development - globally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build a partnerships program at RippleX to establish XRPL as the preferred L1 blockchain for decentralized apps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead, manage, motivate, and coach a distributed team of high performing business development professionals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop new opportunities for partnership and XRPL ecosystem expansion (e.g. consumer apps, gaming).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage with CEOs and leadership teams in the world of crypto/blockchain - they are your peers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a player-coach, directly; structure, negotiate, and execute high profile deals with projects and companies in the crypto ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with the RippleX leadership team to help set the strategy and direction for the business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep collaboration across functions to solve problems, ideate, drive results and unlock value with partners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE’RE LOOKING FOR:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are passionate about crypto, developers, and the move to a decentralized world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You know how to inspire, lead, and get it done.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have keen product and business instincts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can vet entrepreneurs because you are one, or have been one.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You work and play well with colleagues and partners because you have a high EQ, are self aware, and understand it&#39;s just more fun that way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are driven to succeed and comfortable being held accountable to results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can communicate an idea in a memo, a presentation, or to an audience of 5000.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have experience, motivation, and demonstrated results growing teams and talent, and celebrate team successes. Helping teams achieve breakout success.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;15+ years strategic business development or deal making/closing experience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our UK/EU applicant privacy notice &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3668626?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Project Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">About Celsius Network</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Celsius addresses the financial needs of today’s consumers worldwide through a democratized interest income and lending platform accessible via a mobile app. With a mission to put unparalleled economic freedom in the hands of the people, and a core belief that financial services should only do what is in the best interests of the community, Celsius is a modern platform where membership provides access to curated financial services that are not available through traditional financial institutions. Crypto holders can earn high-yield compounding interest by transferring coins to their Celsius Wallet and can borrow fiat currency against their crypto collateral at the lowest interest rates in the space.  </span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">The Celsius team is committed to doing good and doing well. We believe in the power of disruption and the importance of decentralization to create a new system that acts in the best interest of everyone. Each member of our team brings something unique and innovative to the table, but the common thread that links us together is our passion for blockchain, equality, and leading the next financial revolution that changes the equation to bring power back to the people. </span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Position: Project Manager, PMO</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Responsibilities: </span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Lead programs and projects across the global business</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Coach, guide and support Projects across the business functions</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Work on a variety of cross functional projects and programs</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Evaluate and monitor project portfolio </span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Performs regular project analysis and make recommendations</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Work from a holistic, strategic view when required</span></span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Requirements:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Undergraduate Degree</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">4+ years of Project Management experience in both Agile and waterfall methodology</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Exceptional analytical and quantitative problem-solving skills</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Experience with Atlassian products</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Ability to engage and work collaboratively across many different levels of the organization</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Ability to communicate complex ideas effectively – both verbally and in writing</span></span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Excellent business acumen, analytical, and statistical skills</span></span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 13px;">Celsius is currently operating fully remotely while navigating COVID-19 guidelines, however, Celsius has offices in Hoboken, New York City, London and Tel Aviv and employs remote employees based in cities all around the world. </span></span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xW6QWaNfysw&ab_channel=CelsiusNetwork" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=439&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/731816/celsius_network.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celsius@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5fa72b05-b42d-48a9-806e-c3fdccb06776]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Executive Director]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Securitize]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://securitize.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Palm Beach]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span>Securitize is the global fintech that’s creating real-time access for investors to invest and trade in the private markets, and in turn, for companies to raise the capital they need to grow. Recognized as a top 50 blockchain company, we are the industry-leading and the first end-to-end digital securities issuance and compliance platform operating on the blockchain.</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span>We just received $48m in Series B from Wall Street &amp; venture capital funding from top investors to aggressively expand our teams across New York, Miami, San Francisco, and remote offices. We are a global team comprised of top blockchain and financial industry talent-based globally, based in Tel Aviv, Buenos Aires, Tokyo, New York, and San Francisco. We’re backed by leading financial institutions and blockchain investors, including Blockchain Capital, Morgan Stanley, Banco Santander, and Coinbase.</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span>Location:</span></span><span> This is a remote opportunity.</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span>Securitize ‘s CEO is seeking a trust advisor and a strategic <span style="font-weight: bold;">Executive Business Director</span> to coordinate and manage the essential activities of our business, making strategic plans to ensure all business functions are efficient and at their most productive. The ideal candidate will serve as a trusted advisor to the CEO and help to set the Securitize strategic direction. The successful candidate will serve as the strategic partner to address opportunities for growth while maintaining discipline in cost management, financial management, and capital structure. </span></p>
<p><span>----Key opportunities may include targeted mergers, acquisitions, capital expansions, restructuring, strategic alliances and partnerships, joint ventures, operational investments, and possible portfolio divestitures. You must be a creative and results-driven thinker, an excellent problem solver and possess incredible interpersonal skills to effectively manage staff and act as the central contact for all business communications.</span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span>Responsibilities:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Spearhead special projects: lead a metrics overhaul, conduct market research on an adjacent business opportunity, run an acquisition process (end-to-end).</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Lead the development of the strategic plan/framework for the organization while adhering to direction set by the CEO and Board of Directors. This includes formalizing and leading the strategic planning process, focusing on long term trends and outlook, and competitive intelligence.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Co-lead the process of developing the building blocks of the strategic plan including working with finance to ensure the financial impact of each component is projected.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Identify, engage, establish, and manage productive working partnerships to support Securitize products and technology platform, while developing and strengthening the ecosystem.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Drive identification and integration activities, processes, and change management requirements.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Maintaining strong understanding of client business and strategy, economic models, financial results, industry trends, and operational developments.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Support the fundraising process and own financial and operations support.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Prepare Board Meetings and Boards Packs, manage investor updates and support in Investor pitch decks.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Have experience with M&amp;A and various financing instruments.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 13px;"> </span><span>Drive executive-level operations – strategic and OKR planning, and business reviews.</span></li>
<li><span> Support in strategic tasks and projects of the founders and the CEO, e.g., go-to-market strategies, partnerships, including high-level aspects of tasks intersecting with vertical units, such as core hiring, business intelligence, growth marketing, product strategy.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span>Additionally, you will:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Coordinate strategic business initiatives and guide to completion.</span></li>
<li><span>Manage logistics with the Board of Directors, including meeting dates and agendas, reports, and other meeting preparation, communicating with the Board on all the above</span></li>
<li><span>Act as a main consultant to the CEO.</span></li>
<li><span>Work with and/or lead cross-functional teams.</span></li>
<li><span>Assist CEO with internal communication, and ensure any problems are resolved.</span></li>
<li><span>Keep CEO abreast on current company climate (employee wellbeing, project statuses, new proposals, etc.)</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span>Requirements:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li>Minimum of 6 years experience in a consultant management role</li>
<li>Fintech experience is highly preferred</li>
<li><span style="font-weight: bold;">Required Knowledge:</span> Must have extensive knowledge of the crypto/blockchain ecosystem.</li>
<li><span> Seasoned professional, with a strong strategy orientation, who has previously held several business and operational roles in fast paced and complex environments, especially in start-up / entrepreneurial environment.</span></li>
<li><span> Experience with operational, accounting, tax, legal, regulatory on M&amp;A.</span></li>
<li><span> Ability to present in front of management teams and board of directors with confidence and persuasion.</span></li>
<li><span> Strong knowledge of finance, investment, and equity markets as well as knowledge of SEC disclosure regulations.</span></li>
<li><span> Ability to successfully manage multiple projects from conception to completion in a fast-paced team environment.</span></li>
<li><span> Strategic thinker capable of providing clear, balanced advice/counsel on a broad range of strategic and complex management, product and go to market issues.</span></li>
<li><span> Superb communication, facilitation, negotiation, and listening skills, accompanied by the ability to know how and when to influence, persuade, direct, challenge, and relinquish control.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">The idea candidate will exhibit the following Chief of Staff attributes:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"><span style="font-weight: bold;">Super Organizer</span> — An ideal candidate needs to be a methodical organizer. </span></li>
<li><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"><span style="font-weight: bold;">Strategic Thinker</span> — The individuals must see the big picture of things. A strategic mindset helps align detailed work to the big picture strategy, as well as evaluate what is urgent versus important.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"><span style="font-weight: bold;">"Get things done" mentality- </span>The CEO needs to know that responsibilities or tasks are guaranteed to get done. </span></li>
<li><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"><span style="font-weight: bold;">Trusted Operator</span> — A trusted advisor across the entire leadership team- often exposed to sensitive or confidential information in the normal course of executing the role. Consequently, the person in that role has to innately appreciate how to manage such information in confidence.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span>Join an awesome company entering a hyper-growth phase</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Unlimited Paid Time Off</span></li>
<li><span>Bonus program </span></li>
<li><span>Remote work environment</span></li>
<li><span>Company paid professional development </span></li>
<li><span>100% Medical/dental/vision insurance</span></li>
<li><span>401K</span>
<ul></ul>
</li>
</ul>
<ul></ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-7Nr4euKbfk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://securitize.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=47&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/294965/seciritize.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[securitize@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6fa7bf1d-9e9f-4ac1-9f2a-f1de480d8620]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Securitize]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Service Operations Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Revolut]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.revolut.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Portugal]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">ABOUT THE TEAM</b></div><div>Our Customer Service team is the public face of the company and provides first-class front-line support to our millions of customers. We are also internal customer-champions, working with product teams to ensure users stay at the forefront of everything Revolut does. We're a truly diverse, international group and we work across three European offices.</div><div><br></div><div>We hire people who know how to act fast, look for root causes and solve problems – not follow scripts. We expect every person to drive change and bring value to Revolut by contributing more than just resolving tickets. We dedicate a lot of time for personal and professional growth and as a result, by the time our agents "graduate" support they are fully trained to rock in any other role in the company (and are in demand from lots of teams!).</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">ABOUT THE ROLE</b></div><div>We’re looking for a skilled <b>Technical Service Operations Lead </b>to manage operations teams (up to 100 employees) and collaborate with product teams. A person in this role is responsible for Technical Operations Stream (bugs / outages / technical issues filtering) and working closely (functional management) with Engineering Team and CTO.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>This role is about developing a firm foundation for our operations and continuing to innovate on ways to scale it quickly and effortlessly. We want you to focus particularly on our customer satisfaction and process compliance in this role by finding a balance between consistency and positive experiences for all our customers.</div><div><br></div><div>In addition, this role will be assisting in building out the function globally. You’ll need to combine a sharp eye and discipline for delivery with a creative and process driven mindset to seek out and solve some of our most complex global challenges.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Location: Porto or 100% remote from any other location in Portugal</b></div><br/>WHAT YOU WILL BE DOING:<br/><li>Responsible for the day-to-day management of Team Leaders group with responsibility for separate products (up to 30 employees)</li><li>Daily, weekly, monthly, and quarterly operations KPI review and management</li><li>Develop a process for improving user CSAT without sacrificing quality parameters</li><li>Help build and implement processes and standards for delivery through the global network</li><li>Demonstrate excellent business analytics to perform root cause analysis activities</li><li>Align strategic program objectives</li><li>Responsibility for managing the performance of Team Leaders, coach and mentor them to reach their potential, always leading by example</li><li>Data Analysis of trending issues and continuous improvement of processes</li><li>Ensure correct implementation of staff training, quality assurance, development and performance programs in conjunction with Training Leads and Operational Manager</li><li>Drive continuous Support Improvement and Improve Problem Resolution times</li><li>Work with Product Owners to resolve any backend app errors</li><li>Incident Management as well as escalations to vendors </li><br/>WHAT YOU WILL NEED<br/><li>Experience in managing up to 30-50 employees</li><li>People management experience with strong coaching and mentoring skills</li><li>Excellent technical and analytical aptitude</li><li>SQL skills</li><li>Good understanding of crisis management framework</li><li>Demonstrated ability and commitment to go “Above and Beyond” the daily expectations of role duties when required</li><div><br></div><div>Other skills:</div><li>Track record of resolving mobile application errors  would be beneficial</li><li>Knowledge, understanding of frontend/backend would be beneficial</li><li>Ability to handle multiple priorities and meet deadlines in stressful situations</li><li>Queue, spike and Backlog management experience</li><div><br></div><div><br></div><div>Some international travel might be required</div><div><b style="font-size: 11pt">A little about us…</b>When Revolut was founded in 2015, we had a vision to build a sustainable, digital alternative to traditional big banks. Our mission now is to help our customers improve their financial health, empower them to have more control, and promote financial cohesion across the communities in which we operate. Launching into 2021 with 15 million Personal customers and over half a million Business customers only reinforced our belief in the vast need across the world for better financial services.</div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 11pt">What we’re looking for…</b>Revolut is being scaled up by people all around the world who share our vision. We’re looking for people who align with our five core values: we believe that we Get it Done because we Think Deeper and are strongly rooted in the Dream Team. We Never Settle hence why we always Deliver Wow. You want to join a community of forward-thinking people - we are here for you. We believe in empowering our Revoluters in their work, giving them autonomy and ownership of what they do. We want everyone at Revolut to own their story and their successes - working with us means you’re not just another cog in the machine.</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">THE BENEFITS</b></div><div>• Competitive salary</div><div>• Excellent training and guidance from our team</div><div>• Roll with a free Revolut Metal subscription</div><div>• Private medical care</div><div>• Daily meal allowance</div><div><br></div><div><i style="font-size: 15px">By applying for the above role, you confirm that you have reviewed our&nbsp;<a href="https://www.revolut.com/legal/data-privacy-for-candidates">Data Privacy Notice for Candidates</a>.</i></div><div><span style="font-size: 16px"><i>#LIremote</i></span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EE2yoffomOc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/revolut/099683c2-4efe-4c6e-97ba-a1366bdf4668/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/215308/revolut.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[revolut@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bc6bf986-f138-47a8-a964-82b24f8843a0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Revolut]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
