<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Tax / Tax Director]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[teammanagerhead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>We are looking to recruit a Head of Tax to help Crypto.com in its rapidly growing business.</p><p>This role offers the successful candidate a fantastic opportunity to manage the tax affairs of a business experiencing significant growth in a very dynamic industry.</p><p>Reporting to EVP, Finance, the Head of Tax will be responsible for the overall tax affairs for Crypto.com, including tax compliance, oversight of the relevant tax returns, tax planning and managing Crypto.com’s tax team.</p><p>This is a global role covering all Crypto.com’s entities and the successful candidate will work closely with external service providers and advisors, as well as the broader finance team across the globe and the related teams within the group.</p><p><br><strong>Responsibilities</strong><br><br></p><ul> <li>Direct and oversee the Crypto.com’s overall tax management - ensure compliance with applicable tax regulations, the accurate completion of all tax returns globally, tax strategy, planning, policies, and all operational aspects for tax matters</li> <li>Manage all transfer pricing and all cross border arrangements from a tax perspective</li> <li>Provide tax advisory and support to internal stakeholders for new business initiatives such as new products launch and M&amp;A deals</li> <li>Manage the Crypto.com tax team and the external providers/advisers used</li> <li>Manage all tax related queries raised by auditors and  tax authorities to deal with any </li> <li>Monitor any changes in legislation and its implications on the Group and related entities  </li> <li>Recommend and implement process improvements related to tax filing, systems, etc</li> <li>Ensure appropriate policies, procedures and controls are in place </li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li> CPA/ relevant Tax qualification</li> <li>Ideally 8+ years professional work experience in Tax; knowledge of crypto related tax subjects is a plus.</li> <li>Solid experience  in International Tax and Transfer Pricing is highly advantageous </li> <li>Excellent project management, presentation and interpersonal skills</li> <li>Detail oriented, analytical, with an ability to multitask in a high growth environment</li> <li>Strong willingness to roll up their sleeves to get the job done </li> <li>Passionate about start-ups and the growth of digital assets </li> <li>Excellent command of spoken and written English</li> <li>Good to have crypto knowledge</li> <li> <strong>Estimate and monitor relevant cash flow impacts</strong> for tax related payments<br><br><br> </li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Flat team. Work side by side with the co-founding team</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing a brand new product from scratch alongside with a talented team</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/4ED2FFA483/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, Growth Marketing Intelligence]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ava Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.avalabs.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Miami, Florida, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT AVALANCHE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Avalanche is an open-source platform for launching decentralized finance applications and enterprise blockchain deployments in one interoperable, highly scalable ecosystem. Developers who build on Avalanche can easily create powerful, reliable, and secure applications and custom blockchain networks with complex rulesets or build on existing private or public subnets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT AVA LABS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ava Labs makes it simple to launch finance applications using blockchain technology–with highly scalable and efficient networks, customizable public and private blockchains, the capability to create any digital asset, and more. We are empowering people to build an open, simple, and democratic internet of finance that enables the world to have a more prosperous future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ava Labs was founded by Cornell computer scientists who brought on talent from Wall Street to execute their vision. The company has received funding from Andreessen Horowitz, Initialized Capital, and Polychain Capital, with angel investments from Balaji Srinivasan and Naval Ravikant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead internal data driven projects, overseeing a Data Science team that’s primary focus will be on-chain data &amp;amp; analytics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create and run viral campaigns to capture wide audiences on Twitter, Reddit, Discord, and other platforms to target both individual and institutional investors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with marketing to analyze investor sentiment on current products, and future projects that are coming down the pipeline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Find creative ways of using data to help drive awareness/interest of Avalanche and it&#39;s ecosystem partners through social media campaigns (TikTok, Twitter, Reddit, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analyze data and track metrics to optimize campaigns and ads&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Leverage modern marketing tools and automate your process to scale&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mentor fellow team members in your SME areas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;WHAT YOU WILL BRING&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BS in Computer Science or a mathematics related discipline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;7+ years of hands on professional experience&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of leading multidisciplinary and collaborative teams in a global/distributed capacity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In depth knowledge of cryptocurrency, DeFi, blockchain marketplaces and ecosystems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Some working knowledge of growth marketing, developing campaigns/viral social media strategies using data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Thinks strategically with regard to content, messaging, strategy, narrative and storytelling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mastery of modern Data Science tools and languages.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expert level knowledge of blockchain media outlets and forums&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Data driven and quant focused&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to automate tasks and campaign process flows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h6&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/mWBzFmzzBAg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/avalabs/jobs/4237826004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/571953/avalabs-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[avalabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[a4029032-6a83-4107-89a8-330ee9cccbd1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ava Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Developer Experience Lead - Smart Contracts]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOHK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://iohk.io]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>At IO Global, we believe that unlocking the potential of the community is essential to the success of the system, which is why developer experience is so important.</p> <p>The Developer Experience Lead will build a keen sense of what tools, libraries, and capabilities DApp developers are seeking. They are both the voice of the customer and the development lead, shaping the end-to-end developer experience. The role will involve conceptualizing, defining, and leading the work on various tools and frameworks to make development easier.</p><p><strong>Your mission </strong></p><ul> <li>Develop solutions such as developer tools, libraries, and add-ons to improve Cardano’s developer experience, particularly the end-to-end experience of building DApps using Plutus.</li> <li>Validate and experiment with early/pre-release feature developments to help ensure a robust and consistent developer experience.</li> <li>Identify and ideate key features, tools, and libraries that can make the process of developing and testing smart contracts easier, faster, and secure.</li> <li>Prepare well-informed reports of developers’ needs and detail the business and technical requirements to implement a solution.</li> <li>Author and engage with the developer community via documentation, curated presentations, demonstrations, and learning guides to make it easy for developers to adopt and begin building on Cardano.</li> <li>Build rapport and foster relationships with the Cardano ecosystem as a researcher/evangelist to build an understanding of their developer experience, common issues, and feature wants.</li> </ul><p><strong>Your expertise </strong> </p> <ul> <li>Haskell experience, either professional or otherwise.</li> <li>Strong communication skills, paired with a track record of being able to build meaningful rapport with the developer communities</li> <li>Strong reasoning capabilities with the drive to arrive at the root cause of developers’ wants</li> <li>Enjoy being a “force multiplier” for other groups</li> <li>Prior experience working as a developer and alongside development communities</li> <li>High-level understanding of programming concepts, data structures, and algorithms.</li> <li>This role is analogous to a UX lead role in that a UX lead role represents the voice of the customer, which is an end user, whereas the DevX lead is the voice of the developer using our infrastructure and tools to build DApps</li> </ul><p><strong>Location</strong></p><p>IOG is a fully distributed organization and therefore this is a remote position. Due to team distribution we are ideally searching for someone in a European or US East Coast timezone.  </p><p><strong>All Colleagues</strong></p><ul> <li>Flexible schedule</li> <li>Remote work - ability to work anywhere</li> <li>Laptop reimbursement</li> <li>New starter package to buy hardware essentials (headphones, monitor, etc)</li> <li>Learning &amp; Development opportunities</li> <li>Competitive PTO and Sick Leave plan</li> </ul><p><strong>US Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits coverage through Anthem with 100% premium cost covered by IO Global for the employee and dependents</li> <li>Health Savings Account</li> <li>Life Insurance</li> </ul><p><strong>UK Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Monthly Health Stipend to use towards any wellness or medical coverage/service</li> <li>Pension</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EM-XkuQdUq8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/io-global/j/09EED1AC6B/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143583/iohk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iohk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b89f946-6d3b-434f-aa32-f0e84ecb2992]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOHK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Project Manager (Europe Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.bitfinex.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">Founded in 2012, Bitfinex is a digital asset trading platform offering state-of-the-art services for digital currency traders and global liquidity providers. We're on a mission to create the most innovative cryptocurrencies exchange. This is a unique opportunity, a rare window of time at the tipping point of the financial evolution. Much like the early days of the internet, blockchain technology faces complex new challenges and having the best team plays a pivotal role in success.</p>
<p dir="ltr"> </p>
<p dir="ltr">Our team is fully remote and globally distributed to capture the best talent from around the world. So far our company has grown fast and stayed lean to secure its place as a leader in the space.</p>
<p dir="ltr"> </p>
<p dir="ltr">If you get excited about being in an industry that is breaking new ground and have confidence you can conquer the most challenging feats we'll encounter, we want to talk to you. Join us, and help lay the foundation for a decentralized future</p>
<p dir="ltr"> </p>
<p dir="ltr">We are currently looking for:</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong>Project Manager (Remote)</strong></h2>
<h3 dir="ltr"><strong>​</strong><strong>Job description</strong></h3>
<p dir="ltr">As a Project Manager in the Product team, you will work with fellow project, program and product managers and with members of the engineering and design teams to execute our business and product strategies across the various Bitfinex products and services. </p>
<p dir="ltr">As a Project Manager at Bitfinex you will take ultimate responsibility for one key project. Of all product team members you are closest to the actual planning and implementation of individual projects, so expect to get your hands dirty. You will manage release cycles, running release sprints and retros; collaborate with the development, marketing, etc teams to break work down, taking large-scale projects and turning them into manageable tasks; track &amp; report on progress to Program and Product Managers, and other stakeholders, to ensure business needs are being met; and generally do whatever it takes to ensure that things stay on track, figuring out alternatives if they don’t. In a nutshell, you own the project deliverables and support your team to deliver the highest standards of quality in a timely manner.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Project Managers have the opportunity to progress into: senior project management positions where they work on the most important projects in the company; program management roles that oversee multiple projects and a team of project managers; or product management roles focusing on our customers, our competitors, and business strategy. </p>
<p dir="ltr"><br /></p><h3 dir="ltr"><strong>Responsibilities</strong></h3>
<ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Align project objectives with company goals, and make sure the project team is clear on objectives. Act as the voice of the product team and key stakeholders in their absence. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Ensure that the project targets are met within the project timeline and costs, and monitor and control all stages of the project life cycle. Suggest reasonable solutions and plans for the problems in the process of the project. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Coordinate the progress and quality of each stage of the project to ensure the smooth progress of the project and delivery on time.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Where necessary, lead communications with external partners supporting the project. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Lead process of issue identification and resolution.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Monitor and manage scope. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Manage all documentation, project tracking, and reporting within the product team and cross-functionally where necessary. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Streamline new token listings facilitating cross-department communication.</p></li></ul>
<p><h2>Requirements:</h2></p><ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Minimum 2 years in a project management role working on software development or financial services.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Excellent time-management and organizational habits, and the ability to develop these habits in the teams you join.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Self-starter attitude, strong problem solving skills and sense of responsibility.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Strong analytical and communication skills, and the ability to produce concise reports ongoing to management covering progress of projects, with an aim to improving decision-making on business strategy and product development.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Comprehensive understanding of project management methodologies and best practices, and experience implementing fast-moving, large teams.</p></li></ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fx7gryqZwzw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://bitfinex.recruitee.com/o/project-manager-europe-remote-london/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/227432/Bitfinex_Long_Logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ricardo.pinheiro@bitfinex.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[a48bec57-75b8-41d5-9cff-1828d315ba59]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Liquidity Support Account Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Latoken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote Worldwide]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong></strong>LATOKEN exchange has 2 million accounts including 900k+ users of our Android app rated 4.4 by 25+ thousands of reviews. We leverage the next tech to make account opening as easy as Instagram. The technology and our Olympic sports culture can make us the first billion users digital wallet needed to free people to manage their financial life. Today, is a great moment to join us as crypto is expanding into mainstream financial market and <a>ex CFO of JP Morgan joined</a> our advisory board and <a>2 presidents joined us</a> in Davos.<br><br>For the past 3 years we have been developing our own blockchain (called “Lachain”) and we are now building the DeFi ecosystem based on it (including DEX, dApp, IDO, NFT etc) and launched our <a>mainnet</a>. <a>Here is our backlog.</a></p><p><strong>Mission:</strong> Top liquidity for listed projects.</p><p><strong>Mission description: </strong>Projeсts need a high-quality Market-Making service with top liquidity, as well as low slippage, narrow spreads and high volumes to attract organic traders.<br><br><strong>Key PROBLEM's</strong>:</p><ul><li>In 90 days reach Client retention rate, quarter to quarter &gt; 90%</li><li>Client response time, weekly average &lt; 30 minutes</li><li>Client satisfaction rate, weekly average &gt; 4.5 out of 5</li></ul><p><strong>How</strong>: Stay in touch during working and at times non-working hours to assist clients with their inquiries, inform on account status &amp; resolve client queries, assign client issues to team members &amp; chase to completion, monitor working capital. <br><strong>Constraints</strong>:100% of clients' inquiries and issues are addressed within 12 hours. <br><br><strong>Main performance number:</strong> LS services fees<br><strong>Second performance number:</strong> Number of active MM clients<br><strong>Third performance number:</strong> Liquidity success rate<br><br><strong>Functions:</strong><br>- LS Client : Manage the accounts of LS clients, inform them about working capital top-up need in time, be there to answer their questions in a timely manner.<br>- Deals : Negotiate and close LS deals with clients already listed or to be listed on LATOKEN, pitch our services to them and bring in revenue.<br>- Training : Grow skills through LS workshops and trainings.<br>- Workflow : Follow LATOKEN's teamwide workflow and keep CRM and dashboards well-organized and clear.<br>- Up or Out : Grow to Product Manager in 1 year or free space for other champions.<br><br><strong>Requirement skills and experience:</strong><br>1+ year experience in trading on crypto or stock exchanges, Market Making services. <br>3+ years experience in B2B Sales/Business DevelopmentExperience in Customer Support/Account Management will be a plus.<br>Experience with crypto/token analytics is a strong advantage.<br>Capability to grow as a product manager is a plus.<br>SQL queries / Python skills as a plus.<br>Ability to work in fast-paced environment.<br>Fluent English.</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> Trading, Market Making, Crypto Exchanges, CLS, Altonomy, Korion Labs, Bluesky Capital, B2B Sales, Blockchain, Keyrock, Trading Algorithms, Liquidity Support, Business Development</p><p><strong><br></strong></p><p></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ikbGulIPQs0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.breezy.hr/p/8c6d14426dbb01-liquidity-support-account-manager/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/178323/latoken.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[latoken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[ad8a3cbd-f1ed-4400-b372-af94f5f06cb4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Latoken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[People Operations Co-ordinator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.elliptic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>As digital assets and cryptocurrency become more widely adopted every day,, our products are essential to ensure cryptocurrency is safe and accessible to all.  Our solutions help to prevent financial crime and allow cryptocurrencies to be used for good. Our products are used by some of the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, financial institutions and government agencies to screen over $1 billion of transactions every single week.  </p> <p>Elliptic is backed by some of the top VCs: SBI Group, Albion VC, Octopus Ventures, SignalFire, Paladin Capital, Santander InnoVentures, and Digital Currency Group, and we have grown globally with teams in the UK, USA, Singapore and Tokyo. </p><br>To achieve our mission, we depend on our incredible team of Elliptites.  <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/life-at-elliptic" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Our values</a> are reflected in everything we do and every decision we make, both internally and outwardly to our customers.  We actively encourage Elliptities to challenge the status quo and allow the freedom to innovate and learn every day.  We encourage new ideas and learning, whether that’s through collaboration, our curiosity sessions, or utilising your professional development budget - personal growth is important to us all. <p><br></p><p><strong>The impact you will have:</strong></p><p>At Elliptic we know that our people are our best asset and you will be responsible for delivering our team an amazing employee experience! </p> <p>You will join the People team, and alongside being the first point of contact for the US team you will be responsible for onboarding new team members and supporting and improving all our people processes.. Your role will be instrumental in ensuring that we can scale effectively and efficiently!</p><p><br></p><p><strong>What you will do:</strong></p><p>You will help provide a great all round employee experience by:</p><ul> <li>Delivering a world class remote onboarding experience for new joiners including:</li> <li>Delivering the offboarding process for leavers, ensuring exiting employees are supported during their last months at Elliptic and stakeholders have the information they need to ensure timely deactivation of accounts and systems</li> </ul><ul> <li>Supporting employees across the organisation in a range of People issues and being the US teams first point of contact</li> <li>Creating employee lifecycle communications, such as letters outlining promotions and pay rises, and references</li> <li>Reporting on People data, such as annual leave and turnover rates and using these to drive people decisions and support strategic people initiative</li> <li>Supporting the delivery of our People processes and frameworks including the engagement survey, performance review, compensation review etc</li> <li>Researching and benchmarking compensation levels for new and existing roles</li> <li>Championing and embodying our values and behaviours, preparing our quarterly value awards and celebrating our Chief Value Officers</li> <li>Additional ad hoc people initiatives and duties</li> </ul><p><strong>You will be a great fit here if you:</strong></p><ul> <li>Love helping others and being a go-to person in the business</li> <li>Are approachable and friendly, with the ability to put people at ease and engage with people across all areas and levels of the business</li> <li>Embrace receiving feedback and using this to continually improve the experiences of employees and the processes that support this</li> <li>Are extremely organised, with a genuine desire for producing high quality outputs and excellent attention to detail</li> <li>Are technically savvy, comfortable picking up new systems and helping onboard others to new systems too</li> <li>Are a real team player - this is a truly cross functional role, and is key to our success</li> <li>Are passionate about the importance of the role the People team play in the delivery of company goals </li> </ul> <p><strong>Our ideal candidate has:</strong></p><p>Experience in a People and/or Operations role that covers:</p><ul> <li>Managing onboarding for new joiners, with a focus on delivering an incredible experience at all times to both new joiners and their future managers</li> <li>A generalist understanding of HR policies, laws and procedures in the U.S.</li> <li>Experience managing sensitive data and keeping it accurate and up to date</li> <li>Experience managing an HRIS </li> <li>Experience with excel and using data to drive decision making </li> </ul> <p><strong>Bonus Points for:</strong></p><ul> <li>Knowledge and understanding of HR policies, laws, and procedures in the U.K., Singapore and/or Japan</li> <li>Knowledge of BambooHR</li> <li>Experience delivering remote onboarding </li> <li>Experience in a rapidly scaling software company</li> </ul><ul> <li>Competitive salary</li> <li>Share options</li> <li>Private health insurance</li> <li>Strong focus on personal development, with $1,000 per annum personal training budget &amp; LinkedIn Learning subscription</li> <li>Collaborative, flexible and friendly environment: We understand that flexibility is the key to maintaining a healthy work-life balance, especially at the moment. We’re working remotely right now and are carefully considering our strategy for remote working in the longer term</li> <li>Social events, which include monthly team lunch on us, quarterly full day events and an annual company 3-day event - this year these are taking place virtually</li> <li>Enhanced parental leave; we provide eligible employees, regardless of gender or whether they become a parent by birth or adoption, 16 weeks fully-paid leave and job-protected leave.</li> </ul><p><br></p><p>We know Diversity and Inclusion is much deeper than just hiring, but it’s important for us to mention it here.  We welcome and embrace individuals of all backgrounds and identities at Elliptic, and this is an ongoing priority for us.  We know incredible people don’t all think in the same way.  We want to be challenged every day.  We believe our diverse team of individuals underpins this by bringing creative thinking and innovation to Elliptic every day.  We are committed to creating a diverse, inclusive and equitable workplace, so we welcome applications from everyone, even if you may not think you fit all of the requirements of our roles.  We foster an environment of psychological safety, where everyone feels comfortable to bring their whole self to work. </p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ebOLNjlYiNg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/elliptic/j/369F89E4AB/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145877/elliptic.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[elliptic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[fefe721f-d5ba-4eb0-9b9b-f4156a27cb2b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Risk Operation Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Crypto.com</strong></p>  <p>Founded in 2016, Crypto.com today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest growing crypto app, along with the Crypto.com Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the Crypto.com Exchange and Crypto.com DeFi Wallet. Recently launched, Crypto.com NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment and sports.</p>  <p>Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, CCSS Level 3, ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks. </p>  <p>With over 2,600 people in offices across the Americas, Europe and Asia, Crypto.com is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a href="https://crypto.com" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com</a></p><p><strong>Responsibilities</strong></p><ul> <li>Assist in the operation processes related to new product listing, product parameters and model parameters updates.</li> <li>Proactively identify, report and ensure transparency of risks, and immediate escalation of material issues to risk managers.</li> <li>Support risk managers and take a lead in development and automation of risk reporting and analysis.</li> <li>Provide support in handling and reporting data elements to meet regulatory requirements.</li> <li>Assist with documentation of risk reporting procedures and ensure in line with models and methodology documentation.</li> <li>Assist in the daily risk reporting and monitoring of the markets and measuring the risk exposure of market makers' portfolios.</li> </ul><p><strong>Requirements</strong></p><ul> <li>Educated to undergraduate/master level in Computer Science / Maths or numerate subjects.</li> <li>Rigorous and focus on details, strong logical thinking and reasoning skills</li> <li>Proficient in Python (5 years of working experience) and SQL or noSQL data structure/ data model and database management. Working experience with time-series data, Pandas, Flask, Numpy is a must.</li> <li>Keen to develop and apply understanding of risk principles – Initial Margin, VaR, collateral haircuts, stress testing, back testing, liquidity stress testing.</li> <li>Experience related to Financial/ Risk management; exchange/clearing house risk management experience is a plus.</li> <li>Knowledge of crypto market, corporate action events and their impacts on the pricing adjustment is a plus</li> <li>Highly proficient written and verbal communication skills.</li> <li>Ability to coordinate within teams across businesses.</li> <li>Analytical and problem solving skills.</li> <li>Passionate about cryptocurrency and blockchain.</li> </ul><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1.</li> <li>Be the owner of your own learning curve.</li> <li>The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing a brand new product from scratch alongside with a talented team</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/046F7FEC5B/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[QA Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Strike]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://beta.strike.me/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Strike&#39;s mission is to build a more connected financial world.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strike allows users to send and receive money anywhere, instantly, with no fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strike is built on top of the Bitcoin network - the largest global, interoperable and open payments standard. Strike believes that open payment networks enable universal participation in the financial system, ushering in a new digital economy with truly borderless money transfers. Strike leverages Bitcoin’s open payment network to offer users the first global peer-to-peer payments app and a novel bitcoin-native neobanking experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Role:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a key member of our QA team, you’ll directly impact the lifeline of the business by maintaining a high bar for quality of our top rated iOS, Android and Web apps. You’ll own major features, working closely with different disciplines across the company.&lt;br&gt;We’re looking for an engineer that will grow with the company and is excited about Strike’s mission and potential. The person joining us must be comfortable with a team-first approach in a remote work environment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Building test plans for new features and improving existing test plans for feature updates and customer feedback&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Executing tests on our release candidates for iOS, Android and Web apps&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Owning features through inception, design feedback, implementation, and launch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with Product Designers, Product Managers, Backend Engineers, and Customer Support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Requirements:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience developing software using C#, JavaScript, React&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with automated test tools including TestCafé, Testing Library, Selenium, Waldo, xUnit&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with API tools including Swagger, Postman, Proxyman&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills and passion for tough technical problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and voice of customer experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience automating end to end UI tests for iOS, Android and Web clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with cross-functional teams in fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Additional Qualifications:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with consumer centric app testing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong sense of quality, product intuition and user empathy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience ensuring a consistent user experience across different platforms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-drive to improve the app experience above and beyond what’s outlined in the spec&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Bitcoin and Lightning Network protocol&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We do not make hiring decisions based on educational history whatsoever. Our founder is a college dropout. We employ high school dropouts, PhD candidates and everything in between. We do not hire credentials. We simply hire talented, passionate individuals who are excited to be a part of our team.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://strike.me/jobs?gh_jid=4247632004&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/712431/strike.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[strike@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[28384812-e332-465c-ba22-66f5df8ede20]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Strike]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Regulatory Counsel (US)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://blockchain.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Miami, San Francisco, Remote (US)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain.com is the world&#39;s leading software platform for digital assets. Offering the largest production blockchain platform in the world, we share the passion to code, create, and ultimately build an open, accessible and fair financial future, one piece of software at a time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for an exceptional lawyer to take on this exciting role and join our fast-growing team as Senior Regulatory Counsel (US). You will be working on ground-breaking, novel regulatory matters in the crypto space, including pioneering new crypto licensing regimes, working closely with Blockchain.com’s Policy Team on crypto policy development, and helping shape the regulatory environment in the US and Canada. You will contribute to the P-REAL team (Product, Regulatory, Employment and Litigation) within the broader Legal department and have responsibility for regulatory matters as they pertain to the US business. You will work with that business to address challenging legal and regulatory matters along our continued journey of growth.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Practically speaking, this includes the provision of legal and regulatory support on a variety of matters spanning entity licensing and registration, product distribution, service provider relationships, and more. If you have experience in a fast-paced environment and are looking for an opportunity to be a founding member of the Legal Team, this is the perfect opportunity for you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide legal and regulatory support to the US business on matters that affect Blockchain.com with an eye towards how they impact the business globally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor, assess and advise the business on legal and regulatory issues that impact entity licensing and registration, product development and distribution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support Blockchain.com in its various licensing and registration initiatives (US and Canada, including CTA registration and NY BitLicense).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Compliance in respect of regulatory licensing matters and liaise with local regulators where necessary.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure that the US business is aligned with applicable laws and regulations in the region (and coordinate with colleagues in the UK, Europe and Latin America).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work effectively across business units and product-related functions to resolve complex business and risk issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage outside counsel relationships as necessary.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;LLB/law degree and admission in a US jurisdiction.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;6+ years relevant regulatory experience; in-house FinTech experience a bonus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven high-performing legal experience in an in-house environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work well under pressure with diligence, organisation, and minimal supervision, and provide practical, business-friendly advice to clients.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong analytical and strategic skills; ability to drive issues to a quick resolution that factors in many non-legal variables, such as brand-risk, communications, government relations, tax, insurance, finance and other business units.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;High degree of professional ethics and integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to anticipate legal issues or risks and to build the processes and systems to prevent them from occurring.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;COMPENSATION &amp;amp; PERKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary based on experience and meaningful equity in an industry-leading company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provided the latest Apple equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Unlimited vacation policy, work hard and take time when you need it.&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain/jobs/3745261?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180745/blockchaininc.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchaininc@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5457bd3d-b464-4d43-bfd6-5c9d9e62930e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Engineer- Ecosystem Projects]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://protocol.ai/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We are looking for someone who can either structure and orchestrate, as a tech lead, or drive feature work, as a Senior Engineer, for <a href="http://web3.storage" class="postings-link">web3.storage</a> and <a href="http://nft.storage" class="postings-link">nft.storage</a>, across the API, client library, and postgres database (e.g. user auth via wallets, token scoping, client libraries that encrypt user data).&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div>Contribute to developing tooling, libraries and SDKs that will enable engineers to build decentralized products that integrate with IPFS and FileCoin. Become an integral part of product teams like <a href="http://Web3.storage" class="postings-link">Web3.storage</a> and <a href="http://Nft.storage" class="postings-link">Nft.storage</a>.&nbsp; Be a pillar in laying the frameworks for storing data in decentralized applications.</div><br/>As a Senior Engineer, you will…<br/><li>Develop the core tooling and frameworks to enable decentralized applications</li><li>Have a full spectrum on some of the implications of building Web3 products&nbsp;</li><li>Own the delivery and adoption pipeline of our products.&nbsp;</li><li>Be an integral part of our OS community&nbsp;</li><li>Deploy our stack, like running go-ipfs nodes in the cloud and scaling them</li><br/>You may be a fit for this role if you...<br/><li>Have more than 5-7 years of experience with building in production systems and services in JS frameworks, Golang or Rust&nbsp;</li><li>Have a solid understanding of systems design, and are able to flesh out products end to end&nbsp;</li><li>Proficient in Javascript, Typescript, <a href="http://Node.js" class="postings-link">Node.js</a>, <a href="http://Nest.js" class="postings-link">Nest.js</a>&nbsp;</li><li>Have a solid grasp of different API frameworks and databases&nbsp;</li><li>Have an interest or understanding of Web3 and decentralization</li><br/>Bonus points if you…<br/><li>Have an interest or understanding of&nbsp; Web3&nbsp;</li><li>Have used Web3 tooling like <a href="http://Web3.js" class="postings-link">Web3.js</a>, <a href="http://Ether.js" class="postings-link">Ether.js</a>, IPFS, Hardhat or Infura&nbsp;</li><li>Are an Open Source contributor at heart</li><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">What’s it like to work at Protocol Labs?</span></b></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs mission is to improve humanity’s most important technology, the Internet. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how it works. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Our projects include IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As a distributed team, we hire anywhere in the world, and at various levels of experience (entry, senior, staff). We look for people with unique perspectives and diverse backgrounds.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We have a great benefits package, including parental leave, contributions to your retirement, competitive pay, and unlimited time off. For U.S.-based employees, we also provide platinum-level health, dental, and vision coverage for you and your family.</span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EClPAFPeXIQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/protocol/b514f7a0-6561-4e24-bf2a-4ab0d4fda85c/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/207125/protocol_loabs.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[protocollabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c4028873-6454-47fc-a65d-6c6d1ed8cb1f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Talent Acquisition Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tron]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tron.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a Recruiter who is experienced to support our Talent Acquisition function. This person will partner with hiring managers to find top talent and fulfill our hiring needs. You will be an asset to the HR team and company by driving recruiting processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with hiring managers and business partners to understand business objectives, and identify recruiting strategies to address them&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the strategy to recruit all levels of candidates including niche, technical candidate talent pools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build strong relationships with candidates, hiring managers, and business partners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Source, interview, and evaluate candidates in a timely manner while always providing a positive candidate experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive the offer process, including negotiating and closing candidates on offers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Network and maintain relationships with key talent communities for active and passive opportunities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deliver an exceptional candidate experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage jobs and candidates in Greenhouse (ATS)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Continuously work on ways to improve the recruiting process and candidate experience. Stay up to date on innovative recruiting trends and practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Other ad hoc projects as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3-4+ years of end-to-end recruiting experience with exposure to a high volume, fast-paced environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;IT technical recruiting background is strongly preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to communicate effectively with candidates, hiring managers, and senior level partners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Greenhouse preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An ability to learn systems, processes, and procedures quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/gU6Jfz2jOHA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/rainberry/jobs/5773065002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180174/300px-Tron_logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tron@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f44423ad-b7da-465f-8880-ebeb8930922a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tron]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tron]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tron.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;p-pdf_iframe__page&quot; data-page-number=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BitTorrent offers a unique and compelling work environment. We are proponents of the open internet and serve one of the largest user demographics in history. We take these responsibilities seriously and hire accordingly. We work with only the most talented people. Everyone on our team is here to do meaningful work with broad reaching impact. We have a fun yet challenging work environment that fosters diversity, creativity, and teamwork.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a highly motivated Data Analyst who is passionate about data to join BitTorrent’s team. You will partner with teams across the organization to uncover valuable insights, solve their data needs and to drive our business.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will show a strong grasp of business models and statistics, excellent understanding of hypothesis testing, great analytical and problem-solving skills, and the ability to coherently describe technical concepts and analysis implications clearly to a wide audience.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop informative analyses, data visualizations, dashboards, and reports to deliver business insights.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide analytic support and expertise in defining KPIs, specify technical data requirements, and ensure all product feature and initiative launches have proper metric tracking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own A/B testing measurements: Design measurement frameworks, summarize insights, and recommend strategic decisions based on data to improve the performance of our organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apply a diverse set of tactics including statistics and quantitative reasoning to solve problems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Skills&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree Business, Mathematics, Statistics, or other analytical field &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ of professional experience as a Data Analyst&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced SQL skills and experience with relational databases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of statistics and data science concepts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with R or Python is a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills and comfortable presenting data clearly to audience of all levels&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in BI dashboards and visualization tools is a plus (Tableau, Data Studio, Google Analytics, Advanced Excel)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BitTorrent is an equal opportunity employer and values diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status or disability status.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/gU6Jfz2jOHA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/rainberry/jobs/5773101002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180174/300px-Tron_logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tron@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f44423ad-b7da-465f-8880-ebeb8930922a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tron]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Manager (Binance Card and Pay)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Global]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a Marketing Manager to inspire growth and awareness about Binance Card and Pay products. This role will work remotely with the responsibility of growing our user base and managing relationships and marketing activity for Binance Pay merchant partners . It requires working both highly autonomously and cross functionally with the central marketing team and Card/Pay business units. </div><div><br></div><div><b>This is a remote position and can be based in any global location. </b></div><br/>Responsibilities: <br/><li>Deploy successful online and offline marketing campaigns from ideation to execution</li><li>Establish and manage relationships and marketing activity with merchant partners&nbsp;</li><li>Help grow our user base and increase awareness of the Card/Pay products in fun, creative and informative ways</li><li>Monitor event/campaign progress and results using data analysis and user feedback to ensure ever-improving efficacy and user experience</li><li>Work closely with regional teams to support their Card/Pay marketing efforts</li><br/>Requirements: <br/><li>2 years of proven success in marketing management, eg. marketing campaign design, content marketing, email marketing, top of funnel growth and funnel optimisation</li><li>Strong written communication capacity and interpersonal skills: be able to build and manage strong relationships with their team, cross-functional colleagues, and external partners</li><li>Solid understanding of Binance’s Products and Services, have strong understanding of cryptocurrency / blockchain-related terminologies and trends</li><li>Data-focused: Able to roll up your sleeves to pull and analyse and gain insights from the data</li><li>User-focused and product-driven: strong understanding of product, tech and platform</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/4c4712b1-82b9-4092-b524-276d13d2176c/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Back-End / Java Developer (Binance Gift Card)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Asia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div>Binance Gift Card Team is looking to expand our development team with talented, experienced Back-end developers to build, improve and maintain a multitude of applications for the Binance ecosystem.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Translate business requirements and use cases into functional applications.</li><li>Design, build, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable Java code.</li><li>Review, test, and verify code for adherence to quality and security standards.</li><li>Ensure the best possible performance, quality and responsiveness of the applications.</li><li>Identify bottlenecks and bugs, and devise solutions to these problems.</li><li>Help maintain code quality and organization.</li><li>Identify areas for modification in existing programs and subsequently developing these modifications.</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>5+ years of experience with full lifecycle of project development for Java Applications.</li><li>Strong skills in Core Java, server-side Java technologies, and Spring frameworks.</li><li>Extensive experience in software design, architecture, development integration.</li><li>Solid knowledge of event processing models, multi-threading, enterprise integration pattern, Web Service and REST.</li><li>Ability to supervise and mentor junior developers on the team.</li><li>Bonus for degrees in: Computer Science, Computer Engineering, or Software Engineering.</li><li>Good Problem solving skills and knowledge of Data Structures and Algorithms.</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/178f7dc4-9baa-4164-bec2-0e9260610ee8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Cypress QA Automation Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">At Kraken we provide people with the means to explore the world of cryptocurrency trading.&nbsp; We are passionate about delivering the best possible user experience possible while maintaining our impeccable track record of security. If you too enjoy bringing excellence to the table then we have a place for you at Kraken.</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We are building an integrated e2e Automation Test platform to allow all our product teams to move fast and with confidence, and continue to deliver at an incredible cadence.</span></div><br/>What you will do:<br/><li>Work with Product Managers, Engineers, and QA Analysts</li><li>Deliver a best-in-class integrated e2e test automation platform</li><li>Create highly reusable test steps that can be easily used by others to write test cases</li><li>Advocate for quality in all aspects of our product.</li><br/>Who you are:<br/><li>Passionate about the Kraken mission of accelerating the adoption of cryptocurrency so that the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion</li><li>Ambition to build best-in-class QA automation solutions using modern technologies and approaches</li><li>Experienced or interested in Cypress and Javascript. If you are a strong Selenium (or similar) automation engineer who has used Cypress as a hobbyist and wants to use it in a high-impact Production environment, we would also love to speak to you. </li><br/>Nice to have:<br/><li>Experienced in Typescript</li><li>Full stack automation experience</li><li>Exposure to or interest in DevOps</li><li>Active trading account in cryptocurrency</li><li>Direct QA experience in exchange markets</li><div>Location tagging: #US #EU</div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/01b0307b-0fd7-44c4-a75d-84a1af55045b/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Platform Engineer - Card Issuing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://blockchain.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain.com is the world&#39;s leading software platform for digital assets. Offering the largest production blockchain platform in the world, we share the passion to code, create, and ultimately build an open, accessible and fair financial future, one piece of software at a time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for experienced software engineers from a variety of technical backgrounds with a proven track record in building scalable, reliable and performant systems. You will play a critical role in evolving the core platforms which drive our retail products. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As an engineer in the Card Issuing team, you will be responsible for a key part of the Blockchain.com roadmap. Issuing cards to our customers will help us bring Blockchain.com’s products further in the daily lives of our users. Looking after their spendings requires a great amount of care and our mission is to design, build, and maintain reliable systems that ensure broad access and efficient payments for all our customers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be at the forefront of the cryptocurrency ecosystem building out new distributed software to handle our rapidly growing user base of 50M+ wallets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Become a key member of a dedicated engineering team committed to rapidly shipping, and iterating on products that directly impact millions of users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Advocate best practices, code quality, test coverage and drive technical discussions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gain exposure to an array of open-source technologies such as Kafka, PostgreSQL, Redis, Cassandra, RabbitMQ, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Optimise existing systems for scalability, extensibility and performance whilst building out reusable, modular code for use across Blockchain’s products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure security is at the forefront of everything you do, employing advanced encryption schemes to secure user and company data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work within interdisciplinary teams to continually deliver the highest quality software to our users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with a variety of APIs and systems from different card program partners (ex: GPS, Marqeta, Contis, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design, build, and maintain systems to securely move funds&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with product, risk, and finance teams within Blockchain to ensure our payment flows are seamless and reliable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The foremost quality for this position or any position at Blockchain.com is integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You possess an innate curiosity, are a strong advocate for the best engineering practices and thrive on learning new technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You take a pragmatic approach to developing clean solutions to complex problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience building and shipping highly-available, fault tolerant distributed systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You pride yourself on consistent high levels of test coverage, strong technical documentation and effective monitoring.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of algorithms, data structures, databases and large-scale systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An appreciation of the entire stack (including but not limited to front-end, service oriented architecture, databases, network layers, etc.) and how they impact the performance of your application.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Preferably experience in at least one JVM based language such as Java, Kotlin, Scala, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Preferably experience in card issuing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPENSATION &amp;amp; PERKS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Amazing and accessible office location in the heart of London and San Francisco.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Unlimited vacation policy; work hard and take time when you need it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Unlimited books policy; order the technical resources you need or simply pick something up from our company library.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Catered team lunch every Monday, Wednesday, and Friday.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Apple equipment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Full-time salary based on experience and meaningful equity in an industry-leading company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;London Benefits: Private Medical Insurance (BUPA), Dental, Pension, Life, Short Term &amp;amp; Long Term Disability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;San Francisco Benefits: Medical, Dental, Vision, 401K, Flexible Spending Account, Commuter, Life, Short Term &amp;amp; Long Term Disability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;APPLICATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Favorite GIF.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;LinkedIn profile.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Link to Github, StackOverflow, personal website and/or blog (if applicable).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;When you apply to a job on this site, the personal data contained in your application will be collected by one or more of the following subsidiaries of Blockchain Luxembourg S.A (each, a “Controller”):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain Access UK Ltd.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain (GB) Limited&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain (US), Inc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain (LT), UAB&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You may contact our Data Protection Officer by email at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;dpo@blockchain.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Your personal data will be processed for the purposes of managing Controller’s recruitment related activities, which include setting up and conducting interviews and tests for applicants, evaluating and assessing the results thereto, and as is otherwise needed in the recruitment and hiring processes. Such processing is legally permissible under Art. 6(1)(f) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation) as necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Controller, which are the solicitation, evaluation, and selection of applicants for employment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your personal data will be shared with Greenhouse Software, Inc., a cloud services provider located in the United States of America and engaged by Controller to help manage its recruitment and hiring process on Controller’s behalf.&amp;nbsp; Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, your personal data will be transferred to the United States once you submit it through this site. Because the European Union Commission has determined that United States data privacy laws do not ensure an adequate level of protection for personal data collected from EU data subjects, the transfer will be subject to appropriate additional safeguards under the standard contractual clauses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your personal data will be retained by Controller as long as Controller determines it is necessary to evaluate your application for employment.&amp;nbsp; Under the GDPR, you have the right to request access to your personal data, to request that your personal data be rectified or erased, and to request that processing of your personal data be restricted. You also have to right to data portability. In addition, you may lodge a complaint with an EU supervisory authority.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain/jobs/3753820?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180745/blockchaininc.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchaininc@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5457bd3d-b464-4d43-bfd6-5c9d9e62930e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
