<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Polychain Capital]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://polychain.capital/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create robust ETL pipelines for a heterogeneous set of data, including but not limited to on-chain data across various blockchains, social media, and market data that can be consumed efficiently online and offline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assess reliability + availability of data from data vendors’ APIs, creating a data acquisition strategy where data is missing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support all research data identification, extraction, manipulation, and analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage in prototyping and building statistical models for production&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in architecting, maintaining, and deploying data ingestion pipelines for a wide variety of structured and unstructured data&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong knowledge of designing microservice-oriented real-time systems in GCP&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with data pipeline orchestration (i.e. Airflow, MLFlow, Neptune, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Software engineering experience in Python (+pandas, jupyter, sklearn)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Should be able to create simple data visualizations and backend storage feeding the visualizations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of data structures, networking, and databases&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in a Linux environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Background in computer science and statistics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Capable of multitasking and prioritizing through different projects to iterate quickly under high pressure situations (read: hacking skills)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Resourceful and solutions oriented thinker; comfortable operating in an environment of ambiguity and little structure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent communication skills and ability to work with multiple teams across the firm, including operations, accounting, and security as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Either fresh grad or perhaps up to a year post graduate work experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Time zone and location flexible&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/polychaincapital/jobs/3639356?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145853/polychain_capital.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[polychain@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9e67fe19-6bcc-4752-a2c5-6643ec1e33b1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Polychain Capital]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Finance Executive, SG/Group Entity]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Xfers]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.xfers.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About Xfers </b></div><div>Xfers as a part of Fazz Financial Group portfolio — a holding company of over 10 FinTech startups dedicated to enabling financial access for everyone — is on a mission to provide financial access to millions of underserved communities in Southeast Asia through building a financial ecosystem that anyone can participate in safely. Our range of last-mile financial rails power businesses across Southeast Asia - from startups to family businesses. By removing the pain of setting up and managing digital payments, more business owners can focus on growing their business, in turn encouraging fairer and healthier competition, and fostering stronger, more vibrant economies. For more information, visit: <a href="http://www.xfers.com" class="postings-link">www.xfers.com</a></div><div>But there is much more to do. We know how important our mission is to the improving the livelihoods of millions of people in Southeast Asia, and that's why we're looking for passionate and driven people to join us to accelerate financial access for everyone.</div><div><br></div><div><b>About the role and team&nbsp;</b></div><div>Finance Executive for SG/Group entity</div><br/>Responsibilities <br/><li>Ownership and accountability over financial operations and reporting</li><br/>What you may be doing <br/><li>Ensure proper recording and reconciliation of cryptocurrency assets</li><li>Support merchant operations and liaise with stakeholders on system infrastructure</li><li>Prepare month end closing for Group i.e. consolidation/allocation/ESOP</li><li>Assist with annual audit for SG/Group entities</li><br/>What we are looking for in you / Ideal profile <br/><li>Proficiency in use of SAP</li><li>At least 2-3 years experience with consolidation accounting</li><li>Strong time management and able to complete tasks on time</li><li>Strong communication skills to manage internal stakeholders</li><li>Fast learner and open to learning about new products</li><li>Diploma or Degree in Accountancy</li><br/>Nice to haves <br/><li>Broad understanding of the Payments and FinTech industry&nbsp;</li><div>We love reviewing all the applications we receive, but unfortunately, we may not be able to get back to everyone individually.&nbsp; If we’d like to move forward with your application, we’ll definitely be in touch!</div><div><br></div><div>Xfers is an equal opportunity employer. Individuals seeking employment at Xfers will be considered without regard to race, religion, national origin, age, sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, sexual orientation, marital status, medical condition, ancestry, physical or mental disability, or any other characteristic protected by applicable laws. </div><div><br></div><div>By submitting your application, you agree that Xfers may collect your personal data for recruiting, regional organization planning, and related purposes.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/xfers/249066f1-a398-41fa-a81f-a79b921aa022/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/597930/xfers_logo1.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[xfers@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b0a8343f-a5d7-46f6-beef-6fa07262d235]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Xfers]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[11:FS]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://11fs.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>11:FS is on a mission to change the fabric of financial services. Our <a href="https://11fs.com/services/consulting" class="postings-link">Consulting &amp; Research</a> practice builds challenger propositions globally, like we did for Natwest with Mettle. Our <a href="https://11fs.com/products/11fs-pulse" class="postings-link">Pulse</a> team creates a benchmarking tool used by the likes of Monzo, Starling, Natwest and Tesco Bank. Our <a href="https://11fs.com/products/11fs-foundry" class="postings-link">Foundry</a> team are delivering a Financial Services Operating System to help businesses quickly add financial services to their offering. On top of all of that, we’re a <a href="https://11fs.com/services/media" class="postings-link">media</a> company, generating content that supports our brand and changes the conversation - not necessarily in that order. </div><div><br></div><div>To do this we need an amazing team so we have pulled together the best in financial services and beyond. </div><div><br></div><div>We truly live our values at 11:FS, and they are critical to your entire journey here. ‘Cultural Add’ is as, if not more, important as pure technical fit, and as part of your interview process we’ll deep dive in our values and your beliefs. Everyone at 11:FS fits our 4 core values: Team, Attitude, Communication and Impact, and this remains at the core of our growth.</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">11:FS has built digital banks and challenger banks around the world and from this experience we are creating 11:FS Foundry. Fintechs or tech companies looking to challenge the status quo often face prohibitive costs of adopting these same old systems, or the daunting task of building something new from scratch. 11:FS Foundry is our financial services operating system, allowing our customers to get financial services propositions to market faster, avoid vendor lock-in and deliver incredible experiences.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">We are looking for a Product Manager to join our growing team to help drive the delivery of the foundry platform. Working with our engineering teams, helping shape the roadmap and bringing the product to life.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">What you'll be doing:</b>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Customer insights and development&nbsp;</b>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will assist the </span><i><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">“Product Lead” </span></i><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">on identifying the ‘jobs to be done’ for different end-customer segments, structuring primary and secondary research into insightful proposition ideas and proposals</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Create proposition</b>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will develop solutions that bring together a real answer to a customer need, remixing design patterns, understanding what can be built in software, and what the potential business model could be. You'll be exposed to senior decision makers, and will need to communicate these product concepts clearly and concisely.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Development and test</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will work together with the best designers, engineers, and clients, to create and develop Foundry’s financial operating product. You will help drive the team that develops those propositions into perfectly formed products, managing the backlog, running ceremonies and ensuring agile principles within the team.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Roadmap</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will help shape the roadmap and backlog of work, supporting the team in planning how the product will develop in specific markets.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">About you</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">We are looking for product managers who have worked in a B2B environment - ideally experience working with and building SaaS products. If you had experience working for or with financial service clients or even just a genuine interest in finance and fintech more specifically that would be amazing. That said, it's not a hard requirement.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will have good commercial understanding, experience with core product tooling (e.g. JIRA, Figma, Notion or similar) and the ability to communicate exceptionally well.</span></div><br/>What we are looking for:<br/><li>Product Management experience ideally in either B2B/SaaS environments.</li><li>Experience working in a startup environment, happy to get involved in a variety of activities to drive the business forward.</li><li>Experience working with teams of 5-10, engineers, designers and product people.</li><li>A good understanding on UI and UX principles.</li><li>Stakeholder management skills with demonstrable experience in influencing technical teams.</li><li>Experience driving end-customer interviews and turning these insights into amazing products and services.</li><li>Experience in or a passion for Fintech.</li><li>Most importantly a positive attitude and outlook</li><div>We strongly encourage people of colour, lesbian, gay, bisexual, transgender, queer and non-binary people, parents, and individuals with disabilities to apply. 11:FS is an equal opportunity employer and welcomes everyone to our team. If you need reasonable adjustments at any point in the application or interview process, please let us know.</div><div><br></div><div>In your application, please feel free to note which pronouns you use (For example - she/her/hers, he/him/his, they/them/theirs, etc).</div><div><br></div><div>Unfortunately we are unable to sponsor Visas at this time, but please do check back in with us in the future.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/11fs/3c675811-4cec-442a-914f-a8553cae9fd3/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/549642/11FS-400x400.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[11fs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d28fc801-0423-4108-8476-3745eba53edb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[11:FS]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Affiliate Business Development Manager (Arabic/Eng) - Remote]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKEx]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.okex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Middle East (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for VIP clients’ relationship management, identify and follow up on any future business opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and enhance relationships with local crypto influencers, being in contact with them frequently, build partnerships with influencers for the purpose of user acquisition.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Planning and execution of online and some offline marketing activities, events, and campaigns with influencers or media channels.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expand the user base and grow awareness of the OKEx brand.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Devise creative ways to identify potential affiliates and acquire users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in translations and proofread content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of affiliate marketing experience in the Cryptocurrency space&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in building large affiliate networks from start to finish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid project management skills and the ability to manage multiple priorities and deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with analytical tools and reporting such as Google Analytics and Amplitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of fundamental affiliate customer acquisition KPIs and optimization methods to improve performance through data analysis and segmentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent in &lt;strong&gt;Arabic&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;English&lt;/strong&gt; is a MUST&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More experiences will be considered as Senior Manager&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Immediate Available is preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okex/jobs/4814699003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175406/okex.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bcbc2afc-a2fd-45d8-bba3-e7ce4b53b3d8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKEx]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Research Analyst (Crypto) - Waterdrop]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CertiK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://certik.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York / Seattle / Bay Area / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 12pt">About the Company</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">Founded in 2018 by professors of Yale University and Columbia University, CertiK is a pioneer in blockchain security and data analytics. CertiK's mission is to secure the cyber world with cutting-edge innovations and insights.&nbsp;&nbsp;CertiK raised over $60 million from the Series B funding round in 2021. Our investors include top VCs like Tiger Global, Coatue Management, Shunwei Capital, and Hillhouse Capital as well as industry leaders like Coinbase Ventures and Binance.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 12pt">About You</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">You’re a self-starter. You believe in tackling the most important problems, even if they are the most difficult problems. You’re comfortable with the unknown and understand that #startuplife means that you’re going to be wearing multiple hats. And that’s what motivates you. You’re accountable and obsessed with improvement, both in yourself and in others. You’re up to the challenge of building a world-class company that aims to be the infrastructure for more secure software for all.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 12pt">About the Role</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">As a Research Analyst, you will be focused on analyzing on-chain data for a variety of crypto projects. You will consistently identify high signal trends for crypto users and investors to make informed decisions. You will be working closely with the product and marketing teams as a subject matter expert to create data insights that will serve CertiK’s new and existing user base.</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Monitor and analyze on-chain data to discover crypto investment opportunities</li><li>Identify on-chain metrics and design alert criteria that serve as signals for project growth and adoptionConduct data quality checks to find any abnormalities</li><li>Participate in community showcases to condense detailed research findings into easily digestible content on a consistent basis</li><li>Produce high-quality research reports focused on data analysis using CertiK tools&nbsp;Continuously research and learn about new trends and projects within emerging areas (e.g. DeFi, NFTs, Blockchain Gaming)</li><li>Prepare datasets for data and engineer teams, including manual labeling of wallets and smart contracts</li><li>Assist product and marketing teams on research-focused content creation</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Open to all levels of experience</li><li>Passionate about crypto - we are looking for people who enjoy learning about new crypto projects and have a pulse on the industry</li><li>Exceptionally analytical and detail-oriented</li><li>Ability to dive deep into data to identify investing trends and opportunities</li><li>Effective verbal and written communication skills - comfortable with writing and translating analytical research into easy to understand insights</li><li>Self-motivated with the ability to consistently produce results under limited supervision</li><li>Ability to work in a fast-paced startup environment and shift gears based on team needs</li><li>Ability to juggle multiple projects and independently prioritize initiatives</li><li>Experience with data analysis tools, such as Excel and SQL, is a plus</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/certik/0a5a6c3b-fd10-4eaa-aef1-82ac06c94482/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/452745/CertiK-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[certik@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f6c22067-35b7-4b78-a01c-cb1e9232298a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CertiK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, Business Development Operations]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Forte Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.forte.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Forte is seeking an exceptionally organized and diligent &lt;strong&gt;Director of Business Development Operations&lt;/strong&gt; with a track record of managing the process for cross-functional business development efforts in a scaling business. You will play a key role in driving growth and business success across the organization. You are excited to gain exposure to a wide range of different problem spaces -- spanning tech/gaming, blockchain, and economics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Examples of projects will include driving our business development pipeline for strategic prospects, coordinating business critical initiatives, partnering with PMs to design a self-onboarding process and associated tool for small/medium prospects, and leading pipeline reporting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will be comfortable working independently and across cross-functional teams in a fast-paced and evolving environment. They will be an excellent communicator and a leader with a passion for delivering results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this role, you will...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the overall business development operations process, partnering with cross-functional teams to empower the BD team to drive forward key deals and partnerships conversations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and enforce the overall process to enable end-to-end project management for BD operations, and lay the foundation for future growth and scale across the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive BD enablement by leading the creation and maintenance of decks, demos, case studies, and educational materials, partnering at times with BD, Strategy &amp;amp; Operations, Marketing and other teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directly contribute to the success of deals that have organization-wide impact by supporting deal cycle operations for large enterprise partnerships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with functional teams (BD, Product, Marketing, Legal, Finance…) to problem-solve complex business challenges in a highly dynamic, fast-paced environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uncover areas of opportunity to improve processes and operational performance and drive change management with the Leadership team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain documentation for processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage and report out projects, status and proactively work with teams to remove project blockers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Takes pride in holding oneself and others accountable to meet deadlines and a high bar for quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prioritize and execute in the face of ambiguity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit and hire a great business development operations team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be a good fit, you will need...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in business, finance, economics or other highly quantitative field.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of professional experience in Operations Management, Business Development or Customer Success.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing 2+ direct reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience gathering business requirements, developing and implementing efficient processes, decision matrix, dashboards and reporting to surface meaningful KPIs and actionable intelligence to leadership.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think clearly, grasp the big picture, analyze quantitatively and problem solve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to foster cooperation amongst business stakeholders and get things done.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills; ability to present in a clear and concise manner to all levels in the company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to prioritize, multitask and adapt to a fast moving environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advanced skills in Google Suite and experience with other standard program management tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort interacting with C-level executives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonus if you also have...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in gaming and gaming-adjacent industries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A genuine appreciation for blockchain technology and the benefits it can offer the games industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience with Airtable and Confluence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience with SugarCRM (or similar CRM software/saas).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience with program management tools like Monday.com or Asana.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-growth or early-stage startup experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Forte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Forte is building economic technology for games. Its end-to-end platform enables the emergence of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.forte.io%2F%3Fp%3D507&amp;amp;esheet=52430260&amp;amp;newsitemid=20210520005295&amp;amp;lan=en-US&amp;amp;anchor=community+economics&amp;amp;index=5&amp;amp;md5=47dfe9eadc11aa00eabe6c1dcfa3cc30&quot;&gt;community economics&lt;/a&gt;, a system where the interests of game developers and players are aligned, leading to healthier, sustainable game communities. The team is composed of longtime industry members (Unity, ngmoco, Riot Games, Electronic Arts, Sony, and Rockstar Games, among others), and is currently working with over 20 acclaimed game developers from across the industry to reimagine the economics of games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/forte/jobs/4818616003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/511563/forte-labs-logo_Cropped.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[forte@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[509e5842-f758-4b3e-8b54-bfc3ca4c2a98]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Forte Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crypto* Talent Acquisition Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ledger]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ledger.fr/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Paris]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Ledger is the global leader of security solutions and infrastructure for cryptocurrencies and blockchain applications, with more than 3.5 million users in 165 countries. Ledger combines hardware and software expertise to secure billions of dollars worth of almost 2,000 different crypto assets - worldwide, 15% of these assets are managed through the Ledger ecosystem.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto* means cryptography &amp; cryptocurrency at Ledger, we will recruit a lot in those 2 areas for our innovation team and Product Security - Ledger Donjon. </div><div>&nbsp;</div><div>Are you willing to join a company with a startup spirit that is still growing faster?</div><div>Motivated by the challenge of recruiting top profiles, scale teams?</div><div><br></div><div><i>Our Stack : LinkedIn Recruiter, Lever, Time, Love ( x repeat)</i></div><div><br></div><div>In full growth, we have an ambitious recruitment plan, meaning a real issue in terms of talent acquisition and onboarding.</div><div><br></div><br/>Missions: <br/><li>Being responsible of the all recruitment process from sourcing, direct approach, management of applications via ATS, following candidates through their all process to the closing</li><li>Work on Crypto* recrutements with Technical expert </li><li>Connecting with Hiring Managers - your internal customers to carry out the closing of your positions in self-reliance to collaborate, engaging regular exchange and collaborate with Hiring Managers</li><li>Participate in HR improvement projects</li><li>Developing the visibility and attractiveness of Ledger</li><li>Ensuring a watch on innovative actions in your field</li><li>Participate in our referral policy program</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>Experience in operational recruitment, ideally in a context of strong growth or on a market where there is a dearth of good engineers</li><li>Mastering the recruitment process through direct approach</li><li>Being data driven and monitoring your work with KPIs</li><li>Willing and able to take a step back from your recruitment activity in order to carry out structuring projects for the talent acquisition activity</li><li>Having worked in an international context and being comfortable in English (speaking, talking, reading)</li><li>Understanding the Tech / Dev Open Source &amp; Crypto*/ Blockchain ecosystem</li><br/>Benefits:<br/><li>Competitive compensation package and ESOP according to the Company policy</li><li>Flexible working hours, remote-friendly environment</li><li>Strong focus on personal development including internal/external trainings and attendance to conferences, internal talks, technical meetups and Hackathons</li><li>High performance office equipment</li><li>Comprehensive health insurance policy offering extensive medical, dental and vision care coverage</li><li>Meal Vouchers with Swile (ex Lunchr)</li><li>Annual company outing for Ledgerdary Days, plus frequent parties, snacks and drinks</li><li>Employee discount on Ledger products</li><div><b><i>Ledger guarantees equity for all during the recruitment process, without any distinction of gender, ethnicity, religion, sexual orientation, social status, disability or age</i></b></div><div><br></div><div><br></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/ledger/fb38203f-8d08-4a2e-af15-9071aeece2fb/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/142943/ledger.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ledger@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[83f3aace-4751-47ca-bbcd-26157dd3bc4a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ledger]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of Business Development, Memberships]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[The Block]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.theblockcrypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Founded in 2018 and based in NYC, The Block is the leading research, analysis, and news brand in the digital asset space. The Block's team is spread across 7 timezones, covering the global cryptocurrency space 24/7. </span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Block delivers deep insight into how the emerging digital assets sector interacts with traditional finance, technology, governments, and markets. We reach hundreds of thousands of technologists, financial market participants, Fortune 500 professionals, global service providers, policymakers, and more through our main website, dedicated Research Portal, podcast, and events. </span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We are currently seeking a Director of Business Development to join our rapidly growing Membership sales team. The Director of Business Development will lead a team of driven Business Development Associates and manage front-line managers on the team.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Director of Business Development should bring a proven track record of success in achieving lead and pipeline generation targets and previous experience motivating teams. They will align outbound and inbound lead generation goals, strategy, and tactics to our go-to-market initiatives.&nbsp; This role will collaborate closely with marketing, sales, and enablement groups to maximize pipeline creation.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Hire, onboard, and directly manage new Business Development Associates (BDAs) and Account Management Associates (AMAs), who serve as the top-of-the-funnel sales reps focused on qualifying prospects and clients and setting meetings for AEs and AMs, respectively. </li><li>Set and define the Business Development strategy for inbound and outbound teams</li><li>Develop your team’s skills for researching, prospecting, qualifying, and pipeline creation</li><li>Provide regular coaching, feedback, and professional development by utilizing internal sales tools</li><li>Coach the team on effective sales techniques and product knowledge</li><li>Closely monitor metrics with the aim to and make recommendations that will increase productivity</li><li>Collaborate with sales managers and account executives/ managers to ensure proper alignment on account coverage, target personas, meeting quality, and BDA to AE hand-off</li><li>Work closely with Marketing and Sales leadership to ensure lead quality and quantity to support top of the funnel metrics&nbsp;</li><li>Articulate the value proposition of The Block in the market, and maintain in-depth knowledge of our products, our competitors, and industry trends</li><li>Work closely with Sales leadership to develop career pathways for BDAs and AMAs</li><li>Track and report on team progress to monthly and quarterly goals for lead conversion, initial sales meetings, and pipeline sourced</li><br/>Qualifications<br/><li>3+ years managing a team of Business Development Associates, preferably in a B2B SaaS sales environment</li><li>Second-line management experience</li><li>Proven record of meeting and exceeding lead conversion, meeting, and pipeline targets&nbsp;Experience working with Marketing and Sales leadership&nbsp;Excellent leadership, interpersonal, communication, and conflict resolution skills</li><li>Passionate about inspiring and developing team members</li><li>Expert in using sales tools and products to drive productivity</li><li>Proven ability to effectively hire and train new BDAsAbility to the culture of intensity around activity and performance</li><li>An interest in the evolving crypto and digital assets industryImpeccable time management and organizational skills</li><li>Adaptable to changing startup environment </li><li>Collaborative spirit and results-oriented</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/theblockcrypto/73117ccc-fe1d-494f-b041-473036281a3e/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/374217/theblock.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[theblock@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[27d78dc7-e726-4a53-af38-f0660605e195]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[The Block]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Recruiter]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Latoken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote Worldwide]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong><strong>LATOKEN exchange has 2 million accounts including 900k+ users of our Android app rated 4.4 by 25+ thousands of reviews. We leverage the next tech to make account opening as easy as Instagram. The technology and our Olympic sports culture can make us the first billion users digital wallet needed to free people to manage their financial life.</strong></strong></p><p><strong><strong>Today, is a great moment to join us as crypto is expanding into mainstream financial market and <a>ex CFO of JP Morgan joined</a> our advisory board and <a>2 presidents joined us</a> in Davos.</strong></strong></p><p><a>Here is our backlog.</a></p><p><strong>Unit:</strong> Talent Growth<br><strong>Role: </strong>Recruiter <br><strong>Role Mission: </strong>Hire Champion-level talents.</p><p><strong>Details: </strong><br></p><ul><li><strong>Story:</strong> Teammates need Champion-level talents to be hired to raise the bar for units and ensure they deliver their objectives.</li><li><strong>Goal</strong>: Successful hires &gt;7 per month.</li><li><strong>How:</strong> <ul><li>Attract candidates via SignalHire, Telegram groups, MIPT, ITMO, Indian University of Technology, contests partnerships, etc.</li><li>Do 2 batches with cheating game/case per week via Signalhire+Business Quiz=&gt;Calendly invite.</li><li>Promote LATOKEN brand, screen &amp; interview, bring to offer &amp; close candidates.</li></ul></li><li><strong>Conditions:</strong> Hires should be crypto-motivated team players.</li></ul><p><strong>Main performance number:</strong>  Offers signed.<br><strong>Second performance number:</strong> Hired above average 360.<br><strong>Third performance number:</strong> Screening Tests.<br><br><strong><em>Functions:</em></strong></p><ul><li><strong>Offer &amp; Close :</strong> Tie offer features to opportunities &amp; benefits for the candidate to prepare and sell the offer.</li><li><strong>Find &amp; Research :</strong> Build own pipeline of relevant candidates using creative sourcing channels (SignalHire, Telegram groups, MIPT, ITMO, India Universities of Technology, contests partnerships, etc.).</li><li><strong>Scrum :</strong> Participate Stand-ups, Sprints with Demos, Grooming and Retro driven by Stories Who need What, Why.</li><li><strong>Sell &amp; Attract :</strong> Sell LATOKEN jobs and attract talented candidates from top companies.</li><li><strong>Batches : </strong>Fill in 3 batches per week with 21 candidates (participated) selected out of 100 applicants by CV and test scores.</li><li><strong>Vacancies :</strong> Post vacancies in 4 channels with descriptions from roles approved with bar raiser. Candidate profile and role requirements grandma clear with role requirements, keywords, 3 ideal CVs, and SH query.</li><li><strong>SH blast : </strong>Approve SH list of prospects on Team Health meeting with 3 relevant candidates from 100 to 105 in the list. Make email blast and with calendly to batch. Score candidates' CVs and request to pass a test before the batch, otherwise change the batch date.<em><strong></strong></em></li></ul><p><em><strong>Requirement skills and experience:</strong></em></p><ul><li>2+ years in recruitment or sales at high-pace international capital markets, fintech, blockchain, or tech companies. </li><li>Willingness to challenge for overachievement. </li><li>Prefer growth to comfort. </li><li>Passion for and understanding of IT and digital currency. </li><li>Fluent English.</li></ul><p><em><strong>Reward:</strong></em></p><ul><li>We give proof that a teammate's life made an impact - LATOKEN share in Nasdaq index and millions in your pockets from vested options.</li><li>Breakthrough technology and Product - Market - Timing Fit.</li><li>Worldwide multibillion users market.</li><li>Join us to build the first digital exchange wallet with a billion users.</li></ul><p><strong>Feel a great fit - apply now or forward to a great candidate.</strong><br></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.breezy.hr/p/0631877ea7a401-recruiter/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/178323/latoken.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[latoken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[ad8a3cbd-f1ed-4400-b372-af94f5f06cb4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Latoken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Lead Product Manager, Signing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York; Portland, Oregon; Chicago, Illinois; Los Angeles, California; San Francisco, Cal]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is a crypto exchange and custodian that allows customers to buy, sell, store, and earn more than 30 cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, bitcoin cash, ether, litecoin, and Zcash. Gemini is a New York trust company that is subject to the capital reserve requirements, cybersecurity requirements, and banking compliance standards set forth by the New York State Department of Financial Services and the New York Banking Law. Gemini was founded in 2014 by twin brothers Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss to empower the individual through crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto is about giving you greater choice, independence, and opportunity. We are here to help you on your journey. We build crypto products that are simple, elegant, and secure. Whether you are an individual or an institution, we want to help you buy, sell, and store your bitcoin and cryptocurrency. Crypto is not just a technology, it&#39;s a movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, our mission is to &lt;strong&gt;empower the individual&lt;/strong&gt; and that includes giving our employees flexibility of choice — our Office Optional Policy allows employees to choose to work from one of our physical locations or from home.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select roles that are location-specific will still be eligible for flexible schedules.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p2&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Department: &lt;/strong&gt;Product&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our team is made up of skilled product managers with experience in banking, fintech, and cryptocurrency. We draw from top players in the financial and technology industries who are ready to stretch themselves and face the unique and exciting challenges of the digital asset world. We are an internal “think tank” that tackles complex, cross-functional projects, iterates on existing products, and acts as the go-to team for Leadership’s technical vision.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role: &lt;/strong&gt;Lead Product Manager, Signing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In this role, you&#39;ll focus on building a deep understanding of the latest developments in cryptography as well as the cryptocurrency industry and leveraging that understanding to enable effective decision making on the team at Gemini responsible for implementing and leveraging the cryptography that enables the utility of cryptocurrencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;ll be quantifying the opportunities present in the emerging sectors of the industry and identifying critical paths toward enabling Gemini to participate in a meaningful way. We expect product managers to identify, manage, and iterate on opportunities for expansion of the cryptocurrency utility case while helping to define the scope and objectives for continuous product success.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Product Managers combine systematic analysis, experience, and ideation with partner teams to create detailed roadmaps and launch product initiatives across the company. The ideal candidate is an expert cross-functional collaborator, involving all relevant stakeholders and ensuring technical feasibility for critical team initiatives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role reports directly to the Associate Director of Product, Wallet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Own the design, development, and maintenance of ongoing metrics, reports, analyses, dashboards, by pulling data from internal and external sources&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Define the data elements and data structure that our team should leverage to enable analytical and reporting capabilities for our product roadmap&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Design and influence operational best practices for reporting and analytics to enable the team to scale as we grow presence in new and existing territories&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Enable effective decision making by retrieving and aggregating data from multiple sources and compiling it into a digestible and actionable format&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Use data-oriented approaches to identify potential areas of improvement within the business, with a specific focus on asset support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Partner with compliance, legal, and development teams to deliver products in-line with a consistent asset strategy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimum Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Bachelor’s Degree in any quantitative discipline (such as Statistics, Mathematics, or Operational Research) or in Business, Finance, Computer Science, or Economics or equivalent experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; 3+ years of experienced developing requirements and creating requirements documents and process flows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Knowledge of and experience with cryptocurrencies, cryptography, and/or blockchain technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Proficiency in organization, prioritization, and attention to detail, with proven ability to manage multiple projects with concurrent timelines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Affinity for teamwork-oriented culture and demonstrated willingness to roll up sleeves&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Superb verbal and written communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; An ability and interest in working in a fast-paced, ambiguous and rapidly changing environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Experience in regulated industries, FinTech, cryptocurrency, or retail banking preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Comfort designing financial technology, such as exchanges or trading platforms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Execute best in a fast-paced startup environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-CM1&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3644465&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Global Recruitment Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Digital Assets Holding]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://digitalasset.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Digital Asset&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset helps companies of all sizes and across industries get distributed applications to market faster, and stay there longer. At the core of our service offering is DAML (daml.com), the open source and platform-independent smart contract framework that enables developers to write an application once and deploy it anywhere. Today, we work with some of the largest companies in the world to harness the transformative power of smart contracts - a component of the distributed ledger technology (DLT) stack - and change the way applications are developed, deployed and used to solve real-world business challenges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset is a global company with offices in New York, London, Budapest, Zurich, Hong Kong, and Sydney.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As we grow our team, we will maintain the dynamic, collaborative and pragmatic way of working that has grounded our efforts from the beginning.&amp;nbsp; If you seek to develop solutions others have yet to contemplate, this opportunity may be right for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset (DA) is looking for an experienced and creative Global Recruitment Manager who thrives in a fast-paced and entrepreneurial environment.&amp;nbsp; Under the direction of the Director of Human Resources, the Global Recruitment Manager is responsible for managing the recruitment process and team (both direct and indirect), and for sourcing and selecting qualified candidates domestically and internationally for DA.&amp;nbsp; In view of the highly technical nature of recruitment in a variety of subject areas, the Global Recruitment Manager will collaborate closely with executives and directors of each of our functional areas.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop global recruitment systems, policies, procedures, tools and templates to ensure streamlined, effective, and high quality services are delivered, with regular recruitment metrics and reporting on progress.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and recommend global recruitment strategies to ensure successful searches.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Maintain the firm’s ATS (Greenhouse) and guide effective use by hiring managers, interviewers, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify potential candidates through direct sourcing, job boards, databases, contacts/networks, and external agencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mentor and coach DA managers and key staff in recruitment procedures and best practices.&amp;nbsp; Conduct regular interviewer training.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate candidate debrief meetings with hiring managers and interviewers, and model evidence-based selection decision-making.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage the firm’s relationships with external agencies, providing guidance and feedback, and ensuring that we get quality candidates that meet our job specifications.&amp;nbsp; Keeping agency fees under control is a key aspect of the Global Recruitment Manager’s role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Play an active leadership role in the firm’s Diversity, Equity &amp;amp; Inclusion programs and initiatives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in building the positive employer brand for DA -- work with Marketing &amp;amp; Communications on specific initiatives; attend conferences, career fairs, and special events when they support the firm’s strategic plans; etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Conduct reference checks, as needed, for potential hires into key roles.&amp;nbsp; Extend employment offers, support salary negotiations, and help close candidates where needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Maintain the firm’s library of job specifications/hiring plans; understand and support visa considerations; and complete other duties, as assigned.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Criteria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;10+ years previous recruitment experience, in a fast-paced environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Business Administration, Human Resources Management or related field.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong ability to source candidates directly and to qualify them against job requirements; interest in implementing new sourcing methods and innovating on hiring practices by using new methods or channels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using time management skills, such as prioritizing/organizing and tracking details or meeting deadlines of multiple projects with varying target fill dates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work well under pressure and in a fast-paced and dynamic environment, with a high degree of accuracy and attention to detail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of and commitment to driving diversity throughout the hiring process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent oral and written communication skills, strong interpersonal skills, and assertive and professional demeanor, and ability to represent the firm to diverse audiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analytical skills to assess (and report on) the results of recent and current recruitment efforts/initiatives, and to be able to draw information and insights that enable process improvements and more effective outcomes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interest and ability in monitoring market trends to help ensure that the firm is taking the best approach and using the most effective sources to capitalize on available talent.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong orientation to internal client satisfaction, with the ability to foster productive professional relationships and work collaboratively in a team environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect With Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a rare opportunity to help define an industry and join a dynamic team of technology innovators.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, national origin, sex, religion, sexual orientation, age, disability, citizenship status, veteran status or any other basis protected by applicable law. If and as required by applicable law, all persons hired to work at Digital Asset will be required to verify identity and eligibility to work in the location for which they have an offer to work and to complete the necessary employment eligibility verification documents upon hire. Applicants with disabilities who require accommodation should contact &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:recruiting@digitalasset.com&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;recruiting@digitalasset.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As part of our commitment to equal opportunity, Digital Asset believes that all employees should receive equal pay for equal work and is committed to this principle in its pay structure. DA also offers family-friendly benefits in addition to flexible work arrangements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/digitalasset/jobs/3668721?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/289153/digital-asset-holdings-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[digitalassets@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b9e3329f-7812-4695-a1f7-5b094cbac58f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Digital Assets Holding]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer, New Grad]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celo.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<br/>About Us:<br/><li>We are a full-stack company i.e. we are building both blockchain protocols and the user experiences on top of them</li><li>We are experienced startup founders and operators</li><li>We are highly technical, with backgrounds at places like Google and MIT</li><li>We are mission driven with a big goal: to bring sound currency and property rights to those who need it most</li><li>We have a strong engineering culture, which values open-source</li><br/>You Will: <br/><li>Implement, test, and audit the stability and/or identity portion of the Celo protocol</li><li>Work with senior engineers to contribute high level decisions about the Celo protocol and architecture</li><li>Build back-end services that power our APIs</li><li>Help to hit product milestones by writing high quality, well tested code </li><li>Help communicate and implement best practices across the engineering team</li><li>Author detailed technical specifications</li><li>Perform and participate in code reviews</li><li>Identify and resolve performance bottlenecks</li><li>Work in a high performance scrum team</li><li>Collaborate with product and design teams</li><br/>You Have:<br/><li>A strong passion for Celo's mission </li><li>Ability to write high quality, well tested code</li><li>Ability to grow and adapt to a rapidly evolving technology stack</li><li>Strong experience developing production software</li><li>Strong communication skills and ability to lead technical discussions</li><li>Experience building software that is reusable, extensible, and modular</li><li>A passion for testing and achieving high test coverage</li><li>Enthusiasm to work in a startup environment</li><li>Bonus: Deep understanding or passion for blockchain technology</li><li>Bonus: Background is distributed systems, cryptography, or programming languages</li><li>Bonus: Knowledge of Solidity and the EVM</li><br/>What we offer:<br/><li>Competitive salary, equity, and coin plan</li><li>Medical, dental, and vision insurance</li><li>Commuter benefit</li><li>401k plan</li><li>Beautiful office space</li><div><span>cLabs ("Celo Labs") started Celo in 2017 and is one of many contributors to the open source project Celo.&nbsp;cLabs builds financial technology to enable prosperity of all beings.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>cLabs is a Teal organization, a method of decentralized management and organizational governance. Roles are defined around the work, not people, and there is a high degree of autonomy. As such, we're all proud to hold the job title of "Partner." For more information on our culture, we encourage you to check out our blog at&nbsp;</span><a href="https://medium.com/celohq/the-future-is-teal-cc264a5d51d3" class="postings-link"><span>https://medium.com/celohq/the-future-is-teal-cc264a5d51d3</span></a><span>.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>To build technology and products that are used and loved by people and solve real-world problems, we need to build a team with many different perspectives and experiences. We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. We encourage candidates from all backgrounds to apply and always consider qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records, in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>Applicants in need of special assistance or accommodation during the interview process or in accessing our website may contact us by sending an email to assistance(at)</span><a href="http://celo.org" class="postings-link"><span>celo.org</span></a><span>. We will treat your request as confidentially as possible. In your email, please include your name and preferred method of contact, and we will respond as soon as possible.</span></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/clabs/196ad7de-6676-47de-9737-418eab99f932/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145322/celo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c6054e2e-9096-43cc-9ea8-c4a05ab9335a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Risk Operation Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p><strong>About Crypto.com</strong></p>  <p>Founded in 2016, Crypto.com today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest growing crypto app, along with the Crypto.com Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the Crypto.com Exchange and Crypto.com DeFi Wallet. Recently launched, Crypto.com NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment and sports.</p>  <p>Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, CCSS Level 3, ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks. </p>  <p>With over 2,600 people in offices across the Americas, Europe and Asia, Crypto.com is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a href="https://crypto.com" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com</a></p><p>Requirements</p><p><strong>Responsibilities</strong></p><ul> <li>Assist in the operation processes related to new product listing, product parameters and model parameters updates.</li> <li>Proactively identify, report and ensure transparency of risks, and immediate escalation of material issues to risk managers.</li> <li>Support risk managers and take a lead in development and automation of risk reporting and analysis.</li> <li>Provide support in handling and reporting data elements to meet regulatory requirements.</li> <li>Assist with documentation of risk reporting procedures and ensure in line with models and methodology documentation.</li> <li>Assist in the daily risk reporting and monitoring of the markets and measuring the risk exposure of market makers' portfolios. </li> </ul><p></p><p><strong>Requirements </strong></p><ul> <li>Educated to undergraduate/master level in Computer Science / Maths or  numerate subjects.</li> <li>Rigorous and focus on details, strong logical thinking and reasoning skills</li> <li>Proficient in Python (5 years of working experience) and SQL or noSQL data structure/ data model and database management. Working experience with time-series data, Pandas, Flask, Numpy is a must. </li> <li>Keen to develop and apply understanding of risk principles – Initial Margin, VaR, collateral haircuts, stress testing, back testing, liquidity stress testing.</li> <li>Experience related to Financial/ Risk management; exchange/clearing house risk management experience  is a plus.</li> <li>Knowledge of crypto market, corporate action events and their impacts on the pricing adjustment is a plus</li> <li>Highly proficient written and verbal communication skills.</li> <li>Ability to coordinate within teams across businesses.</li> <li>Analytical and problem solving skills.</li> <li>Passionate about cryptocurrency and blockchain.</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1.</li> <li>Be the owner of your own learning curve.</li> <li>The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing a brand new product from scratch alongside with a talented team</li> </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/2EE8645201/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[careers@crypto.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain/Solidity Developer (Codefi)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Consensys]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.consensys.net]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Europe, United States, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About ConsenSys&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is the leading Ethereum software company. We enable developers, enterprises, and people worldwide to build next-generation applications, launch modern financial infrastructure, and access the decentralized web. Our product suite, composed of Infura, Quorum, Codefi, MetaMask, and Diligence, serves millions of users, supports billions of blockchain-based queries for our clients, and has handled billions of dollars in digital assets. Ethereum is the largest programmable blockchain in the world, leading in business adoption, developer community, and DeFi activity. On this trusted, open source foundation, we are building the digital economy of tomorrow. To explore our products and solutions, visit http://consensys.net/.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Codefi product group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Codefi is at the forefront of the blockchain fintech revolution. It builds, deploys and runs critical applications across both Enterprise and crypto/DeFi, multiple blockchain verticals (digital assets, payments, data, markets, networks, staking, Ethereum 2.0), as well as ConsenSys’s other industry leading products, including MetaMask, Quorum and Infura. The Codefi team is composed of multiple decentralised product teams across all verticals distributed across Europe and US and working mostly remotely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;With our products like MetaMask, Infura, and Quorum serving as gateways for over a million worldwide users to interact with new blockchain and “DeFi” applications like Uniswap, Maker, Compound, we need innovative problem solvers who are interested in tackling the complex challenges that exist in the blockchain and financial ecosystems and scaling developer and user-facing systems to tens of millions of users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll get to work on&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain technology and “DeFi” are changing finance by making it accessible and equitable to everyone, everywhere. You’ll play an integral part in this transformation by making interacting with complex financial and blockchain data not only simpler and better, but delightful.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Blockchain/Solidity Developer you will join a world class technical team, with State of the Art expertise in developing &amp;amp; delivering advanced decentralized applications across various crypto/DeFi use cases (NFTs, staking, lending/borrowing, trading/AMMs) and institutional use cases (digital assets and payments). You will join a multinational agile and product team where you will be responsible for the delivery of Solidity smart contracts and DApps in production to a wide range of users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years of experience as a Software Engineer&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;1y+ years of Solidity smart contract development experience&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years of as front-end or fullstack or backend developer (React, Node.js, ideally Typescript)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience developing, deploying and running Dapps/smart contracts in production on Ethereum mainnet or L2/sidechain (ideally DeFi Dapps/protocols and/or token-based use cases)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of secure Solidity development patterns for tokens and DeFi protocols&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of Javascript ethereum SDKs (web3,js, ethers.js)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good knowledge of most prominent ERC/EIP Ethereum standards&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good knowledge of smart contract development tools/frameworks (Truffle, Hardhat)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using smart contract auditing tools (MythX, other)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in CI/CD setup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;High quality and testing standards&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good documentation practises&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points for any of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience developing and contributing to open source projects &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(incl. but not limited to Solidity open source codebases)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with DeFi protocols mechanics and smart contract codebases, and/or digital assets/payments and other token standards like ERC-777/20/721/1155/1400 and existing open source&amp;nbsp; implementations (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.openzeppelin.com/contracts/4.x/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;OpenZeppelin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ConsenSys/UniversalToken&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Universal Token&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge/understanding of cross-chain interoperability techniques (HTLC, bridging)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge/understanding of L2 technologies (ZK/optimistic rollups, PoS/PoA sidechains)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using smart contract auditing techniques (fuzzing, other)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep knowledge/experience understanding of EVM&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BSc/MSc in Computer Science or related subject&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Other skills to demonstrate:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication in English&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Teamwork, flexibility, initiative, communication and organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to share knowledge, train other developers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Willingness to constantly learn &amp;amp; improve, challenging yourself to stay at the top of your game&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Don&#39;t check all of the boxes? Don&#39;t sweat it. We’re passionate about building a diverse team of humans and as such, if you think you&#39;ve got what it takes to create a world-class infrastructure and tools function in our chaotic-but-fun, decentralised, remote-friendly, start-up environment—apply anyway. While we have a pretty good idea of what we need, we&#39;re ready for you to challenge our thinking on who needs to be in this role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join ConsenSys?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Here are some of the perks of being part of a unique organization like ConsenSys&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the most recognized tech companies in the blockchain ecosystem globally.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; A work experience at ConsenSys is a tremendous reference for your future career. ConsenSys alumni have moved on to become tech entrepreneurs, CEOs, and team leads at tech companies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The forefront of a revolution.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; We fundamentally believe blockchain is a next generation of technology that&amp;nbsp; can lay the foundation for a more just and equitable society. You can be a part of building the digital economy of tomorrow and radically transforming our society for the better.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A dynamic startup environment with deep roots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. We are one of the earliest blockchain companies and a leader in the space.&amp;nbsp; You’ll join a network of entrepreneurs and technologists that reaches the edge of our ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep technical challenges&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Blockchain technology is just over 10 years old. Ethereum itself is still a toddler. There is much to be done before these platforms can scale to the order of millions or billions of users. We are building the tools, infrastructure and applications l that are pushing the technology forward.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous learning and improvements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. You’ll be constantly exposed to new concepts, ideas and frameworks from your peers and as you work on different projects — challenging you to stay at the top of your game.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Don&#39;t check all of the boxes? Don&#39;t sweat it. We’re passionate about building a diverse team of humans and as such, if you think you&#39;ve got what it takes to create a world-class infrastructure and tools function in our chaotic-but-fun, decentralised, remote-friendly, start-up environment—apply anyway. While we have a pretty good idea of what we need, we&#39;re ready for you to challenge our thinking on who needs to be in this role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ConsenSys is an equal opportunity employer. We encourage people from all backgrounds to apply. We are committed to ensuring that our technology is made available and accessible to everyone. All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, national origin, ancestry, sex, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age, genetic information, religion, disability, medical condition, pregnancy, marital status, family status, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;ConsenSys is aware of fraudulent recruitment practices and we encourage all applicants to review our best practices to protect yourself which can be found &lt;a href=&quot;https://consensys.net/careers/best-practices-to-avoid-recruitment-fraud/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://consensys.net/open-roles/gh_jid?gh_jid=3648652&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/341584/consensys.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[consensys@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[1036a9a0-3cf5-4e0b-bfa9-5c096c0d3a02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Consensys]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City, New York]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The Marketing Team at Chainalysis is dedicated to collaboration and creating cutting-edge research, real customer success stories, and the infinite possibilities in-between to drive expansion around the world. We’re the connectors and facilitators for key-players in the cryptocurrency industry.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are seeking a Full Stack Web Developer who is excited about working for a high paced start-up and is willing to take ownership, deliver value, and make a difference in our processes and outcomes. This is an exciting opportunity for anyone interested in cryptocurrency and emerging technologies. You will be collaborating with a cross-disciplinary team in all phases of development from content development to design.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if you…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build web pages using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript that are responsive, accessible, and perform across all types of devices — phones, tablets, and desktops.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the digital infrastructure development from front-end to back-end, working closely with design.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Test code for cross-browser/platform compatibility and troubleshoot any technical issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform website maintenance in WordPress, keeping plugins updated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Remain up to date on web trends and standards.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build and test marketing emails and landing page templates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are familiar with Figma, Photoshop, Illustrator, or comparable tools for design and developer collaboration.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have industry experience building rich web experiences using modern frameworks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are able to thrive in a startup environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have strong communication skills to help articulate technical concepts to all stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-DP1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5668374002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Backend Developer (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Current Media]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://current.us/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote from anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is Current?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to enable passive income and access to capital for budget-conscious consumers through their everyday activities. We accomplish this with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=us.current.android&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;a superapp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://modephone.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;smartphone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; that pay users to listen to music, charge their phone, play games, complete surveys; and connect them with exclusive deals to save and earn even more. You can learn more about us &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://currentmobile.us&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve seen 10x user growth in the last year: over 500,000 people earn on Current daily, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;we pay over $1M to people each quarter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and are maintaining positive margins at $20M+ annual run rate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Engineering and Product team works in autonomous, cross-functional pods. Each pod has a Product Manager, 5-7 Engineers, and a QA Engineer rallied around a core part of the product; together they are responsible for defining and achieving a set of OKRs. Our team of 50 is distributed across the globe, with half in Engineering and Product, and with leaders and builders from Google, Facebook, Amazon, Intel and numerous startups. We plan to be 80+ people by the end of 2021, supporting millions of daily users.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are rigorously data-driven, viewing everything as an experiment and utilizing feature-flagging to support continuous delivery and A/B testing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for passionate Backend Developers to join one of our cross-functional pods, focused on a focused problem area in the product. At Current, you’ll find yourself:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;working closely with your PM to understand the customer’s needs, and find minimal ways to test hypotheses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;taking projects from planning through technical implementation, deployment, and post-deployment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;writing high-quality, stable, maintainable, observable and well-tested code.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;working in a 2-week sprint, shipping to production daily.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;collaborating with peers outside of your pod to help mature Current’s infrastructure and get us ready for the next 10x.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for multiple senior-level Developers to join the team. We offer a generous salary and benefits based on experience and location.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Technology&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We rely heavily on the following technologies to provide a seamless earning experience for millions of users:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://rubyonrails.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ruby on Rails&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for our main application.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://nodejs.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;NodeJS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for some smaller services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for our infrastructure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.postgresql.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Postgres&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/rds/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;RDS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;) and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;DynamoDB&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for our persistent data stores.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://redis.io/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Redis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/elasticache/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Elasticache&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;) for our in-memory cache.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/mperham/sidekiq&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Sidekiq&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/sqs/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SQS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for our asynchronous queues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/codedeploy/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CodeDeploy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cloudbees.com/products/codeship&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CodeShip&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for our CI/CD pipeline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://kotlinlang.org/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kotlin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; (60%) and Java (40%)&amp;nbsp; for our Android apps.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We&#39;d love to talk with you if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;the company and problem space excite you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you have plenty of experience building robust and scalable products, including hands-on experience creating web applications with Rails.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you’re excited to deliver high-quality features at a fast pace, and are eager to find the most minimal way to test hypotheses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you&#39;re passionate about automated testing and continuous delivery.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you’re a candid and empathetic communicator.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you’re excited to join a growth-stage startup, and to help level-up the company. Expect some chaos!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you’re confident working independently on large problems, but know when and how to include others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you have experience building large-scale systems that store and process lots of data (a plus, but not required).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you have some experience with technical leadership (a plus, but not required).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interview Process&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The process is normally a 30-minute initial interview, a 1-hour technical and culture fit interview, a 1-hour technical interview, and 1 hour interview with the CTO. For the larger technical interview, we will send you a product brief 24 hours beforehand to review and prepare an implementation plan. During the interview, we will review your plan together and ask you to implement a part of it in a shared coding editor.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We all share the same core values:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lead with Purpose&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Leadership does not necessarily mean management. Everyone is a leader, no matter the role. Taking pride in your responsibilities, finding &amp;amp; executing solutions is key.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Focus on the ‘Why’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;- The best solutions start with everyone understanding the problem and its impact. We’ve found that if someone understands the ‘why’, they will produce an innovative &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;‘what’ and ‘how’&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. If we cannot explain the ‘why’ clearly, we don’t understand the problem ourselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bring a Sense of Humor&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Our work environment is a lighthearted &amp;amp; positive place where employees are united by humor and camaraderie; we believe laughter is a great way to uplift employee morale and form bonds with each other.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Set New Precedents&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - We drive innovation and push boundaries for all company activities while understanding that anything worth doing will have roadblocks. We set a new standard of worth for people’s time, data, and attention while rewarding what most other companies take.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaboration&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - We won’t thrive without recognizing others’ strengths. Listen and evolve together, helping and supporting each other for the sake of a collective goal.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;We believe in the following workplace norms:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Honor Commitments, Your Word Matters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Specific, Measurable, Attainable, Relevant &amp;amp; Timely (S.M.A.R.T) Asks &amp;amp; Answers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Allow OKRs To Guide Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Individual &amp;amp; Departmental OKRs will largely impact success at Current Mobile.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Agree to Disagree &amp;amp; Commit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; -Voice concerns in a respectful &amp;amp; appropriate manner directly to your manager or the Executive Team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assume Positive Intent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - Always start from the idea that a person meant well or was doing their best, no matter what they say or do.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we are offering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;***We are a remote-first company so this position is 100% remote from anywhere that can overlap with US CST / EST hours***&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participation in the company&#39;s equity &amp;amp; token plan.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We pay out individual bonuses every two months in accordance with our bi-monthly OKRs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Health, dental, and vision insurance with employer contribution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with highly curated high-caliber people.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Celebrate employee personal milestones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Remote team-building activities every 6-8 weeks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Virtual happy hours &amp;amp; virtual coffee buddies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bonus.ly - we use bonus.ly as a way to recognize and reward employees for their hard work + commitment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monthly virtual yoga + meditation classes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We follow the “12 PM to 1 PM CST Break” - no meetings during this time to encourage team members to take a break in their workday!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://current.us/jobs/?gh_jid=5710524002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/351812/Current_Media.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[current@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[38be4d80-6e57-4589-a599-b71d9fc28633]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Current Media]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crypto Research Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">About the role</b></div><div><br></div><div>Kraken’s legal team works cross-functionally across the company, focusing on key new product initiatives at the bleeding edge intersection of decentralized systems and the law. As a Crypto Research Analyst, you will drive the diligence process for Kraken’s new asset listings, as well as support reviews for new staking services, parachain auctions and other special projects. This role sits within the Legal department - however, no legal training or qualification is required.</div><div><br></div><div>This is a fully remote role.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Conduct technical, corporate, and market-based research on crypto projects in connection with our asset listing process</li><li>Liaise directly with crypto project teams</li><li>Communicate your findings to members of Kraken’s Legal team through oral and written reports&nbsp;</li><li>Analyze primary source material such as whitepapers, Github repos, and block explorers</li><li>Monitor network progress and developments, including forks, network upgrades, and consensus changes</li><li>Manage a robust, multi-faceted review pipeline, ensuring deadlines are consistently met</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Experience in the crypto industry, or demonstrable passion for and knowledge of crypto-native projects and protocols</li><li>Strong written and oral communication skills - including the ability to translate complex technical concepts and industry terminology so that people across the organization can understand it&nbsp;</li><li>Keen attention to detail, and a commitment to quality</li><li>Project management skills requisite to process multiple projects simultaneously&nbsp;</li><li>A team player who works collaboratively with various functions across the company&nbsp;</li><li>Bachelor’s degree and 2-4 years of work experience&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Nice to have:&nbsp; meaningful experience with computer science, software engineering, or operating a crypto side project</li><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">Location Tagging: #US #EU</span></div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/dbf72066-f5a3-47b3-b87d-8dc0d04ca118/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Account Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitcoindepot.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Depot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is seeking an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Account Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; that will oversee and expand business relationships with targeted clients. This role will develop and implement strategy, sales plans, and forecasts for overall business development, sales and account management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Depot is the largest multi-cryptocurrency ATM Network in the world offering users the ability to buy and sell Bitcoin, Litecoin, and Ethereum instantly at hundreds of locations. Our mission is to provide the most secure, convenient, and fastest cryptocurrency transaction. Our vision is to bring cryptocurrency market to the masses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are proud to be an Atlanta Journal-Constitution Top Work Place for 2021.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generates and develops added-value business with existing clients to meet specified production goals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manages consistent growth within particular client base&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Makes and develops contacts with selected clients and strategic partners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Maintains and develops client relations for new and larger established existing clients, assuring all existing clients are contacted regularly to ensure customer satisfaction and develop need-based marketing relations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develops customer relations including but not limited to sales leads, research, warm calls, qualifying leads, developing leads, and customer service&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Closely interacts with customer service, accounting and operations team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develops and implements a sales action plan with objectives and strategies to increase revenue and aggressively acquire new accounts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Seeks and creates opportunities to expand business with current clients’ identifying further business needs and presents a solution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Grows existing accounts and prospective clients to full potential and generates maximum revenue on a long-term basis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attends conventions, conferences, and trade shows as needed; prepares post-event reports and analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Regularly interacts with executives of major clients&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analyzes existing and anticipated client needs and promote company services to meet such requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manages the preparation and implementation of sales and business development plans, sales forecasts and strategies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Formulates the overall objectives and strategy to develop a high-value relationship within all areas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understands prospective client’s culture, product portfolio, competitive position, financial state, investment plan, organization structure and key decision makers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Functions as liaison between client companies and operations staff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Negotiates contracts and work agreements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generates weekly, monthly, and quarterly reports, tracking work as specified by manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Promotes company endorsed programs and services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Performs other related duties as assigned by management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree (B.A.) in business related field or equivalent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum of 2 years related experience or equivalent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated ability to create sales results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong organizational, problem-solving, and analytical skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage priorities and workflow&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Acute attention to detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven ability to handle multiple projects and meet deadlines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to deal effectively with a variety of individuals at all organizational levels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to communicate professionally and effectively in person, on the phone, electronically, or through other means to individuals and groups&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient with Google Suite&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Salary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous PTO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Health benefits offered with a company contribution towards premiums&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Wellness benefits&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401K Matching&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Revenue Sharing Plan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Casual dress environment when in office&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monthly company celebrations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Advancement opportunities based on results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitcoindepot/jobs/4817574003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/556151/bitcoin-depot-image-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitcoindepot@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[49753fb8-b518-4786-89b5-9d1bf0e19ac0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Product Marketing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[PayStand]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paystand.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Millbrae, California, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paystand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paystand is a hungry, fast-growing, Series-C startup with three locations! Nestled in the beautiful Santa Cruz mountains, just south of Silicon Valley is where we started. We have our offices in amazing and historic Guadalajara Mexico and Salt Lake City with the dramatic backdrops of the mountains of Utah.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to unlock capital efficiency for enterprise businesses through our transformative&amp;nbsp;“Payments as a Service” platform. Our smart billing and payment network uses revolutionary internet, blockchain, and FinTech services to digitize receivables, automate processing, reduce time-to-cash, lower transaction costs, and produce new revenue for our clients. Paystand is venture-backed, having been consistently recognized as one of the top innovators in FinTech, and fastest growing companies in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role At A Glance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paystand is seeking a creative, technology-oriented Head of Product Marketing who combines technical product savvy with a customer lifecycle marketing mindset. You are part product and technology enthusiast and part marketer with a passion for engaging audiences and making innovative technology accessible. You are well-versed in trends within fintech and the general B2B landscape, but also know how to position new technology to drive engagement and adoption.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As the Head of Product Marketing you’ll be responsible for product launches, go-to-market, messaging, positioning, user and market research, and improving our overall product experience. We’re looking for a leader who is the comfortable setting overall strategy and building/managing teams but is also no stranger to doing the work. You will be responsible for building and leading the Product Marketing team, while also managing cross-functional interaction between Sales, Marketing, and external agencies to implement new campaigns and strategies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own Product Marketing, messaging, and growth strategy with an ability to own, ideate, and drive projects to completion.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Launch new products &amp;amp; manage go-to-market execution. Create the vision and strategy for product development through customer research, compelling customer stories, and strong project management execution.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up-level our positioning and messaging. Our business model is unique in the payments industry and our value propositions are new to CFOs and finance organizations. You’ll be responsible for generating much wider product awareness.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cross-functional project management. Collaborate across Product, Marketing, and Sales to drive new products and messages to the final stages, helping enable all our GTM functions with strong product messaging.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own and manage all product marketing activities associated with the Paystand platform and product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Product Management to define product/service offerings and deliver corresponding marketing content for core audiences.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deliver product marketing materials and training across all Paystand products/services to support Sales.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage internal data and platform insights that will further support messaging and product positioning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gather market feedback through a variety of channels, including customer interviews, surveys, and events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive product messaging and campaign messaging at key Paystand events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the competitive landscape in relation to Paystand’s core product positioning and messaging.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the team on lead generation strategy, internal/external communication, sales enablement, client services support, and channel marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8-10 years experience in fintech, software, and/or SAAS product marketing (fintech highly preferred).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track record of successful go-to-market campaigns at high-growth companies, delivering compelling product narratives to different audiences, especially within B2B.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong quantitative skills, excellent analytical thinker, and a data-driven mindset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent writer, with a history of taking complicated or detailed technology concepts and turning them into customer-facing value propositions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-tasker comfortable working in a fast-paced environment where strategies or campaigns can quickly shift as business needs warrant.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with ERP and the accounts receivable/payable cycle is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A left-brain / right-brain thinker who marries quantitative experimentation with a sense of customer empathy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven collaboration, interpersonal, problem solving, and verbal &amp;amp; written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BA or MA degree in business, marketing, or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Time Off: Flexible vacation policy to encourage people to get out and see the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team Fun: Regularly scheduled events, sports, game nights, book clubs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Learning: Learning &amp;amp; Development opportunities for you to grow your skills and career.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great team: Working with fun, hardworking, nice people who are committed to making a difference!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Legal benefits + additional benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity for growth in a fast-paced early-stage startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We understand that no candidate is perfectly qualified for any job. Experience comes in different forms; many skills are transferable; and passion goes a long way. Even more important than your resume is a clear demonstration of dedication, impact, and the ability to thrive in a fluid and collaborative environment. We want you to learn new things in this role, and we encourage you to apply if your experience is close to what we’re looking for. We also know that diversity of background and thought makes for better problem solving and more creative thinking, which is why we&#39;re dedicated to adding new perspectives to the team. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Availability &lt;/strong&gt;- Bay area/Scotts Valley, CA.&amp;nbsp;Salt Lake City area, UT. Guadalajara, MX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(This is not a remote position)***No recruiters please***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only English resumes will be considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://paystand.com/job-listing/?gh_jid=4821934003&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/188126/Paystand.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paystand@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9713c611-4d29-448b-a71c-3c8d3ca06a70]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[PayStand]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Market Data Systems Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[DRW]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://drw.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Chicago]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRW&lt;/strong&gt; is a technology-driven, diversified principal trading firm. We trade our own capital at our own risk, across a broad range of asset classes, instruments and strategies, in financial markets around the world. As the markets have evolved over the past 25 years, so has DRW – maximizing opportunities to include real estate, cryptoassets and venture capital. With over 1000 employees at our Chicago headquarters and offices around the world, we work together to solve complex problems, challenge consensus and deliver meaningful results. It’s a place of high expectations, deep curiosity and thoughtful collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Market Data Systems Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; on our Market Data Systems team, you will play an integral role in all operational aspects of onboarding, managing and maintaining various datasets (real time and historical) used by traders and quantitative researchers to analyze financial markets, determine trading opportunities, and establish trading strategies.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will do in this role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a subject matter expert in market data platform, consisting of real time platform and generic financial time series platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with traders, researchers and engineers to integrate market data platform into research lifecycle&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interact with researchers to identify required data feeds and onboard them&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhance market data platform for internal data publishing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Propose solutions for various integration use cases for internal systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will need in this role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in market data systems (OneTick, Activ Financial, KDB, B-Pipe, Elektron)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in working with datasets of any shape or form (timeseries, reference data, fundamental data, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in data related concepts (metadata, descriptive metrics, attributes, properties, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with databases and query construction&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Programming skills: Python/C++&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a fast-paced environment, prioritize multiple tasks and projects, and efficiently handle the demands of a trading environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional skills or experience which enhance consideration for this role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with Amazon Web Services or other cloud providers (S3, Athena)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience working with variety of financial data providers and exchange data&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience working with traders and quantitative researchers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with real time software concepts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about DRW&#39;s processing activities and our use of job applicants&#39; data, please view our Privacy Notice at &lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;California residents, please review the&amp;nbsp;California Privacy Notice&amp;nbsp;for information about certain legal rights at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#LI-SK1&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/drweng/jobs/3671657?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145892/drw.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[drw@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bf32acf8-cf47-410b-aa59-74974c4d6afd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[DRW]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Circle]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.circle.com/de/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berkeley - also open to remote in US]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Circle is a global financial technology firm that enables businesses of all sizes to harness the power of digital currency and public blockchains for payments, commerce and financial applications worldwide. Circle platforms and products provide a suite of internet-native financial services for payments, treasury infrastructure and capital formation. Circle is also a principal developer of USD Coin (USDC), which has become the fastest growing dollar digital currency in the world. USDC has grown to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;over 35 billion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in circulation and supported over&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; $1.3 trillion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in transactions in the past year. Circle’s payments and treasury infrastructure services available through the Circle Account and APIs helps bridge the legacy financial system and digital currency and blockchain based finance.&amp;nbsp; Circle’s SeedInvest service brings internet-native fundraising and capital formation to startups and growth companies.&amp;nbsp; Combined, Circle’s suite of services helps companies to participate in a more open, global and inclusive financial system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be part of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;With the mission “To raise global economic prosperity through the frictionless exchange of financial value,” Circle was founded on the belief that the internet, blockchains and digital currency will rewire the global economic system, creating a fundamentally more open, inclusive, efficient and integrated world economy.&amp;nbsp; We envision a global economy where people and businesses everywhere can more freely connect and transact with each other with new technologies for digital money and internet-native finance. We believe such a system can raise prosperity for people and companies everywhere. Our mission is powered by the values we espouse and which we expect all Circlers to respect. We are Multistakeholder, serving the needs of our customers, our shareholders, our employees and families, our local communities and our world. Furthermore, we are also Mindful, Driven by Excellence, and High Integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Engineering at Circle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Over the past year, Circle has been expanding its product offerings and unveiled Circle APIs: a set of solutions and smarter technology to help businesses accept payments in a more global, scalable and efficient alternative to traditional banking rails (spoiler: we’re using USD Coin under the hood).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re going to rapidly grow our API customer base and enable even more businesses to easily integrate and benefit from the breakthrough of programmable money on the internet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you’re data-driven, interested in building something meaningful and would love to work in an entrepreneurial environment, we can’t wait to hear from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will aspire to our four core values:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multistakeholder&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - you have dedication and commitment to our customers, shareholders, employees and families and local communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mindful&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - you seek to be respectful, an active listener and to pay attention to detail.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driven by Excellence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - you are driven by our mission and our passion for customer success which means you relentlessly pursue excellence, that you do not tolerate mediocrity and you work intensely to achieve your goals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Integrity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; - you seek open and honest communication, and you hold yourself to very high moral and ethical standards.&amp;nbsp; You reject manipulation, dishonesty and intolerance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here is our team hierarchy for individual contributors:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Principal Software Engineer (V)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Staff Software Engineer (IV)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Senior Software Engineer (III)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Software Engineer (II)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Software Engineer (I)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be responsible for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Software Engineer on the Circle team, you will build scalable microservices that are responsible for reliable and secure APIs that transfer value &amp;amp; assets across all blockchain protocols (think Bitcoin and Ethereum, for example) as well as traditional banking protocols (think credit cards, bank transfers etc).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll bring to Circle (not all required):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;1+ years of professional software development experience in object oriented languages like Java and Go&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A broad understanding of API design and REST principles, know how to derive and communicate a good design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Cloud Services (AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure, etc)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with SQL databases and designing schemas&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Willing and able to learn unfamiliar languages and technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in the deployment of production-quality, scalable software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A focus on coding standards and code quality with speed -- a desire to have great test coverage to enable continuous delivery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent communication skills, able to collaborate with remote teams, share ideas and present concepts effectively&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Self-starter with a curious mindset, you enjoy moving at a fast pace, shipping software that improves the user experience and constantly improving your work with little supervision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;equal opportunity employer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and value diversity at Circle. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/circle/jobs/5711006002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143132/circle.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[circle@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[e4722b14-c590-4410-b876-45bc581c49c8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Circle]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
