<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sr. Product Manager - API / Core Platform Services]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bittrex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Bellevue, WA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Bittrex, a Seattle-based cryptocurrency exchange,&amp;nbsp;is hiring a Senior Product Manager over our API / Core Platform Services. Founded by three cybersecurity engineers in 2014,&amp;nbsp;we build our products with security first, offering&amp;nbsp;access to over 100 cryptocurrencies in the United States along with lightning-fast trade execution and dependable digital wallets.&amp;nbsp;We believe in the potential of blockchain and its ability to provide game-changing solutions, and we’re looking for talented and passionate individuals to join our exceptional team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Senior Product Manager with strong technical skills to be responsible for the product roadmap and delivery of the core platform services that everything else builds upon. This position plays a crucial role in the growth strategy of Bittrex. You will have the opportunity to collaborate with business units, technology teams, and API end-users to drive initiatives dealing with API products servicing the entire customer journey. Our Core Platform team is accountable for developing and maintaining APIs, Policies, Databases, Performance, and Notifications so we need someone who has experience with APIs, is data-driven, process oriented, technically adept and has a proven track record of Product Management achievement. As a Senior Product Manager, you will be working alongside talented developers, support and operations teams, and our Core Platform Product Owner to ensure core platform services are meeting the needs of other teams and our customers. You will also be responsible for driving our API strategy and prioritizing the implementation of staking functionality for relevant assets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this role you will evaluate new requests for services and coordinate the needs of other engineering teams and customers to formulate a service and API strategy. The ideal candidate holds themselves to a high standard as they execute key PM responsibilities including; conducting research and competitive analysis, creating and owning the product roadmap, defining business requirements and prioritizing product initiatives.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Discovery-&lt;/strong&gt; Continually work to identify what users really need and what would be valuable, useful, and feasible. Work in collaboration with support teams, and product teams to deliver services they need for their product roadmaps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Usage &amp;amp; Performance metrics- &lt;/strong&gt;Review current data tracking capabilities and ensure that sufficient data is being gathered that can guide in decision making.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Strategy&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Vision &lt;/strong&gt;- Set the strategic vision for platform services and where the product is going to be in the next 1,3,5 years and what it will take to get there. Represent and communicate shared vision across the team and with stakeholders across the company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Roadmap &lt;/strong&gt;– Outline and communicate the short-term platform services product vision in a 1-to-3-month Roadmap. Coordinate with the Product Owner to ensure the product backlog reflects timelines and deliverables that align with the vision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prioritization of Initiatives &lt;/strong&gt;– Coordinate with the Product Owner to ensure that the priority of strategic items match the product roadmap and stay in sync when adjustments are made.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business KPI Reporting- &lt;/strong&gt;Review and report on how well platform services are helping to meet the KPI’s outlined in the corporate strategy.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Business Requirements – &lt;/strong&gt;Collaborate with legal, finance, UX, Security, and Compliance to outline business requirements needed for a given initiative.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financial Modeling &lt;/strong&gt;– collaborate with finance and others to model the financial benefits of roadmap initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Review of Engineering Plan- &lt;/strong&gt;Review stories created to ensure that no misunderstanding occurs as the team translates business requirements into epics/stories&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Thought Leadership:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;Leverage feedback from internal and external partners to influence company strategy. Drive cross-team initiatives. Be the PM who understands how things work conceptually as well as technically and why they work that way.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of experience in product management, with a proven track record of taking products from ideation to launch and working directly with software development teams to ship software products in an agile development environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building, supporting, and versioning public facing APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of REST APIs, Web Sockets, Asp.net, Javascript and/or Azure. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience releasing software at a global scale.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sufficient technical depth to advise, support, and gather feedback from internal and external partner developers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in organization, prioritization, and attention to detail, with proven ability to manage multiple projects with concurrent timelines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to thrive in a fast-paced startup environment where you sometimes need to wear multiple hats and step outside your box of responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent at executing PM responsibilities and best practices in an agile organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated success in driving product ideas into fully functioning products that deliver on the organization’s KPIs. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;History in owning the strategy and roadmap for successful products.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven track record of strategic decision making, balancing the needs of the business, security, legal or other stakeholders. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written, verbal and storytelling communication skills. &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Greater consideration will be given to those applicants who can demonstrate the following skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of cryptography and security fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of digital asset exchanges and trading systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building services on cloud infrastructure (e.g. Azure, AWS)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bittrex is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to age, ancestry, color, family or medical care leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran status, race, religion, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by applicable laws, regulations, and ordinances.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/wPebbTGCUCQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bittrex/jobs/5800280002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175858/bittrex.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bittrex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[80244eca-7fc4-4796-8431-8d6255bccb6c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Lead - Banking Operations (Remote - Work from Anywhere)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Xapo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://xapo.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xapo is an international fintech startup on a mission to protect and grow its clients’ life savings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re a fully distributed team that works remotely from 50+ countries around the world. We may come from many different cultures and backgrounds, but it’s our values, our resourcefulness, and our drive that makes us Xapiens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We work hard, think globally, and inspire each other to grow every day. If you’re the best at what you do and share our passion, we want you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us, wherever you are, and help us build a digital bank worthy of the digital age at Xapo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Position overview&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for a Technical Principal to join our Banking Operations engineering function. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Xapo we are building truly cross functional teams with full ownership of design, architecture, build, test, delivery and operations. You will collaborate closely with your fellow team members from the product, apps, design and QA communities of practice.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Tech Principal you will provide guidance and coaching around technical good practices as well as playing an active role in the Development Community of practice.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Although we are headquartered in Gibraltar, this is a full time, 100% remote position. Work from anywhere!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support, coach and develop team members into top performing engineers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build a great place to work for talented and motivated people&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Designing, developing and deploying backend services with a focus on high availability, fault tolerance, low latency and security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Take full end to end responsibility of the services your team owns, from development through to production operation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Skills needed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Significant software engineering experience in one or more general purpose programming languages (we use Python)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great teamwork and communication skills, comfortable preparing high quality documentation and designs to aid understanding and knowledge sharing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of microservice architectures, container based 12 factor apps and cloud native patterns around fault tolerance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building contract first services and adopting patterns and frameworks to enable appropriate automated testing at unit, contract, service and end to end levels.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building services that can be deployed on demand, quickly and with quality. Excellent understanding of CI/CD patterns and good practice.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understands the role of high quality observability in building highly scalable and performant software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with a public or private cloud vendor&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in Finance is beneficial&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Other requirements&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A dedicated workspace&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A reliable internet connection with the fastest speed possible in your area&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Devices and other essential equipment that meet minimal technical specifications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Alignment with Our Values.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY WORK FOR XAPO?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPACT GLOBALLY, WORK REMOTELY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shape the Future: Improve lives through cutting-edge technology, work 100% remotely from anywhere in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own Your Success: Receive attractive remuneration, enjoy an autonomous work culture and flexible hours, apply your expertise to meaningful work every day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expect Excellence: Collaborate, learn, and grow with a high-performance team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT XAPO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We founded Xapo to address two of the biggest issues with Bitcoin adoption: accessibility and security. In a matter of years, we developed an industry-leading platform that introduced cryptocurrency into the daily lives of millions worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, we’re bringing our expertise to all facets of our users’ finances. Because no matter who we are or where we’re from, we all deserve more options, more control, and more peace of mind where our money is concerned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re an Equal Opportunity Employer – we believe that diversity is critical to our success as a global company. An inclusive workplace is the foundation of Xapo – it allows us to create products that cater to clients around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/xapo61/jobs/4886700003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175504/xapo500x500.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[xapo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f1ade05b-4c67-4366-b825-57e86b9f373d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Xapo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Delivery Management Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.elliptic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>As digital assets and cryptocurrency become more widely adopted every day,, our products are essential to ensure cryptocurrency is safe and accessible to all.  Our solutions help to prevent financial crime and allow cryptocurrencies to be used for good. Our products are used by some of the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, financial institutions and government agencies to screen over $1 billion of transactions every single week.</p> <p>Elliptic is backed by some of the top VCs: SBI Group, Albion VC, Octopus Ventures, SignalFire, Paladin Capital, Santander InnoVentures, and Digital Currency Group, and we have grown globally with teams in the UK, USA, Singapore and Tokyo. </p>To achieve our mission, we depend on our incredible team of Elliptites.  <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/life-at-elliptic" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Our values</a> are reflected in everything we do and every decision we make, both internally and outwardly to our customers.  We actively encourage Elliptities to challenge the status quo and allow the freedom to innovate and learn every day.  We encourage new ideas and learning, whether that’s through collaboration, our curiosity sessions, or utilising your professional development budget - personal growth is important to us all.<p><strong><br>Do you want to be part of the future of finance? Are you excited about solving problems that have never been solved before? Do you get a buzz from mentoring and helping others succeed?</strong></p> <p><strong>The impact you will have:</strong></p><p>As Delivery Management Lead you will be responsible for mentoring the growing number of delivery managers to help them and their product-engineering teams go smoothly from idea conception through to successful launch. This will require you to empower them, encourage the sharing of best practice and putting in place processes and procedures to help them flourish. </p> <p>However, you’ll also be hands on with delivery as you work with at least one product-engineering team as their delivery manager. This will enable you to be hands on with the design and build; challenging engineers about design choices, product managers about functionality and learn in depth about our tech, stack and tooling.</p><p><strong>What you will do:</strong></p><ul> <li>Steer the growing delivery management function by mentoring and managing the delivery managers</li> <li>Put in place best practice, efficient process and knowledge sharing opportunities to level up the delivery management function</li> <li>Report to key stakeholders and the senior management team about key delivery metrics and progress</li> <li>Work collaboratively with the Product Managers and Tech Leads to define the roadmap for your product-engineering team/s, and ensure resource and capacity is mapped out especially where there are cross team dependencies or blockers</li> <li>Coordinate with the Delivery Managers to ensure release timelines, map dependencies and ensure alignment across the entire Product-Engineering function</li> <li>Evolve processes and methodologies to build fun, efficient and scalable delivery teams</li> </ul><ul> <li>Facilitate agile ceremonies in the scrum master role and share best practice with other delivery managers</li> <li>Develop and own communication plans to effectively and proactively communicate project status, issues, and risks to stakeholders</li> <li>Own the release planning process for your product-engineering team/sto ensure engineers, product and key stakeholders are all aligned and ready for on-time and successful releases</li> </ul><p><strong>You will be a great fit here if you:</strong></p><ul> <li>You’re a people person and love to help others develop and grow in their roles</li> <li>You enjoy taking both the macro view as well as diving deep into the details on a project</li> <li>You’re naturally curious, love learning new things, and are proactive in sharing knowledge with others.</li> <li>You possess a strong sense of urgency in driving projects to completion while achieving the desired business outcomes.</li> <li>You are comfortable collaborating with client facing teams as well as technical teams to creatively solve complex problems </li> <li>You want to build deep technical and product knowledge to work with the product managers and engineers to create innovative solutions and products, and to be able to collaborate with engineers on technical choices and cross team dependencies.</li> </ul><p><strong>Our ideal candidate has:</strong></p><ul> <li>Successfully led delivery teams previously and/or has a strong focus on mentoring and managing</li> <li>A proven track record of resolving issues and risks in a cross functional and collaborative way both at the macro function level as well as a product-engineering team level</li> <li>Experience of managing a product backlog and roadmap driven by multiple stakeholders and priorities</li> <li>A track record of success in delivering complex and cross team projects within the SaaS sector</li> <li>Used a variety of delivery methodologies, including Scrum, Kanban and Waterfall as well as a wide range of project management tooling; ZenHub, JIRA, Asana, Confluence, etc</li> </ul> <p><strong>Bonus Points for:</strong></p><ul><li>Knowledge or experience within the cryptocurrency/blockchain sector</li></ul><ul> <li>Share Options</li> <li>Holiday - 25 days + public holidays</li> <li>Private Health Insurance - we use Vitality!</li> <li>Work Pension Scheme</li> <li>Quarterly full-day off-sites &amp; annual company 3-day offsite</li> <li>Personal training budget &amp; LinkedIn Learning subscription</li> <li>Home office allowance</li> <li>Enhanced parental leave; we provide eligible employees, regardless of gender or whether they become a parent by birth or adoption, 16 weeks fully-paid leave and job-protected leave</li> <li>Full access to Spill Mental Health Support</li> <li>Our offices provide all of the amenities you could need</li> <li>Work with top of the range equipment - MacBook Pro and any other equipment you need</li> </ul><p>We know Diversity and Inclusion is much deeper than just hiring, but it’s important for us to mention it here.  We welcome and embrace individuals of all backgrounds and identities at Elliptic, and this is an ongoing priority for us.  We know incredible people don’t all think in the same way.  We want to be challenged every day.  We believe our diverse team of individuals underpins this by bringing creative thinking and innovation to Elliptic every day.  We are committed to creating a diverse, inclusive and equitable workplace, so we welcome applications from everyone, even if you may not think you fit all of the requirements of our roles.  We foster an environment of psychological safety, where everyone feels comfortable to bring their whole self to work. <br></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ebOLNjlYiNg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/elliptic/j/09E9D40FAF/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145877/elliptic.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[elliptic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[fefe721f-d5ba-4eb0-9b9b-f4156a27cb2b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Enterprise Account Executive, LATAM (Spanish-speaking)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Enterprise Account Executives are fast learners, expert storytellers and problem-solvers and we’re obsessed with expanding cryptocurrency markets and helping customers track and prevent fraud and abuse. Our goal is to make sure every cryptocurrency business and financial institution sees the value of implementing our solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enterprise Account Executives are experts at moving prospects through the sales funnel, tailoring their sales approach to the potential buyers’ needs, and evangelizing Chainalysis solutions in a compelling yet approachable way. We measure success by the attainment of assigned quota, accuracy of forecasting, and the growth of accounts in your region.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You exceeded your quota and continue to increased our foothold in our LATAM accounts through strategic and relentless prospecting and developing your sales pipeline as well as expanding existing accounts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve helped us develop compelling product positioning and messaging specific to market trends, competitive drivers, region-specific sales channels, and more&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your relationships with customers are built on trust and transparency resulting in network referrals that ultimately build Chainalysis’ brand awareness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve built a diverse pipeline of opportunities resulting in consistent and accurate forecasting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve consistently used data from sales figures, marketing campaigns, and promotional activities to enable you to meet and exceed sales goals&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Product and Engineering teams rely on your advice and input to inform new product features and solutions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have relationships across departments at Chainalysis allowing you to provide expert advice to prospects related to technical concepts, product roadmaps, solutions implementations, training, and craft appropriate customer proposals&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Recent experience closing complex software sales within the LATAM market with financial services customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong relationships with VAR and System Integration Partners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Key industry knowledge and ability to effectively articulate the Chainalysis value proposition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track record of over-achieving quota (top 10-20% of company) in past positions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to negotiate pricing, terms and conditions and other concessions in complex, multi-year sales agreements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Financial Intelligence, Blockchain, Cyber Security, and/or Cryptocurrency technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-MM1 #LI-Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yNpNz-FvSYQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5800385002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Associate, Finance and Operations]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Pantera Capital]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.panteracapital.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City, Bay Area, or Puerto Rico]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Pantera Capital is the first institutional US-based asset management firm focused exclusively on blockchain and digital assets. We manage over $5bn in equity and tokens across liquid (long / short) and illiquid (venture) strategies. </div><div><br></div><div>We are seeking to hire a Finance &amp; Operations Associate to join the Co-investments and Special Opportunities team based in any of our offices (Bay Area, New York, Puerto Rico). This role reports into the Head of Special Opportunities.</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for an intellectually curious and detail-oriented team player who has previously covered venture and/or growth equity funds in a fast-paced investment management firm.  The ideal candidate is experienced in creating and improving processes such as cash flow management, client management within Salesforce, and subscription document life cycle. </div><div><br></div><div>Additional responsibilities include: assisting with investor follow-ups, document and client distribution list management, and data room setup.</div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Ensuring accuracy of Limited Partner ("LP") information throughout the subscription process, including precise calculation of allocations based on co-investment rights.</li><li>Managing communication with existing and prospective LPs, with particular focus on the notification process for capital calls and distributions.</li><li>Maintaining accurate investor data in the CRM (Salesforce), including tracking and timely replies to ad-hoc LP requests. </li><li>Partnering closely with the Finance and Accounting team to file and track documents, reconcile cash flows, and manage any outstanding communications cross-functionally to provide a seamless LP experience.</li><li>Bonus points for ability to implement automation and efficiency improvements to existing processes.</li><br/>Qualifications:<br/><li>Bachelor's degree in accounting, business, finance, or similar, with a strong academic background at a highly ranked school.</li><li>3+ years of experience in a comparable industry such as  investment management, investment banking, management consulting, public accounting, fund administration. 	Experience with private and alternative investment fund structures preferred.</li><li>Excellent Excel and financial analytical skills.</li><br/>Desired Skills:<br/><li>Ability to work efficiently in a fast-paced and deadline driven environment.</li><li>Highly organized, able to manage multiple projects simultaneously and adequately prioritize.</li><li>Extreme attention to detail and concern for quantitative accuracy, given high-visibility of these activities with limited partners and portfolio companies.</li><li>High EQ and ability to cultivate relationships both internally (cross-functionally) and externally (to improve overall client relationship).</li><li>Impeccable work ethic.</li><li>Ability to roll up their sleeves and do anything and everything to get the job done</li><br/>Compensation:<br/><li>Compensation is competitive and based on experience</li><li>Salary plus performance based bonus</li><li>Healthcare</li><li>401k matching</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/N0d45K1SH4Q" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/panteracapital/1b9e039b-8826-42da-8b37-075f5bef53c1/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145535/pantera_capital.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[pantera@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[39ddee3c-0f1b-4fd8-9347-b2206455a7c1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Pantera Capital]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Center Facilities Technician]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ankr]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ankr.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Cumberland, Kentucky, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About ANKR</strong></p><p>Ankr provides Web3 infrastructure for easy, accessible and affordable deployment of blockchain nodes, API’s, decentralized staking infrastructure and Layer 2 scaling solutions, designed to lower the entry barrier for everyday people, enterprises, and developers to contribute to blockchain ecosystems.</p><p>Check us out at <a href="https://www.ankr.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://www.ankr.com/</a></p><p>Ankr was founded in 2017 in Berkeley, California. Its founding team and headquarters are based in San Francisco. Ankr’s distributed team of 50+ people operates from offices in San Francisco, Shanghai, Moscow, and Amsterdam.</p><p>Joining our operations team means that you will be at the forefront of all we do, maintaining critical facilities infrastructure as part of a close-knit team delivering best-in-class service.</p><p>The Data Center Facilities Technician will be responsible for performing repairs, corrective maintenance, and complex installations, training can be provided.</p><p><br></p><p><strong>What we are looking for in a Data Center Facilities Technician:</strong><br></p><ul> <li>Performs site inspections and monitors the building and alarms</li> <li>You will be responsible for performing preventative maintenance on site infrastructure (e.g. maintenance of primary infrastructures)</li> <li>Undertakes repairs and corrective maintenance</li> <li>Assists in coordinating critical infrastructure</li> <li>You are responsible for completion of site logs and data gathering for permits, such as MOPs and scripts</li> <li>You are expected to respond to all on-site incidents and take action as required</li> <li>May instruct on-site staff during simple incidents</li> <li>Completes complex work requests and circuit installations</li> <li>Effectively collaborates with internal and external departments</li> <li>Provides input to your peers for complex / critical maintenance activities</li> <li>Works through issues in a confident, positive way; is able to influence without authority</li> <li>Carries out more complex infrastructure projects</li> </ul><ul> <li>High School Diploma</li> <li>Able to perform all essential job functions, including walking, standing, bending, stooping, climbing, lifting and manual dexterity, with or without reasonable accommodation</li> <li>Ability to work days/nights/weekends/holidays, if needed and/or required</li> </ul><p>Ankr is an equal opportunity employer. All applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, religion, color, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, status as a protected veteran, or status as a qualified individual with disability.</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/ankr/j/D2FFE821AB/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/746707/ankr-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ankr@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3b58522a-6fba-41ac-b017-94bbed42523c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ankr]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer, Wallet]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York; Portland, Oregon; Chicago, Illinois; Los Angeles, California; San Francisco, California; Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is a crypto exchange and custodian that allows customers to buy, sell, store, and earn more than 30 cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, bitcoin cash, ether, litecoin, and Zcash. Gemini is a New York trust company that is subject to the capital reserve requirements, cybersecurity requirements, and banking compliance standards set forth by the New York State Department of Financial Services and the New York Banking Law. Gemini was founded in 2014 by twin brothers Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss to empower the individual through crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto is about giving you greater choice, independence, and opportunity. We are here to help you on your journey. We build crypto products that are simple, elegant, and secure. Whether you are an individual or an institution, we want to help you buy, sell, and store your bitcoin and cryptocurrency. Crypto is not just a technology, it&#39;s a movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, our mission is to &lt;strong&gt;empower the individual&lt;/strong&gt; and that includes giving our employees flexibility of choice — our Office Optional Policy allows employees to choose to work from one of our physical locations or from home.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select roles that are location-specific will still be eligible for flexible schedules.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Department: &lt;/strong&gt;Software &lt;/span&gt;Engineering&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is regulated and licensed like a bank, but it’s run like a tech startup, and engineering is the core of the company.&amp;nbsp; There’s a wide range of tough problems to solve at Gemini – from properly securing hundreds of millions of dollars worth of customer funds, to developing innovative new blockchain products, to finding new techniques to combat fraud, to shaving microseconds off our API response times, and everything in between.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;All of Gemini’s engineers are able to work across the software platform, not just on their own specialization or subteam. We value a thoughtful, collaborative software development process, coupled with a pragmatic approach to problem solving and delivering software.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Staff Software Engineer, Wallet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As an engineer in wallet, you’ll be working as part of the core team of engineers responsible for supporting blockchain technologies across Gemini’s platform. The team supports everything related to accepting deposits, issuing withdrawals, and the secure storage of cryptocurrency on the platform. This includes everything from key management and signing infrastructure to blockchain integrations and token additions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve feedback cycles at all levels of development (examples: improving the experience of iterating on code locally, deploying to test environments, deploying to production)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quickly ramp up on relevant industry and competitive trends&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Consistently delivers code that sets the standard for quality and maintainability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build secure contract protocols and backend services to connect Gemini users with the crypto ecosystem&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Systematically thinks through potential design impacts on other teams and the company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review other software engineers’ code for correctness, style, and information security concerns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the performance, maintainability, and operations of the Gemini code base by engaging in occasional refactoring and upgrade projects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 5 years of software engineering experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expertise in Scala or in a similar backend programming languages, such as Java or C#&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify and advocate for foundational work and practice improvements in their vertical&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Genuinely passionate about working with developers and improving their experience and velocity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technical aptitude around Blockchain Technology, Cryptography OR Custodian Services for Cryptocurrency*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to work closely across teams and manage dependencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A customer- and product-focused mindset, with the ability to make well-reasoned tradeoffs between speed and quality.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to adapt and handle multiple competing priorities in collaboration with peers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Can successfully plan and execute projects involving multiple developers and complex requirements, prioritizing strategically&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-GG1&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/70jrfYSxKC4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3300445&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Mobile/Web3 Engineer (Codefi)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Consensys]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.consensys.net]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States, Europe, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About ConsenSys&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is the leading Ethereum software company. We enable developers, enterprises, and people worldwide to build next-generation applications, launch modern financial infrastructure, and access the decentralized web. Our product suite, composed of Infura, Quorum, Codefi, MetaMask, and Diligence, serves millions of users, supports billions of blockchain-based queries for our clients, and has handled billions of dollars in digital assets. Ethereum is the largest programmable blockchain in the world, leading in business adoption, developer community, and DeFi activity. On this trusted, open source foundation, we are building the digital economy of tomorrow. To explore our products and solutions, visit http://consensys.net/.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Codefi product group&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Codefi is at the forefront of the blockchain fintech revolution. It builds, deploys and runs critical applications across both Enterprise and crypto/DeFi, multiple blockchain verticals (digital assets, payments, workflows, data, staking, Ethereum 2.0), as well as ConsenSys’s other industry leading products, including MetaMask, Quorum and Infura. The Codefi team is composed of multiple decentralised product teams across all verticals distributed across Europe and US and working mostly remotely.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;With our products like MetaMask, Infura, and Quorum serving as gateways for over a million worldwide users to interact with new blockchain and “DeFi” applications like Uniswap, Maker, Compound, we need innovative problem solvers who are interested in tackling the complex challenges that exist in the blockchain and financial ecosystems and scaling developer and user-facing systems to tens of millions of users. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Codefi teams work closely in partnership with MetaMask and Infura to design, build and deploy delightful user and developer experiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll get to work on&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;MetaMask Mobile has been growing rapidly from our September 2020 launch and now serves almost 3 million monthly users as a cross-platform wallet and web3 browser. As this user base continues to grow, we are working to make MetaMask more robust, accessible, intuitive, delightful, stable and secure. We’re hiring a Senior Web3 Mobile Engineer to join our highly collaborative Codefi/MetaMask team in making this happen and build delightful DeFi and other user experiences into MetaMask Mobile.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for someone with deep experience in both Javascript and ideally ethereum. This person will be helping lead development of features that require interfacing with and extending web3 solutions, patterns and protocols. This could be work related to NFTs, tokens and other programmable assets, decentralized file storage, layer-2 networks, smart contract wallets, decentralized identity systems, wallet provider apis and more.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What excites you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working with engineers and other colleagues with an eye for design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Products with real impact: Your work will touch millions of end users, the best applications in DeFi and NFTs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Built on modern Mobile front-end framework React Native&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digging through crypto/DeFi/NFT users complex challenges—and reimagining the experience completely&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What excites us&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Multiple years of experience shipping javascript code to production&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great understanding of the ethereum blockchain and ecosystem&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with blockchain related development through any of: work experience, hackathons, open source work, personal projects, or similar experiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excitement for helping build a mobile product written in Javascript/Typescript and React Native.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Multiple years of experience in roles requiring collaboration design, QA and product&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A passion for our mission and values&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactive and self-driven to be successful working in a remote environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Brings enthusiasm and the hustle to shipping high-quality code&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are kind, empathetic, and supportive towards the team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Timezone: EST / PST ideally, if in EU/UK you are able to have &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;~4 hours overlap with the American time zones&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bonus points for&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re a MetaMask user!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in Typescript is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in blockchain and building Dapps is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A background in Mobile consumer product startups is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;UI instincts, but not necessarily the ability to create comps from scratch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Don&#39;t check all of the boxes? Don&#39;t sweat it. We’re passionate about building a diverse team of humans and as such, if you think you&#39;ve got what it takes to create a world-class infrastructure and tools function in our chaotic-but-fun, decentralised, remote-friendly, start-up environment—apply anyway. While we have a pretty good idea of what we need, we&#39;re ready for you to challenge our thinking on who needs to be in this role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join ConsenSys?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Here are some of the perks of being part of a unique organization like ConsenSys&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the most recognized tech companies in the blockchain ecosystem globally.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; A work experience at ConsenSys is a tremendous reference for your future career. ConsenSys alumni have moved on to become tech entrepreneurs, CEOs, and team leads at tech companies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The forefront of a revolution.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; We fundamentally believe blockchain is a next generation of technology that&amp;nbsp; can lay the foundation for a more just and equitable society. You can be a part of building the digital economy of tomorrow and radically transforming our society for the better.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A dynamic startup environment with deep roots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. We are one of the earliest blockchain companies and a leader in the space.&amp;nbsp; You’ll join a network of entrepreneurs and technologists that reaches the edge of our ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep technical challenges&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Blockchain technology is just over 10 years old. Ethereum itself is still a toddler. There is much to be done before these platforms can scale to the order of millions or billions of users. We are building the tools, infrastructure and applications l that are pushing the technology forward.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous learning and improvements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. You’ll be constantly exposed to new concepts, ideas and frameworks from your peers and as you work on different projects — challenging you to stay at the top of your game.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is an equal opportunity employer. We encourage people from all backgrounds to apply. We are committed to ensuring that our technology is made available and accessible to everyone. All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, national origin, ancestry, sex, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age, genetic information, religion, disability, medical condition, pregnancy, marital status, family status, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is aware of fraudulent recruitment practices and we encourage all applicants to review our best practices to protect yourself which can be found &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consensys.net/careers/best-practices-to-avoid-recruitment-fraud/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/PTVt2eg0FTA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://consensys.net/open-roles/gh_jid?gh_jid=3648948&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/341584/consensys.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[consensys@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[1036a9a0-3cf5-4e0b-bfa9-5c096c0d3a02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Consensys]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Brave Wallet - Sr. Android Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Brave]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://brave.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;h2&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Brave is looking for an experienced Android­-focused Senior Software Engineer to work on our Brave Wallet Product. This is a high­ profile and impactful, hands­-on position on a growing team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;5+ years experience with Android development&lt;br&gt;Strong Java development skills&lt;br&gt;Working experience with writing C++ code&lt;br&gt;Android Studio and/or Eclipse IDE experience&lt;br&gt;Demonstrated experience developing for material design&lt;br&gt;Android SDK, NDK, and JNI experience&lt;br&gt;Experience with software development via distributed development teams&lt;br&gt;Comfortable working in an open source setting&lt;br&gt;A passion for helping protect users’ privacy and security&lt;br&gt;Written and verbal communication skills in English&lt;br&gt;Proven record of getting things done&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Competitive salary&lt;br&gt;Unlimited PTO&lt;br&gt;Generous 401k plan&lt;br&gt;Stock option grant&lt;br&gt;Travel and conference budgets&lt;br&gt;Commuters benefit (On site only)&lt;br&gt;100% Remote&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;We follow open-source peer-review practices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/kLiLOkzLetE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/brave/jobs/1053060?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145908/brave.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[brave@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d9771ed5-e81b-4920-bc38-de085de85437]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Brave]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Internal Communication Director]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.axiomzen.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We're looking for a driven <b>Communications Director</b> to join our team. You’ll work cross-functionally with team members across the organization on projects big and small to help reach and capture our audiences and communities with important updates and support key partner and partnership communications.</div><div>The dynamic nature of this role requires that the ideal candidate has a great attitude and working&nbsp;knowledge of the blockchain/NFT space (plus a strong appetite to build on that knowledge!).&nbsp;We are looking for someone creative and eager to grow as part of our team and able to flourish in the fluidity of the role. The role will be seen as a business storyteller and must interact seamlessly with a broad range of individuals including members of the engineering and product teams, community and social teams as well as key external partners.</div><div><br></div><div><b>A little about us:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Dapper team members are humble and curious entrepreneurs, builders, and tinkerers who share a passion to demystify blockchain technology and tap its potential to create change in the world. Our people are our greatest strength: our diverse crew flourishes in a distributed hierarchy where personal autonomy and professional growth are encouraged. We value our culture above all else: regardless of where you came from, what you studied, or who you used to work for, your role here will necessitate both a high level of creativity and strategic thinking on complex issues. Everyone here is a founder, and no one fits in a box. We’re all driven by an insatiable thirst for learning and development, and that’s what brings us together.</div><br/>What we will accomplish together:<br/><li>Ensuring our company voice and goals are shared with stakeholders in thoughtful, digestible and transparent ways</li><li>Managing company website content and blog, while building out a repository of impressive communications assets for external and internal use, all that help tell our amazing and evolving story</li><li>Managing core media monitoring activity</li><li>Supporting company social media activity</li><li>Supporting partner communication initiatives thoughtfully, diligently and strategically</li><li>Take on special projects with gusto</li><br/>A little bit about you:<br/><li>You thrive under pressure from multiple angles, laugh a lot, and enjoy working with passionate people.</li><li>Passion for communications with previous experience and demonstrated ability to communicate to all levels within an organization.</li><li>Strong subject matter specific writing skills</li><li>You are capable of applying your skills yourself, with a team, and across a variety of use cases.</li><li>We believe in processes and the power of planning, but you will often have to roll with the punches and prioritize the most impactful tasks on the fly.</li><div><b>More about Dapper Labs:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Dapper Labs is the world's first blockchain entertainment company. We are the creators of industry-leading experiences including CryptoKitties and NBA Top Shot, as well as Dapper Wallet, the simplest way to manage your assets and use the blockchain. We are also the original developers behind Flow, a new decentralized blockchain designed from the ground up for scalability and ease of use.</div><div><br></div><div>Our mission at Dapper Labs is to make the world a more open, empowering, and enjoyable place through consumer adoption of decentralized technologies. We have raised over $600M from leading VCs including Fred Wilson (USV) and Chris Dixon as well as Venrock, Samsung, Google Ventures, Coatue, NBA players, and global artists, among others. Dapper Labs partners include the NBA and NBPA, the NFL-PA, Ubisoft, Warner Music, Turner, Dr. Seuss, Genies, and the UFC, as well as 100+ others.</div><div><br></div><div>Visit our website to learn even more about Dapper Labs, including <a href="https://www.dapperlabs.com/careers#benefits" class="postings-link">information about benefits and perks</a>.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Vvp75OCtwa0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axiomzen/7c8f6108-d35a-4963-8f41-7a477a4c8adf/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194192/axiomzen1.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axiomzen@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5da21464-b527-48a0-a501-0b4f2e445537]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Paralegal (Toronto)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[ChainSafe Systems]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://chainsafe.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Toronto]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe Systems is currently seeking a full-time Paralegal to join our Operations Team in Toronto. Our company is growing fast, and with both a clear vision and strong values, we are the industry leaders in designing and developing scalable solutions for the decentralized web.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe is a unique company in a nascent space that is growing quickly and building a stellar global reputation.&quot;Beyond offering experience across every major blockchain space to our team, we provide an open, inclusive, and supportive environment where we help folks reach their full potential as a human and as a professional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Culture fit and alignment to our core values are extremely important to us. We are fueled by an immense intellectual curiosity of what technology can do and the impact it can have. You will thrive here if you are intensely driven by tackling technical challenges that no one else has solved yet and are inspired by the possibility of building the next generation of web infrastructure and decentralized systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with the Legal Counsel, the Paralegal will be a crucial team member of the legal team, assisting with corporate, immigration and employment law matters. The Paralegal will work with the Legal Counsel to manage ChainSafe’s day-to-day and strategic legal needs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You Will Do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with internal teams and external counsel on cross-functional initiatives related to ChainSafe’s business operations globally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist with creating and maintaining legal templates, policies, and knowledge sharing resources&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Review, file and manage legal documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare and draft changes to standard contracts, including service agreements and NDAs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide training to promote awareness and engagement on relevant legal issues, policies, tools, and processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate with external counsel on assisting with immigration matters relating to employee relocation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Correspond with external counsel on legal matters internationally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare and send legal/regulatory documents for use in international jurisdictions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in a law firm or in-house environment (2 or more years is preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Completion of a post-secondary paralegal. Paralegal diploma preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal skills and a desire to constantly learn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple projects and initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work efficiently, understand timelines, and operate with limited supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe is a remote-first company with an international team. We offer opportunities for personal and professional learning and growth, value autonomy and responsibility, and have a results-driven environment, flexible work hours and time-off policy, as well as competitive salary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To apply for this position, please fill out the linked application form and please attach your CV/resume.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainsafesystems/jobs/4279584004?gh_jid=4279584004&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/820874/chainsafe-systems-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainsafe@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5f6a040d-27de-4887-98d1-3606d387ad93]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[ChainSafe Systems]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
