<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Digital Production Assistant, CoinDesk TV (Contract Position)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://coindesk.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinDesk is seeking to contract a Digital Media Production Assistant to assist with the production of CoinDesk TV and how that content appears on coindesk.com and off-platform. Responsibilities include updating the CoinDesk homepage with daily and weekly livestream shows, maintaining quality standards for copy attached to CoinDesk TV, and publishing videos to unique URLs. Staying closely on top of schedules, fast and confident editing of copy, and good communication skills (mostly via Slack) are all crucial parts of the job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role will work closely with the multimedia team, coordinating copy changes, adding video IDs and supporting producers on the fly, within the CMS, when needed. Digital news experience and strong editorial skills are preferred, and this individual should be comfortable using programs like Airtable, Slack, WordPress and JW Player.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role will work closely with the multimedia team, coordinating copy changes, adding video IDs and supporting producers on the fly, within the CMS, when needed. Digital news experience and strong editorial skills are preferred, and this individual should be comfortable using programs like Airtable, Slack, WordPress and JW Player.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Liaise with CoinDesk TV production team and Editorial dept., ensuring deadlines are met&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor Slack channels for updates to live broadcast and when clips are ready to publish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Confirm schedules and guests of daily and weekly shows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Prepare and publish episode pages to unique URLs in advance of broadcast&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Update and maintain episode and clip pages as broadcasts transition from live to VOD&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Optimize episode pages for SEO (i.e. the SEO title, meta description)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Upload cut videos to CMS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Copy edit live stream copy as well as titles, deks and descriptions for all episodes and clips throughout the day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Embed videos into related stories, both current and evergreen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Curate and embed videos on related landing pages (ie. price pages, recent videos etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Upload YouTube videos with headlines and descriptions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Recommend ways to optimize workflow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Copy editing and publishing copy for social media posts for video, including fact-checking social media handles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Skills:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Copy editing/proofreading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong communicator —&amp;nbsp;a grand master of how to use Slack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Extremely organized - able to manage separate editing and uploading tasks simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with content management systems, esp. WordPress&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with project management software, esp. AirTable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with digital video hosting platforms such as JW Player, Brightcove and others&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with YouTube publishing dashboard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with social media language and syntax on Twitter, Facebook and Linkedin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;Details:&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Rate: $30-$40/hr, depending on skills and experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Hours: 6-8 hours per day, 5 days a week&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EQUAL OPPORTUNITY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In an effort to attract, retain, develop and promote the most qualified individuals, CoinDesk is committed to treating all applicants and employees in a nondiscriminatory manner with respect to the terms and conditions of employment, without regard to race, color, religion or belief, sex, national or ethnic origin, ancestry, age, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status/service, physical or mental disability, or any other classification protected by applicable law. This mandate governs all aspects of employment, including recruitment, selection, promotion, training, education, social and recreation programs, compensation, discipline, termination and access to benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For more information on our DEI initiatives, please visit: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/dei/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://www.coindesk.com/dei/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACCOMMODATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinDesk is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the application process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:accommodations@coindesk.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accomodations@coindesk.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVID-19 VACCINATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;COVID-19 vaccination is required for all employees whose position is based out of the NYC office. However, CoinDesk will consider accommodations for disability- and religious-based reasons on a case by case basis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/coindesk/jobs/5108434002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145913/coindesk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coindesk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[459b477b-1ae2-43d1-a1a8-7a40fbe3f487]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Trading Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinlist]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://coinlist.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA / New York, NY / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;CoinList is where early adopters invest in and trade the best digital assets, and is now one of the fastest growing crypto financial platforms. We support the full lifecycle of crypto investment, from token sales through token distribution, trading, lending, and crypto-specific services such as staking and access to decentralized-finance opportunities. CoinList users trade and store Bitcoin, Ether, Filecoin, and many other popular crypto assets through our full-service exchange, CoinList Pro, mobile apps and CoinList.co, while also getting access to the best new tokens before they list on other exchanges. We are the blue chip platform for blockchain companies, helping Filecoin, Blockstack, Solana, Celo, Algorand, Dapper, and others raise over $800 million. Our customer base includes validators, miners, founders, CEOs, crypto funds, bitcoin OGs, as well as a broad array of crypto enthusiasts. We are backed by top-tier investors, have offices in SF and NY, and are just getting started.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a Trading Engineer at CoinList, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Co-architect and build CoinList’s trading infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automate trading and settlement processes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Co-develop trading strategies, alpha, and algorithms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create data pipelines and analysis frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build integrations to exchanges, aggregators, and counterparties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ideate and build DeFi related products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An experience trading engineer from a top-tier financial institution; 5+ years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A modern quantitative engineer who builds fast, scalable infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced with Javascript (Node, React), Python, and Java or C++&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Naturally analytical and a pragmatic problem solver&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Someone who takes ownership of projects and responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As an early employee at CoinList you will be a critical part of our core team and have a huge influence over the direction of the company. We will compensate you well, invest deeply in your development, and do everything we can to make sure this is the single best work experience of your life.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/coinlist/jobs/5422888002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145375/CoinList.jpeg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinlist@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[53dcfcc4-4b3a-448c-81ad-47bdcbb7143e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinlist]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Trading ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore, Singapore; Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is a crypto exchange and custodian that allows customers to buy, sell, store, and earn more than 30 cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, bitcoin cash, ether, litecoin, and Zcash. Gemini is a New York trust company that is subject to the capital reserve requirements, cybersecurity requirements, and banking compliance standards set forth by the New York State Department of Financial Services and the New York Banking Law. Gemini was founded in 2014 by twin brothers Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss to empower the individual through crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto is about giving you greater choice, independence, and opportunity. We are here to help you on your journey. We build crypto products that are simple, elegant, and secure. Whether you are an individual or an institution, we want to help you buy, sell, and store your bitcoin and cryptocurrency. Crypto is not just a technology, it&#39;s a movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;empower the individual &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;and that includes giving our employees flexibility of choice — our Office Optional Policy allows employees to choose to work from one of our physical locations or from home. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Select roles that are location-specific will still be eligible for flexible schedules.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Department: &lt;/strong&gt;Software Engineering&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is regulated and licensed like a bank, but it’s run like a tech startup, and engineering is the core of the company.&amp;nbsp; There’s a wide range of tough problems to solve at Gemini – from properly securing hundreds of millions of dollars worth of customer funds, to developing innovative new blockchain products, to finding new techniques to combat fraud, to shaving microseconds off our API response times, and everything in between.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;All of Gemini’s engineers are able to work across the software platform, not just on their own specialization or subteam. We value a thoughtful, collaborative software development process, coupled with a pragmatic approach to problem solving and delivering software.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role: &lt;/strong&gt;Senior Software Engineer&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As an engineer on our backend team, you’ll architect and solve complex problems that will directly influence the direction of the digital asset space. There’s a wide range of problems to solve at Gemini – from properly securing millions of dollars worth of customer funds, to developing innovative new blockchain products, to shaving microseconds off our API response times. We have a strong culture of code reviews, and a focus on security, with the end goal of writing and shipping high-quality code by getting things right the first time. We want to continue building the best product we can as we scale and grow our business. If you get excited about solving technical challenges that directly impact our customers, clients, and the rest of the Gemini team, we’d love to hear from you.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role can be based in our New York, Chicago, San Francisco, Singapore, or Portland, Oregon offices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop new products and product features on the Gemini platform, as part of a tight knit team of two to eight developers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write automated tests and work with our QA team to ensure the operation and correctness of new product features.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide technical input and knowledge to the planning, design, and requirements process for new products and features.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Review other software engineers’ code for correctness, style, and information security concerns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Improve the performance, maintainability, and operations of the Gemini code base by engaging in occasional refactoring and upgrade projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support your team’s production software by responding to an occasional alert or bug report.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 6&amp;nbsp;years of software engineering experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Advanced proficiency in at least one language. We use mostly Scala and C++ on our backend and Typescript on the frontend – it’s great if you’re comfortable in those or if you’re willing to learn.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to work closely across teams and manage dependencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A customer- and product-focused mindset, with the ability to make well-reasoned tradeoffs between speed and quality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to adapt and handle multiple competing priorities in collaboration with peers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with or being a power user of Bitcoin, Ethereum, and/or blockchain technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work experience or knowledge of the finance industry, payments, trading and/or exchange systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-WC1&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/70jrfYSxKC4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3371360&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Global Identity and Onboarding]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.okcoin.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Dublin, Dublin, Ireland]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who We Are&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Imagine a world where everyone is a trader. Okcoin is on a mission to make crypto investing and trading more accessible to anyone around the world. We are building the next generation of tools to help onboard the investors and traders who have been on the fence about crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Okcoin is a global exchange with offices in San Francisco, Malta, Hong Kong and Singapore. We are a collective of global citizens with a common passion to help decentralize finance and level the economic playing field for everyone around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Global Identity and Onboarding team is at the heart of managing and balancing risk and reward for our global platform. This is a great opportunity to bring your extensive knowledge, expertise, and leadership to continue building and maturing this function. We work closely with all our key stakeholders, such as Compliance, Product, Engineering, Customer Service, Marketing, Risk Operations to successfully launch various growth campaigns and new products while understanding the associated risks with identity and onboarding for business growth. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Opportunity&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for an experienced Head of Global Identity and Onboarding to join our fast-growing global operations team. This role will develop, lead, and oversee our Onboarding and Identity strategies, programs, processes, and front-line teams. This senior leader will report to our Chief Customer and Risk Officer, and take full accountability to grow and lead the operations team responsible for building out and managing operational processes and programs required to comply with regulatory, KYC, and onboarding requirements on a global scale.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The right leader in this role should have a solid understanding of anti-money laundering (AML) requirements, including Know Your Customer/Business (KYC/KYB). Successful candidates for the role will have a minimum of 5+ years experience managing teams within payments, fintech, or financial services, and growing high performing, global teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At your core, you’ll thrive in a fast-paced, collaborative, process-driven environment and be able to adapt and adjust plans on-the-fly. You must also have strong prioritization skills and willingness to roll up one&#39;s sleeves to get the job done. Most importantly, you’ll drive results and significantly support the growth and adoption of our platform and features, while building the risk and rewards culture to enable business growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Be Doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define the global vision, direction, high-level priorities, strategies and&amp;nbsp; goals for the Identity and Onboarding operations team in collaboration with cross functional stakeholder&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead and grow a high performing global operations team and continue to evolve and mature the people, processes and technology&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Hire, develop, and retain key talent while adding bench strength and structure to the team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify gaps in current systems, processes, policies and strategies, and propose data-backed enhancements and improvements to mitigate emerging risks, or optimize for efficiency and quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide guidance on complex, high-visibility cases, processes, and projects; adapting and realigning priorities in response to emergent challenges or shifting business priorities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead operational strategy development cross functionally in partnership with Compliance, Risk, and Product teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist with coordination of regulatory exams, financial partner audits, or internal business unit assessments in relation of Identity and Onboarding operations as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Look For In You:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of senior leadership experience in a related business functions with a history (and preference) of being strategic, analytical and operational execution-oriented&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Must have a solid understanding and experience in deploying global identity and onboarding programs aligned to KYC and AML requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven track record of designing and implementing risk operational strategies for optimization and efficiency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven track record of designing and implementing risk technology strategies and solutions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong capabilities and experience in driving analytics to enable business growth while balancing risk and rewards&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work collaboratively with a broad range of business functions, with an emphasis on key business partners and senior management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to thrive in a fast-paced, dynamic environment, with the abilities to adopt a roll up your sleeves and just do it mindset and mentality&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Natural coach, mentor and leader, with commitment to supporting team growth by adopting effective employee engagement and diversity strategies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You either are already or are eager to become an expert in the blockchain and cryptocurrency landscape and will understand how speculators, traders, digital asset exchanges, blockchain money services businesses and financial institutions operate.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with product management processes and tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;MBA preferred, but not required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with teams across offices and timezones&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fluent in Mandarin and English&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights of Perks and Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Market competitive total compensation package&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive insurance package including medical, dental, vision, disability &amp;amp; life insurance (Company pays 100% for employee/80% for dependents)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401K with company contribution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible PTO policy, company paid holidays, and flexible hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;UberEats Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paid Parental Leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Referral Bonus Program paid in BTC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Company Donation Match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;More surprises when you join!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Okcoin Statement:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Okcoin is committed to equal employment opportunities regardless of race, color, genetic information, creed, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, lawful alien status, national origin, age, marital status, and non-job related physical or mental disability, or protected veteran status. Pursuant to the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance, we will consider for employment qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xAd9NClUmZY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okcoin/jobs/4829122003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/551872/OKCoin_400x400.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okcoin@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[57e0c7fc-df31-4da2-b52b-befd9a7f36e9]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Marketing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[ChainSafe Systems]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://chainsafe.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe Systems is currently seeking a Head of Marketing to establish and lead a new marketing department from the ground up. As our first Marketing hire, you’ll have the opportunity to have a tremendous impact, but it is important that you are a self-starter with an entrepreneurial spirit. You will be working very closely with the leadership team to understand our marketing needs across the organization and drive initiatives to address them. You will build the marketing team, both from a processes and hiring perspective, while contributing to critical marketing efforts to help push ChainSafe forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe is a unique company in a nascent space that is growing quickly and building a stellar global reputation. &quot;Beyond offering experience across major blockchain ecosystems to our team, we provide an open, inclusive, and supportive environment where we help folks reach their full potential as a human and as a professional.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Culture fit and alignment to our core values are extremely important to us. We are fueled by an immense intellectual curiosity of what technology can do and the impact it can have. We are building the next generation of web infrastructure and decentralized systems and you will thrive here if you are intensely driven by tackling challenges in a fast-moving enviornment with a tight knit team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a very exciting time as Web3 and blockchain technology is continuously pushing the boundaries of what is possible and new opportunities arise on a daily basis. It is a great time to join and this position is both fun and extremely rewarding!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a new marketing department at ChainSafe from the ground up, including establishing the department’s strategy &amp;amp; best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct the high-level competitive positioning for our innovative Web3 products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with our product teams to help with product marketing, including value propositions, market segmentation and go-to-market strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work hands-on for key organizational marketing projects, including product marketing and online marketing initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit, scale, coach and mentor the marketing team as needed to help meet ChainSafe’s marketing needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuously look for ways to improve our marketing practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate effectively with leadership and the organization to influence outcomes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and manage marketing budgets &amp;amp; costs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop branding plans &amp;amp; campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or time-equivalent working experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years working at a startup with a role focused on marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of hiring &amp;amp; managing other marketing professionals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of the techniques and methods of product marketing and online marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to learn multiple functional areas of business – engineering, design, finance, sales, or marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to engage with engineers, designers, and company leaders in a constructive and collaborative relationship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with and passion for Web3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience doing marketing for a SaaS product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building and leading a marketing team at a startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in development, product management, sales engineering or another technical role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We offer fast opportunities for personal growth, mentorship, professional development funding, tons of autonomy and responsibility, a results-driven environment, close collaboration with an international team, exposure to a wide array of ecosystems and trailblazing technologies, and flexible work hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At ChainSafe, we are a compassionate group of builders and makers, working to bring our ideas to life. You’ll be part of a team that believes in the vital importance of community and contributing to advance humanity with open-source and decentralized technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chainsafe.io/corevalues&quot;&gt;We care deeply about our values and look for these in every team member:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; A dedication to self-improvement and professional development; a commitment to community and collaboration; a drive for accountability, diligence, and autonomy; and above fostering a place of acceptance, friendliness, and compassion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us who you are and learn more about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are ready to join us, assemble your highlights (Portfolio, LinkedIn) and show us your best work. Get ready to have incredible conversations about your work. For our team’s project highlights, explore our &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.com/invite/xSAwrnCWcg&quot;&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/chainsafe&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://chainsafe.io/projects&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome your fresh perspectives and ideas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At ChainSafe, diversity and inclusion is more than a statement; equality and accessibility are guiding principles embedded in who we are - and why we do what we do. Our leadership is committed to continuously improving their own level of education to make the fairest and inclusive hiring and performance decisions from an informed perspective. We recognize the benefits of a diverse team and aspire to embed respect for all people into our culture, values, and day-to-day practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If at any time we can provide accommodations to facilitate your application and interview process, please let us know. We will strive to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainsafesystems/jobs/4299467004?gh_jid=4299467004&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/820874/chainsafe-systems-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainsafe@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5f6a040d-27de-4887-98d1-3606d387ad93]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[ChainSafe Systems]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Growth Manager (Remote Spain)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.bitfinex.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">The Marketing Growth Manager will support all areas of the marketing department and the head of marketing to launch campaigns, market existing products and meet marketing KPIs and growth targets that are met for the year. This will be a fully autonomous role and the ability to seek opportunities and build campaigns from the ground up is essential.</p>
<p dir="ltr">From determining positioning, competitive analysis, feature prioritization and external communications, you help shape the voice of Bitfinex and our suite of products to help us grow our user base. This means you work with a cross-functional team across Business Development, legal, Developers, Web Design, product development, engineering and more. In this role, you'll be involved with product marketing strategy from beginning to end.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Demonstrable experience in a wide range of digital marketing including marketing database management, content creation, email marketing, social media, display advertising campaigns and events promotion.</p>
<p dir="ltr">Highly creative with experience in identifying target audiences and devising digital campaigns that engage, inform, and motivate our audience of cryptocurrency enthusiasts.</p>
<p><br /><br /></p><h3 dir="ltr">Currently looking for:</h3>
<p><br /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Bitfinex Marketing Growth Manager (Remote)</strong></p>
<h3 dir="ltr">​<strong>Job description</strong></h3>
<p><br /></p><ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Supporting the central marketing team with their day to day operational marketing activities</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Working closely with the marketing manager to identify new opportunities to market Bitfinex. You will take ownership of campaigns to meet our marketing objectives for the year as well as your own targets</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Strong analytical skills to identify areas of opportunity and improvement across our website and products</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Supporting the growth of other key teams within Bitfinex by developing new campaigns to promote product launches</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Research and create engaging content that also supports the growth of our SEO strategy</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Work with the design teams to create effective campaigns on both social media, email and at events. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Come up with new and innovative campaigns and take ownership of each campaign from start to finish once agreed with the marketing manager. Campaigns will include, email marketing, influencer outreach, content marketing and community engagement.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">A creative thinker, able to come up with innovative new ideas and solutions.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Ability to work to tight deadlines </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Pro-active in their approach so opportunities can be spotted and fast action can be taken to take an idea to market</p></li></ul><p><h2>Requirements:</h2></p><ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">MANDATORY EXPERIENCE in these sectors or similar industries: Crypto, Financial, Medical/Pharma, Cannabis, eSports and Gambling or other regulated environments.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Motivated team player who actively seeks challenging projects and proactively shares experiences and knowledge towards the team’s goals.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Good understanding of multichannel marketing and how users interact with each channel</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience in using data, research and customer feedback to improve a campaign to inform future activities</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience in planning and developing digital marketing campaigns from start to finish working with a number of teams to ensure a marketing campaign is ready for project launch</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience using a number of email marketing solutions</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Work closely with the marketing manager and social media strategist to enhance and maintain the company's social media presence</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Be able to write captivating copy to engage existing users and attract new users to the website</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Google certification would be an advantage</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Knowledge of the cryptocurrency industry and trading would be an advantage but not necessary</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Work to strict deadlines for project launches and experience using project management tools such as Asana. </p></li></ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fx7gryqZwzw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://bitfinex.recruitee.com/o/marketing-growth-manager-remote-spain/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/227432/Bitfinex_Long_Logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ricardo.pinheiro@bitfinex.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[a48bec57-75b8-41d5-9cff-1828d315ba59]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Podcast Editorial Fellow]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[The Block]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.theblockcrypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Founded in 2018 and based in NYC, The Block is the leading research, analysis, and news brand in the digital asset space. The Block's team is spread across 5 continents and 15+ time zones, covering the global cryptocurrency space 24/7.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Block delivers deep insight into how the emerging digital assets sector interacts with traditional finance, technology, governments, and markets. We reach hundreds of thousands of technologists, financial market participants, Fortune 500 professionals, global service providers, policymakers, and more through our main website, dedicated Research Portal, podcast, and events.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Block’s flagship podcast, The Scoop, is looking for a tenacious individual with a background in financial journalism to support editorial elements of the show. You will work directly with the show’s host Frank Chaparro as well as other leaders across The Block in a role that spans several teams.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As an editorial fellow, you will join several recording sessions with top CEOs and decision makers in the crypto, technology and financial sectors and extract key insights for short news briefs, long-form analysis, and social media content. Through this role you will be able to build your own personal brand in the industry whilst reporting on a wide-range of topics.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Given its cross-team and cross-disciplinary nature, this role requires someone who is comfortable spending the requisite time to get up to speed on complex topics ranging from zero-knowledge proofs to over-the-counter derivatives. A sense of what is newsworthy is a must, as is comfortability being pushed towards excellence.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities <br/><li>Listen in on 2-3 podcast recordings a week and identify key quotes, insights from guests</li><li>Produce multiple pieces of content per episode</li><li>Help draft podcast summaries&nbsp;</li><li>Organize podcast transcripts</li><li>Work with podcast producer and host on researcher guests to come up with questions, potential angles that can induce a newsworthy response&nbsp;</li><li>Quarterly analysis pieces that draw from the podcastIdentify opportunities to highlight and market shows as series. Ex: Unicorn CEO series or Exchange exec series</li><li>Apple Notes podcast summaries for Twitter and social channels</li><br/>Qualifications<br/><li>Background in reporting on finance or technology; ability to breakdown complex topics; strong reader comprehension skills&nbsp;</li><li>At least 2 years of undergraduate studies complete&nbsp;</li><li>A passion for news and a strong desire to hit high signal stories&nbsp;</li><li>Deeply curious about the world and willing to take initiatives on projects without being asked</li><li>Enjoys listening to podcasts&nbsp;</li><li>Can do attitude&nbsp;</li><div><b style="font-size: 11pt">Why You Should Work Here:</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">1. The culture of The Block lies in our key behaviors. It’s who we are and it’s how we show up everyday - Confident Humility, Actionable Curiosity, Tenacious Ownership and Respectful Partnership.</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">2. We take care of our employees and we have the benefits and perks to support it. Unlimited PTO, remote first environment, high health plan employer contributions, monthly wellness stipend, generous parental leave policy, 401k match, fitness partnerships, fertility benefits, One Medical membership and citibike membership.&nbsp;</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">3. Impactful work. Regardless of your role at The Block you’re making a meaningful contribution to our mission in accelerating the evolution of financial systems through independent reporting and technical research of all projects influencing the future of financial services.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Block is an equal employment opportunity employer.&nbsp; Qualified candidates are considered for employment without regard to race, religion, gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, national origin, age, military or veteran status, disability, or any other characteristic protected by applicable law.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">During our application process we collect completely anonymous diversity information. Providing this information is voluntary but we want you to know what we do with it. We use the data to ensure that our recruiting practices are bringing diverse talent to the organization and we are reacting where we are coming up short. We strive to use the data to ensure we have the tools and resources for all employees both during the interview process and should those employees choose to join us at The Block.&nbsp;</span></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/theblockcrypto/8d82298a-7021-4e96-a82b-a730c8caced8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/374217/theblock.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[theblock@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[27d78dc7-e726-4a53-af38-f0660605e195]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[The Block]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[KYC Analyst [Remote Turkey]]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.bitfinex.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Founded in 2012, Bitfinex is a digital asset trading platform offering state-of-the-art services for digital currency traders and global liquidity providers. We're on a mission to create the most innovative cryptocurrencies exchange. This is a unique opportunity, a rare window of time at the tipping point of the financial evolution. Much like the early days of the internet, blockchain technology faces complex new challenges and having the best team plays a pivotal role in success.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Our team is fully remote and globally distributed to capture the best talent from around the world. So far our company has grown fast and stayed lean to secure its place as a leader in the space.</p>
<p>If you get excited about being in an industry that is breaking new ground and have confidence you can conquer the most challenging feats we'll encounter, we want to talk to you. Join us, and help lay the foundation for a decentralized future.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Currently looking for:</p>
<p><strong>KYC Analyst (Remote)</strong></p>
<p><strong><br /></strong></p>
<p><strong>Job description</strong></p>
<p>The primary purpose of this position is to provide administrative and analytical support to the KYC Onboarding Team with a view to ensure KYC reviews are prioritized and completed in a timely way and that all applicable information is appended to each case file in accordance with documented procedures.</p>
<p>The position will entail written and, on occasions, verbal communication and the incumbent should demonstrate a natural ability to communicate politely and clearly with internal and external parties, whilst in command of the facts pertinent to the case.</p>
<p>The incumbent will maintain and develop strong relationships and network amongst peers in the industry to learn and share best practices and analytical techniques.</p>
<p>In performing the role, the incumbent will continuously strive to continuously self-develop and enhance their skill sets incl. understanding blockchain technology, virtual currencies, suspicious activities in the space, criminals’ modus operandi and best investigative practices to mitigate against the risk of money laundering, financing terrorism or violating sanctions on behalf of Bitfinex and to ensure the company’s robust Regulatory Compliance.<br /></p><p><h2>Requirements:</h2></p><p>In addition to the skill set preferred requirements listed below the incumbent must be able to work independently with minimum supervision, (seeking guidance as required), flexible as to working arrangement and hours and confident in making decisions as delegated by Manager Compliance / CCO.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong>Knowledge:</strong></p>
<ul><li>Secondary education (University or College Preferred)</li><li>Experience in KYC analytical function</li><li>Introductory level AML experience incl. customer and enhanced due diligence,</li><li>(CDD/EDD), AML/CTF/Sanctions Investigations, SAR/STR reporting</li><li>Basic knowledge of blockchain technology, (enhanced in the role)</li></ul>
<p><strong>Skills:</strong></p>
<ul><li>Excellent written and verbal English communication skills</li><li>Proficient in Microsoft Excel, (incl. creating pivot tables)</li><li>Demonstrated critical-thinking skills, (decision-making)</li><li>Demonstrated attention to detail</li><li>Organizational understanding, (enhanced in the role)</li></ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fx7gryqZwzw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://bitfinex.recruitee.com/o/kyc-analyst-remote-turkey/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/227432/Bitfinex_Long_Logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ricardo.pinheiro@bitfinex.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[a48bec57-75b8-41d5-9cff-1828d315ba59]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfinex]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director - Social Media & Community Marketing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CertiK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://certik.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About the Company</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">Founded in 2018 by professors of Yale University and Columbia University, CertiK is a pioneer in blockchain security, utilizing best-in-class AI technology to secure and monitor blockchain protocols and smart contracts. CertiK’s mission is to secure the cyber world. Starting with blockchain, CertiK applies cutting-edge innovations from academia into enterprise, enabling mission-critical applications to be built with security and correctness.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">CertiK is one of the fastest growing and most trusted companies in blockchain security and has become a true market leader. To date, we have collectively worked with over 1800 enterprise clients, helped secure over $90 billion worth of digital assets, and detected over 31,000 vulnerabilities in blockchain code. Our clients include leading projects such as Aave, Polygon, Binance Smart Chain, Terra, Yearn, and Chiliz. Our Q1 2021 revenues have more than quadrupled the revenue of the full 2020 year. Since Q1 2020, our team size has more than doubled, and this rate of growth will continue in 2021, creating a highly effective, remote-friendly culture with talents located worldwide.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">CertiK just raised over $140 million in Series B, B+, and B2 funding rounds over four months in 2021, putting the company close to unicorn status at nearly $1 Billion in valuation. Our investors include top VCs like Sequoia, Tiger Global, Coatue Management, Shunwei Capital and Hillhouse Capital as well as industry leaders like Coinbase Ventures and Binance.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">About the Role</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">We’re looking for an energetic, creative minded, well organized, and self-motivated </span><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">Director of Social Media and Community Marketing</b><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">, to grow our presence and audience. If you are comfortable in a new emerging space like Blockchain/Crypto/NFT, and have the attitude of figuring things out, driven by results, and adapt to additional responsibilities, then keep reading. </span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Own the social media and community marketing strategy, including but not limited to strategy initiatives like: high quality contents strategy, paid social media, influencer relationships, competitive research, contests, community engagement and growth.</li><li>Determine &amp; maintain KPI/measurement frameworks &amp; overall social media and community listening frameworks including crisis management</li><li>Manage and provide leadership, mentoring, coaching and career development planning for team members.</li><li>Work closely with cross-platform teams in the development of social media and community campaigns and strategies to build follower, engagement and positive sentiments.</li><li>Interface with security incident team in pushing out timely news flash alerts on social media platforms e.g. Twitter.</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>8+ years of relevant experience (social media and community) marketing, preferably with a blockchain, crypto or developer, open source community style audience.</li><li>Proven experience managing multiple social media and community channels worldwide, with examples of successful KPI achievements relating to growth and engagement.</li><li>Experience working in a fast-paced, high growth software startup company where change is a constant</li><li>Able to demonstrate growth hacker strategies for drastically growing audiences across social media and community channels like: Twitter, LinkedIn, Telegram, Discord.</li><li>Experience managing a team with different skills sets and years of experience.</li><li>Self-starter, ability to lead innovative, entrepreneurial efforts and drive for excellence</li><li>Creative, extreme attention to detail and highly organized.</li><li>Able to function independently, as well as collaboratively with other team member</li><li>Familiarity with use of social media reporting platforms e.g. Sprout Social.</li><li>Familiarity with Blockchain, Crypto, NFT type audiences and engagement of such an audience is a plus.</li><div>CertiK is proud to offer medical, vision, and dental insurance, 401(k) plan with company matching, life and accidental death and dismemberment insurance, HSA (with high deductible plan), FSA, and other benefits to all full-time employees, along with flexible paid time off and holidays.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>In compliance with federal law, all persons hired will be required to verify identity and eligibility to work in the United States and to complete the required employment eligibility verification form upon hire. </div><div><br></div><div>CertiK is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. We will not discriminate against any applicant or employee on the basis of age, race, color, creed, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity or expression, medical condition, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, marital status or civil partnership/union status, physical or mental disability, pregnancy, childbirth, genetic information, military and veteran status, or any other basis prohibited by applicable federal, state or local law.</div><div><br></div><div>CertiK will consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with local and federal requirements.</div><div><a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf" class="postings-link">https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf</a></div><div><br></div><div>All CertiK employees are expected to actively support diversity on their teams, and in the Company.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/aEn2UaqeHho" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/certik/efbd37ce-a6d8-4c4c-a7bf-2a85d56b06d6/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/452745/CertiK-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[certik@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f6c22067-35b7-4b78-a01c-cb1e9232298a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CertiK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Recruiting Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://protocol.ai/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About Protocol Labs</b></div><div><br></div><div>Protocol Labs drives breakthroughs in computing to push humanity forward. Protocol Labs is a product-development lab, but behind the protocols and tools we build, behind the research and implementations, are passionate people, teammates and community members. We are a fully distributed company. Our team of more than 175 members works remotely and in the open to improve the internet — humanity's most important technology — as we explore new advances at the intersection of many exciting fields (crypto, networks, distributed systems) and cultures (startups, research, open source, distributed work).</div><div><br></div><div><b>About the People Team</b></div><div><br></div><div>The PL People Team enables Protocol Labs’ success&nbsp; by designing and leading innovative people programs that attract and enable Labbers to do their best work. Our team is composed of Recruiting and People Operations. Together, we support all initiatives involving attracting, hiring, engaging, retaining, and developing Labbers.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>The Recruiting Manager role will partner closely with the Head of Talent and Recruiting Operations Manager to build out a team of recruiters and execute on a variety of highly impactful recruitment project areas.</div><div><br></div><br/>Key Responsibilities<br/><li>Manage current team of recruiters and onboard/train new recruiters as needed.&nbsp;</li><li>Provide mentorship and effective career development to members of your team.&nbsp;</li><li>Demonstrate expertise in recruitment best practices and lead by example by sharing these best practices.&nbsp;</li><li>Serve as a strategic business partner to leadership and engineering as it relates to its hiring goals.&nbsp;</li><li>Continuously use data to assess recruitment effectiveness and adjust outreach strategies.</li><li>Define, design, and implement recruiting programs to improve candidate experience, streamline the interview process, and achieve other goals related to the recruiting team’s organizational effectiveness.&nbsp;</li><li>Deliver results and drive hiring strategies in a fast-paced environment.</li><li>Document recruiting processes to provide insights to PL, hiring managers, and candidates.</li><br/>You may be a fit for this role if you have<br/><li>8+ years of experience in technical recruiting</li><li>2+ years of experience managing a team of recruiters and/or sourcers&nbsp;</li><li>Experience working in a very fast-paced, startup environment</li><li>Experience communicating and working with cross-functional teams</li><li>Experience providing a consultative recruiting approach with internal stakeholders and specifically engineering</li><li>Experience recruiting for both requisition-style hiring as well as pipeline hiring.&nbsp;</li><li>Experience managing teams of 6+ direct reports</li><br/>Nice to Have<br/><li>Experience with Greenhouse</li><li>Knowledge or interest in Web3/Crypto/Decentralization</li><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">What’s it like to work at Protocol Labs?</span></b></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs mission is to improve humanity’s most important technology, the Internet. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how it works. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Our projects include IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As a distributed team, we hire anywhere in the world, and at various levels of experience (entry, senior, staff). We look for people with unique perspectives and diverse backgrounds.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We have a great benefits package, including parental leave, contributions to your retirement, competitive pay, and unlimited time off. For U.S.-based employees, we also provide platinum-level health, dental, and vision coverage for you and your family.</span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EClPAFPeXIQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/protocol/5c499c9b-fe0c-4250-99f8-1d2e48047338/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/207125/protocol_loabs.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[protocollabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c4028873-6454-47fc-a65d-6c6d1ed8cb1f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Core Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://protocol.ai/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Ecosystem]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs makes breakthroughs in computing technology to push humanity forward. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how things work. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Core Engineers have the challenging and exciting task of working on complex problems in an environment defined by curiosity, passion, and a love for open source. This will be an opportunity to work directly on our projects including IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Ecosystem ⇄ Outercore</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Outercore, the subsidiary that represents grants, accelerators, and special projects at Protocol Labs is looking for a Core Engineer to help us build the future of p2p distributed networks. If you’re excited about working on Filecoin, Libp2p, IPFS, and working on the genesis of smart contracts on the Filecoin Network (FVM), this role may be for you.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Everything Outercore does is open source and we encourage everyone to work out in the open. We’re comfortable sharing unfinished work and trying out new things. The goal is to come up with solutions the entire ecosystem can benefit from.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">A Core Engineer will work on Filecoin, Libp2p, IPFS, the FVM until they are comfortable enough to start building new applications, prototypes, or protocols that companies in the Filecoin ecosystem can use and grow their businesses. We consider this “Application” research.</span></div><br/>As a Core Enginner, you will be tasked with:<br/><li>Take engineering leadership in projects to improve the Web3 ecosystem and help set a course for the future of the ecosystem’s technology.</li><li>Deeply understand the problems in the Web3 ecosystem as it relates to Filecoin.</li><li>Build great software that other companies and individuals will use to achieve their goals.</li><li>Help us grow this Filecoin ecosystem to its full potential.</li><br/>What we’re looking for:<br/><li>A proactive and autonomous builder that can draft a roadmap forward and execute with code. You are someone who has a passion for hands-on development of distributed systems as well as problem solving within a complex system. You enjoy diving deep into technical elements of your projects to the point where you’re naturally the designated expert on the topic.</li><div><br></div><li>You can anticipate the needs of a project ahead of time and lay groundwork to get ahead of those needs. This may involve hiring, coordinating, and acquiring technology. You love to create and drive consensus on designs, and deliver results!</li><li>Ideally, you have worked on at least one project with users that involved large amounts of data storage and network traffic.</li><div><br></div><li>You have some interest in IPFS and Filecoin, if you do not have any interest, you should be genuinely curious about what those technologies are and hope to develop an interest. We will ask what content addressing is!</li><div><br></div><li>You’re familiar with open source work and the Go programming language or you are someone who is willing to pick the language up and you have the foundation to do so.</li><div><br></div><li>You have a B.Sc. in Computer Science or a related field. A degree is not required but a lot of what we do requires a computer science foundation.</li><div><b style="font-size: 18px">What’s it like to work at Protocol Labs?</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs mission is to improve humanity’s most important technology, the Internet. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how it works. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Our projects include IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As a distributed team, we hire anywhere in the world, and at various levels of experience (entry, senior, staff). We look for people with unique perspectives and diverse backgrounds.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We have a great benefits package, including parental leave, contributions to your retirement, competitive pay, and unlimited time off. For U.S.-based employees, we also provide platinum-level health, dental, and vision coverage for you and your family.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">What’s it like to work at Protocol Labs?</span></b></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs mission is to improve humanity’s most important technology, the Internet. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how it works. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Our projects include IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As a distributed team, we hire anywhere in the world, and at various levels of experience (entry, senior, staff). We look for people with unique perspectives and diverse backgrounds.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We have a great benefits package, including parental leave, contributions to your retirement, competitive pay, and unlimited time off. For U.S.-based employees, we also provide platinum-level health, dental, and vision coverage for you and your family.</span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EClPAFPeXIQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/protocol/dfe69091-33c9-4d96-a9bd-f6802940290b/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/207125/protocol_loabs.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[protocollabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c4028873-6454-47fc-a65d-6c6d1ed8cb1f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Social Media Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOTA Foundation]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.iota.org]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Social Media Manager</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">The IOTA Foundation</span></span><span style="color: #222222;"> is the global not-for-profit foundation behind an ecosystem of open-source digital infrastructure in the blockchain and cryptocurrency space, including its distributed ledger technology (DLT) known as the Tangle, an incentivized staging network called Shimmer, and Assembly, a network for permissionless smart contracts.  </span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">The Tangle</span></span><span style="color: #222222;"> is an open, feeless and scalable distributed ledger, designed to support frictionless data and value transfer with the goal of being the most reliable DLT infrastructure for Web3 applications and digital economies. As a robust network for exchanging value and data between humans and machines, it is the first distributed ledger built for the Internet of Everything. The Tangle is highly scalable, allowing transactions to be added in parallel unlike blockchain alternatives; it also boasts low resource requirements, as well as zero-fee and fast transactions with finality within seconds. </span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Assembly </span></span><span style="color: #222222;">is a scalable multi-chain network for sharded, composable smart contracts. Anyone can launch their own smart contract chains with the flexibility to customize fee and incentive structures. The chains are overseen by permissionless and decentral dynamic validator committees of nodes that execute and validate smart contracts; these validators are assigned to their chains by a root chain through a marketplace, and the validators are rewarded with the network’s native token, ASMB. </span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Assembly delivers flexibility, scalability, and interoperability, and is a smart contract network for mainstream innovation and mass adoption. It does so by offering inexpensive, fast and secure smart contracts, trustless and feeless smart contract interoperability, full customization and composability of dApps, compatibility with Ethereum virtual machine and other benefits.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Mission: </span></span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="color: #091e42;"><br></span><span style="color: #091e42;"><br></span><span style="color: #091e42;">Does crypto make your world go round? Do you consider making memes a skill? Is crypto Twitter your home? If so, you're our person.</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">As a Social Media manager you will help us to design creative strategies and deliver our vision by creating and managing content on our social media channels (mainly Twitter, Discord and others) for crypto and Web3. Assembly addresses its audiences in English so you will need to have an extremely high proficiency.</span></p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Responsibilities:</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Develop strategy and implement plans to grow our communities on key channels and platforms (eg, Twitter, Discord, etc.)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Coordinate social media marketing campaigns and day-to-day activities (publishing, analytics, listening) on an operational level</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Develop relevant and appealing content to reach the company’s target audiences, write copy text on your own and align with stakeholders and the design team</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Create, curate, and manage published content on social platforms, including creating metadata, uploading content and creating live streams on YouTube </span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Oversee design (ie: Social media graphics, thumbnails, ads, landing pages, Twitter profile, Blog, etc.) as well as copy text on them including quality assurance regarding any copied text on them</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Work with ecosystem teams to develop and expand community and/or influencer outreach efforts</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Use social media marketing tools such as Hootsuite / Sprinklr (both publishing and analytics)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Measure the success of the channels and campaigns: Report on and analyze key metrics and tweak strategy as needed</span></li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Compile reports for management showing results (ROI)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Monitor, listen and respond to users </span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Requirements</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Your Personality</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Self-driven individual who takes responsibility for projects from their inception</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Ability, desire, and dedication to pick up new platforms or technologies as well as improve in existing ones</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Team player with a creative mindset</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Critical thinker and problem-solving skills</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Multi-tasking and time-management skills</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Ability to work in a fast-paced environment</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Your Expertise</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Crypto-savvy and understands how to engage Web3 and crypto communities</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Able to make and curate memes and gifs</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Minimum of 3 years experience as Social Media Specialist and experience of social media management for tech/Web3 company(s) (experience with DLT and smart contracts is a plus)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Native or advanced  writing and communication skills in English and must have a thorough understanding of social media management</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Good knowledge of Twitter, Discord, Reddit, YouTube and other social media best practices for tech companies</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Good understanding of social media KPIs</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Solid understanding of social media/web analytics on each channel</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Understanding of social media publishing tools like Sprout / Hootsuite and others that can be useful to streamline and organize postings</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Ability to coordinate an editorial calendar with teams and work across teams to assure high-quality publishing </span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #091e42;">W</span></span><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">hat we offer</span></span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Flexible work environment</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The opportunity to work with the brightest minds in the industry</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Fun while working. We have a friendly and casual culture</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Posting for a good cause. The opportunity to make a true difference with social media</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Having a real impact within a technology that’s booming </span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Culture of trust, empowerment and constructive feedback</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">A flexible and agile organization with a flat hierarchy</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The IOTA Foundation is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity and are committed to creating an inclusive environment for all employees.</span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LVY9DzwyzdU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://iota.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=190&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180020/iota.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iota@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[89e42fc6-4d4d-416c-82b4-a1443bc5e101]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOTA Foundation]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Vice President, Customer Success]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chronicled]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://chronicled.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">As Vice President of Customer Success, you are a proven software executive with a track record of building strong customer success, loyalty, and satisfaction programs for software businesses that delight customers, improve brand loyalty, and can scale within a rapidly growing company.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You can recruit, manage, lead, and motivate both technical and non-technical professionals and know how to get things done by collaborating with other teams.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You ensure our customers realize maximum value across their lifecycle, resulting in their renewal, growth of lifetime value and customer satisfaction. This role is based in our San Francisco office or remote in the US. Our work environment is one where ambition thrives and so will you.</span></div><br/>What you will do: <br/><li>Lead and scale a world-class Customer Success and Professional Services organization </li><li>Develop effective ROI-focused customer success programs to ensure successful on-boarding, adoption, retention, renewal and expansion for our customers base</li><li>Increase customer lifetime value through higher product adoption, usage, customer satisfaction and overall health scores</li><li>Define and drive the ideal customer experience in close partnership with senior leadership across Product, Engineering, Marketing, and Sales</li><li>Partner with Product on aiding the development and growth of existing and new products for our customers</li><li>Partner with Revenue Operations to create and build Customer Success systems and processes as well as measuring operational metrics and tracking/reporting for the exec team, company and board</li><li>Drive customer implementations and delivery in on-boarding new customers&nbsp;documenting end to end processes, enabling scale in a growing organization.</li><li>Enhance customer implementation process full ultimate efficiency </li><li>Inspire and drive a company-wide culture of Customer Success, creating a strong culture that fosters customer advocacy</li><br/>What you will need: <br/><li>5+ years of experience in Customer Success / Professional Services Leadership </li><li>Experience in leading teams at a Enterprise Saas company </li><li>Previous startup experience in developing and scaling a customer success and professional services organization from scratch</li><li>Proven ability to prioritize projects and initiatives to align to corporate and divisional programs</li><li>Ability to develop and maintain productive relationships across organizations to ensure that business initiatives are achieved</li><li>MBA or equivalent experience nice to have </li><li>Experience in the Life Sciences industry or Fintech is a plus</li><br/>You are: <br/><li>A driver of Performance: Proven ability to be a change agent by creating or adopting new customer programs that maximize customer satisfaction and drive the bottom line in a fast growing, dynamic and global company</li><li>Detail oriented: Proven ability to prioritize projects and initiatives to align to corporate and divisional programsAn Excellent Communicator: Ability to develop and maintain productive relationships across organizations to ensure that business initiatives are achieved</li><li>A True Team Player: Demonstrates collaboration as a core value, both with our customers and within the company.&nbsp;</li><li>A Leader: You have experience identifying and developing managers from within the team as well as developing challenging career paths for more junior roles within the team as well as the developing talent for progression in the rest of the company.&nbsp; Is a proven recruiter with a proven ability of attracting as well as nurturing great talent into the Customer Success Team</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/5MArmZpzU68" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/chronicled-2/b2ee4b5b-5175-4b38-8896-5046a4bfd3c2/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/301749/chronicled.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chronicled@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d44ed840-83fb-4e02-8dd2-2347727f060d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chronicled]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Market Risk Manager - Crypto/DeFi - US/UK (Remote Optional)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">Highly desirable skills: </span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li>Knowledge and/or experience investing in crypto assets, particularly in DeFi</li>
<li>Risk management experience as either a front-office or second-line market risk manager</li>
<li>Hands-on experience in coding and/or working with relational databases, creating automation solutions for risk-related tasks</li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">Role details:</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li>Perform quantitative and qualitative analysis of the market risk of the firm positions</li>
<li>Contribute to formulating hedging strategies and risk management procedures based on the analysis results.</li>
<li>Interact with the front end to develop understanding of the firm’s risk-taking, how it fits the business model (understand the risk/reward that allows the firm to generate yield for the customers).</li>
<li>Work continuously on the improvement of the analytical framework, processes and techniques used for the market risk analysis, maintain close contact with professionals and teams covering adjacent areas (i.e. operational risk).</li>
<li>Based on the results of the risk analysis and intra-firm communication suggest  analytical and/or procedural improvements to risk monitoring that would cover potential blind spots.</li>
<li>Support the risk infrastructure buildout. </li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">Requirements/expected abilities and skills:</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li>Analytical mindset: ability to think logically, view the market in terms of possible risk/reward scenarios, quantify outcomes.</li>
<li>Desire to learn new things, ability to concentrate and maintain focus in disruptive  start-up environment, strong interest in crypto business (cryptocurrency markets and products).</li>
<li>Ability to communicate clearly, formulate questions and properly prepare for discussions, meetings.</li>
<li>Self-discipline, ability to work individually with and without close contact with supervision and/or other team members.</li>
<li>Methodical and logical approach to given assignments, ability to plan and prioritize tasks, deliver on schedule while maintaining steady communication &amp; work-related feedback to team members and supervisors.</li>
<li>Understanding of financial markets (5 years or more concentration in a specific area preferable). Understanding of options and volatility/structured products a strong plus. Other relevant experience like P&amp;L analysis and/or reconciliation a plus. Financial Engineering background a plus</li>
<li>Risk management experience (trading or risk control function) desirable. Currency trading experience a plus.</li>
<li>High level of proficiency in productivity tools used in financial analysis (strong working knowledge of Excel, understanding of/experience in relational databases, python, SQL etc.)</li>
<li>Crypto investment experience, ideally in DeFi</li>
</ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xW6QWaNfysw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=534&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/731816/celsius_network.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celsius@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5fa72b05-b42d-48a9-806e-c3fdccb06776]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[HR Business Partner (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitfury.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Kyiv, Kiev, Ukraine]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;div id=&quot;header&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at Bitfury:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is a leading emerging technologies company. &amp;nbsp;At Bitfury, you can build the solutions of the future, with the most significant technologies of the millennium, in a modern and flexible workplace. We work a bit faster, and a bit smarter, so we can make the world a bit better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of Working at Bitfury:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Experiences &amp;amp; Global Impacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is an international company with 200+ team members in more than 16 countries. No matter your assignment, your work will support global technology initiatives and best-in-class security operations in North America, Asia and Europe, as well as help us fulfil our mission to make the world more trusted and secure.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building the Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe big data, artificial intelligence, blockchain technology, tokenized economies and cryptocurrencies are the future of our digital, global economy. Bitfury is building this future through our products that offer digitised security, asset management, government services and more. We consider ourselves first and foremost a technology company. We are a diversified organisation, with operations across multiple facets of the AI, blockchain, and digital currency sectors. If you are passionate about emerging technologies, you can build your future at Bitfury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Your Career&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is growing fast and looking for the next generation of leaders and entrepreneurs to help us. At Bitfury, you will be expected to create the future – not just execute it. If you are a self-starter, driven and collaborative team member, you can create a dynamic future for yourself and your career at Bitfury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modern Workplace with Intelligent Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury lets you work in the way you need to work to make your work faster, smarter and better. We will give you the resources you need to succeed – competitive pay and benefits, educational support, intellectual challenges, professional advancement, personal accommodations including remote work, and more. We pride ourselves on being less bureaucratic and a lot more impactful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start-up Culture with Established Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with the world’s leading experts and engineers, you will have the opportunity at Bitfury to pursue results that will power your success as well as lead to the adoption of game-changing technologies. Our teams work every day to make the impossible possible, to change the game, to be agile and effective, and most of all – to empower the rest of the world to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ersonal and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rofessional&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;haracteristics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We at Bitfury ensure our team members possess the ability to think out of the box and make the impossible possible. We are self-motivated and result-oriented, and we have an “owner of the company” mindset. We are constantly self-educating and developing. We are able to work in a team and collaborate. We have a “do good” mindset and are not afraid to dream big. And of course, we always deliver in time what we promised and with extreme attention to detail — because if we are not able to do the little things right, we will never be able to do big things right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;&quot;&gt;We are looking for an experienced HR Business Partner to lead HR operations in multiple locations across Europe.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be fully responsible for HR activities of Bitfury internationally;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cover on-boarding, adaptation, evaluation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in HR policies design, transformation and implementation;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adapt global policies to the European market;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage outsourcing providers;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Consult employees on HR matters;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain HR administration processes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with all required internal and external stakeholders/organisations related to HR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements and Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of current/previous international experience as HR BP/Manager/Generalist;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Labour Law and&amp;nbsp;practices;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent&amp;nbsp;written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to multi-task and prioritise workload;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven effective written and verbal communication skills;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Earnest and dedicated focus on HR&amp;nbsp;activities;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work both independently and as a part of a team;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work under pressure and handle multiple projects and deadlines;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to resolve conflicts.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/DtkFJoj24rE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitfury/jobs/5850913002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145862/bitfury.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitfury@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bff43dfe-8ac3-4757-8a78-7559c9e9e327]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Production Coordinator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ava Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.avalabs.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Brooklyn, New York, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Avalanche is an open-source platform for launching decentralized finance applications and enterprise blockchain deployments in one interoperable, highly scalable ecosystem. Developers who build on Avalanche can easily create powerful, reliable, and secure applications and custom blockchain networks with complex rulesets or build on existing private or public subnets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded by the creators of Avalanche, Ava Labs makes it simple to launch finance applications using blockchain technology–with highly scalable and efficient networks, customizable public and private blockchains, the capability to create any digital asset, and more. We are empowering people to build an open, simple, and democratic internet of finance that enables the world to have a more prosperous future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;p-rich_text_list p-rich_text_list__bullet&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;unordered-list&quot; data-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Production support for our Events Management team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Ensure all team members are assigned to leading events as either speakers or panelists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Align with core business objectives by producing events globally while working with local team, community managers and regional stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Assist with the management of&amp;nbsp; in-person and virtual events strategy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Organize in-person meetups for community and business development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Coordinate operations and logistics at events&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Assist with management of sponsorships and event costs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Promote events to potential attendees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;p-rich_text_list p-rich_text_list__bullet&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;unordered-list&quot; data-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;2 - 7 years experience in events management&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;In-depth understanding of tech-focused events (e.g. hackathons, meetups, summits)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Passion for brand building, community engagement and events marketing&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Flexibility and resourcefulness to execute on ad-hoc/sudden changes during events&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Expert level organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;High EQ&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Proactive problem solver&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Responsive, Reliable &amp;amp; Accountable&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Google Business Suite&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot; data-stringify-border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Experience supporting global events (preferred)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#LI-PA1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY AVA LABS?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re a world-class team of experts in computer science, economics, finance, and law with offices in New York City and Miami. We&#39;re passionate individuals creating a frictionless world by redefining the way people build and use finance applications. &lt;/span&gt;The company has received funding from Andreessen Horowitz, Initialized Capital, and Polychain Capital, with angel investments from Balaji Srinivasan and Naval Ravikant.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ava Labs is committed to diversity in the workplace and we’re proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer. We do not hire on basis of race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, citizenship, age, disability, veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, parental status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, or any other basis protected by local, state or federal law. All employment is decided on the basis of qualifications, merit, and business need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/mWBzFmzzBAg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/avalabs/jobs/4308876004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/571953/avalabs-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[avalabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[a4029032-6a83-4107-89a8-330ee9cccbd1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ava Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, Sales Operations]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Forte Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.forte.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Forte is seeking an exceptionally organized and diligent &lt;strong&gt;Director of Sales Operations and Enablement&lt;/strong&gt; who will build the sales processes, tools, metrics, and playbooks that make our Sales organization an outstanding function.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You have familiarity with multiple sales systems and tools, are structured, results-driven, and love to think big and solve ambiguous problems. You will report to the Senior Director of Business Operations and will be a key partner to our Marketing and Sales/BD teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Examples of projects include creating processes for the Sales team to move leads through qualifications and the pipeline, maintain data integrity, ensuring that all data seamlessly flows between the Marketing and the Sales Team, move MQLs to SQL qualifications, and report on all aspects of the Sales funnel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will play a key role in driving growth and business success across the organization. You are excited to gain exposure to a wide range of different problem spaces -- spanning tech/gaming, blockchain, and economics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will be comfortable working independently and across cross-functional teams in a fast-paced and evolving environment. They will be an excellent communicator and a leader with a passion for delivering results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this role, you will:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build the sales operations and enablement function from the ground up.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage all sales operations activities including developing and improving the sales operations process, building account prioritizations, qualifying opportunities, managing forecasting, owning pipeline management and process.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with the Sales/BD and Marketing leadership teams to conduct analyses and determine how to design processes to accelerate pipeline generation and increase win rates.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track, analyze and report on key metrics (such as pipeline growth and pipeline potential)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain documentation for processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate and represent Sales/BD’s needs in all existing and future sales &amp;amp; CRM systems, in partnership with the Director of Business Systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To be a fit, you have:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8+ years of experience in Sales Operations or Sales Enablement preferably at a high-growth SaaS company.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical and data-driven, with demonstrated experience finding data-driven insights to improve sales productivity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience managing 2+ direct reports.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with a wide range of sales &amp;amp; CRM systems, including Hubspot and Salesforce.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Independent project management skills including the ability to define and execute against project timeframes, dependencies and risk factors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to think clearly, grasp the big picture, analyze quantitatively and problem solve.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for developing, mentoring, and growing a team, with a natural ability to bring people together and spark collaboration.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A./B.S. Degree, MBA is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in gaming and gaming-adjacent industries.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A genuine appreciation for blockchain technology and the benefits it can offer the games industry.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prior experience with Airtable, Confluence or Notion.&lt;br&gt;Experience with sales/revenue tools to scale sales efforts (e.g. Outreach, ZoomInfo, Gong…).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High-growth or early-stage startup experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The opportunity to build something that&#39;s never been built before - to solve new problems and to develop solutions with a team of industry leaders by your side.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you&#39;ll be hands-on with the latest tools and technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The opportunity to merge personal passions or interests you may have for blockchain and/or gaming with your professional path.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive compensation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous home office stipend for creating a comfortable and productive work space&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monthly stipend for snacks, meals, and things you may need to enhance your remote work experience!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paid medical, dental, and vision insurance - employer contributions for employees and dependents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k match up to $4000/year + Pre-tax commuter and FSA benefits&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Unlimited PTO - take time when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Forte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Forte is building economic technology for games. Its end-to-end platform enables the emergence of community economics, a system where the interests of game developers and players are aligned,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;leading to healthier, sustainable game communities. The team is composed of longtime industry members (Unity, ngmoco, Riot Games, Electronic Arts, Sony, and Rockstar Games, among others). Forte is currently working with over thirty acclaimed game developers from across the industry to reimagine the economics of games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/K378r1KeRio" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/forte/jobs/4930299003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/511563/forte-labs-logo_Cropped.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[forte@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[509e5842-f758-4b3e-8b54-bfc3ca4c2a98]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Forte Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Producer, Games]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.axiomzen.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Reporting to the Studio Head, the Senior Producer has a servant-leader attitude and is responsible for efficient management of the development team. The Senior Producer will strive for continuous improvement and drive towards achieving the vision of the game(s) and/or project(s) they’re involved with. </div><br/>Key Responsibilities:<br/><li>Ensure teams are focused and free from distraction by removing impediments, and that they are aligned with the vision and are working towards the agreed goals.</li><li>Streamline and optimize processes and workflows, implement best practices and work towards continuous improvement of the team.</li><li>Create and manage production schedules across different titles and projects run in the company.</li><li>Collaborate with external stakeholders for requirement gathering, resolving impediments, collating project related queries and communicating about status updates.</li><li>Implement and run project management systems using Agile and other industry standard methodologies.</li><li>Proactively prevent potential issues by seeking overarching knowledge about the product and process, and escalating any issues to the appropriate personnel.</li><li>Document meeting outcomes, and follow-up on action points.</li><li>Oversee the creation and maintenance of Continuous Integration (CI) systems</li><li>Adopt currently used project management tools including, Jira, Slack etc. and research and recommend improvements if they see a need.</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>5+ years in the games development industry with at least 2 years as a Producer/ Game Manager/ Project Manager.</li><li>Knowledge and experience in Agile methodologies.</li><li>Strong leadership and interpersonal skills.</li><li>Passionate about creating and delivering games and prototype experiences to stakeholders and customers</li><li>Goal focused mentality, and can quickly adapt and pivot as per the requirements and new information of the project being undertaken.</li><div><b>More about Dapper Labs:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Dapper Labs is the world's first blockchain entertainment company. We are the creators of industry-leading experiences including CryptoKitties and NBA Top Shot, as well as Dapper Wallet, the simplest way to manage your assets and use the blockchain. We are also the original developers behind Flow, a new decentralized blockchain designed from the ground up for scalability and ease of use.</div><div><br></div><div>Our mission at Dapper Labs is to make the world a more open, empowering, and enjoyable place through consumer adoption of decentralized technologies. We have raised over $600M from leading VCs including Fred Wilson (USV) and Chris Dixon as well as Venrock, Samsung, Google Ventures, Coatue, NBA players, and global artists, among others. Dapper Labs partners include the NBA and NBPA, the NFL-PA, Ubisoft, Warner Music, Turner, Dr. Seuss, Genies, and the UFC, as well as 100+ others.</div><div><br></div><div>Visit our website to learn even more about Dapper Labs, including <a href="https://www.dapperlabs.com/careers#benefits" class="postings-link">information about benefits and perks</a>.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Vvp75OCtwa0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axiomzen/7a376642-e68f-4ac4-a530-bbfa16f11c0b/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194192/axiomzen1.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axiomzen@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5da21464-b527-48a0-a501-0b4f2e445537]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.axiomzen.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Full-time | Axiom Zen | Remote | Business Operations</div><div><br></div><div>The Business Associate role is a dual role between investments and strategic business initiatives. Members of this team will gain exposure and drive impact across all facets of our company, embedding within cross-functional teams and working collaboratively to identify and tackle some of our most complex (and interesting) business challenges.</div><br/>Some of your initial responsibilities will include:<br/><li>Developing insight into our fast-evolving market(s) and competitors and making recommendations for strategic shifts or other next steps based on findings.</li><li>Analyze and drive investments for Axiom Zen’s venture arm.</li><li>Structuring, analyzing and making concrete recommendations to solve complex strategic challenges.</li><li>Defining, designing and introducing scalable processes and use of data to support strong decision-making companywide.</li><li>Leading cross-functional business projects.</li><br/>This role is for you if:<br/><li>You are highly analytical -- able to structure and dive deeply into strategic and operational problem spaces. You are able to distill and anchor on first principles.</li><li>You are a strong communicator -- skilled at relaying complex topics across a variety of audiences (executive and peer-level, technical and non-technical). We are remote-first, so will place a premium on strong written communication skills.</li><li>You are a natural collaborator -- able to build strong relationships, and skilled at bringing teams together to drive impact.</li><li>You have a passion for solving tough problems and a desire to do whatever it takes to get things done -- strong ability to work effectively in a highly-dynamic environment is a huge plus.</li><br/>You might have one the following in the last 2-5 years:<br/><li>Investment banking or venture capital.</li><li>Strategy / management consulting.</li><li>Product management or a related GTM function within a dynamic industry.</li><li>Business operations or corporate strategy in a high-growth environment.</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Vvp75OCtwa0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axiomzen/59063601-85d8-4447-aded-385270bf0e75/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194192/axiomzen1.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axiomzen@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5da21464-b527-48a0-a501-0b4f2e445537]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Social Media Community Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Nifty's]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://niftys.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT NIFTY’S, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nifty&#39;s is the eco-friendly home for NFTs (non-fungible tokens) from your favorite brands and creators on the blockchain. Nifty&#39;s, based in Miami FL, brings together premium publishers, brands and creators with collectors, curators and the communities of fans that will emerge around them. Offering an easy-to-use interface, the innovative platform will allow members to collect, discover, and curate the most important digital art and other collectibles from across the rapidly expanding NFT universe. Nifty&#39;s will provide creators with a premium, powerful, flexible and safe platform to launch their NFTs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FUNCTION&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Social Media Communications Specialist to build an awesome community across our various social media channels that reflects the Nifty&#39;s vision and culture. The Social Media Communications Specialist will manage community content on Nifty&#39;s social medial platforms, including Twitter, Instagram, and Discord with the goal to shape and grow the Nifty&#39;s community.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES &amp;amp; DELIVERABLES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In partnership with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Social Media Lead&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; assist in development, implementation and management of our social media strategy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In partnership with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Social Media Lead&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, brainstorm and develop social first campaigns in line with the Nifty&#39;s brand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage scheduling and publication of planned social media content&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Continuously Monitor conversation and respond to (appropriate) consumer questions and feedback in a timely fashion across all social media channels&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist in social media copywriting, ensuring all messaging is engaging and positions Nifty&#39;s as thought leader in the NFT space.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build, maintain and leverage a strong network of industry professionals and influencers via social media &amp;amp; discord.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Measure, report and communicate performance of owned initiatives and influencer/partnerships.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with brand design and brand marketing to ensure content is informative, consistent and creative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with Partnership, Customer Success, Design and Product teams to provide up to date and accurate content&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In partnership with &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Social Media Lead,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; establish and execute against KPI&#39;s&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor SEO and user engagement and suggest content optimization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Use social media marketing and project management tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Keep abreast of the latest Web3 and social media best practices and technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Stay close to users in the ecosystem to understand their needs and provide the engineering team with key user insights and problems to solve&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be an internal advocate for users to ensure we are solving for thei&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;r pain points&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide constructive feedback&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;One to two years related experience in community support or social medial management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven work experience in similar role&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of Discord, Twitter, Instagram, Sprout Social and Brandwatch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Other things to note:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nifty’s, Inc. strives to be a best-in-class and equal opportunity employer.  All qualified applicants &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, religion, color, national origin, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, age, status as a protected veteran, among other &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;things, or status as a qualified individual with disability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This job posting highlights the most critical responsibilities and requirements of the job. Other duties may be assigned as needed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nifty&#39;s, Inc. Privacy Policy can be found here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://niftys.com/privacy-policy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://niftys.com/privacy-policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/niftysinc/jobs/4310851004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/943210/niftys.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alexander+niftysinc@cryptocareers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6167914b-84e3-41bb-934a-cdb803281ce7]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Nifty's]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Mobile Marketing Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKEx]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.okex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who We Are:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;OKEx is on a mission to make crypto investing and trading more accessible to anyone around the world. We are building the next generation of tools to help onboard the investors and traders who have been on the fence about crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; OKEx is a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;globally licensed exchange with offices in San Francisco, Malta, Hong Kong, and Singapore. We are a collective of engineers, product managers, and marketers with a common passion to help decentralize finance and level the economic playing field for everyone around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Opportunity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking a talented and passionate Mobile Marketing Manager to join our Growth team. Candidates should be experienced, but willing to collaborate, adapt and learn. We’re a new team and growing rapidly. This is a great opportunity to get involved with more entrepreneurial professionals in a dynamic environment. Data analysis as well as ingenuity and creativity are vital as we’re driving improvements to our products, user experiences and engagement.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Be Doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Develop, manage, and optimize Twitter ad campaigns across multiple regions/cultures&lt;br&gt;Manage execution of data-driven campaigns in partnership with internal stakeholders to ensure business objectives are met&lt;br&gt;Manage campaigns end-to-end, including strategy, targeting, set-up, testing, execution, reporting and optimization&lt;br&gt;Manage targeting and segmentation for each campaign&lt;br&gt;Analyze campaign performance to provide actionable recommendations and deliver continuous improvements to programs&lt;br&gt;Monitor daily program automations and data processes; troubleshooting when necessary&lt;br&gt;Report on significant learnings and present the impact of significant findings to leadership&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Look For In You:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;3+ years of mobile user acquisition experience ideally in the fintech space&lt;br&gt;2+ years of App Store optimization experience&lt;br&gt;Solid project management skills and the ability to manage multiple priorities and deadlines&lt;br&gt;Experience with Twitter ad campaigns&lt;br&gt;Understanding of fundamental mobile KPIs and optimization methods to improve performance through data analysis and segmentation&lt;br&gt;Experience creating personalized customer lifecycle journeys on mobile&lt;br&gt;Experience with AB Testing, experiment development and reporting presentation&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bilingual in Mandarin/English&lt;br&gt;Crypto experience or a willingness to learn&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;OKEx Statement&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;OKEx is committed to equal employment opportunities regardless of race, color, genetic information, creed, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, lawful alien status, national origin, age, marital status, and non-job related physical or mental disability, or protected veteran status. Pursuant to the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance, we will consider for employment qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/x9kSkBMcOuo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okx/jobs/4930106003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175406/okex.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bcbc2afc-a2fd-45d8-bba3-e7ce4b53b3d8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKEx]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Finance (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[DeFi Alliance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.defialliance.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Chicago, IL]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 32px">Background</b></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 24px">About Alliance DAO</b></div><div>Alliance is the leading Web3 accelerator and founder community. Since early 2020, we've helped the top 1% of Web3 founders start and grow their companies. We do so through a 9-week program led by leading experts. Our community includes fellow founders, lawyers, auditors, market makers and more. Together, we will grow Web3 to one billion users by 2025.</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 24px">Origin Story</b></div><div>In March of 2020, top-tier trading and venture firms CMT Digital, Cumberland DRW, Jump Capital and Volt Capital joined to form the DeFi Alliance, an accelerator program to help early stage DeFi startups source liquidity. We accelerated more than 90 startups with the support from more than 200 entities in our support network. In January of 2020, DeFi Alliance and hundreds of other top builders joined forces to form Alliance DAO, the world's first digital startup nation, to accelerate the best Web3 startups.</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 24px">Products</b></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Web3 Accelerator Program.</b> A 9-week program featuring talks from leading experts, hands-on mentorship, demo days and more to&nbsp;help build&nbsp;your project and community.</div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Alliance DAO Network (ADN)</b><b>.</b> A community of stakeholders in the Web3 startup ecosystem. Our members include fellow founders, lawyers, auditors, market makers and many more. Our community is supported by various online products such as a founder’s forum, web app, jobs board and governance tools.</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 24px">What We Offer</b></div><div>🤩 Work with world-class Web3 founders, investors, and other industry leaders and be exposed to the most exciting projects working at the cutting edge of Web3</div><div>🤝 Join a growing team with a strong reputation, investment portfolio, and Accelerator business led by experienced entrepreneurs who have founded some of the leading companies in the crypto space</div><div>💰 Competitive salary</div><div>📈 Competitive equity/token compensation</div><div>🏝 Unlimited vacation policy</div><div>🦷 Medical, dental, and vision</div><div>🏡 A remote work environment with an international and diverse team</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 32px">Position Spec</b></div><div><b>Head of Finance</b></div><div><b>Location</b>: Remote </div><div><b>Compensate</b>: Competitive salary plus equity/tokens </div><div><b>Start Date</b>: Immediately </div><div><b>Experience</b>: Senior/Executive</div><div><br></div><div>Our investment manager is seeking a Head of Finance to lead its corporate/fund i) invoicing, payments and other transactions, ii) bookkeeping, iii) accounting, reporting and forecasting, iv) audit, v) equity management and entity structuring, vi) valuation, and vii) strategic vision. As our first senior financial hire, you will lead the execution of the above, build the necessary tools and processes to streamline, and grow the finance team and function over time. To be successful in this role, you should have previous experience as Head of Finance, CFO/CRO, or other senior financial positions with experience at a startup and/or funds. </div><br/>Key Outcomes<br/><li>Take ownership of the firm's corporate/fund i) invoicing, payments and other transactions, ii) bookkeeping, iii) accounting, reporting and forecasting, iv) audit, v) equity management and entity structuring, vi) valuation, and vii) strategic vision.</li><li>Work closely with our COO, fund admin, accountants, tax and audit firms and other third party vendors to successfully execute the above</li><li>Build the necessary tools, automations and processes to streamline all financial efforts</li><li>Build and lead a team over time </li><li>Lead or present at board, investor, or community meetings</li><li>Issue equity or token grants to internal employees</li><li>Specific early objectives include: i) assist in completion of year-end tax and audit, ii) build out tools or processes for on-chain bookkeeping/accounting/reporting, iii) finalize Fund II's valuation policy, iv) finalize process for monthly/quarterly corporate accounting</li><li>Serve as a mentor and resource for our accelerator cohort founders</li><li>Lead or participate in strategic treasury planning, practices, tooling and thought-leadership for DAOs </li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Served as Head of Finance, CFO/CRO or other senior financial position with experience at a startup and/or fund </li><li>5+ years experience in financial roles with 2+ years experience in a senior or lead position</li><li>2+ years experience in fund or investment finance</li><li>Exceptional skills in data and database management (spreadsheets, Python, SQL or other relevant languages)</li><li>Excellent communication skills both written and verbal</li><li>Entrepreneurial spirit (willing to not only perform the internal work that needs to be done but to work with Web3 founders and build strategic treasury planning, practices, tooling and thought-leadership for DAOs )</li><br/>Highly Desired Attributes<br/><li>Familiarity and experience with crypto and Web3 communities and values</li><div><b style="font-size: 24px">Alliance&nbsp;At A Glance</b></div><div>Alliance focuses on venture capital, incubators, accelerators, bitcoin, ethereum, cryptocurrency, and blockchains. We are a distributed team of 10-15.</div><div><br></div><div>You can view our website at&nbsp;<a href="http://alliance.xyz/" class="postings-link">http://alliance.xyz/</a>&nbsp;or find us on&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/alliancedao" class="postings-link">Twitter</a>&nbsp;and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/alliancedao" class="postings-link">LinkedIn</a>.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/defialliance/31b90eba-8cf8-44c5-b937-16d892bb4ad8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/881780/defi-alliance-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[defialliance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[fbf638d0-96f8-49df-9e12-35e249aaeb3a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[DeFi Alliance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Client Experience Analyst (West Coast)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Genesis Global Trading]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://genesistrading.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<h3>About Genesis</h3><p>Genesis is a global leader in institutional digital asset markets. We provide a single point of access for digital asset trading, derivatives, borrowing, lending, custody and prime brokerage services. </p>    <p>Genesis facilitates billions in trades, loans and transactions on a monthly basis. We have a proven track record driving results for some of the largest digital asset-focused hedge funds, quant funds, family offices, VC’s, market makers and exchanges.</p><p><br></p>    <h3>Join Our Team</h3>    <p>Genesis is expanding to solve some of the toughest challenges in digital asset financial markets. </p><p><br></p>    <h3>About This Role – Client Experience Analyst (West Coast)</h3>    <p>Genesis Trading is seeking a Client Experience Analyst to provide high-touch user support and client advocacy. In this role you will support both internal and external clients across trading, lending, and custody business lines. Analysts will help to ensure a premium-level user experience for our primary technology applications. The opportunity in this role is unique as it allows for the Analyst to gain valuable internal support experience in addition to being a client-facing role. The Client Experience Analyst will have excellent written and verbal communication skills, and a thoughtful approach to working with internal and external teams.</p><p>This position will be very hands-on and will report to a Client Experience Manager. The primary platform the Analyst will be working on is Genesis Prime, which provides an integrated user experience for clients to trade, borrow, lend, and store digital assets. You will be on the frontlines working with new and existing clients, advocating for our clients, and solving technical issues. It is expected that Analysts will work to become subject matter experts in the digital asset space to effectively partner with clients and internal departments on identifying appropriate solution offerings.<br></p><p>A successful candidate will be dedicated to making sure that client questions, issues, and requests are dealt with quickly, appropriately, and correctly.</p><p><br></p><h3>Primary Responsibilities</h3><ul> <li>Utilize CRM to manage all client interactions and support requests</li> <li>Improve CRM workflows and help build reports detailing client interactions for internal stake holders</li> </ul><ul><li>Support internal operational workflows for sales, trading, finance, and compliance teams</li></ul><ul><li>Liaise with our AML and Onboarding teams to ensure frictionless onboarding of new clients</li></ul><ul><li>Educate new and existing clients on how to use the Prime application by providing comprehensive platform demos</li></ul><ul><li>Act as the primary liaison for sales, trading, account management, and technology teams to troubleshoot and resolve customer issues</li></ul><ul><li>Drafting documentation, i.e., standard operating procedures and customer facing documentation</li></ul><p><br></p><h3>Requirements</h3><ul> <li>1-3 years of experience in a client experience, customer success, or client support role, ideally at a technology or financial services company</li> </ul><ul><li>Ability to work specific hours based on the coverage required each week</li></ul><ul><li>Knowledge of the digital asset space is a requirement for this role, we are looking for candidates who specifically want to be working in crypto</li></ul><ul><li>Experience with ticketing systems (JIRA and Hubspot), SLAs, and KPIs</li></ul><ul><li>Familiarity with user management systems and identity verification procedures</li></ul><ul><li>Proven troubleshooting and customer-focused problem-solving skills</li></ul><ul><li>Must be a disciplined self-starter with an ability to work autonomously</li></ul><p><br></p><h3>Personal Attributes</h3><ul> <li>Strong interpersonal and communication skills</li> <li>Self-starter yet knows when to ask for help and works great in a team</li> <li>Strives to simultaneously achieve high-velocity and high-quality output</li> <li>Willingness and ability to meet aggressive deadlines</li> <li>Thrives in a dynamic and high-pressured environment</li> <li>Proven troubleshooting and problem-solving skills</li> </ul><p><br></p><h3>Benefits</h3><ul> <li>100% Premium Coverage for Medical, Dental, &amp; Vision for you and your dependents</li> <li>Flexible Spending Accounts, Health Savings Accounts, Tax-Free Transit Benefits, &amp; Other Supplemental Benefits Available</li> <li>Flexible Time Off</li> <li>Generous Parental Leave</li> </ul><p><br></p><h3>Why Genesis</h3><p>Genesis is dedicated to creating best-in-class infrastructure for institutional investors, developing advanced products that lower barriers, increase profitability and broaden access. Our team has decades of experience at top Wall Street investment banks and Silicon Valley technology firms, and includes leading experts in blockchain, distributed computing, cryptography and cybersecurity.<br><br></p><p><strong>Digital Asset Ecosystem</strong></p><p>Genesis operates at the heart of the digital asset ecosystem:</p><p>→ We are a subsidiary of Digital Currency Group (DCG), the largest investor in the bitcoin and blockchain space.</p><p>→ We have an unparalleled global network at the intersection of data, finance and technology.</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Accelerating Momentum</strong></p><p>Our addressable market is expanding rapidly as new institutional investors enter the space. Recent results include:</p><p>→ 300%+ Y/Y trading volume growth</p><p>→ 400%+ Y/Y loan origination growth</p><p>→ 300%+ Y/Y active loan growth</p><p>→ 150%+ Q/Q derivatives transaction growth</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Diversity And Inclusion</strong></p><p>Genesis invests in creating a welcoming environment where everyone can feel supported and connected at work.</p><p>→ We help employees develop a deep understanding of the problems we’re trying to solve.</p><p>→ We thrive on ideas driven by a broad range of perspectives.</p><p>→ We believe diverse teams lead to better products and bigger outcomes.</p><p><br></p><p><em>Genesis is an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.</em></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/genesistrading/j/76F6A456FA/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/393086/genesistrading.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[genesis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c9bd0dc3-d1d2-4216-adf4-36b49462bc09]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Genesis Global Trading]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[TechOps Engineer (NFT)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Global]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Familiar with the product and technical details of NFT system, directly connected with users and customer service personnel, and solved the online consultation and customer complaint related to certain product/technical knowledge transmitted by customer service</li><li>Organize product and technical personnel to deal with problems that cannot be solved directly, and become a bridge between customer service and product/technical personnel. Categorize and summarize online problems, accumulate knowledge base, and deal with them directly afterwards</li><li>Coordinated and dealt with online accidents, organized personnel to review online accidents, and tracked follow-up improvements</li><li>The employee must allocate time to deal with the above work independently on weekdays, and then decide whether to recruit more personnel according to the situation, which may require shift work</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>Bachelor degree or above, major in computer, software development or related, recruitment of outstanding fresh graduates</li><li>Strong language skills, good communication and coordination, strong customer service awareness</li><li>Have certain code and SQL writing ability, can solve fixed online problems independently</li><li>For smart contracts, blockchain background is preferred</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/a03eef6a-8565-427f-9710-b5346f73d49d/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Content Writer - EU]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Europe]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">Binance is looking for an experienced Content Writer who can produce stimulating written content to educate, inspire and excite our existing and new audiences in Europe. Your material will shape how the world sees Binance!</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">A proficient Content Writer will be responsible for inbound marketing strategies and creation of content for avenues such as our homepage, blogs, social media, PR announcements as well as Binance Angels.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">Content development, with the intent of attracting customers, will be a large part of this position. Content developed needs to be fresh, up to date, and engaging for the customer.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">Having a strong interest in blockchain/DLT/Cryptocurrency space, new technologies and marketing is pivotal in this role. The expansion of the company’s digital footprint is your ultimate goal, along with building brand awareness and bringing our platform to users and fans in the European region.</span></div><br/>Responsibilities :<br/><li>Draft, create, improve and proofread content quickly, efficiently, and against deadlines, guidelines, and briefs</li><li>Create copy in different writing styles for various channels: blog, PR, website, video scripts, with the goal of educating, exciting, and inspiring our global audience and attracting new fans to our platform</li><li>Collaborate with product and business development, marketing specialists, designers, video editors, and other teams and creatives to quickly draft engaging content pieces that enhance the visibility of Binance and our products&nbsp;</li><li>Research topics, such as specific personas, industries and technologies, and use our resources to create copy that speaks authentically to our audiences</li><li>Incorporate SEO best practices into writing, including the integration of keywords, in-line links, formatting and more</li><li>Communicate with internal stakeholders to gather requirements and translate them into content needs</li><li>Regularly curate, write and proofread flash and breaking news articles, responding quickly to market-moving news, industry movements and company updates</li><li>Expand our reach by leveraging owned, earned and paid distribution channels, including email, push alerts, social media, communities, affiliates and Angels</li><li>Help with translations and proofread content </li><li>Stay informed on trends in digital technology</li><br/>Requirements : <br/><li>Native in English</li><li>Excellent writing and research skills, strong attention to detail</li><li>Bachelor's or higher degree, ideally, in English, Journalism, Media, Communications, Marketing or related fields</li><li>3 years of content creation and/or editorial experience (in news, tech, finance)</li><li>Eager to work with new financial technologies (ie. cryptocurrency, blockchain and Fintech)</li><li>Possess the following qualities: inquisitive, proactive, responsive, and responsible</li><li>Strong ability to multitask and work quickly under tight daily deadlines</li><li>Fundamental understanding of web traffic metrics, analytics and content optimization</li><li>Strong teamwork and communication skills, ability to work remotely and sync regularly on progress and delivery</li><li>Portfolio of writing samples</li><div><b style="font-size: inherit">Conditions:</b></div><div>・  Competitive salary</div><div>・  Flexible working conditions</div><div>・  Flat organisation</div><div>・  Great Locations with a highly talented and international colleagues</div><div>・  Be a part of the exciting future of the crypto-currency revolution and work on the world's no.1 crypto-currency exchange!</div><div><br></div><div><b>About Binance</b></div><div>Binance Exchange is the leading crypto exchange by trading volume and users, with customers in over 180 countries and regions. Capable of processing more than 1.4 million orders per second, Binance is one of the fastest trading platforms in the world. The platform focuses on security, robustness, and execution speed—attracting enthusiasts and professional traders alike.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/a443237a-10fb-4c15-9939-64a1b00bc2e0/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Security Engineer - Remote in Europe or Central/South America -]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ultra]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ultra.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Tallinn]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 17pt">About Ultra</span></div><div><br></div><div>Ultra is a blockchain company launching a PC games distribution and an app ecosystem.&nbsp;Ultra aggregates all gamers’ activities in one place: from buying, playing and reselling games, to accessing live-streaming platforms, tournaments, reviews and contests, as well as interacting with communities and brands.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>The team is currently composed of 70+ full-time members, working across 5 continents. To learn more, visit our website:<a href="https://ultra.io/" class="postings-link"> https://ultra.io/</a></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 18pt">The Role</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">Ultra is looking for a Security Engineer to join our growing team. This is an exciting position in which you will be collaborating with cross-functional teams to provide guidance on security best practices.</span><b>&nbsp;</b><span style="font-size: 12pt"><b>Under the supervision of Ultra's Head of Security, you will be leading and implementing projects that relate to improving Ultra's security on every level</b>. You will play a key role in Ultra's security strategy.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 18pt">Your Profile</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">You are committed to using your technical skills to build a solid and secure platform for all our users.&nbsp;You are proactive, a team player, you have an analytical mind and good attention to detail. You are a problem-solver, critical thinker and a good communicator.</span></div><br/>Key Requirements<br/><li><b>You have Offensive/Defensive Security Certification</b>, ideally but not limited to: OCSE, OSCP, CISSP, GSE&nbsp;</li><li><b>You are an expert in Bash, Python</b></li><li>Proficient experience with tools such as Nessus, Nexpose, Metasploit, WebInspect, Appscan, nmap, Kali Linux…</li><li>5+ years experience in a Linux environment</li><li>You are involved in the hacking community: you have taken part in CTF, Whitepapers, opensource projects, vulnerability disclosure programs, bug bounties or other</li><li><b>You are fluent in English</b></li><br/>It's great (but not mandatory) if you also have:<br/><li>Computer/Software/Electrical Bachelor Degree or more</li><li>Military, banking, law enforcement, or government experience</li><li>Proficient in C++, ruby, java</li><li>ISO/IEC 27001 Lead Implementer or ISO/IEC 27001 Lead Auditor.</li><li>System administration background</li><li>Experience with kubernetes, terraform, etc..</li><li>Experience pentesting graphql,nodejs, chrome applications</li><li>Knowledge in blockchain</li><br/>What you will do<br/><li><b>Your tasks</b></li><li>Penetration testing and configuration auditing</li><li>Implementing and enforcing company security policies</li><li>Conducting forensic investigation into fraud and system abuse</li><li>Risk analysis of application services</li><li>Collaboration with development teams to improve security</li><li>Application security Architecture</li><li>Automate security tools&nbsp;</li><div><br></div><div><b>Your challenges</b></div><li>Ultra could be considered as a multitude of smaller sub-projects, each having its own leader. Your interpersonal skills and your ability to multitask will allow you to work efficiently with tech teams, but also business teams at Ultra. </li><li>You will work with Ultra staff and entities all around the world, and collaborating with them remotely/asynchronously will be part of your daily routine. </li><li>Your ability to investigate, organize, manage your priorities, provide insights and relevant reporting will help define Ultra's security strategy.&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><div><br></div><div><b>At Ultra, you will:</b></div><li>Participate to the construction from the ground-up of global gaming platform</li><li>Have the chance to discover the vast crypto space with all its innovation and challenges</li><li>Have a direct impact on the architecture and technologies</li><li>Work with passionate engineers, product managers, testers... in a multicultural environment</li><br/>What's next<br/><li>If your application is selected, you will enter our recruitment process:</li><li>Meet a Recruiter</li><li>Take our Technical test</li><li>Meet Erik, Head of Security, and Hugo, Head of Engineering at Ultra</li><div><span style="font-size: 9pt">🌈 Ultra is a true international company currently spread across the globe (Estonia, Belgium, France, Portugal, Ukraine, USA, China, South Africa…). We thrive off diverse perspectives! We recognize that diversity has different aspects: gender, sexual orientation, ability, ethnic origin, social, age, lifestyle, and more! We're committed to giving equal opportunities, and fostering a culture where everyone is heard and feels a sense of belonging.</span></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/ultra/dd407782-0932-407a-9687-1c17a964da4c/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/549658/ultra-logo-400x400.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ultra@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[01d06fb8-7df1-4a55-9ad1-eceeb24b632e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ultra]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crypto Indices Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://coindesk.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About CoinDesk Indices&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinDesk Indices are the industry standard for institutional single- and multi-asset benchmarks for crypto assets. The flagship CoinDesk Bitcoin Price Index (XBX) has been in operation continuously since 2014. Financial institutions rely on the XBX and other CoinDesk Indices products to benchmark billions of dollars in assets under management and to price hundreds of millions in over-the-counter transactions, daily.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinDesk Indices is seeking a Data Analyst to gather, cleanse, analyze and validate market data related to digital assets. These data will be critical inputs to the development, management and rebalancing of the world’s leading cryptocurrency index offering of industry benchmarks and market indices for index-linked products. This role will also research digital assets to determine and assign the appropriate classification for the Digital Asset Classification Standard. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Acquire, cleanse, and standardize market data for digital assets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop business rules and processes to ensure the quality and timeliness of market data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with index managers to understand and interpret market data used to maintain and rebalance indices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide input to Index Committee meeting discussions and recommendations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with engineering team to develop workflows to ingest and validate market data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong quantitative skills and the ability to troubleshoot and resolve data issues and follow escalation protocols for critical and unresolved issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to multi-task and contribute to key initiatives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide responses to client inquiries related to index data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years of experience in the financial industry with specific knowledge of cryptocurrencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Undergraduate degree in quantitative or financial field such as finance, accounting, economics, mathematics, computer science, or engineering&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing financial data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to build and support models using excel or other programming language&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Must be curious, a methodical thinker, and detail oriented&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong communication skills with the ability to simplify complicated concepts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Previous role researching and analyzing cryptocurrencies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with managing indices and/or portfolios.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Programming experience including Python.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Technical knowledge of blockchain protocols and smart contracts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EQUAL OPPORTUNITY&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In an effort to attract, retain, develop and promote the most qualified individuals, CoinDesk is committed to treating all applicants and employees in a nondiscriminatory manner with respect to the terms and conditions of employment, without regard to race, color, religion or belief, sex, national or ethnic origin, ancestry, age, marital status, sexual orientation, gender identity, veteran status/service, physical or mental disability, or any other classification protected by applicable law. This mandate governs all aspects of employment, including recruitment, selection, promotion, training, education, social and recreation programs, compensation, discipline, termination and access to benefits.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For more information on our DEI initiatives, please visit: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coindesk.com/dei/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://www.coindesk.com/dei/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ACCOMMODATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CoinDesk is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the application process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:accommodations@coindesk.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accomodations@coindesk.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVID-19 VACCINATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;COVID-19 vaccination is required for all employees whose position is based out of the NYC office. However, CoinDesk will consider accommodations for disability- and religious-based reasons on a case by case basis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/coindesk/jobs/5820354002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145913/coindesk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coindesk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[459b477b-1ae2-43d1-a1a8-7a40fbe3f487]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CoinDesk]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Research and Intelligence Manager, Corporate Strategy & Operations]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ripple’s Corporate Strategy and Operations team was formed to lead strategic initiatives and scale executive operations, while providing a neutral POV to senior leadership to inform strategic decisions. It has a unique vantage point looking across all functional areas and the overall strategic direction of the company.&amp;nbsp; We are looking to scale the CS&amp;amp;O Team to help bring external market perspective in the form of market research and intelligence in the ever evolving space of Fintech, Blockchain, and Crypto.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This intelligence will inform the company&#39;s strategy, product roadmap, investments among other decisions at a corporate level- across all BUs and functional areas. This role will also help position Ripple as a thought leader.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ideal candidates will have a strong interest, curiosity and experience in Digital Assets, Crypto Markets, Blockchain, and Payments. They will have a strong mix of strategic thinking, the ability to engage with senior executives at outside firms in order to have the latest/ greatest developments. They should also be well-versed in the hot spots for engagement with said community including Discord, Telegram, Twitter, Reddit etc.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understand and share insights around emerging topics in crypto and blockchain to make them easier for senior executives to comprehend and digest&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop a deep understanding of various crypto and blockchain technologies and projects from both technology and business perspectives and drive actionable insights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Become a go-to resident expert in all things crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify key areas relevant to Ripple based on discussions with senior leadership and cross functional stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Initiate and support thought-leadership across the crypto/blockchain industry to position Ripple as an industry crypto/thought-leader.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Regularly communicate with internal stakeholders, external vendor partners to collect, harmonize &amp;amp; review data, build models, interpret results, and formulate key insights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with internal stakeholders to translate insights into real actions in business (e.g. product strategy, M&amp;amp;A strategy, etc.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attend key industry events on behalf of Ripple to gain first-row seat to the latest discussions in Crypto/Payments world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Educate internal teams about the latest in crypto and fintech&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We’re Looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;6+ years of work experience related to market intelligence, publications,&amp;nbsp; consumer and/or industry research (ideally with key partners and customers in the payments, FinTech, crypto and financial services industry.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A strong interest, curiosity and experience in digital assets / crypto markets. Ability to understand technical terminology and advantages is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Very strong communication and presentation skills, particularly with translating data/ complex concepts towards actionable insights that can be easily understood by a general business audience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong teamwork and collaboration skills across a highly-matrix organization.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to procure and partner with key their-party research vendors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to interact and represent Ripple at industry events&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong presence across key communication channels used by Crypto enthusiasts today, including and not limited to Twitter, Discord, Telegram, Reddit etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice &lt;/a&gt;and our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/ca-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;California Applicant Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; for reference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3863740?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Infrastructure Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://mythical.games/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a Data Infrastructure Engineer with experience in&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; distributed systems design, big data architecture, and backend operations. As a Data &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Infrastructure &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engineer, you’ll be responsible for the design and implementation of infrastructure driving analytics and data science solutions across the company. You’ll be hands-on as specialized DevOps, helping to manage and future-proof an exciting tech stack that includes GCP, Kubernetes, BigQuery, CockroachDB, Kafka, KSQL, Airflow, and Snowplow.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In this role, you’ll work on a cross-functional team of data engineers to ensure robust, stable infrastructure is in place to support the data needs of multiple teams, partners, and games. At Mythical, we are proud to be one team and work together; the data engineering team works in close alignment with our analytics engineers, machine learning engineers, and data scientists to deliver solutions for any team at the company that may benefit from data wizardry.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design, implement, and maintain high-performance, scalable data architecture to support both batch and real-time data analytics pipelines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in alert monitoring, respond to and resolve data infrastructure incidents as they arise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create infrastructure diagrams, BoE calculations, and documentation to support analytical data operations and infrastructure scale-out&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help inform and make data backend tooling decisions, guide optimization efforts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Play key role in maintaining data resiliency, security, and governance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years of experience working in with backend, distributed systems in an operational capacity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building out microservices and containerized systems running in the cloud using Kubernetes/k8s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency with backend systems administration, DevOps, CI/CD, and object-oriented programming&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable optimizing complex SQL scripts and event streams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable maintaining large, unstructured datasets and cloud storage architecture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with real-time distributed stream-processing frameworks such as Apache Kafka&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Microservice, scalability, and continuous improvement based mindset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exposure to any/some/all of the following: Kafka, CockroachDB, Snowplow, GCP, Terraform&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interest in blockchain technology and video games&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team values diversity and believes that it strengthens our games, products, and communities. We strongly encourage POC, folks with disabilities, those belonging to the LGBTQIA+ communities, and folks across all gender identities to apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We offer our team benefits such as (but not limited to) high-quality Vision, Dental, and Health Care, generous Parental Leave, and Unlimited PTO to ensure that they actually take time off without the stress of needing to accrue time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you need assistance around accommodations due to a disability, please reach out to accessibility@mythical.games. We’ll be with you as soon as possible; our goal is to ensure an accessible and equitable interview process for everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Zfsp0FQ5X8s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/mythicalgames/jobs/4931402003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/351124/Mythical-Logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[info@mythical.games]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[541f8953-1749-4738-90d8-efd04dd286d1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Learning Experience Designer- Crypto U]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re Coinbase. We’re the world’s most trusted way to join the crypto revolution, serving more than 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/our-mission-strategy-and-culture-18a92a3bb0fa&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web 3.0 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture. We’re a remote-first company looking to hire the absolute best talent all over the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve got positive energy. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for an innovative designer of world-class learning experiences to help us accelerate the performance and engagement of every employee at Coinbase. We are a remote first company, and this person will be responsible for creating compelling learning solutions that scale, and drive results everywhere our people are.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build a cohesive brand for all Coinbase Learning and Development offerings.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design, develop, implement, and evaluate curricula programs ranging from crypto and blockchain education, to leadership development programming.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create highly effective multi modal learning experiences using known digital learning tools, and approaches nobody else has thought of yet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Architect best-of-bread orientation and onboarding programs that make incredible first impressions, extend learning beyond the classroom, and accelerate performance in the first 90 days of joining Coinbase.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we look for in you (ie. job requirements):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum 5 years experience with instructional design and learning technologies with an emphasis on learner experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fluency with rapid instructional design models, and designing for global scale in remote and distributed environments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building asynchronous and synchronous classroom-based and virtual training programs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Learning technology experience with a focus on content creation and visual design e.g.&amp;nbsp; (captivate, articulate, ispring suite, evolve, photoshop, illustrator, etc).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exceptional project management skills, with experience designing curriculum for a range of audience types from management and leadership to technical engineering.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; juggle multiple projects and deliver results within tight deadlines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written, verbal, and visual communication skills; concise and data driven.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;PID: P35985&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Notice for Colorado applicants as required by sb19-085 (8-5-20). Target annual salary for this role performed in Colorado, is $127,000&amp;nbsp;+ target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please note that for employees based in the US, Philippines, Canada or Singapore, if your role requires you to be present in a Coinbase office or if you choose to be physically present in a Coinbase office or sponsored location, participate in any in-person gathering (including offsites) or engage in business travel sponsored by Coinbase, you will be required to be fully vaccinated (as defined by applicable law).&amp;nbsp; If you receive an offer, you will receive additional information about the grounds and process for an exemption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations[at]coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3845591?gh_jid=3845591&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Security & IT Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span>About Celsius Network</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span>Celsius addresses the financial needs of today’s consumers worldwide through a democratized interest income and lending platform accessible via mobile and desktop app. With a mission to put unparalleled economic freedom in the hands of the people, and a core belief that financial services should only do what is in the best interests of the community, Celsius is a modern earning and lending platform where membership provides access to curated financial services that are not available through traditional financial institutions. Crypto holders can earn yield on the digital assets in their account with Celsius, and can borrow fiat or stablecoins against their crypto collateral at the lowest interest rates in the space.  </span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span>The Celsius team is committed to doing good and doing well. We believe in the power of disruption and the importance of decentralization to create a new system that acts in the best interest of everyone. Each member of our team brings something unique and innovative to the table, but the common thread that links us together is our passion for blockchain, equality, and leading the next financial revolution that changes the equation to bring power back to the people.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">Position: Security &amp; IT Engineer</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span>Key Responsibilities:</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Troubleshoot and solve technical issues with hardware and software.</span></li>
<li><span>Resolve help desk tickets for internal employees via phone, in person, or electronically.</span></li>
<li><span>Resolve technical issues in a timely manner using available resources within the company.</span></li>
<li><span>Handle Serbian Office support and requirements for onsite employees.</span></li>
<li><span>Perform hardware and software installations, configurations and updates as needed.</span></li>
<li><span>Handle onboarding and off-boarding of employees.</span></li>
<li><span>Provide introductory on-line &amp; classroom training for company products.</span></li>
<li><span>Log bugs and enhancement requests for our IT and security systems.</span></li>
<li><span>Monitor and alert of Security and IT issues that arise.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span>Requirements:</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span>At least 3 years experience in the IT field preferably providing customer support.</span></li>
<li><span>Extensive knowledge of Windows 10, Mac OS X, Office 365 administration, G Suite management, Okta management, Jira administration, User rights management for Cloud services. </span></li>
<li><span>Extensive experience with Security tools: Endpoint security and management tools, Firewalls, VPN’s and Password managers. </span></li>
<li><span>Experience with Crowdstrike, ManageEngine, Zendesk, AWS Workspaces, OpenVPN and Database client connectivity is an advantage.</span></li>
<li><span>Extensive knowledge of client computer hardware systems.</span></li>
<li><span>Knowledge of LAN and wireless networks.</span></li>
<li><span>Excellent customer service and communication skills.</span></li>
<li><span>Strong troubleshooting and critical thinking skills.</span></li>
<li><span>Ability to manage projects and tasks in an organized fashion.</span></li>
</ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xW6QWaNfysw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=555&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/731816/celsius_network.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celsius@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5fa72b05-b42d-48a9-806e-c3fdccb06776]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Global Tax Director]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Republic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://republic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY, or Houston, TX, or Salt Lake City, UT]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 11pt">Republic</b><span style="font-size: 11pt"> is a financial technology firm that allows everyone to invest in private markets. Republic operates several distinct business lines including a retail investment platform, a private capital division, and a blockchain advisory practice. The Republic ecosystem has deployed over $800 million in investments, has supported over 600 companies, and is comprised of a community of over 1.5M users across 100 countries. Republic is backed by dozens of leading investment firms and financial institutions and its affiliated entities have co-invested with the best names in venture and private equity. Founded in 2016, Republic is headquartered in New York City with offices worldwide.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We're looking for an energetic and talented individual to join our growing team. This is a key position tasked with performing functions related to tax matters across Republic’s business units. The successful hire will be comfortable working with a high degree of integrity including the ability to successfully deal with sensitive or confidential information. This role will require excellent technical knowledge of US federal tax, US taxation on foreign income, state &amp; local taxes and more. Moreover, the candidate must have strong interpersonal skills and possess a strong business acumen.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Lead the development, analysis and implementation of planning ideas to minimize global taxes that agrees with the overall company strategy;</li><li>Responsible for the review of US GAAP calculations, entity tax provisions, deferred and current tax and consolidated provision calculations;</li><li>Responsible for the filing of foreign, US and state consolidated corporate income tax returns;</li><li>Manage relationships with outside tax advisors;&nbsp;</li><li>Work with various business units to opine on tax implications for a wide range of transactions;</li><li>Maintenance of the global tax calendar and ensure that the company is in compliance with filing deadlines across the globe;</li><li>Create and implement improvements for the tax provision process and other tax processes. Implement any tax technology as needed; and</li><li>Perform other related duties as assigned.</li><br/>Qualifications:<br/><li>10+ years prior related experience, including a minimum of 5 years international tax experience</li><li>Bachelor’s Degree in Accounting, Finance, or other business-related field. CPA, JD or MBA preferred.</li><li>Proficient in Microsoft Office; Advanced Excel is a plus</li><li>Ability to work under pressure, independently and follow instructions</li><li>Strong analytical, quantitative, and problem-solving skills</li><li>Strong math aptitude and ability to work accurately with numbers</li><li>Excellent organizational, written and interpersonal skills, attention to detail</li><li>Applies principles of taxation to analyze financial information</li><li>Ability to work and interact with personnel at all levels within the organization</li><li>Knowledge of industry related concepts and terminology</li><li>Able to work in a fast-paced environment, with significant competing deadlines.</li><li>Able to grasp processes and concepts quickly and resolve issues.</li><li>History of solving multiple complex operational and tax challenges</li><li>Advanced knowledge of GAAP requirements and SOX requirements preferred. IFRS background a plus.</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Qy1lzYTV6Uc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/republic/acc52ab8-4f2d-4358-a6cf-d2d3d9d0933c/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/211719/Republic.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[republic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b024f433-5745-442c-98f6-a3b65ac4a9b0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Republic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Visual Brand Designer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York; Portland, Oregon; Chicago, Illinois; Los Angeles, California; San Francisco, California; Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is a crypto exchange and custodian that allows customers to buy, sell, store, and earn more than 30 cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, bitcoin cash, ether, litecoin, and Zcash. Gemini is a New York trust company that is subject to the capital reserve requirements, cybersecurity requirements, and banking compliance standards set forth by the New York State Department of Financial Services and the New York Banking Law. Gemini was founded in 2014 by twin brothers Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss to empower the individual through crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto is about giving you greater choice, independence, and opportunity. We are here to help you on your journey. We build crypto products that are simple, elegant, and secure. Whether you are an individual or an institution, we want to help you buy, sell, and store your bitcoin and cryptocurrency. Crypto is not just a technology, it&#39;s a movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, our mission is to &lt;strong&gt;empower the individual&lt;/strong&gt; and that includes giving our employees flexibility of choice — our Office Optional Policy allows employees to choose to work from one of our physical locations or from home.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Department: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Design&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team actualizes Gemini’s mission by designing best in class products and brand experiences. In Design, we think comfort zones are the enemy of creativity.&amp;nbsp; Our team blends beauty with tech to create a world-class product interface for our exchange. We are inspired by design, fueled by data, and obsessed with the user, both retail and institutional. Our work is simple, engaging, effective and cohesive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role: &lt;/strong&gt;Visual Designer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This designer will be focused on marketing and brand design with the ability/option to learn and collaborate with product design. This individual will support business goals related to brand building, brand recognition, and marketing. They will contribute to the Gemini look and feel and have the ability to creatively express the brand across a variety of mediums.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Evolve and apply our visual identity; become fully immersed in the Gemini brand and mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support day-to-day creation of brand, marketing, comms, and sales assets working closely with project leads&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with other designers and project leads to the develop visual approaches for product launches, features updates, and ad campaigns&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design assets for social channels and support the communications team with creative approaches to social media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with marketing to design emails, ads, and digital and print collateral&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop new designs as well as iterate on existing designs for the gemini.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Explore new directions and design patterns to meet the requirements while always pushing the quality of design forward&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years of experience in a similar role and or formal design training&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient in Figma or sketch, Adobe CC, Google Suite&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience designing for the web and mobile, and with using design systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Can execute on a predefined design direction as well as take and implement feedback&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Clear understanding of visual hierarchy, balance, rhythm, typography and color&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to problem solve and provide multiple simplistic solutions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Creative mindset and ability to adapt to change&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Has a collaborative work ethic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interest in motion/video design&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-JM1&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/70jrfYSxKC4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3845852&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Trading]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BitGo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.bitgo.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, Palo Alto, NYC, Seattle, Austin or Toronto - Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitGo is the leader in custody and security solutions with over $60B in assets under custody. Founded in 2013, BitGo is the first digital asset company to focus exclusively on serving institutional clients. In 2018, it launched BitGo Trust Company, the first qualified custodian purpose-built for storing digital assets and established BitGo New York Trust in 2021. BitGo also offers market leading trading, lending, and borrowing services and supports over 400 digital assets on its platform. BitGo provides the security and operational backbone for more than 500 institutional clients in 50 countries, including many of the world’s top cryptocurrency exchanges and platforms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitGo is looking for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Software Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to join our team and help us build new features and applications. BitGo processes a significant amount of cryptocurrency transactions so our applications need to be fast, accurate, scalable and secure. Our integrated platforms interact with a number of exchanges, agencies, and governments around the world, and we use the best technology the industry offers to build them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design and build strong, resilient, performant, and robust APIs, libraries, and services to power our trading platform&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own functionality and scalability features by taking responsibility from inception to deployment and customer integration&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expose and document functionality to the UI, third-party developers, and our internal and external tooling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate closely with all engineering teams and product managers to ensure consistency in understanding of technical requirements and overall work quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide mentorship to your peers in the broader engineering team through code reviews and education on best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Experience:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for teammates who share and practice our values: open communication, transparency, taking ownership, and a high level of craftsmanship. We are looking for coworkers who share our vision and mission: deliver trust in digital assets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Golang or similar backend languages like Java, C++, Python, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building trading systems, risk engines, or similar order placement systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with SQL databases like MySQL or Postgres&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Confident with RESTful API design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great with unit and functional testing and debugging&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in Git/GitHub and branching methodologies, code review tools, CI tools, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree in computer science, applied mathematics, or another technical discipline&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong interest in cryptocurrencies and blockchain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellence in data structures, algorithm design, problem solving, complexity analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work independently in a fast-paced environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 2 years of back-end, server-side software development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with microservices and service-oriented architectures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of and experience working in the financial industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with large-scale, real-time, and distributed applications with high performance requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with FIX&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with Docker and Kubernetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work full-stack and familiarity with React and GraphQL&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why Join BitGo?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Disrupting an industry takes vision, innovation, passion, technical chops, drive to deliver, collaboration, and execution. Join a team of great people who strive for excellence and personify our corporate values of ownership, craftsmanship, and open communication. We are looking for new colleagues who bring innovative ways of thinking and problem solving, and who want risks to be part of the team that changes the world’s financial markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Here are some of the benefits of working at BitGo:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive base salary, bonus and stock options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% company paid health insurance for employee, partner and dependents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Up to 5% 401k company match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paid parental leave, Paid vacation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Free commuter/parking pass; 5 min from Caltrain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Free custom lunches, dinners and snacks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Computer equipment and workplace furniture to suit your needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great colleagues and inspiring startup environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Benefits may vary based on location&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Cryptocurrencies are the most disruptive change the financial services industry has seen in years. Join us and you’ll be able to look back and say you were part of the team that transformed investing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yGR7NLjXslU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitgo/jobs/5862161002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175514/birgo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitgo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b720d671-6d88-4863-a59d-ea5d1c6feea8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BitGo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Technical Account Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[r3]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.r3.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>R3’s Professional Services is comprised of innovative problem-solvers and strategic, fast-moving engineers and consultants who collaborate with customers to solve their challenges and build business solutions. As part of the post-sales organisation, Professional Services is responsible for driving successful customer outcomes through supporting the design, build and deployment of solutions. This team provides you with the opportunity to solve real-world business and technical challenges with large global corporates, banks and startups across many industries – Financial Services, Real Estate, Energy, Digital Assets, Identity and Healthcare.</div><div>&nbsp;</div><br/>Responsibilities: <br/><li>Your mission as a Technical Account Manager (TAM) is to provide personalised support, deepen relationships with enterprise customers, and&nbsp;consult customers on the best use of Corda Enterprise&nbsp;software to increase value for their business use case.&nbsp;You will tailor support for each customer environment, facilitate cooperation with their other partners, and advocate on their behalf as their trusted technical advisor.</li><li>Research customer’s use-cases, to translate customer business requirements into technical solutions; get to know their workflows to grow the Corda implementation, take ownership of all technical and product initiatives </li><li>Establish a comprehensive understanding of customer solutions, architectural decisions, key constraints, and product development lifecycle.</li><li>Advocate for product enhancements with Product Management &amp; Engineering to help the customer succeed (work with customers and internal R3 teams to define and refine requirements).</li><li>Present to technical executives and directors on the Corda platform strategy, concepts, and roadmap</li><li>Establish regular cadence of meetings (virtually or in-person) with your customers to discuss the latest release of Corda, best practices in DLT, and migration to new version and new developments </li><li>Leverage the power of R3 to bring in experts from Professional Services, Sales, Product and our broader ecosystem to help drive better customer outcomes </li><li>Provide regular reports and reviews to key stakeholders and decision makers (internal and client)</li><li>Work with TAM leads to expand the service offering portfolio and improve processes </li><br/>Key Skills Required for the Role:<br/><li>4+ years of supporting pre/post-sales activity</li><li>Proven software development experience using Java or a JVM based language, anyone with a strong desire to learn Java or Kotlin is also considered. (An excellent opportunity for you to acquire new technical skills. )</li><li>Able to understand non-functional operational requirements</li><li>Understand how to convert business requirements into solution designs</li><li>Good people skills, with the ability to cope with ambiguity</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//player.vimeo.com/video/374680693" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/r3.com/9c309c43-dcf5-4dd7-8c0d-38a8fecd09e8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145208/r3_logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[r3@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[18dbe364-74c1-4303-b076-66cd4e239ce3]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[r3]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Social Media Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">We are looking for a crypto-native content publisher, who is also meticulous in the operational side of content management. This individual should be able to craft Social-Events and manage a content calendar.</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li><b>Content:</b> Cooperate with the existing Social-Media-Manager and supplement gap-contents to existing content-calendar.</li><li><b>Events: </b>Coordinate periodic social-sharing events on (Facebook/Twitter/Instagram/Reddit). Choose winners and distribute rewards. This will be a primary responsibility.</li><li><b>Ad Posting:</b> Coordinate with projects and post sponsored-posts at designated dates</li><li><b>Share Requests:</b> Accept requests from team members, craft content according to request, and share on social.</li><li><b>Launch Coordination:</b> Prepare to share content on a pre-determined timeline in order to simultaneously push launches.</li><li>Engage and build communities through one-on-one as well as one-to-many conversations.</li><li>Analyze social media landscape to supply actionable insight (in real-time) to both the social and greater marketing team with hot topics, breaking news, sentiment/market observations.</li><li>Innovate and implement test-and-learn strategies along with delivering results.</li><li>Measure, report, and analyze the performance of campaigns across channels and translate findings into actionable, data-driven recommendations in order to improve future performance.</li><li>Drive effective and creative social media campaigns, working cross-functionally with product, data, sales and design, and other teams.</li><li>Own and operate multiple official social media and signal channels, as well as the content strategy/output and results for each.</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>3~5 years experience in social media-related roles.</li><li>Native or Fluent English language is a MUST.</li><li>Experience in the blockchain/crypto space is a plus.A meme connoisseur and creator.</li><li>Keen sense and understanding of the crypto market in general.</li><li>Demonstrates a clear and concise style of communication, with a creative/fun spin when relevant.</li><li>Well-versed with Twitter, Facebook, Reddit, and Telegram.</li><li>Bonus if familiar with YouTube, TikTok, and Discord.</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/1fcbb2e5-f127-43d4-971d-2001c44b1e72/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[NFT Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As one of the largest and most trusted </span><b style="font-size: 11pt">digital asset platforms</b><span style="font-size: 11pt"> globally, we are empowering people to experience the life-changing potential of crypto.&nbsp;Trusted by over 8 million consumer and pro traders, institutions, and authorities worldwide - our unique combination of products, services, and global expertise is helping tip the scales towards mass crypto adoption.&nbsp;But we’re only just getting started. We want to be pioneers in crypto and add value to the everyday lives of billions. Now is not the time to sit on the sidelines. Join us to bring crypto to the world.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b>About the Role:</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11.5pt">Kraken is looking for a NFT Team Manager to head up a new team within Compliance. The individual chosen for this role should have the demonstrated ability to develop, communicate, and manage policies and procedures to various Client Engagement teams, lines of business and upper management, proactively identify risks factors associated with NFT Collections, manage and oversee reviews of NFT marketplace flagged content and support management as appropriate, and assess overall customer risk and regulatory requirements. </span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11.5pt">The candidate should have excellent oral and written communication skills and be able to communicate effectively between multiple teams in the organisation. They should be able to thrive in a fast-paced environment, and they are committed to the values of teamwork, integrity, and adaptability. </span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11.5pt">Additionally, they should display strong ability to manage a team of both senior and junior associates, assess production work and reviews, make recommendations and determinations, manage multiple work streams and duties.</span></div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Be the subject matter expert (SME) for Compliance and Operations related to NFT project listings, due diligence requirements for collections, regulatory compliance for NFTs, content moderation to ensure Kraken customers have the best in class NFT Marketplace experience.&nbsp;</li><li>Deep collaboration with Product teams to ensure that all compliance and content moderation requirements are met while developing seamless user journey</li><li>Collaborate with internal Compliance functions to ensure consistency and alignment within the <a href="http://department.Interact" class="postings-link">department.</a></li><li><a href="http://department.Interact" class="postings-link">Interact</a> with Compliance Officers and executive management in all subsidiaries to ensure regional regulations and expectations are met</li><li>Manage and address regulatory inquiries, examination deliverables, audit requests, and remediation needs, as <a href="http://necessary.Respond" class="postings-link">necessary.</a></li><li><a href="http://necessary.Respond" class="postings-link">Respond</a> to and manage client and internal departmental escalations and queries regarding NFT listing due diligence and content management procedures and <a href="http://policies.Evaluate" class="postings-link">policies.</a></li><li><a href="http://policies.Evaluate" class="postings-link">Evaluate</a> NFT Collections and form a recommendation on a case-by-case basis.&nbsp;</li><li>Develop and Manage Policies and Procedures related to the conducting and assessment of open source research and review related to the due diligence review process, content moderation strategy and <a href="http://standards.Manage" class="postings-link">standards.</a></li><li><a href="http://standards.Manage" class="postings-link">Manage</a> the DMCA.</li><li>Reporting and take down and relisting process.&nbsp;</li><li>Manage and track various communication channels and provide timely responses to all <a href="http://stakeholders.Identify" class="postings-link">stakeholders.</a></li><li><a href="http://stakeholders.Identify" class="postings-link">Identify</a> trends, patterns, and new regulatory proposals dynamically that could have a noteworthy impact on our team’s efficiency and develop workflow <a href="http://efficiencies.Familiarise" class="postings-link">efficiencies.</a></li><li><a href="http://efficiencies.Familiarise" class="postings-link">Familiarise</a> yourself with the inter-department <a href="http://responsibilities.Perform" class="postings-link">responsibilities.</a></li><li><a href="http://responsibilities.Perform" class="postings-link">Perform</a> due diligence checks on customers as <a href="http://required.Communicate" class="postings-link">required.</a></li><li><a href="http://required.Communicate" class="postings-link">Communicate</a> effectively to coordinate cross-functional <a href="http://projects.Perform" class="postings-link">projects.</a></li><li><a href="http://projects.Perform" class="postings-link">Perform</a> research in support of ad-hoc NFT related projects.</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>10 years management experience in Content Management, NFTs, Social Media or Cryptocurrency related <a href="http://industries.Deep" class="postings-link">industries.</a></li><li><a href="http://industries.Deep" class="postings-link">Deep</a> knowledge and experience in the NFT Marketplace Environment and Community, including an in-depth understanding of the technical aspects and overall general community culture.&nbsp;</li><li>Bachelor’s degree - Advanced degree a <a href="http://plus.Experience" class="postings-link">plus.</a></li><li><a href="http://plus.Experience" class="postings-link">Experience</a> with customer onboarding, KYC, CDD and customer risk rating and technologies and systems <a href="http://utilized.Executive" class="postings-link">utilised.</a></li><li><a href="http://utilized.Executive" class="postings-link">Executive</a> level communication and organisational <a href="http://skills.Proven" class="postings-link">skills.</a></li><li><a href="http://skills.Proven" class="postings-link">Proven</a> track record and experience working with, and technical implementations of, multiple vendors related to product listings, KYC, content moderation <a href="http://management.Deep" class="postings-link">management.</a></li><li><a href="http://management.Deep" class="postings-link">Deep</a> familiarity with regulatory requirements and regulatory bodies in Europe and US, and other jurisdictions, including banking, capital markets, money transmission, marketing and <a href="http://communications.Demonstrated" class="postings-link">communications.</a></li><li><a href="http://communications.Demonstrated" class="postings-link">Demonstrated</a> ability to author detailed business requirements and effectively communicate with engineering/technology teams.&nbsp;</li><li>Prior success in project management and driving cross functional teams to execute and deliver on strategically important <a href="http://initiatives.Quantitative" class="postings-link">initiatives.</a></li><li><a href="http://initiatives.Quantitative" class="postings-link">Quantitative</a> analysis and decision making.</li><div>#Remote #FullyRemote</div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/23bf92e5-7786-4b49-8bd2-0c0943a04674/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
