<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Content Marketing Manager  (Crystal Blockchain, Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitfury.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;div id=&quot;header&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at Bitfury:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is a leading emerging technologies company. &amp;nbsp;At Bitfury, you can build the solutions of the future, with the most significant technologies of the millennium, in a modern and flexible workplace. We work a bit faster, and a bit smarter, so we can make the world a bit better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of Working at Bitfury:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Experiences &amp;amp; Global Impacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is an international company with 200+ team members in more than 16 countries. No matter your assignment, your work will support global technology initiatives and best-in-class security operations in North America, Asia and Europe, as well as help us fulfil our mission to make the world more trusted and secure.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building the Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe big data, artificial intelligence, blockchain technology, tokenized economies and cryptocurrencies are the future of our digital, global economy. Bitfury is building this future through our products that offer digitised security, asset management, government services and more. We consider ourselves first and foremost a technology company. We are a diversified organisation, with operations across multiple facets of the AI, blockchain, and digital currency sectors. If you are passionate about emerging technologies, you can build your future at Bitfury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Your Career&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is growing fast and looking for the next generation of leaders and entrepreneurs to help us. At Bitfury, you will be expected to create the future – not just execute it. If you are a self-starter, driven and collaborative team member, you can create a dynamic future for yourself and your career at Bitfury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modern Workplace with Intelligent Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury lets you work in the way you need to work to make your work faster, smarter and better. We will give you the resources you need to succeed – competitive pay and benefits, educational support, intellectual challenges, professional advancement, personal accommodations including remote work, and more. We pride ourselves on being less bureaucratic and a lot more impactful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start-up Culture with Established Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with the world’s leading experts and engineers, you will have the opportunity at Bitfury to pursue results that will power your success as well as lead to the adoption of game-changing technologies. Our teams work every day to make the impossible possible, to change the game, to be agile and effective, and most of all – to empower the rest of the world to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ersonal and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rofessional&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;haracteristics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We at Bitfury ensure our team members possess the ability to think out of the box and make the impossible possible. We are self-motivated and result-oriented, and we have an “owner of the company” mindset. We are constantly self-educating and developing. We are able to work in a team and collaborate. We have a “do good” mindset and are not afraid to dream big. And of course, we always deliver in time what we promised and with extreme attention to detail — because if we are not able to do the little things right, we will never be able to do big things right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a talented Content Marketing Manager to join our Crystal team: &lt;a href=&quot;https://crystalblockchain.com/&quot;&gt;https://crystalblockchain.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties and responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Content creation, editing, and management:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Long and short-form content creation for various channels including the blog, social media, ads, website, decks, one-pagers, reports, questionnaires, applications, and other various types of content (training will be provided as needed by the Head of Content).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will be specifically responsible for PR content as we expand our publicity and outreach.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;May assist the Head of Content in proofreading and editing third-party created content.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Occasionally may help with preparing content briefs for freelance writers as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist the HoC with the preparation of a comprehensive content calendar, especially for PR.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Company culture and work environment:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As a remote-first company, you can work from anywhere, but to join weekly company calls and meet daily deadlines, it may be easiest if you’re in a European timezone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Essential:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fluent level of English (Current C2 level in written English).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Creative outlook supported by strong writing skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in proofreading, editing, and reviewing content essential.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to go between long-form content and short-form copy as needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Can work independently but can also follow a brief to the letter when needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working knowledge of best practices for PR and third-party media content.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Desirable:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of blockchain/ fintech/ high-tech industries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Research, strategic, and planning skills related to content marketing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with WordPress and other digital platforms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/DtkFJoj24rE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitfury/jobs/5718160002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145862/bitfury.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitfury@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bff43dfe-8ac3-4757-8a78-7559c9e9e327]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Revenue Accounting Operations Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Ripple is building out its Revenue Accounting Operations function to further accelerate growth by operationalizing and optimizing RippleNet’s strategy across current and emerging products. Reporting to our Revenue Manager, the Revenue Accounting Operations Manager will be responsible for refining Ripple’s order to collect processes, including contract review for billings, collections, and reporting on all bookings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You will partner cross-functionally with Sales, Legal, Customer Success, and Finance teams to ensure seamless communication around ongoing customer contracts and operational execution for each customer. You should have excellent communication, organizational, and analytical skills. Additionally, you should have a genuine interest in the blockchain industry and a desire to understand the RippleNet ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU&#39;LL DO:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage all product vertical’s customer onboarding and build out a scalable, automated, and collaborative processes for software and cryptocurrency customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide guidance and leadership through automation and scalability of billing and collection projects&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Treasury and Accounting Operations on weekly cash and cryptocurrency forecasts and reporting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Review new customer contracts, with the responsibility of owning the resolution of any operational risks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Sales Operations and Customer Partnerships and Success teams on pricing and billing strategy, contract management, and customer tracking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build out RippleNet billable transaction volume data reporting in collaboration with cross-functional teams to optimize, automate and scale&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage and continue to enhance monthly revenue reporting package to C‐Suite leadership team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Document and continuously update desktop procedures for billing and revenue accounting operations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE&#39;RE LOOKING FOR:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor&#39;s degree in a related field (Accounting or Finance)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum of 5‐6 years of practical experience, including experience in revenue operations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to partner effectively with cross‐functional stakeholders and influence decisions and operations successfully across the organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to effectively drive multiple projects to successful completion at the same time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Data‐driven and are not afraid to dig into the details to find the best solution while working in a diverse environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency in Excel, Powerpoint, SQL, Salesforce, Intacct, Tesorio or similar platforms strongly preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our UK/EU applicant privacy notice &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3686890?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Manager, People - HR]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxful]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://paxful.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Paxful&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxful is the people-powered marketplace for money transfers with anyone, anywhere, at any time. Imagine a world where everyone has equal access to finance, no matter who they are, or where they’re from. We&#39;re building it. Our mission is to empower the forgotten four billion unbanked, so they have control of their money in a way they&#39;ve never had before.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working across three offices in different time zones, the Paxful team serves our amazing community of 4 million strong. We build for people, not profits, and consider ourselves to be everyday heroes who don’t wear capes or masks. That’s why we launched Built with Bitcoin, a charitable initiative that aims to build 100 schools, water facilities, and entrepreneurial incubators in emerging markets all over the world. We want to show that bitcoin can have a positive impact and make real changes in the lives of people everywhere.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working alongside our global People team, our HR Manager will be responsible for overseeing and executing all the functions related to HR in the United States, including workforce planning, organizational development, and policies &amp;amp; procedures.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role will be based in the USA, preferably in the New York Metropolitan area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage the full employee lifecycle, including but not limited to: recruiting, onboarding, keeping HR records for all US-based employees, and offboarding&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design and implement systems and processes to support a fast-growing international organization including workforce planning, and performance management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Promote HR initiatives and programs that align with corporate goals and values&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure accuracy of all data entry, process flows, background checks, BambooHR entries and changes, health-check administration, processing employment contracts and contract changes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Oversee and ensure HR programs are comprehensive, competitive, and align with business goals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive learning and development initiatives, and other organizational development projects including culture, team-building and related functions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partnering with hiring managers to ensure organizational structure supports business needs, growth and scale&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage recruiting efforts in the US, including &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;communication with recruitment agencies, screening candidates, and supporting hiring manager interviews&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who You Are&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You should have a passion for HR operations and strong attention to detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are a people first leader that is excellent at building relationships with partners and various teams across the company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We’re Looking For&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 4 years of human resources / HRBP work experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track-record of scaling HR globally in a tech start-up environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with BambooHR, Trinet, Jira, Confluence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Greenhouse is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive insurance plans, commuter benefits, flexible spending account, and 401(k) with 4% company matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible working hours and generous paid time off&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gym membership, massage, chiropractor, or other reimbursements (personal training, dance classes, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Learning and development reimbursement (including online courses, certifications, conferences, seminars, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;One day a year to volunteer and serve your community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Parental leave, including a one-time bonus to support a newborn, adoption, or foster placement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxful&#39;s COVID response: remote work, company-wide online events and weekly meal credits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity &amp;amp; Inclusion at Paxful&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Paxful, we know that a diverse workforce fuels our individual and collective success. We encourage applicants of different backgrounds, cultures, genders, experiences, abilities and perspectives to apply. We are actively working to increase the diversity of experience and perspectives on our team and are looking for someone who can help continue to lead that process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EEOC and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accommodations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxful is committed to diversity in the workplace and we’re proud to be an equal opportunity employer. We do not hire on basis of race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, citizenship, or any other basis protected by local, state or federal law.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re also committed to providing accommodations to people with disabilities. If you need any kind of accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, you can reach out to careers@paxful.com and let us know how we can best help you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other privacy laws may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full Privacy Notice is available at https://paxful.com/privacy-notice. By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/JvYoQb4qyg4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/paxful/jobs/4830562003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/353334/paxful-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxful@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[0cd1eea2-97ef-4cc0-9d15-01fa1a8ce9ca]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxful]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Ops Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[PayStand]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paystand.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Scotts Valley, California, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paystand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paystand is a hungry, fast-growing, Series-C startup with three locations! Nestled in the beautiful Santa Cruz mountains, just south of Silicon Valley is where we started. We have our offices in amazing and historic Guadalajara Mexico and Salt Lake City with the dramatic backdrops of the mountains of Utah.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to unlock capital efficiency for enterprise businesses through our transformative&amp;nbsp;“Payments as a Service” platform. Our smart billing and payment network uses revolutionary internet, blockchain, and FinTech services to digitize receivables, automate processing, reduce time-to-cash, lower transaction costs, and produce new revenue for our clients. Paystand is venture-backed, having been consistently recognized as one of the top innovators in FinTech, and fastest growing companies in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paystand is looking for a Marketing Ops Specialist to join us in creating the future of commercial payments infrastructure. This is an opportunity to work for one of the hottest, early-stage companies in financial technology. You will be a part of a growing team that is fundamentally re-architecting global payments in the digital era with core blockchain technology. We are a team of disruptors and technologists paving the way for a new financial system, with a passion to bring more openness, transparency, and health to the global economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role At A Glance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The role of our Marketing Operations Specialist is to manage the funnel and attribution process that is used across the organization. In this role, you will drive insights into campaign performance by building and managing workflows across our Hubspot Marketing automation platforms and CRM. You will have the opportunity to work with business and technical teams across the three offices to make an impact on marketing analytics and influence the operations roadmap.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a high-impact opportunity to drive improvements in internal process and funnel velocity that lead directly to pipeline and growth.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work closely with Marketing and Sales leaders to define the strategy on funnel and attribution and drive ongoing system improvements by conducting check-ins with key stakeholders, troubleshoot roadblocks, and develop creative solutions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design and develop workflows across Hubspot marketing automation platform to identify and track a lead’s funnel and buyer journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage multi-touch funnel and implement roadmap by working with internal and third-party vendors / agencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Optimize pipeline attribution process across the tech stack to scale with new requirements defined by the leadership team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the lead journey from data ingestion to routing ensuring funnel and attribution is credited appropriately.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fix bugs/issues as they arise and work with Marketing / Sales teams to train on processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Conduct data analysis to track the marketing funnel and produce meaningful and actionable insights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications and Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years in marketing operations, sales operations, or business operations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency with Hubspot, marketing automation, and any response management tool is a must.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage multiple priorities in fast-paced environment, work collaboratively with cross-functional teams, and ensure high quality deliverables with high attention to details.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Someone who flourishes when given responsibility and a sense of ownership.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven collaboration, interpersonal, problem solving, and verbal &amp;amp; written communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BA or BS degree in business, marketing, or technical discipline.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Salary + competitive equity in a high growth-stage startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401k&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock Options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible and Generous PTO (vacations)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Opportunity for advancement &amp;amp; growth in a rapidly expanding team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentorship, learning &amp;amp; education programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Smart, motivated team that likes to have fun&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mission-driven culture, where your work matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We understand that no candidate is perfectly qualified for any job. Experience comes in different forms; many skills are transferable; and passion goes a long way. Even more important than your resume is a clear demonstration of dedication, impact, and the ability to thrive in a fluid and collaborative environment. We want you to learn new things in this role, and we encourage you to apply if your experience is close to what we’re looking for. We also know that diversity of background and thought makes for better problem solving and more creative thinking, which is why we&#39;re dedicated to adding new perspectives to the team. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Availability &lt;/strong&gt;- Bay area/Scotts Valley, CA.&amp;nbsp;Salt Lake City area, UT. Guadalajara, MX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(This is not a remote position)***No recruiters please***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only English resumes will be considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/z5Oi5cFLSmM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://paystand.com/job-listing/?gh_jid=4832055003&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/188126/Paystand.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paystand@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9713c611-4d29-448b-a71c-3c8d3ca06a70]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[PayStand]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Product Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tron]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tron.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitTorrent offers a unique and compelling work environment. We are proponents of the open Internet and we serve one of the largest user demographics in history. We take these responsibilities seriously and hire accordingly. We work with only the brightest engineers and the most talented business people we can find. Everyone on our team is here to do meaningful work with broad reaching impact. We have a fun yet challenging work environment that fosters diversity, creativity, and teamwork.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a driven, community-centric, and technically savvy Product Manager to manage the execution and roadmap for a new revolutionary broadcasting product.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ideal candidate will be a critical thinker, who is organized, and collaborative with the ability to break down complicated projects and see them through to completion. This person will be just as comfortable digging in to conduct technical analysis on complex challenges as they are with cross-functional project planning and streamlining processes. Aligned closely with the Engineering Managers and leads to create greater visibility and control over technical project execution, constantly communicating changes, adapting, and hyper prioritizing. A key focus will be on delivering a world-class product to the end users, developing a community of streamers, advocating for the best UX.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In this role you will&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define key features and experiences, and facilitate their launch.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and maintain a prioritized product roadmap, getting buy-in from stakeholders at all levels of the organization including Marketing, Engineering, and BitTorrent’s leadership team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serve as an excellent cross-functional partner, working with other product managers, designers, and marketers to execute cross-functional initiatives that&amp;nbsp; drive business metrics and build our brand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To thrive in this role, you’ll need&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience in Product Management:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; you have launched and managed at least one web or mobile product: determining needs, aligning priorities, defining requirements, delivering to the market, and ensuring value post launch. Experience in a two-sided marketplace business is a bonus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Love of agile product development: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re comfortable with operating an agile product and engineering team that spans the globe. Familiarity with agile rituals and excitement for driving an ambitious agile team roadmap is a must.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sound business judgement and an eye for detail:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; You obsess over the quality of the product. You are detail-oriented, organized, and able to quickly prioritize while managing multiple projects and responsibilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Customer-centric user experience sensibility: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a deep affinity for your users and are adept at analyzing, understanding and segmenting customers and translating these findings into user experience requirements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Adaptability and love of learning: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You possess the ability to learn on the fly and quickly adapt to a changing (growing) environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excellent interpersonal and communication skills:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; You have a strong executive presence for interfacing with customers, peers, colleagues, and executives. You’re able to distill from complexity the essence at the heart of competing philosophies and approaches and gracefully corral savvy stakeholders towards harmonious solutions. You’re able to succinctly articulate goals, progress, and priorities to all stakeholders in written, verbal, and presentation formats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven track record in managing a product and business analysis in an agile environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2-3 years experience in Product/Project Management or similar roles (Software Engineering manager or lead, Product Owner, Scrum Master). Certifications are welcome but not required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A development or technical background is preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding written and verbal communication skills with an emphasis on communicating both technical solutions to internal and external audiences; as well as being able to communicate the business value. Must be very good at writing clear problem and outcome oriented requirements and user stories.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent time management and organizational skills with the ability to handle multiple projects simultaneously with minimal supervision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Data analysis skills - querying data and analyzing for insights.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong collaboration focus, ownership, urgency, and drive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Come change how the world works&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At BitTorrent&amp;nbsp; you’ll make a real difference in the world, rolling up your sleeves to help reinvent how the world works. As a major player in one of the most exciting and fastest growing markets on the planet, you’ll join a team that’s leading the charge in online work – creating new freedom and opportunity for businesses and freelancers alike. In short, you’ll change lives, which will do wonders for your career, self-esteem and karma.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/gU6Jfz2jOHA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/rainberry/jobs/5732426002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180174/300px-Tron_logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tron@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f44423ad-b7da-465f-8880-ebeb8930922a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tron]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[SEO Copywriter (Russian)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKEx]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.okex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About OKEx:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKEx is a world-leading digital asset trading platform, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKEx provides hundreds of token &amp;amp; futures trading pairs to help traders to optimize their strategy. We are also one of the top digital asset trading platforms by trading volume, serving millions of users in over 100 countries. OKEx derivatives remains a top-notch venue globally and has a daily volume of approximately $10 billion and is widely recognized as the golden standard in the industry. We believe the blockchain technology will eliminate barriers to transactions, increase the efficiency of transactions across society, and eventually have a significant impact on the global economy. We strive to make innovative achievements that change the world and never stop to improve on our customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a highly motivated and result-oriented mixture of specialists with different backgrounds. What we value the most is the ability to learn, speak up and to collaborate. We are open, curious and we love to test even the craziest ideas and share our knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a tech-savvy Russian content writer to produce and manage stellar and unique content for both Google and Yandex. As a part of the team, you will be responsible for helping define the content strategy, write SEO copy for landing pages, perform keyword and&amp;nbsp; industry research and coordinate with various internal stakeholders to collect info needed and help create successful landing pages to help our user base.&amp;nbsp; We strongly believe that SEO is a crucial lever for our growth strategy; the topic has full support from top management including funding for tools and infrastructure. To be successful you will need to gain a significant understanding about the blockchain space and come up with innovative content ideas and write engaging copy to excite the community and help translate content into landing pages. You need to be a passionate content writer and creator who can think out of the box and be able to successfully convey what&#39;s unique about our brand to both technical and non technical audiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in building our SEO content strategy for our new landing pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform in depth analysis and keyword research to help unlock growth across our verticals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proofread and write content for blog posts, ads, press releases, articles, infographics, studies, website, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform basic SEO keyword research and incorporate the findings in the copy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce ideas for new content formats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Measure content performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce relevant content targeting both technical and non technical audiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research industry trends to gain a good technical understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Russian (written and spoken)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Journalism or Communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years experience as a copywriter and a portfolio with published content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have minimum 3 years experience in the tech space and very good technical understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain &amp;amp; crypto experience is a STRONG plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years working with SEO &amp;amp; Google Analytics is a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/x9kSkBMcOuo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okex/jobs/4839070003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175406/okex.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bcbc2afc-a2fd-45d8-bba3-e7ce4b53b3d8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKEx]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Social Media Lead - Global Corporate Comms]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing. We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual, and we want to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno welcomes crypto lovers and crypto newbies. You - just like everyone in the world - are on your own unique crypto-learning journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a mission-driven cryptocurrency company that is building more open and equal access to the future of money. You don&#39;t have to know lots about crypto to be interested in joining us, you just have to feel that upgrading the world to a fairer financial system matters, and that you&#39;d like to be part of this global change. We&#39;re a passionate and committed team taking on a challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people working together with unusual skill, focus and determination. We need the best team on board for our mission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If that sounds like a culture you&#39;d thrive in, then we are excited to hear from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno means moon in Esperanto, we chose the name because at night, wherever you are in the world, you look up at the same moon. We believe in the power of working together, as one team, across borders, with clear focus and shared purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our popular mobile app and website helps people around the world grow and manage their money using the world&#39;s most mature cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum and USDC. We&#39;ve processed over $ 21 billion to date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Over 9 million customers across 40 countries have chosen to hold their crypto wallets on Luno because we offer a delightfully simple experience and bank-grade security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re part of the Digital Currency Group, named in 2021 as one of TIME magazine&#39;s 100 Most Influential Companies, in the “Disruptors” category alongside Tesla, AirBnB, SpaceX, Peloton. TIME noted that DCG is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/collection/time100-companies/5953752/digital-currency-group/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;“mainstreaming cryptocurrency”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re proud to be one of the world&#39;s most international cryptocurrency teams, with colleagues from 43 different nationalities working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria, Australia and Singapore. Financial inclusion is part of our mission, but on a deeper level, inclusion is a way of life, and a way of work for us. It is part of who we are as a company, and a group of human individuals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role in a nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will be a lead resource on the global team at Luno which is responsible for all social media content distribution, community management, and reporting across multiple regions and on various platforms. Your chief responsibilities will be in curating content for Luno’s corporate brand on social channels, as well as engaging as Luno on social media so as to establish the brand as a trusted thought leader and employer of choice. Whether it be industry thinkpiece content, CEO amplification, engineering and product content, or employer branding, you will need to liaise with internal stakeholders to bring this content to life. You will report to the global head of social engagement, and be a part of the global social engagement team, stationed across many continents.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In addition to this, you will be required to take charge of the team for approximately 4 months when the head of the department will be on maternity leave. This will mean managing the regional team leads of our general social media brand presence, nurturing strong relationships with local and global stakeholders, and being answerable for the success of Luno’s social media channels during this time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deeply understanding the global corporate brand communication goals and using all moments of community engagement as an opportunity to further them both.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be the voice of the Luno corporate brand across all relevant social media channels. You will be our brand’s voice on all things crypto and Luno in order to drive an increase in corporate brand awareness through thought leadership, position Luno as an employer of choice, and maintain healthy online relationships with press and news contacts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will respond to all incoming queries, requests and complaints on our corporate comms channels, tailor responses to each individual that is engaged with, offering two-way genuine communication, follow crisis comms procedures should an incident arise, create synergy between the content we publish and the engagement in the comments, and collaborate with your peers and across the timezones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with global and local stakeholders to help craft the content calendar for the channels in your remit, manage publishing across these channels, and compile regular and ad hoc social media reports on wins &amp;amp; misses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Share best practices across your team as a senior member of the team, exploring new tools and processes, helping to develop efficient workflow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage the social engagement team as a maternity cover, and generally serve as a team 2iC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal Lunaut for this role will have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A wealth of experience in social media management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong people management skills and leadership competency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using social media engagement, reporting, and listening tools.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A wealth of experience and knowledge on social media best practices, trends, and post formats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good spelling and grammar, with a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; keen eye that pays attention to detail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written communication skills, with an understanding of how to translate complex topics and technologies into easy to understand messaging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Empathy and the ability to relate to others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good time management, knowing how to prioritise important and urgent matters to get the most out of a busy team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Initiative, knowing how to problem solve and think quickly on their feet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to work well in a team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno is a ‘remote but reachable’ company! At Luno, we trust that people can do their work effectively anywhere and provide Lunauts with the flexibility to decide where they do their best work. For some of us, that’s at home for the majority of the time, for others, that might mean joining other Lunauts in person at one of our Luno workspaces more often. Luno is built on our relationships, so we still value in-person connection and have a minimum expectation of spending time in person once a quarter. So as long as you are based in one country with a Luno workspace, we want to hear from you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not negatively discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3698248?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Compliance Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tron]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tron.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are expanding our world-class exchange and are seeking a qualified legal and compliance professional to support rapid business growth. The Compliance Manager will support the compliance function for the exchange. This role offers a unique opportunity to develop and drive the strategy, framework and execution of a compliance program in a demanding and ever changing Cryptocurrency landscape.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding and ensuring compliance with industry rules, regulations and trends in the cryptocurrency industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assisting in the direction and development of compliance with laws, regulatory requirements, policies, and procedures systematically across our exchange&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitating information requests from state and federal governments, partners, and other regulatory bodies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Cross functional support for the Compliance team as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with key stakeholders within the business, including Finance and Legal functions, to manage and meet all regulatory deadlines in a timely manner&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide input as it relates to updates required to internal policy and procedure based on changes to existing regulation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Remain up-to-date on industry-related best practices and enforcement activities and act as an advisor to the executive team and other partners to roll out and manage adjustments as required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5-8+ years of compliance (and/or legal) expertise in the crypto industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Prior experience successfully engaging with government and regulatory bodies&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Professional or personal experience working in cryptocurrency including the ability to speak intelligently about how the industry functions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Desire and drive to help build a Compliance program capable of supporting the growth and scale of a revolutionary company in the crypto space&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven experience troubleshooting and discovering solutions quickly and effectively with exemplary written and verbal communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/gU6Jfz2jOHA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/rainberry/jobs/5735415002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180174/300px-Tron_logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tron@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f44423ad-b7da-465f-8880-ebeb8930922a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tron]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ankr]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ankr.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Amsterdam, North Holland, Netherlands]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>ABOUT ANKR</p><p>Ankr provides Web3 infrastructure for easy, accessible and affordable deployment of blockchain nodes, API’s, decentralized staking infrastructure and Layer 2 scaling solutions, designed to lower the entry barrier for everyday people, enterprises, and developers to contribute to blockchain ecosystems. Check us out at <a href="https://www.ankr.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://www.ankr.com/</a></p><p><br>Ankr was founded in 2017 in Berkeley, California. Its founding team and headquarters are based in San Francisco. Ankr’s distributed team of 50+ people operates from offices in San Francisco, Shanghai, Moscow, and Amsterdam.<br></p><p>Responsibilities:</p><ul> <li>Design, code and implement business applications</li> <li>Integrate blockchains with our platform</li> <li>Work with APIs and microservices</li> <li>Design and verify cryptographic protocols deployed on the blockchain</li> <li>Define requirements, prototype and design new features for product users</li> <li>Effectively communicate technical details via documentation and demonstration</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>Proven track record of developing modern, secure, scalable complex applications</li> <li>Practical experience with crypto tokenomics, blockchain consensus protocols, P2P networks, cryptographic principles, key management, encryption algorithms</li> <li>Ability to use <a href="https://web3.foundation/about/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Web3 tech stack</a> </li> <li>Familiarity or ability to use Solidity, EVM or Polkadot Substrate</li> <li>Back-end: GoLang (Go) (or C++/Rust)</li> <li>Great listener and communicator</li> <li>Bilingual or high fluency in English</li> <li>Leadership and teamwork skills</li> <li>Able to provide open source code samples</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/ankr/j/F6B8ACECFD/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/746707/ankr-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ankr@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3b58522a-6fba-41ac-b017-94bbed42523c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ankr]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crawler Development Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Asia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Participate in the design and development of crawler systems, capture and analyze multi-platform information, and improve and enhance crawler efficiency.</li><li>esearch various anti-crawling strategies, quickly solve various technical problems, and monitor crawler progress and early warning processing in real time.</li><li>Collaborate with the big data team to manage, analyze, analyze, and apply results.</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Solid foundation in Python or Java, familiar with multi-process and multi-thread programming.</li><li>Familiar with common crawler frameworks Scrapy, Selenium, Webmagic, Puppeteer/Pyppeteer, etc., and have a strong enthusiasm for new knowledge and technology.</li><li>In-depth understanding of HTTP and various login authentication mechanisms can solve problems such as image verification code/slider/account restriction/ip restriction.</li><li>Familiar with common anti-climbing strategies, experience in JS anti-climbing, APP anti-climbing, packet capture analysis, anti-climbing strategy detection, reverse and other fields is preferred.</li><li>Have a strong sense of responsibility and teamwork spirit, clear thinking, good communication skills and technical learning skills.</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/45a9783e-a99f-48ab-9d4a-887ddd5f1042/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Designer - Contract Position]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kiva]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.kiva.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[U.S Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kiva (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://kiva.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;kiva.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;) &lt;/span&gt;is an international nonprofit with a mission to expand financial access to help underserved communities thrive. We run a global marketplace platform to crowdfund microloans for financially excluded entrepreneurs, farmers and students around the world. &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Through Kiva Capital, we serve as a bridge between large scale impact first investors and underserved populations. Our digital identity platform enables borrowers who don’t have a track record with traditional financial institutions to record and verify their financial history and gain access to less costly mainstream financial markets. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our organization combines the culture and technological passion of an internet start-up with the compassion and empathy of a non-profit to create impact and opportunity at global scale. &lt;/span&gt;Since 2005, we have raised more than $1.66 billion in loan capital for 4.1 million borrowers in 77 countries. Our lenders fund over $10 million in loans every month. With offices in San Francisco, Portland, New York, Nairobi, and Bangkok, Kiva&#39;s team includes 100+ employees and 400+ volunteers worldwide. Our team is growing as we pursue exciting new opportunities to create a financially inclusive world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role overview:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is for a 4 - 6 month, remote contract position working for the Creative Studio at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kiva.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kiva&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; (kiva.org) - starting as soon as feasible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Contract Senior Designer, you’ll partner with Kiva’s Creative Studio team. The Creative Studio designs, writes and executes marketing campaigns to drive awareness of Kiva and acquisition of new lenders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Senior Designer/ Contractor will work directly with the Creative Director. You’ll also work closely with other designers and writers on the Studio team, as well as cross-functionally with the Marketing and Content teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At this time, we can only consider applicants with authorization to work in the United States on a permanent, full-time basis; unfortunately we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key responsibilities include:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop concepts for, and design creative, as part of our Tentpole and Evergreen campaigns. Campaign elements include email, social media posts, web and mobile UX, landing pages, and other channels as they are needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bring to life the Kiva story and develop communications that engage consumers with emotive design,&amp;nbsp; while driving acquisition of new lenders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work collaboratively with other members of the creative team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Absorb Kiva Brand style guide and design within those guidelines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create engaging animations for campaign elements and catalog them in Google Drive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work within our Project Management tool to complete tasks on time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work on multiple campaigns and deliverables at once with ease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Regularly bring new ideas to the team, have a curious mindset, and a desire to always improve our creative.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a small team, the Senior Designer Contractor needs to actively look for places to help others and be willing to jump in on tasks when asked for help.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help mentor other designers on the team, providing feedback and guidance based on your experiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5-7 years of experience designing marketing creative at an agency or in-house creative studio.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to decipher a brief and convert that into compelling, succinct designs/ concepts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with documentary-style/human-centric storytelling creative/ emotive design.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A clear understanding of advertising/marketing/ direct response design best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with designing a variety of channels - social, email, website, mobile, landing pages with a thorough understanding of best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong proficiency in designing in Figma.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using Google Suite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A curious nature (ask questions and learn).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ideally 30-40 hrs/week with some flexibility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A competitive hourly rate paid on a monthly billing cycle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully remote working, anywhere within the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An opportunity to improve real lives, solve hard problems, and change the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Friendly, supportive, and adventurous environment with a team of engaged colleagues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Opportunities to connect with and learn from colleagues and partners around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When applying:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please submit a resume or LinkedIn (or other) profile that showcases your work history and experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please include samples of relevant work that you have done - samples that showcase how you would be a good fit for working on Kiva campaigns.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A diverse and inclusive workplace where we learn from each other is an integral part of Kiva&#39;s culture. We actively welcome people of different backgrounds, experiences, abilities and perspectives. We are an equal opportunity employer and a great place to work. Join us and help us achieve our mission!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We will only accept applications directly from candidates. Kiva will not be responsible for any recruiting agency fees, absent a formal agreement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/IEdy6XHkd9k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/kivaorg/jobs/3714314?gh_jid=3714314&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194099/kiva.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kiva@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[12467ec7-a781-4b48-abdb-bfbbc2a9cc79]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kiva]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Account Executive, Public Sector, Nordics]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Copenhagen, Denmark | Aarhus, Denmark]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The sales team responsible for our Nordic&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Law Enforcement / Central Government&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; customers is driven by our mission to make the world a safer place by tracking and investigating activities that involve cryptocurrency like human trafficking, terrorist financing, and money-laundering. We’re experts on the “why” and the “how” with deep relationships and knowledge of navigating government sales processes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Account Executives are servant leaders who can quickly establish trust and build strong relationships with the Public Sector stakeholders, tailoring their sales approach to their needs, and evangelizing Chainalysis solutions in a compelling yet approachable way. We measure success by the attainment of assigned quota, accuracy of forecasting, and the growth of accounts in your region. They are experts at navigating complex sales cycles. and still enjoy the thrill creating a calculated account plan and then closing a deal. We measure your success by your ability to accurately forecast revenue and hit (read: exceed) quotas and the engagement of your team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve upskilled the team’s ability to drive sales wins by participating in and leading client and prospect meetings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Stakeholders across the sales teams and rest of the company trust you and are eager to support and provide resources to your team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve built transparent and valuable relationships with your team and have developed an effective and efficient strategy for recruiting, hiring, and training new Account Executives on the sales motion at Chainalysis.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your team has a reliable cadence for rhythm for forecast meetings and each team member’s forecast is accurate and documented in Salesforce.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your team’s closure rates have increased and customer churn has decreased because of your direct coaching and mentorship.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Senior sales management can trust and rely on your forecasts and sales activity to inform the overall sales strategy across the business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You know the intricacies of your teams’ sales activity and track the results to inform your forecasts and individual development plans.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Recent experience managing and closing complex software sales within Public Sector customers in any of the Nordic markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing the sales cycle from mission/program manager to agency leadership&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong relationships in the System Integrator and Defense community&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Key industry knowledge and ability to effectively articulate the Chainalysis value proposition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track record of over-achieving quota (top 10-20% of company) in past positions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to negotiate pricing, terms and conditions and other concessions in complex, multi-year sales agreements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;History of scaling and coaching high-performing and diverse sales teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Financial Intelligence, Blockchain, Cyber Security, and/or Cryptocurrency technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-MJ1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yNpNz-FvSYQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5742950002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Employee Relations Manager (EMEA)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 16px">Seeking an experienced ER Manager o take ownership for the company’s EMEA and global workplace investigations, performance improvement plan process/policy, and our separation process/policy, including enhancing our exit interview data collection and utilization. The ER Manager will serve as the point of escalation for our HR Generalists, HR BPs, and business leaders on sensitive personnel issues, as well to provide expert level advice and guidance. The ER Manager will have the opportunity to:&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities <br/><li>Provide expert level guidance and advice to HR colleagues, business unit heads, and other leaders within the Company on a wide variety of employee relation issues and workplace investigations</li><li>Develop and maintain all internal guides including people-manager and HR guidelines and checklists for separation procedures and policies, workplace investigations, and disciplinary and grievance processes, including liaison with Legal as needed, design the effective collection and analysis of Exit Interviews</li><li>Analyze and improve performance improvement plan processes and metrics&nbsp;</li><li>Develop and lead coaching sessions on conflict resolution, performance improvement plan communication, and more&nbsp;</li><li>Develop proactive policies for identifying,&nbsp; reporting on, and responding ton high risk/at-risk behavior in a global remote work environmentPartner with IT, Payroll, and Legal to enhance our offboarding procedures and ensure they are seamless and secure</li><li>Contribute to the development, maintenance, and interpretation of the Company’s HR policies and practices, incorporating knowledge of EMEA employment laws and regulations</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>8+ years of relevant Human Resources experience ideally focused on employee relations, employment law, or HRBP/People Partner experiences&nbsp;</li><li>Mastery of state and federal employment law with a strong working knowledge of employment regulations in a variety of international locations&nbsp;</li><li>Stellar project management skills with exceptional attention to detail and discipline to organize and prioritizeExcellent communication (both written and verbal) and negotiation skills</li><li>Handles sensitive information with the utmost discretion and maintains confidentialityExperience working with employees and contractors</li><li>Ability to manage multiple critical priorities/projects without losing attention to detail or a positive attitude</li><li>Completely at ease in an ever changing fast paced ambiguous environmentExtremely flexible, open-minded, and creative when it comes to developing and maintaining HR protocols</li><li>Relentlessly devoted to the ‘people experience’ in all things&nbsp;Extremely tech-savvy with an appreciation for privacy, security, “crypto values”, sound money, and can get along well with other Krakenites&nbsp;</li><div><span style="font-size: 15px">Location Tagging: #EU</span></div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/a8127268-0ca5-4820-a8e2-e09f38d11153/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
