<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Wyre]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.sendwyre.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, California, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p><strong>Wyre is on a mission to bring crypto to the masses.</strong><br></p><p>To accomplish this mission, we’ve built a simple set of tools that allow developers to materialize their projects. Our fiat-to-crypto Checkout gateway is now being used by hundreds of applications (like MetaMask, Opera, Brave, and BRD) to offer the easiest way to convert card payments into crypto. Our flexible White-Label Payment APIs (Transfers API, Custody API, and Users API), enable developers to build e-wallets, merchant processing services, and money transfer platforms from the ground up.</p><p>We focus on compliance, licensing, liquidity, banking, and payment processing services so our partners can do what they do best, creating amazing tools on the blockchain.</p><p>We’re looking for a <strong>Technical Project Manager</strong> to join our Product Organization. You will be responsible for the execution and success of multiple projects that are critical to Wyre's product strategy.</p><p>This role reports up to our Chief Technology Officer.</p><h3><br></h3><h3>Responsibilities<br> </h3><ul> <li>Oversee large scale projects that are highly technical &amp; cross functional in nature</li> <li> Ensure cross functional alignment of goals &amp; execution of release schedules for product initiatives</li> <li> Be accountable for roadmap delivery including adoption and success criteria as defined by your stakeholders</li> <li> Collaborate with external &amp; internal stakeholders (Data Science, Product, Compliance, Marketing, Customer Experience, Engineering etc) to gather business requirements and define objectives</li> <li> Manage requirements documentation, milestone mapping, prioritization, and communication to facilitate project collaboration &amp; executive readouts</li> <li> Create thorough project / release plans, and roadmaps</li> <li> Monitor program status and rapidly identify issues / risks. Succinctly communicate issues to relevant stakeholders and proactively collaborate to ensure timely resolution</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>4+ years of relevant engineering experience</li> <li> 3 - 7+ years of technical projeect management experience at a technology company and/or in a technical capacity</li> <li> Enjoy solving hard problems and can turn incomplete, conflicting, or ambiguous inputs into action plans</li> <li> Ability to communicate with technical and non-technical stakeholders in order to drive alignement</li> <li> Ability to leverage data to inform and support critical decisions and make recommendations</li> <li> Prior experience working on global projects, or in an international setting</li> <li> Able to manage multiple stakeholders and priorities simultaneously</li> </ul><ul> <li>Certification in Program Management or Project Management</li> <li> You are knowledgeable and passionate about cryptocurrency and blockchain</li> <li> Experience with Payments, Financial Services, Regulatory or Compliance initiatives</li> <li> Advanced understanding of Google apps, JIRA, Looker, Tableau, SQL</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>An opportunity to build the future and freedom to work wherever you want</li> <li>Health, dental, and vision benefits for you and your family</li> <li>Life insurance and disability benefits</li> <li>Equity options for all full-time employees</li> <li>401(k) plan with corporate matching</li> <li>Unlimited paid time off to relax and recharge</li> <li>Enjoy a highly fulfilling, mission-driven culture</li> <li>You are an owner! We offer stock options to each of our employee</li> <li> </li></ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/XF10lmj4V1M" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/wyre/j/2B80EF2174/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/195911/SendWyre-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[wyre@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[819988b2-62bb-4397-8af0-2a6f483e05ef]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Wyre]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Finance Associate / Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gauntlet]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gauntlet.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City / San Francisco / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Gauntlet’s mission is to drive adoption and understanding of the financial systems of the future. Gauntlet is the platform for off-chain intelligence that drives on-chain efficiency in Decentralized Finance (DeFi). We work with protocols to manage risk, improve capital efficiency, and manage incentive spend. We also publish cutting-edge research and aim to take a leading role in defining market risk standards across the industry.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Gauntlet is building infrastructure that allows us to simulate and stress-test blockchain protocols, contracts, and network interactions at scale over a wide range of market conditions. Our models ingest a wide range of on-chain and off-chain data, and are continuously calibrated to the current crypto market structure so that our recommendations are always up-to-date. These models and infrastructure power our platform that currently manages risk and optimizes incentives for over $40B in assets.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We're looking for a process-oriented Finance Associate to manage a wide-variety of projects that contribute to Gauntlet's business growth. The ideal candidate has a high attention to detail, the ability to work autonomously, and can present goals and progress effectively. Title and pay can be flexible depending on candidate's experience.</div><div><br></div><div>This role reports to Gauntlet's Head of Finance. </div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Analyze financials on an ongoing basis and communicate key metrics, risks and opportunities to finance teams and c-suite</li><li>Create and maintain rolling financial models, uncover trends and assess business risks and provide recommendations to leadership</li><li>Implement and track budgets for Operations, People, Engineering and Product teams</li><li>Create and refine other operational processes as the Finance team grows</li><li>Organize monthly Financial Review meetings</li><li>Help build financial infrastructure to support the company’s current and future business goals</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>2-5+ years of relevant work experience (ideally in investment banking, corporate strategy, or FP&amp;A)</li><li>B.S. or B.A. in Accounting, Finance, Math, Economics, Business or other technical field preferred</li><li>Advanced Excel and financial modeling experience</li><li>Experience managing and forecasting infrastructure spend preferred</li><li>Ability to multitask</li><li>Detail-oriented and able to work autonomously</li><br/>Bonus Points<br/><li>DeFi/Crypto/Web3 experience or interest</li><li>Experience working at a small, fast growing company</li><br/>Benefits and Perks<br/><li>Remote first - work from anywhere!</li><li>Regular in-person company retreats and cross-country "office visit" perk</li><li>100% paid medical, dental and vision premiums for employees</li><li>Laptop, monitor, keyboard and mouse setup provided</li><li>$1,000 WFH stipend upon joining</li><li>$100 per month reimbursement for fitness-related expenses</li><li>Monthly reimbursement for home internet, phone, and cellular data</li><li>Unlimited vacation</li><li>100% paid parental leave of 12 weeks</li><li>Fertility benefits</li><li>Opportunity for incentive compensation</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/gauntlet/1092a798-9752-48af-94b7-07844462b395/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637342/gauntlet-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gauntlet@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5a52a20d-0bf4-491e-a6c0-a97d19aee27d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gauntlet]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Information Security Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Axoni]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://axoni.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Axoni is building the next generation of capital markets technology. Our solutions are used by the world’s leading banks, asset managers, hedge funds, and infrastructure providers. Our diverse team focuses every day on our goal of building products that will change and improve how our clients and the markets will interact.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are seeking talented, motivated professionals that want to be part of this once-in-a-career opportunity to not only see, but also drive the incredible changes coming to global capital markets. We are building a culture where our team feels valued and everyone is given an opportunity to grow and succeed. We try to live by our Core Values and demonstrate what we believe represent the kind of company we are working to build. These Values are: Delivery is everything; Choose Kindness; Be better every day.</div><div><br></div><div>The <b>Information Security Analyst</b> is responsible for improving security controls associated with information systems, application development, and customer engagements.&nbsp; Candidates should be detail-oriented and have a strong interest in risk management and cybersecurity.</div><br/>You will: <br/><li>Work with the Information Security Architect on implementing cybersecurity processes</li><li>Develop an understanding of company processes and work with team leads on security initiatives</li><li>Work closely with security engineering and IT staff improving security tooling</li><li>Prepare minutes, reports, and presentations on GRC (Governance, Risk, and Compliance) processes</li><li>Research and present reports on information security topics</li><li>Assist with vendor security risk assessments</li><li>Monitor and react to cybersecurity threats</li><br/>You have: <br/><li>Bachelor's degree in Information Security or a related field</li><li>Strong communication and writing skills</li><li>Experience with spreadsheets, data analysis, diagramming, and presentation software (like MS Office)</li><li>Detailed note-taking ability</li><li>3 years minimum professional experience</li><li>2 years Information Security experience OR security certification</li><div>Individuals seeking employment at Axoni are considered without regards to race, color, religion, national origin, age, sex, marital status, ancestry, physical or mental disability, veteran status, gender identity, or sexual orientation. You are being given the opportunity to provide the following information in order to help us comply with federal and state Equal Employment Opportunity/Affirmative Action record keeping, reporting, and other legal requirements.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xO7B4WYKVZE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axoni/902f4e44-4dac-4f67-b63b-9d9758f8df7e/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145318/axoni.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axoni@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b96c34e0-5c46-4ec2-8e42-397e29857c6f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Axoni]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tron]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tron.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;TRON-BitTorrent offers a unique and compelling work environment. We are proponents of the open Internet and we serve one of the largest user demographics in history. We take these responsibilities seriously and hire accordingly. We work with only the brightest engineers and the most talented business people we can find. Everyone on our team is here to do meaningful work with broad reaching impact. We have a fun yet challenging work environment that fosters diversity, creativity, and teamwork. Our team members receive industry leading salaries, premium benefits, and state-of-the-art offices in San Francisco’s SOMA district.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a Blockchain developer responsible for building a cryptocurrency wallet for a well-known desktop torrenting application and its related products. Your primary responsibility will be to design, develop and improve the backend system behind this particular wallet, and to coordinate with the rest of the team working on different layers of the infrastructure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design, build, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable C++ code for the wallet backend application&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and maintain blockchain services supporting the wallet interface&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Implement performance and quality modules&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify bottlenecks and bugs, and devise solutions to these problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help maintain code quality, organization, and automatization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency in C++, with fair knowledge of the language specification&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Thorough knowledge of the standard library, STL containers, and algorithms&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated knowledge of blockchain-based systems and infrastructures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Golang or Python-based backend experience is preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of network protocols, knowledge of Bittorrent protocol is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated problem-solving skills and affinity for technical innovation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of dynamic polymorphism and C++ specific notions, such as friend classes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with templating in C++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of low-level threading primitives and concurrency topics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years of programming experience in C++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years of experience building blockchain-based or distributed systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good to have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of the latest C++ standards (C++11 and beyond)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building production-grade backend systems and microservices in Golang and/or Python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of dApp development standards, testing, and deployment processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building integrations with at least one major public blockchain&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with Solidity smart contracts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of cryptocurrency concepts, especially wallet-related products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient understanding of code versioning tool such as Git&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of Jenkins and VMs to manage automated testing and continuous integration as part of our release process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understand the value of automated testing and continuous integration&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will learn&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Integration of blockchain technologies into applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitTorrent protocol, at least the basics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Scaling an application for use by 100 million users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;More than what you already know&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/gU6Jfz2jOHA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/rainberry/jobs/5773069002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180174/300px-Tron_logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tron@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f44423ad-b7da-465f-8880-ebeb8930922a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tron]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sr. Product Marketing Manager - Strategy + Research]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for an experienced and entrepreneurial Sr. Product Marketing Manager to drive our product strategy for a new crypto liquidity product. This person will deeply understand the market landscape, competitive feature set, and overarching trends influencing the crypto liquidity industry. They will identify target customer segments and use cases, and influence the prioritization of new product features.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ideal candidate has worked in product marketing and or strategy for a disruptive technology, ideally in financial services or blockchain/cryptocurrency. Candidates should be self-starters and comfortable dealing with ambiguity. This individual will be deeply involved in analyzing, strategizing, and collaborating with Product and Engineering to develop, refine, and scale a new product experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU’LL DO:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track competitive product and messaging trends for a new crypto liquidity product, at both a domestic and international level, ensuring timely updates to Product, Engineering, and Marketing teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Train field teams on the crypto liquidity landscape and how to position Ripple’s value proposition relative to competitors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Research and identify key differentiators for crypto liquidity product and develop operational plan for executing on these features or strategies, including (but not limited to) product build and M&amp;amp;A activity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Uncover new business opportunities, use cases, and product features by engaging regularly with prospects / customers and conducting industry market research.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Maintain a pulse on the DeFi landscape, particularly the tokenization of non-standard assets, with an eye toward integrating these elements into the core liquidity platform.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE’RE LOOKING FOR:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;8+ years of work experience, with 4+ years of experience in the fintech or crypto industries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience or interest in launching new products (i.e. taking a product from 0 to 1).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in market and competitive intelligence, research or data analytics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfort in a fast-paced and cross-functional work environment. Love for startups, entrepreneurship, and crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serious attention to detail, organization, and a commitment to excellence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent problem solving skills / comfort with ambiguity. You should be able to take a problem and structure a solution or recommendation with incomplete or limited data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Willingness to interface with global teams in APAC and EMEA regions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;MBA is preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice &lt;/a&gt;and our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/ca-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;California Applicant Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; for reference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3755517?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Backend Engineer, Go Cryptowatch]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b>This role is fully remote.</b></div><div><br></div><div>Help us scale Cryptowatch, Kraken's professional charting and trading platform. Cryptowatch has grown organically from a tiny weekend project to a popular real-time cryptocurrency charting and trading platform which people rely on all over the world. We are seeking talented individuals to help us expand the product in new directions. There's rarely a boring day in crypto, and we're looking for people who want to be part of this exciting ecosystem!</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Maintain and develop a service-oriented backend</li><li>Analyze and identify bottlenecks in performance</li><li>Design secure, stable, and robust architecture</li><li>Improve monitoring of production services to catch warning signs and critical conditions</li><li>Collaborate with frontend engineers to add support for complex user interfaces</li><li>Collaborate with devops to deploy new services and databases</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Expertise writing backend web services in Golang</li><li>Experience using a Linux server environment</li><li>Ability to independently debug problems involving the network and operating system</li><br/>Nice to have<br/><li>Have experience working with instant messaging and chat systems</li><li>Be familiar with with deployment using Docker</li><li>Have experience with protocol buffers</li><li>Have experience with SQL and Redis</li><li>Be proficient &nbsp;with HTTPS and Websockets</li><li>Have experience using AWS</li><li>Be passionate about fast, efficient software</li><div><span style="font-size: 15px">Location Tagging: #US #EU&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/fd088c8a-c645-4123-88fc-44a40c4a320a/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Manager, Business Development (Coinbase Cloud)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase has built the world&#39;s leading compliant cryptocurrency platform serving over 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries. With multiple successful products, and our vocal advocacy for blockchain technology, we have played a major part in mainstream awareness and adoption of cryptocurrency. We are proud to offer an entire suite of products that are helping build the cryptoeconomy and increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for signals that a candidate will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, disrupt ourselves, and expect sustained high performance because we play as a championship team. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people with the desire and capacity to build and share expertise in the frontier technologies of crypto and blockchain, in whatever way is most relevant to their role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As Manager, Business Development - Coinbase Cloud,&amp;nbsp; you will be responsible for identifying, managing and executing key partnerships that will lead to the continued growth and impact of &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/cloud&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Cloud&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; as the world’s leading crypto infrastructure platform. Your mission will be to build and operationalize a comprehensive strategy that defines how Coinbase can attract the world’s leading Web3 developers and enterprises to build on top of the Cloud platform. You’ll work closely with cross functional stakeholders to ensure our product, engineering and marketing teams are able to meet their OKRs by developing solutions to blockers or identifying and executing on partnership needs. Additionally, as Coinbase continues to embrace decentralization, you’ll help lead our strategy on supporting DAOs and ensuring Coinbase is a leader and valued partner in key decentralized ecosystems.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Secure Key Partnerships to Support Cloud’s Growth Strategy&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Engage and negotiate key vendor partnerships that scale our product and engineering teams efforts and allow us to bring the most reliable and secure products to market.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Identify opportunities for strategic partnerships that allow the Cloud platform to be accessed by the broader crypto ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Work cross functionally internally to ensure Cloud’s key customers are having all their business needs met and that they are receiving the utmost value from the Cloud platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Partner with the protocol operations teams to build strong relationships with protocol teams and help them and their ecosystem of developers better leverage the Cloud platform.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop Strategy to Support DAOs&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As DAOs continue to grow and mature, partner with Coinbase incubated DAOs to help build partnerships within the crypto ecosystem to ensure their growth and impact.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support Coinbase incubated DAOs through internal cross functional support helping ensure DAOs teams understand and receive the full support of the Coinbase platform and teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be an expert on all things DAOs, understanding their needs as organizations and identifying opportunities for the Cloud platform to better serve them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proliferate Cloud through the Web3 Developer Ecosystem
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with Cloud Developer Relations team to sign key strategic partnerships for launch of the Cloud platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Become an expert on all things Web3 infrastructure platforms and partner with cross functional teams to ensure they understand the opportunities and concerns that developers have around building on the Cloud platform.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help shape Cloud product roadmaps by recommending new features through problem statements supported with data, developer feedback, industry insights and competitive intelligence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we look for in you (ie. job requirements):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are an excellent communicator and relationship builder.&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are amazing at written and spoken communications, and are able to translate complex topics into relatable concepts and actionable tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are skilled at providing concise, timely and actionable reports to senior leadership on topics ranging from project updates and emerging trends to critical blockers and recommended solutions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can work confidently with cross-functional teams on complex legal, compliance and security matters. You know how to&amp;nbsp; identify, frame and lead the resolution of “hot issues” from both internal and external sources.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are an expert at building strong relationships across a variety of partner verticals. You have outstanding interpersonal skills driven by high emotional intelligence, and can easily drive alignment among differing perspectives.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You love going deep and learning about new technologies and industries&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are a self starter who is intellectually curious and loves to learn new concepts and products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You understand how to leverage tools (Twitter, Youtube, Medium) to go deep on complicated ecosystems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You keep track of trends within your industry so you can identify new business opportunities and you have the skillset and hustle to capture them.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are highly analytical with an ability to present complex information in digestible way&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are a self-starter who works well independently and in teams within dynamic, rapidly changing workplaces.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have significant experience building excel models and synthesizing data in ways that allow executives to make informed decisions based on quantitative data.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are an amazing problem solver who embraces change and ambiguity. You know how to navigate your team within highly regulated and/or ambiguous landscapes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You know how to structure and negotiate strategic and commercial agreements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have at least 5 years of experience creating high-impact partnerships and leading large deals with significant autonomy in high-growth, fast-paced environments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You know how to leverage creative thinking and dealmaking to close complex partnerships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have demonstrated experience driving deals and partnerships that have delivered transformative results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Previous experience or deep interest in the Crypto/Blockchain/Web3 industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Notice for Colorado applicants as required by sb19-085 (8-5-20). Target annual salary for this role performed in Colorado, is $$170,850&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;+ target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations@ coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Please contact accommodations@ coinbase.com for additional information or to request accommodations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3749342?gh_jid=3749342&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain R&D Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[ChainSafe Systems]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://chainsafe.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;section id=&quot;st-companyDescription&quot; class=&quot;job-section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;Company Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;wysiwyg&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe Systems is a blockchain R&amp;amp;D firm on a mission to realize the potential of Web3 infrastructure through sustainable, open-source development. Our vision is to create a world with organizations that empower people to build and innovate through blockchain agnostic tools and other distributed technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are global leaders in the industry, unique in our work across multiple blockchain ecosystems, and currently are pioneering Ethereum,&amp;nbsp;Polkadot and Filecoin technology. We are actively pursuing the development of our own product suite, having recently released&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://files.chainsafe.io/&quot;&gt;Files&lt;/a&gt;, which allows users to upload and store files on IPFS and Filecoin with the goal of furthering development to provide a decentralized alternative to cloud storage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe is a unique company in a unique space, growing quickly and building a global reputation in this nascent space. Beyond offering experience across every major blockchain space to our team, we provide an open, inclusive, and supportive environment where we help folks reach their full potential as a human and as a professional.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here’s what you might want to know before reading on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our stack is progressive and open-source and includes Go, Rust, and TypeScript.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We spearhead ecosystem projects like&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ChainSafe/lodestar&quot;&gt;Lodestar&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ChainSafe/web3.js&quot;&gt;Web3.js&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ChainSafe/forest&quot;&gt;Forest&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ChainSafe/mina-rs&quot;&gt;Mina-rs&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/ChainSafe/gossamer&quot;&gt;Gossamer&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are dedicated to building novel things and solving hard problems which is why we have a dedicated R&amp;amp;D department.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We are global, remote-friendly, and open to contractors (who can commit to a minimum of 35 hours a week). For those local to Toronto, Berlin, or Zagreb, our casual and open-concept offices have meeting rooms, lounge areas, and space to pull up a chair.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Culture fit and alignment to our core values are extremely important to us. We are fueled by an immense intellectual curiosity of what technology can do and the impact it can have. You will thrive here if you are intensely driven by tackling technical challenges that no one else has solved yet and are inspired by the possibility of building the next generation of web infrastructure and decentralized systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;st-jobDescription&quot; class=&quot;job-section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;Job Description&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;wysiwyg&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate would be a software developer with a deep passion for research and development, a cryptography and/or blockchain background.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Solutions Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you like solving complex problems and do not give up until a solution is found&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you like learning new things and explaining them to people&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you are comfortable understanding and contributing to complex codebases&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you are good at reviewing and writing long research documents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you are a trusted source of clear and accurate information for clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you value practicality over perfection&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;you are passionate about decentralization and blockchain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This role will provide an opportunity to be up-to-date with the latest innovations around blockchain technology. The right candidate would be motivated to be both an observer and a driver of these innovations. You will have the opportunity to work on a variety of projects. Every project is on the cutting-edge and quite often we&#39;re figuring things out as we go, so continuous learning &amp;amp; teaching is the norm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Architect and prototype novel blockchain-based and blockchain-adjacent software solutions to enable new features, improved performance, cross-chain integrations, and more for our clients&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate with internal and external stakeholders regularly to understand their goals, share project progress, and address ambiguities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write proposals for new research and development, including detailed project plans with milestones and developer time/cost estimates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write specifications and supporting documentation to help developers implement our solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Peer review research, proposals, and code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;st-qualifications&quot; class=&quot;job-section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;Qualifications&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;wysiwyg&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiar with cryptography and/or blockchain stack including front-end, back-end, smart contracts, and protocol layers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building blockchain protocols or applications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to break down complicated concepts into simple language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of cryptography and security in the context of blockchain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfortable reviewing code in the absence of documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some experience with Go, Rust, JavaScript, and/or Solidity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of distributed systems &amp;amp; peer-to-peer network protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to proactively plan, lead, execute, provide updates, and be accountable for projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong interpersonal skills when collaborating with clients and teammates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eager to constantly learn, ask questions, and deepen your understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing white papers, technical articles, thesis, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with open-source development&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience writing articles or blog posts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Product or business development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;section id=&quot;st-additionalInformation&quot; class=&quot;job-section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;h2 class=&quot;title&quot;&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;wysiwyg&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Founded by Developers for Developers, we foster an Agile environment where tasks are assigned based not just on what you know but what you want to learn. We offer fast opportunities for personal growth, mentorship, professional development funding, tons of autonomy and responsibility, a results-driven environment, close collaboration with an international team, exposure to a wide array of ecosystems and trailblazing technologies, and flexible work hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At ChainSafe, we are a compassionate group of builders and makers, working to bring our ideas to life. You’ll be part of a team that believes in the vital importance of community and contributing to advance humanity with open-source and decentralized technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chainsafe.io/corevalues&quot;&gt;We care deeply about our values and look for these in every team member:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;A dedication to self-improvement and professional development; a commitment to community and collaboration; a drive for accountability, diligence, and autonomy; and above all fostering a place of acceptance, friendliness, and compassion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us who you are and learn more about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are ready to join us, assemble your highlights (GitHub, portfolio, LinkedIn) and show us your best work. Get ready to have incredible conversations with passionate developers like yourself. For our team’s project highlights, explore our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.com/invite/xSAwrnCWcg&quot;&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/chainsafe&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;, and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chainsafe.io/projects&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome your fresh perspectives and ideas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At ChainSafe, diversity and inclusion is more than a statement; equality and accessibility are guiding principles embedded in who we are - and why we do what we do. We recognize the benefits of a diverse team and aspire to embed respect for all people into our culture, values, and day-to-day practices. We encourage women, LGBTQIA+ people, people of colour, and members of any other group underrepresented in the blockchain space (or tech in general) to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe is a remote-first company with an international team. We offer opportunities for personal and professional learning and growth, value autonomy and responsibility, and have a results-driven environment, flexible work hours and time-off policy, as well as competitive salary.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To apply for this position, please fill out the linked application form.&amp;nbsp;Please attach your CV/resume as well as a link to your Github/Gitlab profile or some other software project you have contributed to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainsafesystems/jobs/4174309004?gh_jid=4174309004?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/820874/chainsafe-systems-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainsafe@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5f6a040d-27de-4887-98d1-3606d387ad93]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[ChainSafe Systems]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Enterprise Business Development Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxos]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos is on a mission to enable the movement of any asset, any time, in a trustworthy way. Today’s financial infrastructure is archaic, expensive, inefficient and risky - supporting a system that leaves out more people than it lets in. So we’re rebuilding it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a regulated blockchain infrastructure company, we use technology to tokenize, custody, trade, and settle assets for enterprise clients like PayPal, Novi, Bank of America, and Interactive Brokers. Paxos is a top-funded blockchain company, with more than $500 million in total funding from leading investors like OakHC/FT, Founders Fund, PayPal Ventures, and Declaration Partners. Together, we empower today’s financial leaders to build a more open, trusted economy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos’s &lt;strong&gt;Growth Team&lt;/strong&gt; is looking for a high-energy, driven professional with sound business insight and natural sales instincts to grow our &lt;strong&gt;Enterprise Business Development&lt;/strong&gt; team. You will lay the foundation of the sales effort through prospecting large accounts and engaging in the early stages of the sales funnel alongside our VPs of business development. Our customers include some of the largest companies in the world (global financial institutions like Mastercard, large fintechs like PayPal, and ecommerce giants like MercadoLibre, etc). You will work with our Business Development and Solutions Engineering teams to qualify new prospects, to handle RFIs/RFPs early in the sales process, and to coordinate among multiple internal teams to ensure a smooth handoff to the VP for further selling.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As an Enterprise Business Development Manager, you&#39;ll get to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understand the Paxos platform and the many use cases across all verticals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage with enterprise prospects early in the sales process to qualify and then to map out a potential engagement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Educate C-level and VP-level prospects on the Paxos platform and schedule meetings for the VP of Biz Dev&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage deep discovery to better understand the customer needs, their timelines, and their understanding of the product&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support RFP processes as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage key internal and external partner alliances&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in sales forecasting and other sales leadership activities to help us clarify our sales staging and to help build the most effective sales process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excel in operating in a dynamic and rapidly changing environment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with marketing to ensure all sales content is relevant and effective&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Travel to key customer meetings, to industry events, and to trade shows&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your experience should include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years&#39; in a qualifying or prospecting role; 1+ year in a closing role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A BA/BS degree or equivalent practical experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in a B2B sales type role in Technology and/or Finance, preferably with a global and/or enterprise customer base&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An ability to translate complex business concepts into concise, easy to understand concepts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience driving internal teams, are comfortable working with uncertainty in a fast-paced environment, and able to put structure to nebulous, complex problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfort delivering technical and value-based conversations with C-level executives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years of experience working inside of Salesforce as your CRM&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The desire to learn and to stay on top of a very fast-changing industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll love about Paxos:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos has consistently been named as a “Best Place to Work” by BuiltIn and was recently listed on the 2021 Forbes Fintech 50. All of our employees have significant ownership and impact on our business, as well as benefits like company equity, health insurance, family leave, a $500 quarterly stipend for development, a $500 stipend for home office setup and unlimited PTO. From team product demos and virtual lounge and learns to care packages and an active Slack #shoutouts channel, there are countless opportunities to connect and make your mark. Help us continue to build a new, open financial system from one of our three offices or right from your home!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/12/02/mercadolibre-is-creating-the-biggest-crypto-market-in-latin-america-paxos-powers-the-experience/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;MercadoLibre is Creating the Biggest Crypto Market in Latin America&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/10/19/usdp-chosen-for-novi-pilot/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;USDP Stablecoin Chosen for Facebook&#39;s Pilot of Novi Digital Wallet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/fintech/2021/#413b4e2631a6&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Forbes Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/13/paxos-supports-interactive-brokers-journey-into-crypto-markets/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Interactive Brokers&#39; Journey into Crypto Markets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/fintech-250-startups-most-promising/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CB Insights Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 250 for Crypto Category&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/30/trust-is-not-an-option-its-a-requirement-paxos-explains-its-unique-approach-to-pioneering-a-new-market/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Flourish Crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/23/paxos-national-trust-receives-occ-conditional-approval-for-de-novo-charter/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos National Trust Receives OCC Conditional Approval for De Novo Charter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/29/paxos-raises-300-million-in-series-d-funding-at-2-4-billion-valuation/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Raises $300M in Series D Funding at 2.4B Valuation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2020/10/21/paypal-launches-new-service-enabling-users-to-buy-hold-and-sell-cryptocurrency/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos &amp;amp; PayPal Bring Crypto to Millions of Users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Paxos team is made up of passionate people from all over the world with different perspectives and experiences. If this opportunity excites you, but your experience doesn’t perfectly match the description…apply! Unique voices help us build a more transparent and open economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com/careers/role/5781228002?gh_jid=5781228002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/215201/paxos.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxos@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c782dc3a-8644-40b8-919b-b98b0cb1b35f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxos]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Global Design Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[South Africa]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;The world is changing.&amp;nbsp;We all want something different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual, and we want to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Luno welcomes crypto lovers and crypto newbies.&amp;nbsp;You - just like everyone in the world - are on your own unique crypto-learning journey.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a mission-driven cryptocurrency company that is building more open and equal access to the future of money.&amp;nbsp;You don&#39;t have to know lots about crypto to be interested in joining us, you just have to feel that upgrading the world to a fairer financial system matters, and that you&#39;d like to be part of this global change.&amp;nbsp;We&#39;re a passionate and committed team taking on a&amp;nbsp;challenge of epic proportions.&amp;nbsp;Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people&amp;nbsp;working together&amp;nbsp;with unusual skill, focus and determination.&amp;nbsp;We need the best team on board for our mission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If that sounds like a culture you&#39;d thrive in, then we are excited to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Luno means moon in Esperanto, we chose the name because at night, wherever you are in the world, you look up at the same moon.&amp;nbsp;We believe in the power of working together, as one team, across borders, with clear focus and shared purpose.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Our popular mobile app and website helps people around the world grow and manage their money using the world&#39;s most mature cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum and USDC.&amp;nbsp;We&#39;ve processed over&amp;nbsp;$ 21 billion to date.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Over 9 million customers across 40 countries have chosen to hold their crypto wallets on Luno because we offer a delightfully simple experience and bank-grade security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We&#39;re part of the Digital Currency Group,&amp;nbsp;named in 2021 as one of TIME magazine&#39;s 100 Most Influential Companies, in the “Disruptors” category alongside Tesla, AirBnB, SpaceX, Peloton.&amp;nbsp;TIME noted that DCG is&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/collection/time100-companies/5953752/digital-currency-group/&quot;&gt;“mainstreaming cryptocurrency”&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We&#39;re proud to be one of the world&#39;s most international cryptocurrency teams, with colleagues from 43 different nationalities working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria, Australia and Singapore.&amp;nbsp;Financial inclusion is part of our mission, but on a deeper level, inclusion is a way of life, and a way of work for us.&amp;nbsp;It is part of who we are as a company, and a group of human individuals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Your mission will involve&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working with our Creative Director to implement our new marketing design system across all local content, balancing two equally important objectives with skill and diplomacy: global coherence and local relevance. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In order to drive a step change in the quality and ambition of our visual brand a full Luno rebrand is coming soon, so this is a career-defining opportunity to help shape and execute a new, world-class brand design system from the ground up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help hire and then directly manage a new distributed and remote team of junior to mid-level marketing designers that will sit in all of our major markets around the world - Malaysia and Indonesia to begin with - many more to come very soon. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This team will be key to scaling our global marketing reach and supporting the local relevance of our marketing content as we do so. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As team lead, it will be your responsibility to foster a sense of team belonging and shared purpose in a remote team working across cultures, geographic locations and time zones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Inspire, create and sustain a culture of craft excellence and be both coach and player, enabling your team to consistently deliver high impact design that builds brand trust, recall and drives conversion across multiple different design canvases, from social video content to printed flyers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with our Brand Production Manager to continuously develop processes and systems that support efficient design workflow at scale, for example rituals, reviews, tooling decisions, asset libraries, templates, playbooks, toolkits or other effective collaboration and efficiency solutions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal Lunaut will have:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A world-class portfolio of integrated/omni-channel marketing content, work in social video content is particularly desirable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A strong marketing and growth acumen and appetite to use your design craft to help build a leading global brand on social media&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience across a wide range of other marketing channels, including events, partnerships and sponsorships, flyers etc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A demonstrable track record of experience in design and art direction, including design team management and in-house design experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with rapid-growth or scaling tech business is highly desirable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven ability to build effective design teams, design creative operations that solve business problems and lead design work that meets real commercial and marketing needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Best-in-class technical proficiency, desire to be both coach and player, and willingness to do hands-on design work alongside your design team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;Luno is a ‘remote but reachable’ company! At Luno,&amp;nbsp;we trust that people can do their work effectively anywhere and provide Lunauts with the flexibility to decide where they do their best work. For some of us, that’s at home for the majority of the time, for others, that might mean joining other Lunauts in person at one of our Luno workspaces more often. Luno is built on our relationships, so we still value in-person connection and have a minimum expectation of spending time in person once a quarter. So as long as you are based in one country with a Luno workspace, we want to hear from you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not negatively discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3757459?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Creative Producer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Eco]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://eco.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere (U.S. timezones preferred)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Eco puts your money back to work for you — creating the first consumer fintech product whose creators are aligned with its users. Financial infrastructure hasn&#39;t changed since the 1970s. All we&#39;ve gotten are shinier products built on the same broken systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Eco App changes that, starting by building the best place to save and spend your dollars. We combine high-yield savings with rewarded spending in a single, compounding balance that&#39;s easy to manage. Soon we&#39;ll let you pay your bills and put your financial life on autopilot. And through all of this — unlike every other fintech company — we don&#39;t skim from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;That’s only possible because we’re building Eco Points, a new rewards currency for the Eco community. Eco Points keep us—our company, App users, and the community of people already building for Eco—aligned to win together. And this is just the beginning. New Points features are emerging every month as we think about how Eco can fundamentally upgrade traditional money. And in case you’re wondering: there’s much, much more to Points than meets the eye.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Every day, we&#39;re working on difficult and impactful problems which demand solutions at the intersection of technology, product, marketing, and advocacy. To achieve our mission and realize our vision, we’ve put together an incredible team and are selectively adding to it. We hope you’ll consider joining us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;--&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a Senior Creative Producer at Eco, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop an array of multimedia projects as well as one-off videos; staff teams and manage the resources to execute them as needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design and lead all production efforts for Eco Explore (public event series) and other company events and programs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate the pre-production process: work with internal stakeholders on concept development, scripts, and storyboards; create and communicate project scope and timelines; and manage deliverables within the resources allocated.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate the production process: schedule shoots and determine staff and freelancing needs to support them, finalize deliverables, and post assets to internal or external hosting and social media platforms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Organize the post-production of content and collaborate with freelance post-production team and contractors: editing videos, adding slides and supplemental content, and encoding video resources to the right specifications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support the production process by lending your expertise across: camera work, sound and lighting equipment, video creation and editing software, and encoding best practices and video compression formats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Review cuts and provide consistent feedback.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Act as a liaison with freelancers and contractors and identify competitive pricing for products and services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Hire, lead and train other in-house production staff.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re looking for you if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a minimum of eight (8) years of experience in media production including videography, location shooting, lighting, sound recording, editing and various other related technical duties.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have creative vision and the inspiration to pursue ambitious projects and storytelling techniques.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are proficient with using a variety of digital production equipment (cameras, lighting, sound) and editing software (Premiere, Final Cut Pro, etc).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have familiarity with creating animations and motion graphics (desired but not required).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have broad knowledge of the online video space and distribution platforms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience in managing live-streaming through RTMP or other live broadcasting platforms (desired but not required).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You understand the online video space and can leverage various distribution platforms.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are detail oriented and committed to accuracy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can build agile teams of internal and external contributors to deliver complex productions (e.g. working together with editors, animators, camera operators, etc.).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re a self-starter who can work effectively in a collaborative and fluid team environment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can translate big, complex topics into compelling video storytelling.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience working with high-level talent (desired but not required).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a diverse portfolio of work showcasing skills across the production process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please note that we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, background, religion, gender identity, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship status, marital status or disability. We also consider for employment qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records. If you have a disability or special need that requires accommodation, please feel free to let us know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/econetwork/jobs/5782127002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/644968/eco-200x200.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[eco@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d703e4ac-536e-4837-8c22-e10df11c25af]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Eco]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
