<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Content writer, DeFi]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Ireland, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Crypto.com</strong></p><p>Founded in 2016, Crypto.com today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest growing crypto app, along with the Crypto.com Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the Crypto.com Exchange and Crypto.com DeFi Wallet. Recently launched, Crypto.com NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment and sports.</p><p>Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, CCSS Level 3, ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks.</p><p>With over 2,600 people in offices across the Americas, Europe and Asia, Crypto.com is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a href="https://crypto.com" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com</a></p><p><br></p><p><strong>Role summary</strong></p><p>As a Content Writer, DeFi and Gaming, you will be a key member of the DeFi team and will be responsible for creating high-quality written content that educates our community on the world of crypto, DeFi and Blockchain gaming, keeping them ahead of the crowd. Our team is fully remote, and we welcome candidates from anywhere in the APAC, EUR or UK timezones.</p><p></p><p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p><ul> <li>Write long-form articles on a variety of crypto-relevant topics that keep our community well-informed and knowledgeable on anything crypto: how-to trade, invest, and use crypto; press releases and recaps of industry events; use guides to DeFi protocols and blockchain gaming apps; crypto trends</li> <li>Write matching social media posts to the long-form content</li> <li>Work with a team copywriters, editors, and designers to create impactful and on-trend content for the crypto community</li> <li>Conduct keyword/topics research to spot trending topics in the crypto space, especially for NFTs, Defi, GameFi, blockchain technology, and other emerging trends</li> <li>Perform competitors content analysis to make sure we do not miss any opportunities</li> <li>Keep abreast with the latest crypto and industry trends, consistently contributing fresh ideas to content creation</li> </ul><ul> <li>At least 3 years working experience in content writing and editing</li> <li>Intricate knowledge on DeFi, blockchain, and cryptocurrencies</li> <li>Native-level written communication skills in English</li> <li>Knowledgeable on SEO and popular CMS (wordpress)</li> <li>Preferably knowledgeable on Google Analytics, SEMrush, or other SEO tools</li> <li>Pay minute attention to detail and work well in fast-paced environments</li> <li>Experience working with well-known English media outlets or in corporate communications</li> <li>Self-motivated, independent, strong team player</li> <li>A university degree in Journalism, Communications, or related disciplines is a plus</li> </ul><ul> <li>Attractive compensation package</li> <li>Working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing content from scratch, alongside a talented team</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/68F4302DCF/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Payments Product Counsel]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Strike]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://beta.strike.me/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Strike&#39;s mission is to build a more connected financial world.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strike allows users to send and receive money anywhere, instantly, with no fees.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strike is built on top of the Bitcoin network - the largest global, interoperable and open payments standard. Strike believes that open payment networks enable universal participation in the financial system, ushering in a new digital economy with truly borderless money transfers. Strike leverages Bitcoin’s open payment network to offer users the first global peer-to-peer payments app and a novel bitcoin-native neobanking experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Role:&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As part of Strike’s small legal team, you will help shape the legal, product, and business strategy for a fast-growing fintech company. We’re seeking an attorney with financial services, product counseling, and/or in-house tech company experience. This cross-functional role blends product, regulatory, and commercial counsel responsibilities, and requires an autodidactic mindset to tackle legal issues in collaboration with a range of internal teams.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ideal candidate should thrive working in a fast-paced startup environment and be excited about Strike’s mission and potential. You must be comfortable with a team-first approach in a remote work environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Navigate a complex regulatory and commercial landscape to help design innovative products and services in various countries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide end-to-end product counseling on payments- and banking-related products in partnership with a range of internal teams, including Product, Business, Engineering and Data Science, Compliance, CX, Comms, and Marketing.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Negotiate and finalize commercial agreements from a variety of domains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build and improve template agreements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Research novel legal questions and provide clear and actionable guidance to internal clients.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate, draft, and review written communications to regulators.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build processes to improve the legal team’s and the company’s operating efficiency and mitigate legal risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Member of a US State Bar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;JD from an ABA-accredited law school&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;6+ years of relevant work experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity and experience with payments and banking industry legal issues and applicable requirements and regulations, including NACHA Rules, card network rules, etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience drafting and negotiating agreements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Keen attention to detail and organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong project management and analytical skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to learn new software and cloud-based tools as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice-to-haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;8+ years of legal work experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least one of the following work experiences:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Top law firm or state or federal clerkships&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Financial regulator at the state or federal level&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In-house legal teams at technology companies (ideally fintech)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in the cryptocurrency or payments space&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with outside counsel in international contexts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with commercial relationships relevant to fintech&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://strike.me/jobs?gh_jid=4275479004&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/712431/strike.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[strike@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[28384812-e332-465c-ba22-66f5df8ede20]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Strike]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (backend)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[MomentRanks]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://momentranks.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>The Role</b></div><div>We're looking for an experienced, data-focused backend software engineer who loves scaling data platforms. We work with <a href="http://node.js/">Node.js</a>, Mongo, AWS, and some Go &amp; Python.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Our company</b></div><div>MomentRanks makes collecting <a href="https://opensea.io/blog/guides/non-fungible-tokens/">non-fungible tokens</a>, or NFTs, incredibly easy, fun, and social. NFTs can be collectibles, gaming items, domain names, digital art, and many other items backed by a blockchain. We're making NFTs accessible to the tens of millions of users who are being held back from entering the space.</div><div><br></div><div>We launched in 2021 and already see over 150,000 monthly active users. We're backed by some of the best VCs in the crypto space, including Dapper Labs, and are growing incredibly fast. Check out our <a href="https://twitter.com/MomentRanks">amazing community</a> or our mentions in the <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/03/13/technology/crypto-art-NFTs-trading-cards-investment-manias.html">New York Times</a>, <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/09/05/investing/stocks-week-ahead/index.html">CNN</a>, and <a href="https://fortune.com/2021/08/31/nft-tips-for-designers-artists-brands/">Fortune</a>. </div><div><br></div><div>At MomentRanks, we believe that it is essential to elevate all perspectives in the crypto space so we can make it accessible to everyone. We are dedicated to equal employment opportunities regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity or Veteran status.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Responsibilities</b></div><div>- Develop data ingestion pipelines for blockchain and NFT data </div><div>- Aggregate data from external APIs</div><div>- Implement data and performance monitoring </div><div>- Architect and scale APIs in Node/NestJS, with a focus on both data analytics and social features </div><div>- Be excited to learn about the future of blockchain technologies and other cutting-edge practices</div><div>- Add positive energy in every meeting, and make your coworkers feel included in every interaction.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Desired Experience</b></div><div>- 5+ years in a backend or data engineering role, or impressive side projects</div><div>- Drive and ambition to lead the development of a brand new platform.</div><div>- An ability to write high quality code quickly, with a bias towards shipping</div><div>- Familiar with product and design lifecycles, and collaborating closely with designers, engineers, and product managers.</div><div><br></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/moment-ranks/7482f11c-71ec-4af7-be13-f6876cc25c15/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/828988/momentranks-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[momentranks@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[2efc8afe-6b4a-4713-943d-c9ad29642f80]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[MomentRanks]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[NFT Analyst Intern (NFT/GameFi)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Global]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Research and gather information of NFT, Web3 and GameFi projects</li><li>Review and deliver insights on on NFT/GameFi projects</li><li>Work closely with the team lead to support Investment Partners for the full lifecycle of investment</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Team player,fast learner</li><li>Aim to choose crypto as long-term career pathStrong sense of art or degen in NFT discord channels is a plus</li><li>Knowledge in on-chain data analytics is a plus (Dune analytics, Nansen.ai)</li><li>Heavy game player is a strong bonusFull-time analyst or part time intern with at least 4 days of work per week will be welcome&nbsp;</li><li>Remote working</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/ee01f5f7-3743-41f7-8dc9-d2adcd309321/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Business Analyst ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of M&A Integration]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">This position will be responsible for working with a broad range of Business Leaders, Functional Leaders, and Corporate Development (1) to craft the integration approach for individual acquisitions of various sizes and complexity, and (2) to build the integration playbook for repeatable and effective cross-functional execution.&nbsp; We are looking for an experienced and proactive leader with meaningful insights on best practices.&nbsp; This team member will report to the VP of Business Operations and Expansion, which also holds responsibility for Corporate Development, Business Development, and Business Operations.</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">To be successful, you will have to be able to juggle multiple deal-related responsibilities in parallel, anticipate challenges and corresponding corrective actions, and be very flexible and organized.&nbsp; We would expect you to be articulate, sensible, able to coordinate with other peers and senior executives, and collaborate and deliver results in a fast-paced environment where teamwork, professionalism, confidentiality, and communication are essential.&nbsp; You will be a very key leader, with a mandate to define, grow, and manage an influential team of M&amp;A Integration professionals.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Integration Model: Work closely with Corporate Development and other Functional Leaders to implement a repeatable and flexible cross-functional playbook for the integration of acquisitions of various sizes and complexity.&nbsp;</li><li>Preparation: Set the broad integration strategy and tools, and define value drivers for each dealIntegration </li><li>Metrics:&nbsp; Establish the key milestones, critical deliverables, and repeatable measured outcomes that drive the integration to delivering the value anticipated from the deal</li><li>Business Perspective: Contribute insights to business case development, value driver definition, and execution plans</li><li>Leadership: Encourage adoption of best practices suitable for each situation, and hold colleagues accountable for their contributions throughout the process</li><li>Coaching: Share experiences and know-how at each stage of the deal formulation, prosecution, diligence, and post-merger integration process to improve outcomes at all stages</li><li>Problem Solving: Identify and anticipate roadblocks, figure out constructive solutions, and prioritize the right countermeasures </li><li>Tracking: Track and report deal-by-deal performance during the immediate periods after closing as well as the overall performance of the acquisition portfolio to Functional Leaders, Executives, and the Board on various dimensions of Strategic and Financial Value attained through M&amp;A activities</li><li>Communications: Convey in writing and in conversation concisely and clearly, so as to make complex problems and difficult decisions readily actionable by Executives</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>MBA preferred</li><li>12+ years with business operations experience likely spanning Strategy, Product, Operations, Finance, or Integration, with a minimum of 5 years of concentrated experience in integrations</li><li>Preference for direct experience with leading integration tools and methodologies from a publicly traded company, backed up with multiple years of experience at a top tier consulting firm</li><li>Familiarity with all stages of the M&amp;A process and key requirements for delivery at each stage gained through experience across multiple domestic and international transactions of various sizes and complexity</li><li>Proven ability to lead team members who are direct reports as well as the peer team mates on projects</li><li>Thrives in a fast-paced environment where you get to utilize your resourceful, problem solving nature, and be able to maintain a professional demeanor while working under pressure</li><li>Strong analytical, strategic, and innovation skills</li><li>Ability to deal with conflicting priorities with ease and confidently communicate with team members at all levels</li><li>Highly tech savvy with strong emphasis on cyber security and privacy&nbsp;</li><li>Self-starter yet seek and enjoy the opportunity to collaborate with others</li><li>Detail oriented and analytical, with the ability to follow-throughSelf-motivated and able to thrive in a result-driven environment with tight deadlines</li><li>Compassionate and caring to make the company culture and experience better for all team members</li><div><span style="font-size: 10px">Location Tagging: #US #EU #LI-AN1 #LI-Remote #APAC #CANADA</span></div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/23e6e35a-9f44-45af-adfc-6e95fa725ecd/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Sourcer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://blockchain.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Argentina]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain is the world&#39;s leading software platform for digital assets. Offering the largest production blockchain platform in the world, we share the passion to code, create, and ultimately build an open, accessible and fair financial future, one piece of software at a time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for a talented, driven and ambitious Tech Sourcer to join our growing team to support Blockchain.com’s continued expansion. This is an opportunity to play an instrumental role in building Engineering, Infrastructure and Data functions for one of the world&#39;s fastest growing and most exciting tech companies. The perfect candidate will have a track record of hunting top-tier technical talent in key markets in LatAm!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure a world-class candidate experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build and maintain active pipelines, with highly qualified candidates, for open opportunities across our technical functions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish yourself as a trusted partner and point of contact for hiring managers across the organization, proactively maintaining communication with them in order to keep updated with their latest needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working closely with our Talent Acquisition Associates in order to set out sourcing strategies, allowing the team to deliver efficiently and effectively&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement innovative sourcing and selection tools where necessary, allowing you to identify and engage the best talent using the right tool for the job.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build relationships with relevant industry professional associations, universities, meetups and other appropriate events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The foremost quality for this or any position at Blockchain is integrity.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years of experience in technical sourcing or recruitment, with experience in software engineering roles - with data science, infrastructure and product management experience a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be self-motivated, tenacious and driven, operating with a high sense of urgency while working effectively within a team environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must value delivery, and have a proven track record in the following abilities: organization, motivation and follow through.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be able to identify problems and drive change where necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You&#39;re a charismatic people person who can talk to anyone; you&#39;re flexible, fearless and excited to help build something awesome and share it with the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*Application&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you apply to a job on this site, the personal data contained in your application will be collected by one or more of the following subsidiaries of Blockchain Luxembourg S.A (each, a “Controller”):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain Access UK Ltd.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain (GB) Limited&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain (US), Inc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain (LT), UAB&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You may contact our Data Protection Officer by email at&amp;nbsp;dpo@blockchain.com. Your personal data will be processed for the purposes of managing Controller’s recruitment related activities, which include setting up and conducting interviews and tests for applicants, evaluating and assessing the results thereto, and as is otherwise needed in the recruitment and hiring processes. Such processing is legally permissible under Art. 6(1)(f) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation) as necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Controller, which are the solicitation, evaluation, and selection of applicants for employment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your personal data will be shared with Greenhouse Software, Inc., a cloud services provider located in the United States of America and engaged by Controller to help manage its recruitment and hiring process on Controller’s behalf.&amp;nbsp; Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, your personal data will be transferred to the United States once you submit it through this site. Because the European Union Commission has determined that United States data privacy laws do not ensure an adequate level of protection for personal data collected from EU data subjects, the transfer will be subject to appropriate additional safeguards under the standard contractual clauses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your personal data will be retained by Controller as long as Controller determines it is necessary to evaluate your application for employment.&amp;nbsp; Under the GDPR, you have the right to request access to your personal data, to request that your personal data be rectified or erased, and to request that processing of your personal data be restricted. You also have to right to data portability. In addition, you may lodge a complaint with an EU supervisory authority.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain/jobs/3774284?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180745/blockchaininc.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchaininc@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5457bd3d-b464-4d43-bfd6-5c9d9e62930e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineering Recruiting Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.okcoin.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of Okcoin:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Okcoin is one of the world’s largest and fastest growing cryptocurrency exchanges. We help millions of people buy and sell bitcoin, and over 20 other crypto assets every day — but our work is a whole lot more than that. We’re building an inclusive future of finance, one that opens new opportunities to learn financial literacy, store value, and build wealth for everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ready to help the next billion people experience the future of finance with us? Come on board. We have offices in San Francisco, Malta, Hong Kong, Singapore, and Japan, but we believe in you working wherever you work best.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Overview of Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Okcoin is quickly building a robust recruiting team to meet the rapidly scaling needs of the business. And in terms of hiring, our Engineering team is top priority for us. We are looking for a stellar Recruiter to lead the entire Engineering recruiting function, strategy and efforts. You will be both building and leading the team, while also keeping your pulse on hands-on recruiting by owning a few key engineering reqs yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Specifics of Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build, lead, guide and nurture team of Recruiters, Sourcers and Recruiting Coordinators who are responsible for several vital hiring initiatives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Head of Talent and Global Head of People to develop recruiting strategy specifically tailored for Engineering (candidate experience, employer brand, etc)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Hands-on recruit for select Engineering roles&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner closely with Executives and other leaders to create an informed, smart Staffing Plan, inclusive of competitively intelligent Strategies, Processes and Tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements of Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;7+ total yrs of recruiting experience, primarily in-house&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;4+ yrs recent, in-house, Engineering-specific recruiting experience at cutting-edge startups&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ yrs recent experience managing Recruiters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong strategic orientation and ability to lead in a dynamic environment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;High level of commitment, passion and ability to achieve business vision and mission&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A “rapid results” mindset (e.g. moves fast, thinks fast, works hard, communicates directly, focused, etc)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to build trusted relationships with Executives, hiring managers and your team&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong character and business ethics that are deeply evident in how you work&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfort acknowledging and sharing improvement opportunities across the recruiting function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong communicator and collaborator&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Thrives in ambiguity and can rapidly bring thoughtful solutions to complex problems&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Has exceptional organizational skills and an eye for detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice-to-Have’s for Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto, blockchain or DeFi startup industry experience - *strong plus*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fintech startup industry experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep Engineering recruiting acumen, specifically for rapidly-scaling, booming startups - *strong plus*&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;San Francisco Bay Area startup recruiting experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xAd9NClUmZY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okcoin/jobs/4882760003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/551872/OKCoin_400x400.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okcoin@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[57e0c7fc-df31-4da2-b52b-befd9a7f36e9]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[NFT Community / Social Media Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Energi Core Ltd]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.energi.world]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Global - Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Energi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energi (NRG) is a next-generation Proof of Stake (PoS) cryptocurrency, combining Ethereum-compatible smart contracts with on-chain governance, a self-funding treasury, and a layer 2 masternode network, enabling powerful DeFi applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a fully remote company with no fixed headquarters. The team is spread throughout the Americas, Europe, Africa, Asia, and Oceania. With more than 90 contributors, the team forms a well-linked network across a variety of locations, lifestyles, and backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energi&#39;s culture is driven by integrity, strategic thinking, leadership, and the shared desire to perform at our peak. While our differences make us adaptable and versatile, it&#39;s our shared values that give us the strength and drive to become the cryptocurrency for world consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in It for You?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work flexible hours from anywhere and be part of a team that is driven by strong values and a clear shared vision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directly shape the future of a completely new model for cryptocurrency and blockchain applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenge your skills and push your creative limits working with the latest blockchain technologies &amp;amp; systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play an active role in one of the most significant technological innovations in human history.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receive a competitive salary paid in a combination of BTC and NRG.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’re looking for&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a full-time NFT Community and Social Media Manager who will manage and distribute the content our NFT communities create. This individual will also work across our content, marketing, and NFT teams in order to manage, maintain, and grow Energi’s social channels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You Will Do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shape Energi’s strategy on community development for NFT programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create, program, oversee, and keep track of Discord and Telegram servers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuous listening on brands currently tracking every follower interaction: comments, responses, DMs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Active and creative on social media daily&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effectively manage multiple projects with proven expertise in timeline management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum two (2) years direct experience growing and managing communities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience launching NFT projects and bringing them to life&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how to execute Discord and Telegram bots in server&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Combine creativity and analytics and convert to excellent storytelling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about NFTs, metaverse, cryptocurrency, and all things digital&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient with Google Slides and Adobe Creative Suite&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Self-driven with the ability to deliver results with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluent English communicator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Values aligned with the Energi culture and values&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Considers oneself a Community and Social Media Guru&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for learning and research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eagerness to engage and build communities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Love the magic of collaboration&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This role is not open to 3rd party organizations or agencies. Any candidates sent will be considered free of any charges.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energi is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, pregnancy, disability, age, veteran status, or other characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/8QUIHRakeHo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/energicorelimited/jobs/4276062004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/479023/energi-core-ltd-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[energi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5be3229a-46ba-477a-9178-2772ea9250e4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Energi Core Ltd]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, People Success (HR)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Flipside Crypto]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://flipsidecrypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Boston, MA - Remote OK]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>Director, People Success</strong></p><p>Flipside Crypto is making it’s first full-time hire in People Success (HR) to support the growth of our fantastic team. We are a rapidly scaling tech startup servicing the blockchain/crypto market…this means we assess, decide and adapt our business radically quickly. We are looking for someone to create and lead our new People Success team; to take our rich culture and rituals and constantly evolve them to meet the needs our people; to assess our existing approaches and help us scale them; and to be at the forefront of building a values rich, high integrity, diverse technology company in crypto.</p><p>Reporting to the Chief Operating Officer, you will be a strategic business partner to our department leaders across Flipside Crypto. You will hire a People Success team that ensures our remote culture is rich, values-driven, and delivers high performance. This new leader should have 10+ years of experience as part of a People Success (HR) organization, with at least 5 years of experience leading people and setting direction for a team. You will lead all aspects of People Success including business partnership, talent acquisition, people operations, employee relations, professional development and benefits management.</p><p><strong>Responsibilities</strong> </p><ul><li>Work closely with the leadership team to implement strategies that develop our workforce while improving the overall employee experience.</li><li>Design a high-impact People Success organization and hire new employees to execute on this strategy</li><li>Provide business partnership and guidance to department leaders across Flipside.</li><li>Lead the development of talent management processes that continue our history of high performing, empowered teams</li><li>Provide strategic partnership and mentorship to employees and people managers at all levels to positively impact the motivation, development, and retention of talent.</li><li>Lead and provide guidance on employee relations matters</li><li>Lead our high quality, high velocity talent acquisition efforts ensuring we move quickly, provide our hiring teams the tools and training they need, and create a fantastic candidate experience for any potential team member - whether or not they are offered a position at Flipside.</li></ul><p><strong>Requirements</strong></p><ul><li>10+ years in a people function</li><li>5+ years in a leadership role</li><li>Proven ability to partner with executive leadership</li><li>Demonstrated success in a high-growth organization</li><li>Strong teamwork, communication &amp; cross-functional collaboration skills</li><li>Entrepreneurial spirit/mindset, flexibility toward dynamic change</li><li>Ability to perform in a fast-paced environment, with multiple stakeholders with varying needs</li><li>Strong experience in wide variety of people success strategy and operations</li><li>Experience working in the Technology industry</li><li>Experience in a crypto organization is not required, but a big advantage in understanding the unique culture and ethos of this market.</li></ul><p></p><p>We welcome all qualified persons to apply regardless of race, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, disability, age, or veteran status. Compensation will be competitive and commensurate with experience.</p><p><strong>About Flipside</strong></p><p>Flipside Crypto empowers crypto communities to create and share data-driven insights on the projects they care most about. Flipside powers Community-Enabled Analytics, which uses a bounty program to incentivize on-demand insights based on feedback from the protocol and community participants. CEA provides fully pre-modeled and labeled data, a SQL interface for data queries. Community members can use our dashboard and visualization tools to easily share insights, or leverage auto-generated API endpoints to build whatever they can imagine.</p><p>Flipside customers include FLOW, NEAR, Terra, Algorand, Aave, Compound, Alchemix and many others. Flipside Crypto is led by a team of experienced technology entrepreneurs with multiple exits; it’s backed by Galaxy Digital Ventures, True Ventures, Founder Collective, Coinbase Ventures, Digital Currency Group, Avon Ventures (a venture capital fund affiliated with FMR LLC, the parent company of Fidelity Investments) and other investors.</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/4oOcum2vCVo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://flipsidecrypto.breezy.hr/p/7d7c15b679dc-director-people-success-hr/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/371352/flipside_crypto.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[flipsidecrypto@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9fd60574-03dd-4ff7-969f-631367694cbd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Flipside Crypto]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
