<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, Solutions Architecture, EMEA]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Solutions Architecture team is the backbone that helps the go-to-market (GTM) team run effectively. Our job is to manage the full funnel operations across the customer lifecycle and provide the organization documentation and expertise needed for the teams to function efficiently.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This Solutions Architecture leader is responsible for creating and implementing strategies that improve global operations across our revenue organization. We measure success by your accuracy, speed, and ability to build out processes and infrastructure to drive hiring, team enablement and support sales team activities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if you…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Created and implemented solutions to drive and retain revenue by collaborating with teams such as sales, marketing, and customer success and training&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Surfaced insights, business analytics, and data across all GTM functions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identified bottlenecks and collaborated with leadership/enablement to proactively unblock growth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Optimized our sales strategy, enablement, and execution as a whole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Defined the analytics framework to measure individual and company performance and owned the end-to-end process of tracking and analyzing the sales funnel from lead to customer&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Created models for lead, company, and deal scoring. Designed a strategy for enrichment, attribution modeling, and campaign measurement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Managed the tech stack of the GTM organization. Owned the recommendation, selection, and deployment of new technologies and tools to scale the GTM organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong working knowledge of the tools we use (or similar) to run the business and the ability to quickly learn and optimize new technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have very strong Salesforce reporting, dashboarding, and workflow skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with sales and marketing teams with a growth mindset.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven track record of developing and implementing and driving operations process efficiencies, effective policies and enabling better practice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible, well-organized and the ability to work in a fast-paced startup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Superior analytical, planning, and organizational skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Curiosity to learn and adapt to dynamic research, development, and industry knowledge&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-MJ1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yNpNz-FvSYQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5709197002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Maker]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://makerdao.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<h2 dir="ltr"><strong><span style="font-size: 16px;">About Maker</span></strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">MakerDAO is an Ethereum-based protocol that issues the Dai stablecoin and facilitates collateral-backed loans without an intermediary. Its widespread use and DeFi integration make MakerDAO one of the most operational protocols in the crypto ecosystem.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong><span style="font-size: 16px;">Distributed Teams</span></strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">We form our teams around availability of talent into co-located or distributed agile teams. On the techops side you will work together with our DevOps engineering team across the world, to make sure we have best of breed tools, practices and processes with a strong focus on automating everywhere it makes sense.</p>
<p dir="ltr">To get additional coverage we are looking for two additions to the team. One of them will be located in the Asia-Pacific time zone and the other in the US time zone.This is a completely remote position. The responsibilities sometimes require working evenings and weekends, sometimes with little advance notice. No regular travel is required but the budget for conferences and training is in place.</p>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong><span style="font-size: 16px;">Responsibilities</span></strong></h2>
<ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Manage virtual network infrastructure through our cloud providers such as AWS, including DNS/domain management, firewall and load balancing services.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Manage virtual servers running a variety of services, including web &amp; database servers, Ethereum nodes, team collaboration services, and more.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Schedule and execute OS and service patches and upgrades, keeping our infrastructure up-to-date and protected against security vulnerabilities.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Infrastructure automation. Design, set up, and maintain Infrastructure as Code, providing automated provisioning and orchestration of internal Maker services using Terraform, Docker, and similar technologies.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Operate the internal support desk for these services within the Maker organization. Investigate and troubleshoot issues and clearly communicate incident reports.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Select, secure, and manage administrative cloud services such as Google GSuite, etc., to support internal Maker operations. Manage user accounts within these services.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Manage logging, monitoring, detection and recovery infrastructure, ensuring the continued integrity, availability, and security of the Maker systems.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Software development lifecycle support. Managing development, staging, and production environments.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Collaborate with Maker development teams and QA engineers, supporting release pipelines with continuous integration and deployment of our platform and products. Setup and configuration of software development services such as Github, JIRA, and so on.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Inform and implement the Maker security strategy and policies. Create a culture of awareness and support the Maker teams in creating a secure, distributed working environment.</p></li></ul><p><h2>Requirements:</h2></p><h2 dir="ltr"><strong><span style="font-size: 16px;">Requirements</span></strong></h2>
<p dir="ltr">Experience with the following or equivalent technologies &amp; practices is an essential part of your skill set:</p>
<ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Most AWS services; other cloud providers is a plus</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Linux system administration and shell scripting</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Infrastructure automation and Configuration Management tools</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Ability to design, implement, maintain and collaborate on Infrastructure as Code (Terraform)</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Deploy services to Container Clusters (Docker, Kubernetes, ECS, EKS)</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Monitoring, Observability, Debugging and Performance tuning (Prometheus, Grafana)</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">On-call experience (PagerDuty)</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Basic programming (Python)</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Git/GitHub knowledge - usage and administration of multiple Organisations</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Conceptual and implementational knowledge of CI/CD (GitHub Actions)</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience with disaster recovery implementation and strategies</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Interpersonal skills working with stakeholders at different technical levels and backgrounds</p></li></ul>
<h2 dir="ltr"><strong><span style="font-size: 16px;">Nice to haves</span></strong></h2>
<ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Knowledge of Web3 and a keen interest to learn more</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Configuring and maintaining Ethereum nodes</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Familiarity with working in a startup environment</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience working with Open Source</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Experience working and collaborating in a digital native environment (Discord, JIRA, Notion)</p></li></ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Gqu9GWcx9Wk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://makerdao.recruitee.com/o/devops-engineer/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180500/makerdao.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[maker@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[20fdd764-0853-447b-b33c-968fda16a5f4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Maker]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of People]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gauntlet]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gauntlet.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York City / San Francisco / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Gauntlet’s mission is to drive adoption and understanding of the financial systems of the future. Gauntlet is the platform for off-chain intelligence that drives on-chain efficiency in Decentralized Finance (DeFi). We work with protocols to manage risk, improve capital efficiency, and manage incentive spend. We also publish cutting-edge research and aim to take a leading role in defining market risk standards across the industry.</div><div><br></div><div>Gauntlet is building infrastructure that allows us to simulate and stress-test blockchain protocols, contracts, and network interactions at scale over a wide range of market conditions. Our models ingest a wide range of on-chain and off-chain data, and are continuously calibrated to the current crypto market structure so that our recommendations are always up-to-date. These models and infrastructure power our platform that currently manages risk and optimizes incentives for over $40B in assets.</div><div><br></div><div>We’re looking for a Director of People to run and build out Gauntlet's People function with an emphasis on company culture. The ideal candidate has experience with Recruiting, Human Resources, and People Management and is excited about building internal processes and programs from the ground up.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>You will develop and drive Gauntlet's recruiting strategy</li><li>Develop innovative strategies to find, engage, and hire top crypto talent anywhere in the world</li><li>Create and execute a diverse and inclusive hiring strategy</li><li>Analyze and report on progress to team leads regularly&nbsp;</li><li>Facilitate a positive interview experience for candidates, as well as internal interviewers</li><li>Develop repeatable processes and leverage automation when possible</li><li>Create internal content and handbooks in collaboration with Gauntlet's Marketing team</li><li>Communicate expansion recommendations to C-Suite that enable the business to execute on key objectives while building out Gauntlet's People function</li><li>Train and mentor junior members of the People team and invest in attracting and developing top talent across all roles</li><br/>Qualifications<br/><li>8+ years of Technical Recruiting or People Management experience&nbsp;</li><li>Experience recruiting for and leading teams that hire highly specialized technical talent, preferably with Crypto experience (though not a requirement)</li><li>History of building inclusive and diverse teams&nbsp;</li><li>Deep knowledge across the entire candidate lifecycle, from talent mapping, research, sourcing, interviewing, to closing</li><li>Demonstrated ability to proactively find and engage pipelines of niche talent</li><li>Ability to think strategically and proactively, with a data-driven approach to decision-making</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/gauntlet/e88e6ffc-2f1c-494a-90f8-fb2b5074d025/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637342/gauntlet-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gauntlet@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5a52a20d-0bf4-491e-a6c0-a97d19aee27d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gauntlet]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[SEO Manager (m/f/d)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.parity.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote (Central European Time (CET))]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Every day we interact with technologies controlled by a handful of large companies whose interests and incentives often conflict with our own. If we want the benefits of using their proprietary apps, we’re forced to agree to terms that most of us will never read, granting these companies far-reaching control over our digital lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At the same time, progress in open-source and decentralized technologies like blockchain has shown that we can build systems that prioritize individual sovereignty over centralized control. With these new technologies, there’s no need to trust any third parties not to be or become evil.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Parity Technologies is a team of the world’s premiere blockchain developers building industry-leading technologies that enable developers, startups, and enterprises to create this next wave of better products and services. You’ll join at a critical moment when the future of the decentralized web is being shaped, and perform an influential role in making a more equitable society for our future.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for an experienced, creative and enthusiastic &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;SEO Manager&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to drive both strategy and implementation of continuous on-page and off-page improvements for our websites in order to improve their traffic and rankings.. If you have great communications skills, attention to detail and are data-driven, we want you on our team!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Plan and execute sustainable SEO campaigns to increase rankings and traffic for the different websites and blogs we manage (polkadot.network, parity.io, substrate.io…)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform full technical audits and instil best practice SEO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Plan and execute outreach campaigns for link building&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with the web and content teams to optimise all sites and increase search rankings and organic visits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish KPIs and track ranking performance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Produce reports on campaign effectiveness and create innovative follow-up tactics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure campaigns are in compliance with Web 3.0 values, GDPR and industry regulations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Conduct extensive keyword research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor industry trends and landscape and, continually audit, test and look for ways to optimise and improve organic traffic to the websites&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitor analysis and benchmarking&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Document and standardise work processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Required skills:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of SEO experience as SEO Specialist, SEO Manager or similar role&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent project management and organisational skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be an expert at a large range of intelligent SEO strategies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep understanding of technical SEO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong communication, people and stakeholder management skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in a fast-paced and growing tech startup environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong organization and analytical skill with a keen eye on details&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team player and self starter who isn’t afraid to take initiative&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fluent in English&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bonus:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with open source software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in the blockchain/crypto industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in creating campaigns for a developer audience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;To see how we use your data please see our&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.parity.io/applicant-notice/&quot;&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applicant Notice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LZd6z7HiTLw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/parity/jobs/4834864003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/378609/parity.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[parity@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6edef434-1785-497e-a19b-ce6d949ad50a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[UX/Product Designer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.axiomzen.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote or Vancouver, BC]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 10pt">We’re looking for a Product Designer with a data driven mindset and strive for design excellence in a growing Product Design team.&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">As a remote-first company, every one of us shares a common vision: to create the future we want to live in. Our team is spread across the globe with team members in Canada, US, Mexico and Europe. If you are looking for an opportunity to make an impact, learn from others and innovate within a fast­ growing technology company that creates outstanding products, we want to work with you regardless of your location.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">Some of the best teams at top companies like Adobe, NASA, Microsoft and Apple use ZenHub to deliver great software on time.</span></div><br/>Scope of your role:<br/><li>Collaborate within a multi-disciplinary squad to define, design, and deliver extraordinary solutions for our users.</li><li>Contribute to ZenHub’s design system through innovative UX patterns and develop corresponding documentation.</li><li>Create wireframes, functional specifications, user flows, mockups, prototypes, visual designs.</li><li>Facilitate quantitative and qualitative research that informs your designs and translates insights into feature requirements.</li><li>Identify &amp; evaluate user experience in collaboration with other product designers.</li><li>Participate in internal design critiques and team reviews to share your ideas.</li><li>Run usability tests to validate design decisions.</li><br/>A little about you:<br/><li>3+ years of experience as a product designer working in a cross-functional team.</li><li>Motivated to drive innovation.&nbsp;Clear process for decision making.</li><li>Comfortable collaborating with engineers to understand and execute on achievable solutions within scope.</li><li>Strong conceptual and visual design skills with the ability to translate insights and ideas into product features.</li><li>Strong communication skills, confidence in your work, and openness to feedback.&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><div><br></div><div>Bonus points: </div><li>Experience with design systems</li><li>Animation tools (such as principle and lottie)</li><li>Understanding of metrics, KPIs</li><div><b>More about ZenHub:</b></div><div>Don’t sweat it if you don’t have everything listed in the role description. One of our values is “Growth Mindset”. If you have some of the qualities listed above, and are excited about the role and motivated to learn – we want to hear from you!</div><div><br></div><div>At ZenHub our people are the priority. We believe the more perspectives we embrace, the stronger our team. We recruit the best, and welcome people of all backgrounds regardless of race, religion, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, age, or ability. With a focus on respect and a commitment to continuous learning, we’re building an inclusive culture that supports our team in doing their best work. We work hard to provide our full-time team members perks that make their lives better by offering:</div><div><br></div><div>○&nbsp;<b>Boundaryless working style.</b>&nbsp;We want our team to work from wherever is best for them. Whether you prefer to work from the comfort of your home office or from our bright, spacious, and dog-friendly Zen-den, we support you. For those opting to wfh, we offer a generous monthly stipend to cover ongoing remote work expenses. If you opt to join us in-office, we’ll contribute to your commute expenses or bike maintenance.</div><div>○&nbsp;<b>A flexible vacation policy</b>. We work hard and it’s important we take time to recharge. We have a flexible time off policy with no hard limit and encourage our team members to take a minimum of 3 weeks off per year.</div><div>○&nbsp;<b>A commitment to continued learning and development</b>. We provide an annual professional development budget to use towards conferences, classes, books, and other opportunities to maintain and expand your skill set.</div><div>○&nbsp;<b>Fitness reimbursements.</b>&nbsp;Stay fit with our monthly reimbursements for health-related benefits like gym memberships, fitness apps, and personal training.</div><div>○&nbsp;<b>Top-of-the-line equipment.</b>&nbsp;In addition to receiving a company smartphone of your choice with a paid voice/data plan, every team member receives a generous annual new tech budget to try new gadgets, tools, and platforms.</div><div>○&nbsp;<b>Flexible parental leave policies.</b>&nbsp;We understand the importance and demands of a growing family. In addition to state, provincial, and federal leave allowances, parents on our team have the ability to create flexible schedules or take days off when family needs to come first.</div><div>○&nbsp;<b>Social Connection</b>. When it’s safe to gather again our team will have access to a shared collaboration space in Vancouver, but our team is focused on fostering strong relationships and an equitable experience no matter where in the world you’re working.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out our careers page to learn more about what other benefits we offer!</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Vvp75OCtwa0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axiomzen/25c7ad75-61d2-42dc-b0b2-d8955fabfb3f/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194192/axiomzen1.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axiomzen@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5da21464-b527-48a0-a501-0b4f2e445537]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[SEO Copywriter (Russian)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKEx]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.okex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About OKEx:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKEx is a world-leading digital asset trading platform, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKEx provides hundreds of token &amp;amp; futures trading pairs to help traders to optimize their strategy. We are also one of the top digital asset trading platforms by trading volume, serving millions of users in over 100 countries. OKEx derivatives remains a top-notch venue globally and has a daily volume of approximately $10 billion and is widely recognized as the golden standard in the industry. We believe the blockchain technology will eliminate barriers to transactions, increase the efficiency of transactions across society, and eventually have a significant impact on the global economy. We strive to make innovative achievements that change the world and never stop to improve on our customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a highly motivated and result-oriented mixture of specialists with different backgrounds. What we value the most is the ability to learn, speak up and to collaborate. We are open, curious and we love to test even the craziest ideas and share our knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a tech-savvy Russian content writer to produce and manage stellar and unique content for both Google and Yandex. As a part of the team, you will be responsible for helping define the content strategy, write SEO copy for landing pages, perform keyword and&amp;nbsp; industry research and coordinate with various internal stakeholders to collect info needed and help create successful landing pages to help our user base.&amp;nbsp; We strongly believe that SEO is a crucial lever for our growth strategy; the topic has full support from top management including funding for tools and infrastructure. To be successful you will need to gain a significant understanding about the blockchain space and come up with innovative content ideas and write engaging copy to excite the community and help translate content into landing pages. You need to be a passionate content writer and creator who can think out of the box and be able to successfully convey what&#39;s unique about our brand to both technical and non technical audiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in building our SEO content strategy for our new landing pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform in depth analysis and keyword research to help unlock growth across our verticals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proofread and write content for blog posts, ads, press releases, articles, infographics, studies, website, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform basic SEO keyword research and incorporate the findings in the copy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce ideas for new content formats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Measure content performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce relevant content targeting both technical and non technical audiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research industry trends to gain a good technical understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Russian (written and spoken)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Journalism or Communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years experience as a copywriter and a portfolio with published content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have minimum 3 years experience in the tech space and very good technical understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain &amp;amp; crypto experience is a STRONG plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years working with SEO &amp;amp; Google Analytics is a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/x9kSkBMcOuo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okex/jobs/4839070003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175406/okex.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bcbc2afc-a2fd-45d8-bba3-e7ce4b53b3d8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKEx]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Social Media Lead - Global Corporate Comms]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing. We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual, and we want to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno welcomes crypto lovers and crypto newbies. You - just like everyone in the world - are on your own unique crypto-learning journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a mission-driven cryptocurrency company that is building more open and equal access to the future of money. You don&#39;t have to know lots about crypto to be interested in joining us, you just have to feel that upgrading the world to a fairer financial system matters, and that you&#39;d like to be part of this global change. We&#39;re a passionate and committed team taking on a challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people working together with unusual skill, focus and determination. We need the best team on board for our mission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If that sounds like a culture you&#39;d thrive in, then we are excited to hear from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno means moon in Esperanto, we chose the name because at night, wherever you are in the world, you look up at the same moon. We believe in the power of working together, as one team, across borders, with clear focus and shared purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our popular mobile app and website helps people around the world grow and manage their money using the world&#39;s most mature cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum and USDC. We&#39;ve processed over $ 21 billion to date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Over 9 million customers across 40 countries have chosen to hold their crypto wallets on Luno because we offer a delightfully simple experience and bank-grade security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re part of the Digital Currency Group, named in 2021 as one of TIME magazine&#39;s 100 Most Influential Companies, in the “Disruptors” category alongside Tesla, AirBnB, SpaceX, Peloton. TIME noted that DCG is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/collection/time100-companies/5953752/digital-currency-group/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;“mainstreaming cryptocurrency”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re proud to be one of the world&#39;s most international cryptocurrency teams, with colleagues from 43 different nationalities working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria, Australia and Singapore. Financial inclusion is part of our mission, but on a deeper level, inclusion is a way of life, and a way of work for us. It is part of who we are as a company, and a group of human individuals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role in a nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will be a lead resource on the global team at Luno which is responsible for all social media content distribution, community management, and reporting across multiple regions and on various platforms. Your chief responsibilities will be in curating content for Luno’s corporate brand on social channels, as well as engaging as Luno on social media so as to establish the brand as a trusted thought leader and employer of choice. Whether it be industry thinkpiece content, CEO amplification, engineering and product content, or employer branding, you will need to liaise with internal stakeholders to bring this content to life. You will report to the global head of social engagement, and be a part of the global social engagement team, stationed across many continents.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In addition to this, you will be required to take charge of the team for approximately 4 months when the head of the department will be on maternity leave. This will mean managing the regional team leads of our general social media brand presence, nurturing strong relationships with local and global stakeholders, and being answerable for the success of Luno’s social media channels during this time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deeply understanding the global corporate brand communication goals and using all moments of community engagement as an opportunity to further them both.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be the voice of the Luno corporate brand across all relevant social media channels. You will be our brand’s voice on all things crypto and Luno in order to drive an increase in corporate brand awareness through thought leadership, position Luno as an employer of choice, and maintain healthy online relationships with press and news contacts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will respond to all incoming queries, requests and complaints on our corporate comms channels, tailor responses to each individual that is engaged with, offering two-way genuine communication, follow crisis comms procedures should an incident arise, create synergy between the content we publish and the engagement in the comments, and collaborate with your peers and across the timezones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with global and local stakeholders to help craft the content calendar for the channels in your remit, manage publishing across these channels, and compile regular and ad hoc social media reports on wins &amp;amp; misses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Share best practices across your team as a senior member of the team, exploring new tools and processes, helping to develop efficient workflow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage the social engagement team as a maternity cover, and generally serve as a team 2iC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal Lunaut for this role will have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A wealth of experience in social media management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong people management skills and leadership competency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using social media engagement, reporting, and listening tools.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A wealth of experience and knowledge on social media best practices, trends, and post formats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good spelling and grammar, with a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; keen eye that pays attention to detail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written communication skills, with an understanding of how to translate complex topics and technologies into easy to understand messaging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Empathy and the ability to relate to others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good time management, knowing how to prioritise important and urgent matters to get the most out of a busy team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Initiative, knowing how to problem solve and think quickly on their feet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to work well in a team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno is a ‘remote but reachable’ company! At Luno, we trust that people can do their work effectively anywhere and provide Lunauts with the flexibility to decide where they do their best work. For some of us, that’s at home for the majority of the time, for others, that might mean joining other Lunauts in person at one of our Luno workspaces more often. Luno is built on our relationships, so we still value in-person connection and have a minimum expectation of spending time in person once a quarter. So as long as you are based in one country with a Luno workspace, we want to hear from you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not negatively discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3698248?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ankr]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ankr.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Amsterdam, North Holland, Netherlands]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>ABOUT ANKR</p><p>Ankr provides Web3 infrastructure for easy, accessible and affordable deployment of blockchain nodes, API’s, decentralized staking infrastructure and Layer 2 scaling solutions, designed to lower the entry barrier for everyday people, enterprises, and developers to contribute to blockchain ecosystems. Check us out at <a href="https://www.ankr.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://www.ankr.com/</a></p><p><br>Ankr was founded in 2017 in Berkeley, California. Its founding team and headquarters are based in San Francisco. Ankr’s distributed team of 50+ people operates from offices in San Francisco, Shanghai, Moscow, and Amsterdam.<br></p><p>Responsibilities:</p><ul> <li>Design, code and implement business applications</li> <li>Integrate blockchains with our platform</li> <li>Work with APIs and microservices</li> <li>Design and verify cryptographic protocols deployed on the blockchain</li> <li>Define requirements, prototype and design new features for product users</li> <li>Effectively communicate technical details via documentation and demonstration</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>Proven track record of developing modern, secure, scalable complex applications</li> <li>Practical experience with crypto tokenomics, blockchain consensus protocols, P2P networks, cryptographic principles, key management, encryption algorithms</li> <li>Ability to use <a href="https://web3.foundation/about/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Web3 tech stack</a> </li> <li>Familiarity or ability to use Solidity, EVM or Polkadot Substrate</li> <li>Back-end: GoLang (Go) (or C++/Rust)</li> <li>Great listener and communicator</li> <li>Bilingual or high fluency in English</li> <li>Leadership and teamwork skills</li> <li>Able to provide open source code samples</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/ankr/j/F6B8ACECFD/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/746707/ankr-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ankr@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3b58522a-6fba-41ac-b017-94bbed42523c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ankr]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://mythical.games/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;We are Mythical Games. A venture-backed next-generation game technology company at the intersection of video games and economics led by industry veterans. Our goal is to lead the industry with the launch of exceptional video game experiences that leverage distributed ledger technology while also providing a platform of robust tools that will allow any other game developers to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are seeking a &lt;strong&gt;Quantitative Analyst&lt;/strong&gt; to join our growing marketplace team of quants, developers and product leaders. This role will be primarily responsible for the design, development and operation of pricing and market-making algorithms across a growing portfolio of digital assets. We are looking for someone who is passionate about data, and knows how to solve problems using a mix of economic theory, quantitative modeling and their industry experience in a financial or ecommerce setting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop, monitor, and improve algorithms that provide liquidity on our marketplace; including models for asset valuation, pricing and fee optimization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop causal and predictive models to estimate supply and demand and improve fundamental understanding of the market&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, execute and evaluate pricing and economic experiments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze and assess new sources of internal and external data&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with product managers and ML engineers to productize data solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&#39;s degree in a technical field with exceptional academic credentials (e.g., Mathematics, EE/CS, Statistics, or Operations Research)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate to advanced Python development skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Python scientific computing packages (NumPy, SciPy, pandas, sklearn, PyTorch, JAX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of optimization methods, statistics, econometrics, and machine learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience contributing to risk and profitability decisions in a marketplace or ecommerce setting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MA/MS. in a technical field such as Mathematics, Statistics, Economics/Finance, EE/CS, or Operations Research, or bachelor’s degree with&amp;nbsp;1-3 years of experience in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the GCP suite, including BigQuery, Composer, and Cloud Functions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in and proficiency with blockchain solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for video games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our team values diversity and believes that it strengthens our games, products, and communities. We strongly encourage POC, folks with disabilities, those belonging to the LGBTQIA+ communities, and folks across all gender identities to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We offer our team benefits such as (but not limited to) high-quality Vision, Dental, and Health Care, generous Parental Leave, and Unlimited PTO to ensure that they actually take time off without the stress of needing to accrue time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need assistance around accommodations due to a disability, please reach out to accessibility@mythical.games. We’ll be with you as soon as possible; our goal is to ensure an accessible and equitable interview process for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Zfsp0FQ5X8s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/mythicalgames/jobs/4835235003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/351124/Mythical-Logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[info@mythical.games]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[541f8953-1749-4738-90d8-efd04dd286d1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Economist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://mythical.games/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;We are Mythical Games. A venture-backed next-generation game technology company at the intersection of video games and economics led by industry veterans. Our goal is to lead the industry with the launch of exceptional video game experiences that leverage distributed ledger technology while also providing a platform of robust tools that will allow any other game developers to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are seeking an&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Economist&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;to join our growing marketplace team of quants, developers and product leaders. This role presents an opportunity for a thoughtful economist to make direct contributions to our platform at scale. You will work with cross-functional teams of engineers, researchers, and data scientists, combining causal inference with business intuition to set the tactical and strategic direction of the product and broader business. You will design and support the development of consumer pricing products, market design tools, and decision-making and execution tools for our marketplace management operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leverage economic and econometric techniques to frame and answer questions about marketplace user preferences, supply and demand dynamics, and interactions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support the design, execution, and evaluation of pricing experiments and causal analysis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help set the experimentation roadmap in partnership with research, data, product teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use empirical and experimental data to improve the design of our data products, inventory management, and pricing operations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inform broad strategic and product direction by estimating and applying structural models of supply and demand to evaluate the general equilibrium effects of business decisions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate effectively with senior management and counterparts across the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;MA/MS. in Economics, Finance, or a related technical field with exceptional academic credentials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Intermediate to advanced Python development skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Python scientific computing packages (NumPy, SciPy, pandas, sklearn, PyTorch, JAX)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of optimization methods, statistics, econometrics, and machine learning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional problem-solving skills; able to work independently on long-term technical projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ph.D. in Economics and/or specialization in industrial organization and empirical microeconomics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-3 years of experience in industry or consulting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the GCP suite, including BigQuery, Composer, and Cloud Functions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience contributing to risk and profitability decisions in a marketplace setting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;High volume marketplace experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passion for computer games&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our team values diversity and believes that it strengthens our games, products, and communities. We strongly encourage POC, folks with disabilities, those belonging to the LGBTQIA+ communities, and folks across all gender identities to apply.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We offer our team benefits such as (but not limited to) high-quality Vision, Dental, and Health Care, generous Parental Leave, and Unlimited PTO to ensure that they actually take time off without the stress of needing to accrue time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you need assistance around accommodations due to a disability, please reach out to accessibility@mythical.games. We’ll be with you as soon as possible; our goal is to ensure an accessible and equitable interview process for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Zfsp0FQ5X8s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/mythicalgames/jobs/4835093003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/351124/Mythical-Logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[info@mythical.games]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[541f8953-1749-4738-90d8-efd04dd286d1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Backend Engineer, StraitsX]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Xfers]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.xfers.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About Xfers </b></div><div>Xfers as a part of Fazz Financial Group portfolio — a holding company of over 10 FinTech startups dedicated to enabling financial access for everyone — is on a mission to provide financial access to millions of underserved communities in Southeast Asia through building a financial ecosystem that anyone can participate in safely. Our range of last-mile financial rails power businesses across Southeast Asia - from startups to family businesses. By removing the pain of setting up and managing digital payments, more business owners can focus on growing their business, in turn encouraging fairer and healthier competition, and fostering stronger, more vibrant economies. For more information, visit: <a href="http://www.xfers.com" class="postings-link">www.xfers.com</a></div><div>But there is much more to do. We know how important our mission is to the improving the livelihoods of millions of people in Southeast Asia, and that's why we're looking for passionate and driven people to join us to accelerate financial access for everyone.</div><div><br></div><div><b>About StraitsX</b></div><div>The StraitsX team is building the payments infrastructure for Digital Assets in Southeast Asia. We aim to connect millions of individuals and businesses in the region to the Digital Assets market through our suite of products, including Xfers Wallet and Xfers Direct. In 2020, we released our first stablecoin, XSGD, the largest stablecoin in Asia by supply. </div><div><br></div><div>For more information, visit:&nbsp;<a href="https://www.xfers.com/sg/straitsx">https://www.xfers.com/sg/straitsx</a></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Work with fellow engineers, product managers and business owners in the team to ensure requirements are sound and met</li><li>Design and develop internal tools for business operations, including day-to-day transaction management and transaction monitoring</li><li>Build and maintain auditing tools to ensure the financial integrity of our digital wallet</li><li>Building and maintaining tools and processes to ensure that our digital wallet APIs has a high success and correctness rate</li><li>Develop and maintain our digital wallet, including the corresponding APIs to ensure the success of our clients</li><li>Safeguarding the security aspect of our digital wallet world-class to maintain our track record of zero hacking incidences</li><li>Keep pace with the developments of digital assets in the region</li><br/>Nice to Haves<br/><li>Experience with MVC frameworks such as Ruby on Rails, Laravel or Java Spring</li><li>Experience with managing complex sequences of background jobs and callbacks</li><li>Experience in developing on a large legacy production codebase</li><li>Experience in auditing, accounting and reconciling financial statements at scale</li><li>Experience in development in a zero-downtime CI/CD environment</li><li>Experience working in a blockchain environment in the region</li><div>We love reviewing all the applications we receive, but unfortunately, we may not be able to get back to everyone individually.&nbsp; If we’d like to move forward with your application, we’ll definitely be in touch!</div><div><br></div><div>Xfers is an equal opportunity employer. Individuals seeking employment at Xfers will be considered without regard to race, religion, national origin, age, sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, sexual orientation, marital status, medical condition, ancestry, physical or mental disability, or any other characteristic protected by applicable laws. </div><div><br></div><div>By submitting your application, you agree that Xfers may collect your personal data for recruiting, regional organization planning, and related purposes.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/xfers/d5e9851f-9c90-40b9-a07c-903f7f2ee567/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/597930/xfers_logo1.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[xfers@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b0a8343f-a5d7-46f6-beef-6fa07262d235]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Xfers]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Customer Support Associate EMEA]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.elliptic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>As digital assets and cryptocurrency become more widely adopted every day, our products are essential to ensure cryptocurrency is safe and accessible to all.  Our solutions help to prevent financial crime and allow cryptocurrencies to be used for good. Our products are used by some of the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, financial institutions and government agencies to screen over $1 billion of transactions every single week.  </p> <p>The company has offices in London, UK, New York City, Singapore and Tokyo. We are backed by Evolution Equity Partners, SoftBank, SBI Group, Albion VC, Octopus Ventures, SignalFire, Paladin Capital, Santander InnoVentures, and Digital Currency Group.</p> <p>To achieve our mission, we depend on our incredible team of Elliptites.  <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/life-at-elliptic" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Our values</a> are reflected in everything we do and every decision we make, both internally and outwardly to our customers.  We actively encourage Elliptities to challenge the status quo and allow the freedom to innovate and learn every day.  We encourage new ideas and learning, whether that’s through collaboration, our curiosity sessions, or utilising your professional development budget - personal growth is important to us all.  </p><p><strong>Do you have a passion for crypto &amp; blockchain? Do you love learning and immersing yourself in complex technology and then using your expertise to educate others? Are you experienced in customer facing roles? Are you looking for a values led company, which cares about the growth of its employees?</strong>  </p><p><strong>The impact you will have:<br></strong></p><p>As a Technical Customer Support Associate you will play a key role in supporting our growth and expansion in the region as a technical product expert in all things Elliptic and the ‘go-to’ person for our customer base. Through knowledge sharing, training and advice during the initial onboarding and on an ongoing basis you become a trusted advisor to our customers ensuring continued customer satisfaction.</p><p><strong>What you will do:</strong></p><ul> <li>Lead the day-to-day management of all customer support queries in line with SLAs, including; account maintenance, troubleshooting issues, training requests and general queries</li> <li>Be familiar with challenges faced by Elliptic’s customers in identifying, preventing and investigating criminal activity in digital assets; and map Elliptic solutions to those challenges</li> <li>Creatively identify and solve integration challenges to ensure “stickiness” of the Elliptic platform within the customer’s overall risk and compliance system architecture</li> <li>Work closely with the product and engineering teams to provide a feedback loop on new product development opportunities. </li> <li>Maintain a thorough understanding of our API documentation and capabilities to resolve customer queries and to manage prospect conversations</li> <li>Proactively monitor the automated customer onboarding journeys to assist Customer Success Managers in accelerating the time-to-value and reduce friction in the initial implementation process</li> <li>Internally manage the onboarding, monitoring and maintenance of Elliptic’s small to medium customer base, owning the success of the customers assigned to your region</li> <li>Report on ticketing data to influence our capacity planning and product roadmap, as well as detailed customer level reports to contribute to account business reviews</li> </ul><p><strong>What you will achieve in the first 6 months:</strong></p><ul> <li>Understand our products and empowered to respond effectively to customer support queries</li> <li>Run live training webinars for our SMB customers</li> <li>Successfully onboard customers to obtain value from our products</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><p><strong>You will be a great fit here if you:</strong></p><ul> <li>You love to learn about new technology and are curious about how things work under the hood</li> <li>Passionate about cryptocurrency and the future of finance</li> <li>Always take up the opportunity to broaden your knowledge and continuously improve and develop your skills</li> <li>Thrive working in an autonomous environment</li> <li>Firmly recognise that diverse and empowered teams make us stronger as individuals, a team and as a business</li> <li>Embody proactivity and are happy rolling up your sleeves and getting stuck in with everything required to support customers, from the day to day admin to representing Elliptic</li> <li>Exceptional and empathetic listener, and able to use this quality to truly understand the challenges your customers are facing</li> <li>You enjoy thinking creatively and problem solving under pressure</li> </ul> <p><strong>Our ideal candidate has:</strong></p><ul> <li>Experience in the B2B SaaS space or a complex technical market</li> <li>Experience working with and/or a demonstrable interest in crypto and blockchain</li> <li>Experience working with complex technical products</li> <li>Knowledge and understanding of crypto</li> <li>Demonstrated knowledge of API and backend systems design</li> </ul><p><strong>Bonus Points for:</strong></p><ul> <li>Experience with databases and data analysis</li> <li>Having worked in a startup and/or scaleup environment</li> <li>Ability to work in a second language (Spanish, Portuguese, French, Arabic, Mandarin, or Japanese)</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>Competitive salary</li> <li>Share Options</li> <li>Holiday - 25 days + public holidays</li> <li>Private Health Insurance - we use Vitality!</li> <li>Work Pension Scheme</li> <li>Quarterly full-day off-sites &amp; annual company 3-day offsite</li> <li>Personal training budget &amp; LinkedIn Learning subscription</li> <li>Hybrid working model: we require you to spend a minimum of 2 days each month in our London office, but for the rest of the time you can work from home, in the office or anywhere in the UK to suit your working preferences and personal commitments. At Elliptic you are responsible for managing your working hours and time. We trust and empower our employees to do their job. If you have childcare responsibilities, want to pick your children up from school, go to a yoga class or chop up your day into chunks, you can.</li> <li>Home office allowance</li> <li>Enhanced parental leave; we provide eligible employees, regardless of gender or whether they become a parent by birth or adoption, 16 weeks fully-paid leave and job-protected leave</li> <li>Full access to Spill Mental Health Support</li> <li>Our offices provide all of the amenities you could need</li> <li>Work with top of the range equipment - MacBook Pro and any other equipment you need</li> </ul><p><strong>We know Diversity and Inclusion is much deeper than just hiring, but it’s important for us to mention it here.  </strong></p><p>We welcome and embrace individuals of all backgrounds and identities at Elliptic, and this is an ongoing priority for us.  We know incredible people don’t all think in the same way.  We want to be challenged every day.  We believe our diverse team of individuals underpins this by bringing creative thinking and innovation to Elliptic every day.  We are committed to creating a diverse, inclusive and equitable workplace, so we welcome applications from everyone, even if you may not think you fit all of the requirements of our roles.  We foster an environment of psychological safety, where everyone feels comfortable to bring their whole self to work.</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ebOLNjlYiNg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/elliptic/j/45ABDA3BD0/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145877/elliptic.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[elliptic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[fefe721f-d5ba-4eb0-9b9b-f4156a27cb2b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer - Backend / Full Stack - US]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[f2pool & stakefish]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://stake.fish/en/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Palo Alto, California, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>As our Backend Developer, you will be designing, developing, and deploying software solutions that power various products at stake.fish. In this role, you will work closely with a group of talented product managers, UX designers, and other engineers to build the next generation of staking products. Your work will help with securing a wide range of blockchain networks and contribute to the bedrock of decentralization.<br></p><h3><br></h3><h3>What will you do? </h3><ul> <li>Build new services that meet critical product and business needs using TypeScript and node</li> <li>Develop smart contracts and services that interact with the smart contracts</li> <li>Build data ETL pipelines using Python</li> <li>Create scalable systems to solve different problems using modern cloud technology and industry best practices</li> <li>Create server code that is extensible, well-tested, and secure</li> <li>Leverage automated testing, CI/CD, container orchestration, and other modern development techniques</li> <li>Design database schema that is performant, scalable, and maintainable</li> <li>Proactively make suggestions and challenge the status quo for improving our products and internal processes</li> </ul><h3><br></h3><h3>What excites us about you? </h3><ul> <li>You have extensive experience in software engineering</li> <li>You have a track record of designing, creating, and maintaining production services</li> <li>You are passionate about blockchain technology and a decentralized future, and you are familiar with the technologies behind blockchains.</li> <li>Familiar with Typescript and node; have past experience with at least one of Python/C++/Java/Go/Rust.</li> <li>Familiar with cloud services (such as AWS)</li> <li>Familiar with Docker</li> <li>Able to work independently and set up an efficient development environment </li> <li>You are comfortable with ambiguity, able to take charge and get things done despite the unknowns</li> </ul><h3><br></h3><h3>What will be great to have? </h3><ul> <li>You are contributing to the open-source community</li> <li>You have working experience in a startup environment</li> <li>You have built financial, high reliability, or security systems</li> <li>You have experience with smart contracts / solidity (this is a plus but not required, and we will be happy to bring you up to speed on the job)</li> <li>You are willing to spend a part of your time working from our Silicon Valley office and the rest of your time working remotely.</li> </ul><h3><br></h3><h3>Why are we awesome you ask?</h3><p>We are truly at the forefront of the crypto ecosystem as maintainers of the infrastructure layer of blockchain networks! We practice the crypto team mentality by assembling a truly global and diverse team (with even pseudo anonymous team members). We collectively represent more than 12 different countries and are united in a single mission: building out the future of decentralization. Crypto is here to stay, having introduced novel ideas such as DeFi, NFTs and DAOs. At the core of all this are teams like us working relentlessly to build the necessary tools and applications that help run and secure blockchains. Here are some other reasons why you should join us,</p><ul> <li>We are one of the top staking service providers with over $3B of assets staked across our validators. E.g. Our staking market share for Cosmos rivals that of Binance and Coinbase.</li> <li>Curious about how protocols like Solana and Cosmos have exploded into the juggernauts they are today? We have front row seats to observe and learn how protocols evolve, going from idea to adoption. You will get opportunities to learn about and work very closely with a wide range of blockchain networks.</li> <li>We are crypto nerds at heart. Some people are power DeFi users and some others are intense NFT collectors. You can learn and debate everything on crypto with our teammates.</li> <li>We have some people who have been around this space for ages. They’ll casually drop a few interesting history lessons along the way. Did you know Bitcoin was actually double spent at one point in time?</li> <li>We are a very well capitalized and already profitable startup.</li> </ul><p>We are looking for fun, curious, and committed individuals to swim with us!</p><p>Requirements</p><p>Benefits</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/f2pool-stakefish/j/4384F99C8C/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/732239/f2pool_stakefish.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[f2pool@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[33981a68-3968-406e-a0b6-0c8956f5810a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[f2pool & stakefish]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crawler Development Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Asia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Participate in the design and development of crawler systems, capture and analyze multi-platform information, and improve and enhance crawler efficiency.</li><li>esearch various anti-crawling strategies, quickly solve various technical problems, and monitor crawler progress and early warning processing in real time.</li><li>Collaborate with the big data team to manage, analyze, analyze, and apply results.</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Solid foundation in Python or Java, familiar with multi-process and multi-thread programming.</li><li>Familiar with common crawler frameworks Scrapy, Selenium, Webmagic, Puppeteer/Pyppeteer, etc., and have a strong enthusiasm for new knowledge and technology.</li><li>In-depth understanding of HTTP and various login authentication mechanisms can solve problems such as image verification code/slider/account restriction/ip restriction.</li><li>Familiar with common anti-climbing strategies, experience in JS anti-climbing, APP anti-climbing, packet capture analysis, anti-climbing strategy detection, reverse and other fields is preferred.</li><li>Have a strong sense of responsibility and teamwork spirit, clear thinking, good communication skills and technical learning skills.</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/45a9783e-a99f-48ab-9d4a-887ddd5f1042/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Program Manager, NFTs]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ripple’s Creator Fund was developed to foster innovation in tokenization, with a focus on non-fungible tokens (NFTs). The fund provides targeted support for creators, brands and marketplaces to explore new use cases for NFTs on the XRP Ledger (XRPL), leveraging its innate advantages of speed, cost and sustainability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ripple is looking to hire a Program Manager for the Creator Fund program. As a member of the RippleX team, you will engage with external developers, agencies, creators, and brands to bring a diverse set of tokenization projects to the XRP Ledger. You will own the $250M Creator Fund, leading strategy and operational execution of the fund, and ensure all participants have an excellent experience from their application to execution of NFT projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build and own the operating model for administering $250M to NFT ecosystem participants building on XRPL.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Handle pre- and post-fund administration and oversight of projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage strategy and day to day execution with marketplaces, agencies, creators, and brands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the budget, planning, and allocation of resources across projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop streamlined approval processes with relevant internal stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive and ensure regular, ongoing communication and coordination across functions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate efficient meetings to ensure information exchange and alignment across teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor, analyze, and report on the fund applicants and their progress over time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define and measure success metrics, and assist with the preparation of progress reports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work collaboratively with Legal and Finance to create effective and efficient disbursement processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Recommend and contribute to process improvements, including product enhancements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate with Marketing to promote and drive applicants to ensure the ongoing success of the Creator Fund.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We’re Looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of work experience; 2+ experience in enterprise startup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in a fast paced start-up environment is a big plus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A strong interest, curiosity and passion for digital assets / crypto markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of the NFT ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience in managing global Grant/fund programs at scale.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience in implementing policies and procedures across various internal stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to build and manage relationships with creative agencies, developers, and creators and brands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding organizational abilities and interpersonal skills to develop strong working relationships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong background in marketing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serious attention to detail and commitment to excellence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactive, energetic and relentless towards driving progress.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding verbal and written communication skills.&amp;nbsp; Strong presentation skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent problem solving skills / comfort with ambiguity. You should be able to take a problem and structure a solution or recommendation with incomplete or limited data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent time management skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice &lt;/a&gt;and our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/ca-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;California Applicant Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; for reference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3707090?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of Founder Lab - OWC]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[NEAR]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://nearprotocol.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.openwebcollective.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Open Web Collective&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is an early-stage blockchain venture fund and accelerator.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; By bringing together capital and seasoned advisors, OWC helps founders de-risk, accelerate, and advance Web 3.0. During the three-month long program, our promising pre-seed and seed stage startups work with leading investors and corporate partners to validate and invalidate business ideas, build products, define and grow KPIs, develop product-market fit, and fundraise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our network consists of closely aligned teams, products, and organizations. We’re committed to building the open web: a transformed, decentralized digital world in which each creator and community benefits, not just a few companies. We believe that blockchain technology is a major piece of that transformation, and we work together to connect builders with mentors, solutions, capital—and each other.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Description:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;It’s not just about providing capital; it’s about scaling venture solutions by providing value-added support, piloting, and partnership opportunities to startups in our portfolio and pipeline. For early-stage companies, we focus on business fundamentals, management, and product-market fit. For later-stage companies, it’s all about growth, expansion, and deepening impact.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Director, Founder Lab provides strategic guidance and leadership to our venture building services. The Director, Founder Lab is the leader for the venture building support and resources globally and has a deep understanding of technology, startups, entrepreneurship, and venture capital.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities &amp;amp; Deliverables:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Head of Programs:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help outline a strategy, develop priorities, and measure and report on the impact of our programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with our partners to help with the delivery plan and execution of programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Overseeing identification and recruitment of experienced founders and program staff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop playbooks and resources for program use&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop strategies to sustainably scale the program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Keep track of program data and batch information&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Cultivate a culture of empathy and inclusion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relationship Management:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Grow the network of mentors, service providers, subject-matter experts, and program partners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Actively participate and represent OWC in the ecosystem by attending events and building relationships&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Community Management:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Listen, gather, and share community&#39;s feedback and opinions with the team to track community sentiment and provide actionable reports and recommendations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive community engagement by supporting the marketing team in planning and executing social events and resources for OWC community&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Alumni and Portfolio Support:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Consult and support portfolio companies as needed (ex. exploring new business models, incentive design, fundraising, hiring, introductions to corporates)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identifying emerging needs and opportunities faced by our portfolio companies and alumni and developing plans to address them&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborate with the Investment Team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help the investment team to proactively identify and assess various grants and investment opportunities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;6+ years in a fast-paced environments within technology, startups, entrepreneurship, and venture capital&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor&#39;s degree or equivalent combination of education and experience&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Desire to learn and teach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enjoy working with a global community and a fully remote team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice-to-haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ideally, you have some knowledge of or experience in the blockchain/Web3 ecosystem and/or collaborating with the open-source developer community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have founded and led a company or two in the past as the CEO.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/-hOWM-o7N5k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/near/jobs/5741324002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/291590/near-protocol-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[near@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[968fe95d-e05d-452b-ab80-880386c33b67]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[NEAR]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Development - Securities]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxos]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos is on a mission to enable the movement of any asset, any time, in a trustworthy way. Today’s financial infrastructure is archaic, expensive, inefficient and risky - supporting a system that leaves out more people than it lets in. So we’re rebuilding it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a regulated blockchain infrastructure company, we use technology to tokenize, custody, trade, and settle assets for enterprise clients like PayPal, Novi, Bank of America, and Interactive Brokers. Paxos is a top-funded blockchain company, with more than $500 million in total funding from leading investors like OakHC/FT, Founders Fund, PayPal Ventures, and Declaration Partners. Together, we empower today’s financial leaders to build a more open, trusted economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Paxos&lt;strong&gt; Securities&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;business&lt;/strong&gt; is expanding its team and needs business development experts to help drive change in the industry. Reporting to the head of business development for Securities, this role will own selling into and leading strategic client and partner relationships.The ideal candidate will have experience selling enterprise technology and owning relationships with complex organizations, as well as a strong interest in driving the adoption of the Paxos financial market infrastructure to replace the legacy infrastructure used today.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a Business Development Officer, you&#39;ll get to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Convert from an established pipeline to committed clients and partners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Take ownership of prospects and partners&#39; relationship with the firm.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Connect with new prospects and develop them into clients and partners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Navigate complex client organisations to identify and create relationships with key stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop account plans that drive customer adoption and loyalty.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help customers quantify the value and savings from a modern financial market infrastructure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide customer feedback to Product Management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage with industry groups as part of our marketing outreach.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your experience should include:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;7 plus years of experience selling enterprise software to a customer base of banks and brokers with an understanding of network sales&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A track record of building customer relationships in large enterprises while delivering on commercial goals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great communication skills to present our vision and win customer support.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You might also have:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Aptitude and interest to learn the deeper details of how clearing works.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated passion for driving innovation and change with little supervision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Transparent team player who shares information well.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortability working in a continuous evolving business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Business Development team will play a vital role in growing Paxos’s revenue and expanding our customer base.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Key to this role is an ability to understand Paxos technology, expertly communicate its benefits, and coach others to do the same. You and your team will need to win the trust of our potential clients by consultatively selling the value of the Paxos Platform.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll love about Paxos:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos has consistently been named as a “Best Place to Work” by BuiltIn and was listed on the 2021 Forbes Fintech 50. All of our employees have significant ownership and impact on our business, as well as benefits like company equity, health insurance, family leave, a $500 quarterly stipend for development, a $500 stipend for home office setup and unlimited PTO. From team product demos and virtual lounge and learns to care packages and an active Slack #shoutouts channel, there are countless opportunities to connect and make your mark. Help us continue to build a new, open financial system from one of our three offices or right from your home!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/10/19/usdp-chosen-for-novi-pilot/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;USDP Stablecoin Chosen for Facebook&#39;s Pilot of Novi Digital Wallet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/fintech/2021/#413b4e2631a6&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Forbes Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/13/paxos-supports-interactive-brokers-journey-into-crypto-markets/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Interactive Brokers&#39; Journey into Crypto Markets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/fintech-250-startups-most-promising/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CB Insights Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 250 for Crypto Category&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/30/trust-is-not-an-option-its-a-requirement-paxos-explains-its-unique-approach-to-pioneering-a-new-market/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Flourish Crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/23/paxos-national-trust-receives-occ-conditional-approval-for-de-novo-charter/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos National Trust Receives OCC Conditional Approval for De Novo Charter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/29/paxos-raises-300-million-in-series-d-funding-at-2-4-billion-valuation/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Raises $300M in Series D Funding at 2.4B Valuation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2020/10/21/paypal-launches-new-service-enabling-users-to-buy-hold-and-sell-cryptocurrency/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos &amp;amp; PayPal Bring Crypto to Millions of Users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Paxos team is made up of passionate people from all over the world with different perspectives and experiences. If this opportunity excites you, but your experience doesn’t perfectly match the description…apply! Unique voices help us build a more open, trusted economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com/careers/role/5709811002?gh_jid=5709811002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/215201/paxos.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxos@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c782dc3a-8644-40b8-919b-b98b0cb1b35f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxos]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Metaverse Product Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://swissborg.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Lisbon]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We’re SwissBorg, a fintech startup headquartered in Switzerland.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our flagship product, the SwissBorg app, offers over 450,000+ users the best price and liquidity across 15 fiat and 12 cryptos, as well as giving them the opportunity to earn passive income with our new Smart Yield account. And the community is growing fast, with over $1 billion in assets under management, weekly volume of over 250 million, and over 20,000 Premium users.</div><div><br></div><div>But that’s just the start in our mission to democratise wealth management by building products that allow individuals to manage their crypto assets at a touch of a finger. Whether you’re in Andorra or Zimbabwe, and whether your portfolio is worth one dollar or a million, SwissBorg gives you the best tools to learn about digital currencies and manage your wealth.</div><div><br></div><div>And this is where you come in...</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">What will the investment experience look like in the MetaVerse? In this future, investment opportunities are not only graphs, and individual wealth takes different shapes.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">Our vision is to build a global-scale platform where anyone will be able to align their investments with what they believe in, unlock new opportunities to increase their wealth, and enable communities to connect, engage and exchange values in all kinds of ways.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">As a Metaverse PO you’ll be at the forefront of prototyping, designing, and shipping content. You will work with teams of designers, artists, engineers and more to explore innovative core mechanics and game loops.</span></div><br/>What you might be doing:<br/><li>Reinvent the way we discover wealth</li><li>Gamification is too often only simple incentivization, you will bring gamification to the centre of the SwissBorg Ecosystem starting with the design of the purpose</li><li>NFTs</li><li>Research and stay abreast of all new NFT/crypto projects and global gaming brands signalling interest in the space</li><li>Understand and lead integrations with different blockchains and Ethereum Layer 2 environments</li><li>Collaborate with Scenarist, Tech</li><li>Dream big, ship fast (Fix long term objectives and be programmatic to iterate and learn fast)</li><li>Help establish preliminary processes to align cross-functional teams</li><li>Contribute to strategic decisions, working with the Design, Product and Executive teams</li><li>Partner with PMs, engineers, researchers, content strategists &amp; QA, overseeing the implementation of the user experience from product conception to launch - as well as post-launch design support</li><li>Advocate for Metaverse design within and throughout SwissBorg</li><br/>What you might bring:<br/><li>TBC</li><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Why you should apply: </b></div><div><br></div><div>- Freedom to build up the company that you’ve dreamed of</div><div>- Learn with (cool) experts in finance, engineering, AI, psychology and business</div><div>- CHSB bonus based on our meritocratic system</div><div>- We'll provide you with a Macbook and a cutting edge tech stack to help you do your best work</div><div>- Flexible work hours</div><div>- Annual team retreats with colleagues around the world.</div><div>- Continuous learning and development opportunities</div><div><br></div><div>Oh and are you planning on having a kid? That’s great! We have a bunch of those: you’ll get time off to enjoy that (other) adventure!&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><i>At SwissBorg, we embrace diversity. We strongly believe that getting to the best outcomes requires different perspectives and backgrounds. We’re committed to openness, curiosity and creating an inclusive culture as we know that diverse teams build better products and generate better ideas. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status.</i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/02lonwc5XE4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/swissborg/207c3899-20af-4e24-bcb1-b31f9409f0d0/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/440178/Swissborg-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[swissborg@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f4703261-2e7b-4b75-af19-fbdfc5e62c02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Investor Relations]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[teammanagerhead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Figure]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://figure.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, or New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Figure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Figure is transforming the trillion dollar financial services industry using blockchain technology.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In three short years, Figure has unveiled a series of fintech firsts using the Provenance blockchain for loan origination, equity management, private fund services, banking and payments sectors - bringing speed, efficiency and savings to both consumers and institutions. Today, Figure is one of less than a thousand companies considered a unicorn, globally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our mission requires us to have a creative, team-oriented, and supportive environment where everyone can do their absolute best. The team is composed of driven, innovative, collaborative, and curious people who love architecting ground-breaking technologies. We value individuals who bring an entrepreneurial mindset to every task and will embrace our culture of innovation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every day at Figure is a journey in continuous learning yet a daily focus on getting work done that makes a difference. Join a team of proven leaders who have already created billions of dollars in value in the FinTech space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/americas-best-startup-employers/#6535f31b6527&quot;&gt;Forbes America’s Best Startup Employers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaeldelcastillo/2020/02/19/blockchain-50/?sh=60e7347c7553&quot;&gt;Forbes Top 50 Blockchain Companies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210520005738/en/Figure-Raises-200-Million-Series-D-Co-Led-by-10T-Holdings-and-Morgan-Creek-Digital&quot;&gt;Figure Series D Announcement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Figure is looking for a Head of Investor Relations to lead our company vision and strategy for delivering shareholder value.&amp;nbsp; If you are looking for an opportunity to develop and create a robust investor relations strategy from the ground floor, this role is for you.&amp;nbsp; This role will require a corporate professional who also has entrepreneurial skills and looks to the future with optimism to envision what could be possible.&amp;nbsp; Success in this role will require collaboration, communication, leadership and vision.&amp;nbsp; A driven, self-starter who is confident in taking responsibility and taking projects to completion with minimal guidance will be successful in this role. The successful candidate will engage, develop, and maintain positive interactions with the investment community on behalf of Figure.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop investor confidence and belief in Figure’s vision and strategy for delivering shareholder value&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and execute on a robust investor relations strategy and framework&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create and manage strong reputation by demonstrating consistent and clear communication between internal and external parties&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage equity research and investor relationships&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide insights on market activity and present them to the leadership team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analyze and present financial trends, competitor behavior, shareholder issues, and anything else that could impact the business&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop key investor relations materials in collaboration with senior leadership in the preparation of quarterly updates, presentations, board meetings, and other contact points.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor operational changes through ongoing contacts with company management and develop investor relations messages based on these changes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Conduct industry and competitor research and provide senior leadership with ongoing feedback from the investment community.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with legal counsel to ensure compliance on regulatory matters&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Look For&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A Bachelor’s degree in business, finance, or accounting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;MBA or FMVA Certification a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;8 + years of experience dealing with investors and a strong track record of creating a positive relationship with the investor community, ideally in financial services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong understanding of SEC laws and securities disclosure requirements, as well as filing requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Thorough familiarity with financial modeling techniques and valuation methods used by analysts and investors&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong understanding of macroeconomics, competitor activities, industry dynamics and customer trends&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Entrepreneurial mindset as well as client/investor focused&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to thrive in a fast-paced startup environment and practice independent judgment to plan, prioritize, and organize a diversified workload&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exceptional interpersonal skills, creative problem solving and keen judgment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Superb written and verbal communication to effectively engage and inspire employees and investors.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits and Perks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary and growth opportunities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company quarterly performance based bonus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Equity stock options package&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employer funded comprehensive health, vision, dental insurance and wellness program for employees and their dependents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Employer funded life and disability insurance coverage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company HSA, FSA, Dependent Care, 401k, and commuter benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 12 weeks paid family leave&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In office, remote, and hybrid work location options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Home office and technology stipend for those working outside of a traditional office more than 75% of the time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible time-off plan to empower employees to take the time off that they want and need&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuing education reimbursement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Routine Team swag deliveries!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Depending on your&amp;nbsp;residential location&amp;nbsp;certain laws might regulate the way Figure manages applicant data.&amp;nbsp;California Residents, please review our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a class=&quot;c-link&quot; href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1eDhTkvbpFETeAvGpsB8e6KzaXES4BWNB/view?usp=sharing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-stringify-link=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1eDhTkvbpFETeAvGpsB8e6KzaXES4BWNB/view?usp=sharing&quot; data-sk=&quot;tooltip_parent&quot;&gt;California Employee and Prospective Employee Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for further information.&amp;nbsp;By submitting your application, you are agreeing&amp;nbsp; and&amp;nbsp;acknowledging&amp;nbsp;that you have read and understand the above notice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Figure will not sponsor work visas for this position. In compliance with federal law, all persons hired will be required to verify identity and eligibility to work in the United States and to complete the required employment eligibility verification form upon hire.&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/WgGXwItJTPE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/figure/jobs/5741870002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/174795/figure.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[figure@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f8d02b76-9066-4951-b8c2-8a565502edd0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Figure]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sofia, Sofia City Province, Bulgaria]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>We are Foris Europe - the operational power of Crypto.com.</p><p>Crypto.com is redefining how money is being moved, spent and invested. Crypto.com is democratizing blockchain technology by designing beautiful, simple and useful financial services that have a lasting, positive impact on people’s lives.</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p><ul> <li>Project Delivery Support;</li> <li>Provide technical support for the CS team during the delivery of applications;</li> <li>Work to agreed project schedules;</li> <li>Ensure working and technically acceptable solutions are delivered;</li> <li>Provide support for the CS team relating to client software installations and subsequent pre live testing; </li> <li>Liaise, on a regular basis, with CS Project Manager and Application Analyst as to the progress of assignments;</li> <li>Prompt escalation of issues to Application Analyst in order to allow implementation of appropriate action and prevent internal escalation;</li> <li>Undertake an effective Handover of the application and system knowledge to other support functions. Identify key issues encountered during the delivery and actions taken;</li> <li>Provide support to the CS team during the initial period of live operation.</li> <li>Release management;</li> <li> Create and test software releases inline with procedures;</li> <li> Planning of activities to be undertaken in relation to a release;</li> <li>Resolve CS queries following a release;</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><p><br></p>    <ul> <li>1+ years of relevant experience;</li> <li>Bachelor’s degree;</li> <li>Proficiency in verbal and written English.</li> <li>Impeccable attention to detail;</li> <li>Strong analytical skills;</li> <li>Ability to be a self-starter, work under minimal supervision, and meet all goals within SLA;</li> <li>Self-motivated, attentive to detail and not afraid but excited from often changes;</li> <li>Multitasker, not afraid of a highly dynamic environment and constant change;</li> <li>Fast learner with an eye to synthesize details and connect the dots between complex data relationships;</li>  <li>Strong analytical and problem-solving skills.;</li> <li>Excellent organizational and time management skills;</li> <li>Detail-oriented.</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you!</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team.</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing a brand new product from scratch alongside a talented team.</li> </ul>            <p><br></p><p>If you meet the requirements above and feel ready to dive into our challenging dynamics, by joining the Foris Europe's team on a permanent contract basis, we are looking forward to receiving your CV in English by applying below.</p><p><br></p><p>Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted with information on the next steps of our application process.<br></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/625F8C8FF8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[careers@crypto.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Designer - Contract Position]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kiva]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.kiva.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[U.S Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kiva (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://kiva.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;kiva.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;) &lt;/span&gt;is an international nonprofit with a mission to expand financial access to help underserved communities thrive. We run a global marketplace platform to crowdfund microloans for financially excluded entrepreneurs, farmers and students around the world. &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Through Kiva Capital, we serve as a bridge between large scale impact first investors and underserved populations. Our digital identity platform enables borrowers who don’t have a track record with traditional financial institutions to record and verify their financial history and gain access to less costly mainstream financial markets. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our organization combines the culture and technological passion of an internet start-up with the compassion and empathy of a non-profit to create impact and opportunity at global scale. &lt;/span&gt;Since 2005, we have raised more than $1.66 billion in loan capital for 4.1 million borrowers in 77 countries. Our lenders fund over $10 million in loans every month. With offices in San Francisco, Portland, New York, Nairobi, and Bangkok, Kiva&#39;s team includes 100+ employees and 400+ volunteers worldwide. Our team is growing as we pursue exciting new opportunities to create a financially inclusive world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role overview:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is for a 4 - 6 month, remote contract position working for the Creative Studio at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kiva.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kiva&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; (kiva.org) - starting as soon as feasible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Contract Senior Designer, you’ll partner with Kiva’s Creative Studio team. The Creative Studio designs, writes and executes marketing campaigns to drive awareness of Kiva and acquisition of new lenders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Senior Designer/ Contractor will work directly with the Creative Director. You’ll also work closely with other designers and writers on the Studio team, as well as cross-functionally with the Marketing and Content teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At this time, we can only consider applicants with authorization to work in the United States on a permanent, full-time basis; unfortunately we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key responsibilities include:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop concepts for, and design creative, as part of our Tentpole and Evergreen campaigns. Campaign elements include email, social media posts, web and mobile UX, landing pages, and other channels as they are needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bring to life the Kiva story and develop communications that engage consumers with emotive design,&amp;nbsp; while driving acquisition of new lenders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work collaboratively with other members of the creative team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Absorb Kiva Brand style guide and design within those guidelines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create engaging animations for campaign elements and catalog them in Google Drive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work within our Project Management tool to complete tasks on time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work on multiple campaigns and deliverables at once with ease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Regularly bring new ideas to the team, have a curious mindset, and a desire to always improve our creative.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a small team, the Senior Designer Contractor needs to actively look for places to help others and be willing to jump in on tasks when asked for help.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help mentor other designers on the team, providing feedback and guidance based on your experiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5-7 years of experience designing marketing creative at an agency or in-house creative studio.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to decipher a brief and convert that into compelling, succinct designs/ concepts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with documentary-style/human-centric storytelling creative/ emotive design.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A clear understanding of advertising/marketing/ direct response design best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with designing a variety of channels - social, email, website, mobile, landing pages with a thorough understanding of best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong proficiency in designing in Figma.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using Google Suite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A curious nature (ask questions and learn).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ideally 30-40 hrs/week with some flexibility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A competitive hourly rate paid on a monthly billing cycle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully remote working, anywhere within the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An opportunity to improve real lives, solve hard problems, and change the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Friendly, supportive, and adventurous environment with a team of engaged colleagues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Opportunities to connect with and learn from colleagues and partners around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When applying:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please submit a resume or LinkedIn (or other) profile that showcases your work history and experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please include samples of relevant work that you have done - samples that showcase how you would be a good fit for working on Kiva campaigns.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A diverse and inclusive workplace where we learn from each other is an integral part of Kiva&#39;s culture. We actively welcome people of different backgrounds, experiences, abilities and perspectives. We are an equal opportunity employer and a great place to work. Join us and help us achieve our mission!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We will only accept applications directly from candidates. Kiva will not be responsible for any recruiting agency fees, absent a formal agreement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/IEdy6XHkd9k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/kivaorg/jobs/3714314?gh_jid=3714314&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194099/kiva.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kiva@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[12467ec7-a781-4b48-abdb-bfbbc2a9cc79]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kiva]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Account Executive, Public Sector, Nordics]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Copenhagen, Denmark | Aarhus, Denmark]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The sales team responsible for our Nordic&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Law Enforcement / Central Government&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; customers is driven by our mission to make the world a safer place by tracking and investigating activities that involve cryptocurrency like human trafficking, terrorist financing, and money-laundering. We’re experts on the “why” and the “how” with deep relationships and knowledge of navigating government sales processes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Account Executives are servant leaders who can quickly establish trust and build strong relationships with the Public Sector stakeholders, tailoring their sales approach to their needs, and evangelizing Chainalysis solutions in a compelling yet approachable way. We measure success by the attainment of assigned quota, accuracy of forecasting, and the growth of accounts in your region. They are experts at navigating complex sales cycles. and still enjoy the thrill creating a calculated account plan and then closing a deal. We measure your success by your ability to accurately forecast revenue and hit (read: exceed) quotas and the engagement of your team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve upskilled the team’s ability to drive sales wins by participating in and leading client and prospect meetings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Stakeholders across the sales teams and rest of the company trust you and are eager to support and provide resources to your team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve built transparent and valuable relationships with your team and have developed an effective and efficient strategy for recruiting, hiring, and training new Account Executives on the sales motion at Chainalysis.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your team has a reliable cadence for rhythm for forecast meetings and each team member’s forecast is accurate and documented in Salesforce.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your team’s closure rates have increased and customer churn has decreased because of your direct coaching and mentorship.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Senior sales management can trust and rely on your forecasts and sales activity to inform the overall sales strategy across the business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You know the intricacies of your teams’ sales activity and track the results to inform your forecasts and individual development plans.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Recent experience managing and closing complex software sales within Public Sector customers in any of the Nordic markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing the sales cycle from mission/program manager to agency leadership&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong relationships in the System Integrator and Defense community&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Key industry knowledge and ability to effectively articulate the Chainalysis value proposition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track record of over-achieving quota (top 10-20% of company) in past positions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to negotiate pricing, terms and conditions and other concessions in complex, multi-year sales agreements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;History of scaling and coaching high-performing and diverse sales teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Financial Intelligence, Blockchain, Cyber Security, and/or Cryptocurrency technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-MJ1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yNpNz-FvSYQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5742950002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Manager, Customer Support, Credit Card]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Gemini]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York; Portland, Oregon; Chicago, Illinois; Los Angeles, California; San Francisco, Cal]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Empower the Individual Through Crypto&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gemini is a crypto exchange and custodian that allows customers to buy, sell, store, and earn more than 30 cryptocurrencies like bitcoin, bitcoin cash, ether, litecoin, and Zcash. Gemini is a New York trust company that is subject to the capital reserve requirements, cybersecurity requirements, and banking compliance standards set forth by the New York State Department of Financial Services and the New York Banking Law. Gemini was founded in 2014 by twin brothers Cameron and Tyler Winklevoss to empower the individual through crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto is about giving you greater choice, independence, and opportunity. We are here to help you on your journey. We build crypto products that are simple, elegant, and secure. Whether you are an individual or an institution, we want to help you buy, sell, and store your bitcoin and cryptocurrency. Crypto is not just a technology, it&#39;s a movement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, our mission is to &lt;strong&gt;empower the individual&lt;/strong&gt; and that includes giving our employees flexibility of choice — our Office Optional Policy allows employees to choose to work from one of our physical locations or from home.&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Select roles that are location-specific will still be eligible for flexible schedules.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Department: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;Support&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Support team is a group of highly talented and dynamic contributors. Each individual ensures that our customers have the best experience possible when they need help, have a question, or provide feedback. The team efficiently manages all inbound service requests and communications with customers during the onboarding process and are increasingly contributing to outbound communications.&amp;nbsp; While their main focus is retail customers, they are progressively interacting with institutional customers. During periods of low-service volume, the team also eagerly takes on support-centric projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Role: &lt;/strong&gt;Manager, Customer Support, Credit Card&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, our Support Associates work alongside the brightest minds in a fast-paced and evolving industry. They ensure excellent service standards, respond efficiently to customer inquiries, and maintain high customer satisfaction.We are looking for a brilliant, self-motivated, personable hands-on individual who is hungry and eager to learn. The ideal candidate is a highly organized detail-oriented, self-starter with the desire to make an immediate impact and the ability to work through the unexpected. You will be part of building the Gemini Credit Card email support team and have the chance to make an impact to the growth of this team and how Credit Card customer support is run at Gemini.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide leadership, coaching, and development for a team of multi channel Customer Service Agents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Accountable for hiring, supervision, training, and development of customer support agents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform Quality Assurance Scoring of customer contacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure a strong understanding and fulfillment of regulatory guidelines within financial call centers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist in management of an outsourced Customer Support&amp;nbsp; to ensure customers get the same level of service from internal and outsourced customer service agents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist in generation and review of monthly reporting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify improvement opportunities in the customer experience and plan and execute activities to pursue these opportunities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serve as an escalation point for vendor and customer issues&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist the Head of Operations with customer support strategy and implementation as we scale the customer support function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Maintain procedures and process documentation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent verbal, written, and interpersonal communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of experience with at least 2 years of customer support management experience.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Financial service experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with multichannel customer support&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Zendesk&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work in fast paced changing environments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Credit Card Customer Support experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fintech experience &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It Pays to Work Here&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We take a holistic approach to compensation at Gemini, which includes:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Compensation and Profit-Sharing Equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Retirement Plan Matching&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous Parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive health plans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Training and professional development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Gemini, we strive to build diverse teams that reflect the people we want to empower through our products, and we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, color, ancestry, religion, sex, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship, marital status, disability, gender identity, or Veteran status. Equal Opportunity is the Law, and Gemini is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace and affirmative action employer. If you have a specific need that requires accommodation, please let a member of the People Team know.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-DPL1&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/70jrfYSxKC4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://gemini.com/jobs/job_id?gh_jid=3696512&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144616/gemini.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[gemini@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b400b40b-6d2f-4796-aa2a-d62d33520384]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Gemini]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Developer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[graduatetrainee]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[DRW]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://drw.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Our formula for success is to hire exceptional people, encourage their ideas and reward their results.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Quantitative Developer&lt;/strong&gt;, you will implement software solutions that use advanced statistical methods and have a direct impact on automated trading strategies across multiple asset classes. You will work closely with our Quantitative Researchers on idea generation and development and will be able to solve challenging technological problems. You will have access to cutting-edge technology, hardware and grid computing and will be given immediate responsibility. We do not require prior experience in financial markets and will give you the training required to be successful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How you will make an impact...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design, develop, test and deploy proprietary software solutions for complex algorithmic trading systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Optimize large scale data processing and modelling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with researchers to translate research-based trading strategies into production software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build software to manage risk and execution of our trading system&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Automate human-decision based trading strategies and implement algorithmic trades from trading ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage day-to-day technology requirements of our proprietary trading systems and evaluate new technologies to improve on the current stack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will be at home if you have...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A degree in a technical discipline such as mathematics, physics, engineering or computer science with a focus on statistics, optimization and signal processing graduating between December 2021 and August 2022 (Bachelor&#39;s, Master&#39;s, PhD)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent software development skills in Python, Java or another modern language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong problem-solving and statistics skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skills in asynchronous and multi-threaded software; handling, maintaining and processing large data sets; and network programming&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong understanding of object-oriented design, data structures and algorithms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The proactive ability to take the lead on assignments and deliver practical results in a timely manner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRW &lt;/strong&gt;is a technology-driven, diversified principal trading firm. We trade our own capital at our own risk, across a broad range of asset classes, instruments and strategies, in financial markets around the world. As the markets have evolved over the past 25 years, so has DRW – maximizing opportunities to include real estate, cryptoassets and venture capital. With over 1,000 employees at our Chicago headquarters and offices around the world, we work together to solve complex problems, challenge consensus and deliver meaningful results. It’s a place of high expectations, deep curiosity and thoughtful collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For more information about DRW&#39;s processing activities and our use of job applicants&#39; data, please view our Privacy Notice at &lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;California residents, please review the&amp;nbsp;California Privacy Notice&amp;nbsp;for information about certain legal rights at&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;#LI-HF1&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MdwEImeQcx8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/drweng/jobs/3712650?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145892/drw.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[drw@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bf32acf8-cf47-410b-aa59-74974c4d6afd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[DRW]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Director, Regulatory Security and Technology Risk]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[directorvp]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Circle]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.circle.com/de/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Las Vegas - will also consider remote in US]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Circle is a global financial technology firm that enables businesses of all sizes to harness the power of digital currency and public blockchains for payments, commerce and financial applications worldwide. Circle platforms and products provide a suite of internet-native financial services for payments, treasury infrastructure and capital formation. Circle is also a principal developer of USD Coin (USDC), which has become the fastest growing dollar digital currency in the world. USDC has grown to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;over 35 billion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in circulation and supported over&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; $1.3 trillion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in transactions in the past year. Circle’s payments and treasury infrastructure services available through the Circle Account and APIs helps bridge the legacy financial system and digital currency and blockchain based finance.&amp;nbsp; Circle’s SeedInvest service brings internet-native fundraising and capital formation to startups and growth companies.&amp;nbsp; Combined, Circle’s suite of services helps companies to participate in a more open, global and inclusive financial system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be part of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;With the mission “To raise global economic prosperity through the frictionless exchange of financial value,” Circle was founded on the belief that the internet, blockchains and digital currency will rewire the global economic system, creating a fundamentally more open, inclusive, efficient and integrated world economy.&amp;nbsp; We envision a global economy where people and businesses everywhere can more freely connect and transact with each other with new technologies for digital money and internet-native finance. We believe such a system can raise prosperity for people and companies everywhere. Our mission is powered by the values we espouse and which we expect all Circlers to respect. We are Multistakeholder, serving the needs of our customers, our shareholders, our employees and families, our local communities and our world. Furthermore, we are also Mindful, Driven by Excellence, and High Integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be responsible for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Senior Director, Regulatory Security and Technology Risk is a high-impact role for a passionate leader who thrives by connecting the dots between technology, security, regulations, and controls.&amp;nbsp; In this role, you will be responsible for building the team that documents and advises on information security and technology risk management processes, controls, policies, and procedures.&amp;nbsp; You will be responsible for managing Circle’s responses to audits, regulatory examinations, customer assessments, and other assurance activities.&amp;nbsp; You will work closely with peers from Compliance, Enterprise Risk Management, Internal Audit, Engineering, and Finance to ensure that controls are designed correctly and operate effectively, conduct risk assessments, and remediate issues.&amp;nbsp; You will report on the success of the program using metrics and liaise with regulators and customers as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll work on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner strategically with department heads and build functional relationships with peers across the organization to understand their processes, risks, and controls.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build a team of high performing professionals to deliver the responsibilities of this role at pace with business growth.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead projects to document, automate controls and control tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with other second-line risk management functions including Legal, Compliance, and Enterprise Risk Management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop processes and procedures to ensure compliance with regulations, industry best practices, and customer obligations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write documentation such as processes, control narratives, policies, and procedures.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Consult on the design, implementation, and operation of technology risk management and information security controls.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Plan and lead the design, implementation, and operation of automated and manual control tests.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Test controls to ensure operating effectiveness.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Plan and lead threat modeling, risk assessment, security assessments, and security testing projects; collaborate with system and process owners to mitigate identified risks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish and enforce security standards for adoption and integration with SaaS and cloud-based solutions; ensure CUECs are fully implemented.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead Circle’s response to audits, regulatory exams, and customer assessments, as it relates to information security and technology risk.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive technology projects that implement controls or mitigate identified issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will aspire to our four core values:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multistakeholder - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you have dedication and commitment to our customers, shareholders, employees and families and local communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mindful - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek to be respectful, an active listener and to pay attention to detail.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driven by Excellence - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you are driven by our mission and our passion for customer success which means you relentlessly pursue excellence, that you do not tolerate mediocrity and you work intensely to achieve your goals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Integrity - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek open and honest communication, and you hold yourself to very high moral and ethical standards.&amp;nbsp; You reject manipulation, dishonesty and intolerance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll bring to Circle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor&#39;s degree in computer science, computer engineering, cybersecurity or related field; equivalent experience also accepted.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;13+ years of overall technology or compliance experience with a minimum of five years (can be overlapping) with a focus on cybersecurity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;7+ years of management experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Certifications such as CISSP, CISA, CISM or similar will receive favorable consideration but are not required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enthusiasm for scalable, reproducible controls operation and risk management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven team building and team leadership experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong ability to work collaboratively across teams with quickly changing priorities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Self-motivated and creative problem-solver able to work independently with minimal guidance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage multiple competing priorities and use good judgement to establish order of priorities on the fly.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with standards such as ISO 27001/27002 or the NIST Cybersecurity Framework required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with regulators such as the OCC, SEC, NYDFS, FCA, MAS, and BMA required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SOC 1 / SOC 2 experience required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SOX controls experience is highly desirable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with contemporary privacy regulations including GDPR and CCPA highly desirable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in financial services or financial technology required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to use Python to automate repetitive tasks is highly desirable.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience/familiarity with Google Suite, Slack and Apple MacOS preferred. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;equal opportunity employer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and value diversity at Circle. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/KEvenCaIq70" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/circle/jobs/5744939002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143132/circle.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[circle@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[e4722b14-c590-4410-b876-45bc581c49c8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Circle]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Fullstack Engineer - Matrix]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CertiK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://certik.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York / Seattle / Bay Area / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 11pt">Why Us?</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">CertiK is the leading blockchain security company. Our clients include leading projects such as Aave, Polygon, Binance Smart Chain, Terra, Yearn, and Chiliz. We just raised over $60 million in Series B and B+ funding rounds in 2021. Our investors include top VCs like Tiger Global, Coatue Management, Shunwei Capital, and Hillhouse Capital as well as industry leaders like Coinbase Ventures and Binance.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">About you</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You are the ninja coder who can put an entire system in your mind and quickly figure out a plan to prototype it. You take pride in constructing something pleasing to look at the frontend and elegant at the backend. You enjoy using new technologies and at the same time understand that boring technology is sometimes the best choice.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You are experienced in building a sizable website from scratch and you are driven to challenge yourself. You understand the complexity of continuously improving a website and the organizational complexity in achieving both iteration speed and reliability.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You have a deep understanding of API design and can articulate the pros and cons of various design methodologies. Possibly, you are excited by cool effects and data visualization. You are exposed to related fields such as web security and performance engineering. You write well-tested code and are familiar with CD/CI.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You are a team player and love sharing your knowledge and coaching others. You emphasize personal growth but also put the company's interest first. You do what is right and are bold in taking action and lead. You take the extra mile to deliver with exceptionally high quality or with extremely fast speed.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 10.5pt">About the role</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will own and build the data team's API. The API is currently written in type-graphql but we might add REST and pubsub interface in the future. There might be customers consuming the API both inside and outside the company. In the simplest sense, the API will be a thin layer bridging up the schema with the internal data sources but it could become more sophisticated. You will be responsible for architecting and keep improving the API.</span>&nbsp;<span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will prototype various data features. This could come in the form of data visualization. In short, we want to figure out how the rich offering of our data can be best presented.</span>&nbsp;<span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will also be our local expert on building web tools. Most of such tools would be internal facing. You will help architect such tools and coach other engineers in building out such tools.</span></div><div><br></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Own, architect and develop data team's API fronting various internal data sources</li><li>Explore and define customer needs, collaborate with data scientists and engineers to add data offerings to the API to solve customer pain points</li><li>Own and drive the API's schema design</li><li>Own and drive the API's security and performance engineering</li><li>Collect metrics to understand the API's health and to identify areas for improvement</li><li>Fast-prototype data presentation on the frontend</li><li>Architect and coach other engineers on the internal tools building</li><li>Write succinct documentation</li><li>Present the work to a general audience in the company</li><br/>Qualifications<br/><li>5+ years of experience building websites, both frontend, and backend</li><li>Strong experience in fast prototyping</li><li>Experience in building a sizable website from scratch</li><li>Experience in building scalable API, in either REST or GraphQL</li><li>Strong experience in ReactStrong experience in JavaScript, or preferably, TypeScript</li><li>Experience in website security and performance engineering</li><li>Experience in website reliability engineering</li><li>Experience in website CD/CI</li><br/>Preferred Qualification<br/><li>Familiarity with blockchain and cryptocurrency</li><li>Familiarity with web3.js</li><li>Experienced in a hardware-accelerated web visualization</li><li>Deep expertise in performance engineering</li><li>Familiarity with GraphQL</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/aEn2UaqeHho" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/certik/7f7750df-0ef2-4f55-83de-c6f128619075/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/452745/CertiK-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[certik@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f6c22067-35b7-4b78-a01c-cb1e9232298a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CertiK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Manager, Blockchain Security - Research and Engineering]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase has built the world&#39;s leading compliant cryptocurrency platform serving over 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries. With multiple successful products, and our vocal advocacy for blockchain technology, we have played a major part in mainstream awareness and adoption of cryptocurrency. We are proud to offer an entire suite of products that are helping build the cryptoeconomy and increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for signals that a candidate will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, disrupt ourselves, and expect sustained high performance because we play as a championship team. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people with the desire and capacity to build and share expertise in the frontier technologies of crypto and blockchain, in whatever way is most relevant to their role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Security is a primary competency at Coinbase, and the Security Team keeps a watchful eye over every aspect of it. Every day, we go to battle against some of the most sophisticated attackers in the world to protect billions of dollars worth of digital assets and ensure that our customers and employees can enjoy a safe, trusted experience. As Coinbase scales globally, our team is scaling along with it, using a blend of tooling, automation, and strategic team growth to ensure that we’re well-equipped to protect the next billion users of crypto.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain Security (BlockSec) team’s mission is to Secure funds and data from protocol through wallet. Coinbase has a unique opportunity: enabling our customers to easily and securely interface with blockchains, a.k.a. digital asset networks, a.k.a. cryptocurrencies.&amp;nbsp; Blockchains are a cutting edge technology, with many unique security considerations for any entity that supports interaction with them.&amp;nbsp; Understanding those unique considerations requires deep expertise in blockchains and the ability to maintain that expertise over time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Blockchain Security - Research and Engineering Manager’s responsibility is to identify trends in Blockchain Security and develop minimum viable products to improve Blockchain Security team’s performance through automation, tooling, or process. The role includes:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify trends in Blockchain security using external research in the industry, security incidents and risk identified by Blockchain Security&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Propose solutions and develop MVPs to automate risk identification, management, and mitigation processes&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with BlockSec Operations team to understand heuristics for risk identification and automations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide solutions to achieve 10x scale in BlockSec operations&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ideation and experimentation to develop BlockSec product roadmap&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with BlockSec Platform team to scale the BlockSec products&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with our talent organization to source and hire amazing engineers who will expand the Coinbase culture and products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coach your direct reports to develop novel automation solutions to support BlockSec scaling&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with cross functional partners to prioritize product features&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Set clear targets and objectives, and establish KPIs for the team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What we&#39;re looking for in you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 2 years experience in managing versatile security teams that have had to adapt to the changing needs of a business experiencing rapid growth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 6 years experience and solid foundation in security topics such as product security, application security, security operations, or third party security&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expertise in security research, security product ideation and developing MVPs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expertise in building and leading a security research and engineering team with the ability to provide hands-on technical guidance to the team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience or willingness to research BlockSec risks and risk identification and mitigation methods to develop repeatable innovation&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have knowledge of engineering/tooling and ability to quickly develop working prototypes&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have the unique ability to investigate a new topic using white papers or blog posts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to review multiple security incidents to identify risk patterns&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to design and improve procedures that solve problems in simple and scalable ways&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to communicate with technical and non-technical stakeholders in order to drive alignment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are passionate about growing people and helping them achieve their goals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have an energy and self-drive for continuous learning as Crypto is a constantly and rapidly changing space&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to do both long term thinking and short term planning&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have developed tools to improve efficiency of a security organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience in crypto/blockchain technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations@ coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Please contact accommodations@ coinbase.com for additional information or to request accommodations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3712005?gh_jid=3712005]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Producer (Mid/Senior)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Immutable]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://immutable.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sydney, Australia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">A bit about the role:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Immutable has a unique opportunity for game producers with a hands-on mentality to help shape the future of gaming by associating producing a world-class mobile RPG game with a true play-and-earn business model. We are disrupting the game industry and empowering our players, this is a chance to take ownership and accountability in critical production processes!</div><div><br></div><div>The role as a Producer presents a unique opportunity to contribute to the successful game development, publishing and continued expansion / live development of Guild of Guardians by developing, maintaining, and improving an efficient and sustainable production pipeline built in collaboration between various teams across different time zones. You will also be taking accountability for and ownership over key production processes.</div><div><br></div><div>You will be accompanied by a core team of industry veterans with 100+ games shipped for all major publishers, hence being a perfect environment to learn, develop, improve, and apply all your experiences and skills to the next level!</div><br/>You will have the opportunity to:<br/><li>Pre-empt project risks and dependencies and proactively finding ways to solve them across various tracks (core development, art production, update and distribution strategies)</li><li>Take accountability for and ownership over the key production processes</li><li>Address and remove blockers flagged by other leads and teams</li><li>Coordinate and report on the intersectional activities, projects and deliveries between game production, product owners, marketing and PR</li><li>Ensure that organizational and production processes are upheld at the highest standard by following established processes, challenging those and proposing improvements</li><li>Ensure efficient communication and full-coverage documentation between and from the key stakeholders of all parties involved</li><br/>We would love you to have:<br/><li>At least 2-3 games shipped (preferably mobile games) in a producing or project management role OR;</li><li>At least 4-5 digital products shipped in a senior producing role in digital advertising or similar OR;</li><li>At least 3-4 years of in producing roles for TV / cinema / streaming</li><li>Excellent proficiency with at least one major Project Management Tool (JIRA, ClickUp, Monday, Hansoft - NOT MS Project) and profound knowledge of agile PM frameworks</li><li>Excellent English skills - native or IELTS 8.0+</li><li>Excellent communication skills across international team structures</li><li>Proven stakeholder management skills</li><br/>  Some extra skills that would be awesome: <br/><li>Profound knowledge of cryptocurrencies, NFTs and associated ecosystems / marketplaces</li><li>Game development background</li><li>Unity experience</li><li>Experience with free-to-play game development and game economies</li><br/>Some things we can offer you: <br/><li><b>Competitive Salary and Employee Stock Options:</b> Everyone in our team contributes to the success of our game-changing products, which is why we share all our wins company-wide. As we continue to succeed, stock options and a competitive salary mean you get to enjoy the upside!</li><li><b>Flexible working life and $750 WFH set up allowance:</b> Work-life balance is important. Whether you want to work from home or come to our new, shiny, Sydney office the choice is yours. To help you get comfortable working from home we’ll assist with a $750 contribution</li><li><b>Paid Parental Leave: </b>We celebrate our growing Immutable family! </li><li><b>Employee Assistance Program:</b> A 24/7 service that includes unlimited counselling for you and your family</li><li><b>EOY and Birthday Leave: </b>You can enjoy 2 additional paid annual leave days at EOY and a paid day off for your birthday</li><li><b>Internet and Phone Allowance</b>: $900 annually to put towards your mobile and internet expenses</li><li><b>Learning and Development: </b>We are dedicated to your professional development. You’ll get access to thousands of online learning courses via Go1, Udemy and Naspers. Immutable will also contribute between $1500-$2000 annually for you to invest in your continued education</li><li><b>Wellness Benefits</b>: Work-life balance and your wellbeing are important to us. We will contribute $1200 annually to put towards anything that contributes to your mental or physical wellbeing</li><li><b>Diversity and Inclusion</b>: We are committed to building a diverse and inclusive community for everyone. We’ve joined the Project F initiative aimed at removing the systemic barriers to achieving gender-balanced technology teams</li><li><b>Personal perks: </b>Perkbox benefits including premium access to Aura, Calm, an online fitness portal and discounts at major retailers</li><li><b>Ideal office location: </b>On-top of the Apple store on King Street, Sydney, CBD</li><li><b>Social events</b>: Fun and regular company events to relax and connect with teammates</li><div><b style="font-size: 18px">A bit about us:</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">Unique blockchain assets (“NFTs”) have grown in popularity rapidly over the past few months. These unique assets allow people to own anything from in-game items to digital art to music and financial instruments. However, they are highly illiquid: transactions take minutes or hours to confirm, and </span><span style="font-size: 13.3333px">Ethereum</span><span style="font-size: 10pt"> can process fewer than 5 NFTs per second for the whole world combined.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">To solve this problem for ourselves and for others, we have built Immutable X, a next-generation protocol for trading blockchain assets with instant trade confirmation, massive scalability, and no gas fees without compromising user custody. The goal of Immutable X is to help businesses scale their creation and trading of these unique assets (“NFTs”).</span></div><div><br></div><div><b>Additional Information:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Immutable is committed to building and fostering an inclusive, diverse workplace. We believe in incorporating everyone’s perspectives and experiences as this has been a significant driver in our success so far.</div><div><br></div><div>For this reason, we strongly encourage candidates of all backgrounds to get in touch. Even if you don’t meet all the requirements of a job listing, do yourself (and us) a favour by still applying! It’s highly likely you’ll bring something to the workplace that we haven’t thought of yet, and we would love to hear from you.</div><div><br></div><div><b>We are a 2021 Circle Back Initiative Employer – we commit to respond to every applicant.</b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fT1YFjzry3k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/immutable/5eb86ca7-9799-46e5-b754-e29632db1acf/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/364981/Immutable.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[immutable@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f8630842-e278-44a1-80ce-2963904a6243]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Immutable]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
