<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Development Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Xfers]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.xfers.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Jakarta]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About Xfers </b></div><div>Xfers as a part of Fazz Financial Group portfolio — a holding company of over 10 FinTech startups dedicated to enabling financial access for everyone — is on a mission to provide financial access to millions of underserved communities in Southeast Asia through building a financial ecosystem that anyone can participate in safely. Our range of last-mile financial rails power businesses across Southeast Asia - from startups to family businesses. By removing the pain of setting up and managing digital payments, more business owners can focus on growing their business, in turn encouraging fairer and healthier competition, and fostering stronger, more vibrant economies. For more information, visit: <a href="http://www.xfers.com" class="postings-link">www.xfers.com</a></div><div>But there is much more to do. We know how important our mission is to the improving the livelihoods of millions of people in Southeast Asia, and that's why we're looking for passionate and driven people to join us to accelerate financial access for everyone.</div><div><br></div><div>As business development associate at Xfers, you will play an instrumental role in fueling Xfers' growth in the Indonesia market. You will be focused on acquiring new merchants and servicing current accounts. You will be part of the Indonesia Payments team and reporting to the Business Development Manager of Indonesia Payments - as part of the core team to establish Xfers as a thought-leader in the role of being the Payments Infrastructure for Indonesia. Our team is looking for a highly motivated colleague to help support with building up our business in Indonesia. The ideal candidate is a driven and strategic networker who thrives in a fast-paced, diverse and entrepreneurial environment.</div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Acquire and onboard merchant by maintaining a healthy pipeline of leads, and by developing and taking care of professional relationships.</li><li>Negotiation and closing of deals: lead contract negotiations to establish a strong working relationship with our local merchants, and to ensure economic sustainability and mutual growth of the partnership</li><li>Doing outreach to clients via cold calls/emails/meetings, timely follow-ups, administrative work (Pitch Deck preparation, contract drafting, coordination, reporting).</li><li>Maintain good professional relationships and with merchants</li><li>Monitoring merchants performance</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>1 to 2 years experience in demand generation and/or account management in the technology sector (Bonus: Start up/payment gateaway/FinTech industry)</li><li>Have a good written and verbal communication, negotiation and persuasive skills</li><li>Capable to handle sales quota and expectations in a fast-paced environment</li><li>Able to speak English and Bahasa Indonesia</li><li>Curious and able to understand customer requirements and identify potential Xfers payments solutions to fulfil requirements</li><div>We love reviewing all the applications we receive, but unfortunately, we may not be able to get back to everyone individually.&nbsp; If we’d like to move forward with your application, we’ll definitely be in touch!</div><div><br></div><div>Xfers is an equal opportunity employer. Individuals seeking employment at Xfers will be considered without regard to race, religion, national origin, age, sex, gender, gender identity, gender expression, sexual orientation, marital status, medical condition, ancestry, physical or mental disability, or any other characteristic protected by applicable laws. </div><div><br></div><div>By submitting your application, you agree that Xfers may collect your personal data for recruiting, regional organization planning, and related purposes.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/xfers/cb597400-a9d2-4e93-b4d0-a566f30fd2c8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/597930/xfers_logo1.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[xfers@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b0a8343f-a5d7-46f6-beef-6fa07262d235]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Xfers]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Marketing Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blocknative]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.blocknative.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">👋&nbsp; It’s great to meet you. Thanks for taking the time to read about our latest job opening. Read on to find out more about Blocknative, get some insights into the role we are hiring for, and learn about our process.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Blocknative is the leading platform for real-time crypto applications. We count many of the top DeFi and NFT projects as customers and we power many top trading operations. Our product portfolio includes </span><a href="http://explorer.blocknative.com/" style="font-size: 11pt" class="postings-link">Mempool Explorer</a><span style="font-size: 11pt">, </span><a href="https://gas.blocknative.com/" class="postings-link"><span style="font-size: 11pt">Gas Platform</span></a><span style="font-size: 11pt">, </span><a href="http://onboard.js/" style="font-size: 11pt" class="postings-link">Onboard</a><span style="font-size: 11pt">, and our </span><a href="https://www.blocknative.com/api" style="font-size: 11pt" class="postings-link">API and SDK</a><span style="font-size: 11pt">.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">To learn more about Blocknative, please visit our </span><a href="https://www.blocknative.com/about" style="font-size: 11pt" class="postings-link">About</a><span style="font-size: 11pt"> or </span><a href="https://www.blocknative.com/careers" style="font-size: 11pt" class="postings-link">Career</a><span style="font-size: 11pt"> pages. And don't forget to </span><a href="https://explorer.blocknative.com/?signup=true" class="postings-link"><span style="font-size: 11pt">create your free account</span></a><span style="font-size: 11pt">.</span></div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for an experienced, hands-on Product Marketing Manager and who is comfortable both with self-directed and collaborative work with a demonstrable track record of success B2B marketing and a passion for crypto.</div><div><br></div><div>You’ll thrive in a fast-moving, fluid environment, and be passionate about shaping user-centric products, communications, and working with diverse groups of people across the organization to achieve your goals. You’ll be an experienced professional who thinks strategically but is also prepared to roll up your sleeves and get things done. The ideal candidate should be a passionate, self-motivated, team player with experience working in a quickly evolving environment and who has a willingness to work and learn in a collaborative organization.</div><div><br></div><br/>What are the role responsibilities?<br/><li>Lead growth marketing efforts across various external channels in order to drive customer growth of decentralized application builders and crypto traders customers.</li><li>Own the strategic development and execution of Blocknative’s product marketing strategy.</li><li>Execute multiple aspects of the product marketing lifecycle; from positioning to education and engagement campaigns.</li><li>Own the strategic development and execution of Blocknative product marketing strategy.</li><li>Customer Research: Conduct quantitative and qualitative customer research and distill it into actionable insights.</li><li>Craft audience segmentation and corresponding positioning and messaging.</li><li>Develop marketing content and written materials, including datasheets, web content, presentations, blog posts, FAQs, and video demonstrations.</li><li>Manage all aspects of product launches, from messaging to press to social media.</li><br/>What skills do you bring?<br/><li>84+ years of Product Marketing or Product Management experience, with a minimum of 2 years of experience in the cryptocurrency industry.</li><li>Excellent problem-solving skills. You should be able to take a complex problem and structure a solution with incomplete data and a lot of ambiguity.</li><li>Comfort in a fast-paced and cross-functional work environment. Love for startups, entrepreneurship, financial markets, and new technologies.</li><li>Concise, credible speaker, storyteller, and writer: you can distill a narrative from a complex data set into an executive summary.</li><li>Experience bringing products to market in fintech, a startup environment, cryptocurrency, or decentralized finance (DeFi).</li><li>Experience with social media, content marketing, video production focusing on the right message for the right customer on the right channel (at the right time!).</li><div><br></div><div>* We prioritize people above all else. If you think you’d add to the depth and diversity of our team but don’t fit these qualifications exactly, we want you to apply!</div><br/>What we are looking for:<br/><li>Passionate and familiar with cryptocurrency, blockchain and DeFi ecosystems&nbsp;</li><li>BA/BS degree. An MBA or relevant Masters Degree is a plus</li><li>3+ years of Product Marketing experience within an entrepreneurial environment</li><li>Minimum of 2 years of experience in the cryptocurrency industry.</li><li>Excel at simplifying complex concepts in messaging and differentiated positioning</li><li>Outstanding verbal and written communication skills</li><li>Powerful storyteller: written, verbal, and visual</li><li>Create and expand market awareness around new and existing products</li><li>Develop product positioning and messaging informed by user research and product understanding</li><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 14pt">We hope you apply!</span></div><div>We are also open to exploring contract opportunities as we get to know each other.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Given our early stage, we strive to have you meet as much of the team as possible before extending an offer. Here’s what you can expect:</div><div> - Application review</div><div> - Schedule a call with the recruitment team</div><div> - Schedule a call with the our CEO (Growth) or CTO (product/technical) </div><div> - Schedule a group interview with the growth or Product Technical  team</div><div> - Reference calls/ background checks</div><div>    📝 Offer&nbsp; </div><div><br></div><div>If you want to dig deeper into Blocknative, please explore our <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC9engR8mowKMratKYMBzOXQ" class="postings-link">YouTube channel</a> and <a href="https://www.blocknative.com/blog" class="postings-link">blog</a>: </div><div>&nbsp;<a href="https://www.blocknative.com/blog/blockchain-101" class="postings-link">Blockchain 101</a></div><div>&nbsp;<a href="https://www.blocknative.com/blog/series-a" class="postings-link">Series A Announcement</a></div><div>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 16px">#LI-Remote </span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ZYeJBflHZvQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/blocknative/275e78f6-acb0-4efe-97a2-54539a424b33/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/618216/blocknative.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blocknative@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[a4a47c5f-2975-451b-bc8f-c878367e9160]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blocknative]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager, People]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://mythical.games/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are Mythical Games. A Venture-backed next-generation game technology company at the intersection of video games and economics led by industry veterans. Our goal is to lead the industry with the launch of exceptional video game experiences that leverage distributed ledger technology, while also providing a platform of robust tools that will allow any other game developers to do the same.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are actively seeking a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Program Manager, People &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to join our growing People team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This position will report to the SVP, People and is an incredible opportunity to help build, drive and manage people initiatives that are foundational to a stellar people experience. You will meaningfully contribute to developing and implementing global roadmaps, projects, processes and best practices for our people organization, as we scale.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will partner with people team and cross-functional stakeholders to scope initiatives, secure resources, set milestones, drive delivery, and determine where to iterate to make improvements and set success metrics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will track progress of people initiatives, provide updates as needed, and drive accountability among stakeholders&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will collaborate and communicate effectively with stakeholders on commitments, timelines and deliverables. Effectively prioritize competing projects for the team; understand when to escalate.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will Identify, design, and execute on ideas to scale and improve the support the team provides to internal stakeholders; successfully manage all aspects of program implementation working in partnership with People Business Partners, Talent Acquisition, People Operations, and other cross-functional teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will design and develop solutions to measure progress and success; communicate with internal stakeholders; establish ongoing reporting requirements and key performance indicators for planning purposes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will work closely with peers and internal stakeholders to access, pull, and analyze data from a variety of data sources. Own and drive analyses of data to identify relationships, trends, and potential business impact; interpret data and communicate findings to relevant stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will participate in our people “think tank”, applying curiosity and stepping outside of the box to think and dream big and solution together&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Example of People Team Projects you may lead/participate in:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Talent Strategy and action plan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;DEI Strategy and action plan&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;L&amp;amp;D Roadmap and implementation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Onboarding reinvention&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Annual OKR/Goal Setting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mergers and acquisitions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of project/program management experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Previous experience working in People/HR/Operations org leading and/or managing initiatives, whether specialized or general&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to thrive in fast-growing, start-up environment; you navigate ambiguity gracefully and create order out of chaos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent analytical, organizational and project management skills; strong interpersonal and written/verbal communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to be flexible, adaptable and solutions-oriented in the face of problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passion for trying, learning, improving, and sharing best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactive team member with excellent attention to detail and follow through&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to balance competing priorities in a fast-paced environment, and push back when necessary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong sense of urgency to drive projects to completion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passion for people / human resources&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with Asana, Miro, and/or other project management and collaboration tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deep capability to create visu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;al displays and storie&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;s in Powerpoint, Asana, or other tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team values diversity and believes that it strengthens our games, products, and communities. We strongly encourage POC, folks with disabilities, those belonging to the LGBTQIA+ communities, and folks across all gender identities to apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We offer our team benefits such as (but not limited to) high-quality Vision, Dental, and Health Care, generous Parental Leave, and Unlimited PTO to ensure that they actually take time off without the stress of needing to accrue time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you need assistance around accommodations due to a disability, please reach out to accessibility@mythical.games. We will be with you as soon as possible; our goal is to ensure an accessible and equitable interview process for everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Zfsp0FQ5X8s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/mythicalgames/jobs/4827471003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/351124/Mythical-Logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[info@mythical.games]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[541f8953-1749-4738-90d8-efd04dd286d1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of Market Risk]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://blockfi.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi’s mission is to provide liquidity, transparency and efficiency to digital financial markets by creating products that meet the needs of consumers and corporations across the globe. We build bridges between traditional finance and digital markets that enable growth for all participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re a team of builders and strivers, proud to champion financial inclusivity and offer economic opportunities around the globe. We provide the same inclusivity to our team members. BlockFi is a place where diversity is celebrated, individuality is recognized, and every single team member is valued. We are changing the status quo to be the first financial company that people love, and we rely on our people to make it happen!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team and Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are seeking a highly motivated Director of Market Risk to join BlockFi&#39;s Risk Management team. In this role, you will assess the market risk in portfolios of cryptocurrencies, generate and present reporting, and liaise with trading desks and senior risk management staff.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Mission:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop a thorough understanding of analytics and metrics used to measure market risk and liquidity risk in portfolios of cryptocurrencies and related derivatives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build spreadsheets and code (e.g. Python) to capture risk measurement logic in a repeatable framework, and continuously refine tools as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist senior risk managers in evaluating portfolio construction and risk management techniques used by buy-side clients and counterparties&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop risk methodologies used to evaluate deal by deal risk across lending and investment business activities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Contribute to market risk modeling efforts or validation efforts as appropriate, including risk assessment of cryptocurrency platforms, venues and protocols&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop intermediate expertise in data preparation and data science required to carry out the function&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Communicate with trading desks and senior risk management staff&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Produce ongoing market risk reporting and evaluate status of portfolios against defined limits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assist with risk identification, assessment, and quantification efforts as needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Aggregate metrics and findings and synthesize key themes for senior risk management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Expertise:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engineering or quantitative economics academic background. Expertise in statistical techniques, stochastic calculus and linear algebra. MFE/MSFE/MQF etc. preferred.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;6+ years of experience in a market risk role supporting a capital markets business&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CFA, FRM or PRM certification preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Programming experience ( e.g. in Python ) preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exposure to fundamental market risk metrics such as VaR, stress testing and Greeks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding critical reasoning and problem-solving skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written/verbal communication and interpersonal skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent organizational and time management skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work both independently and in a team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to develop partnering relationships with trading desks while remaining willing to challenge if needed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience and/or passion in digital asset technologies and markets is a plus&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi has experienced incredible growth since our launch in August 2017. Our client base has grown to more than 225,000 (and counting), and the company now boasts more than $15 billion in assets on our platform. We recently completed a Series D funding round placing the company&#39;s valuation at $3 billion, and our team now has more than 500 people worldwide. We have established ourselves as a crypto market leader, and as we expand our product suite and geographic footprint, we expect our addressable market to grow exponentially.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi&#39;s leadership team has decades of experience in the traditional financial services and banking world, and we take a conservative approach to regulation that will position us well for sustainable long-term growth and expansion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team is comprised of highly motivated professionals from diverse backgrounds. We are aiming to become the leading lender in crypto and are poised to redefine the global financial ecosystem for the better. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is one of the first companies to ever offer crypto-backed loans and the only company whose founding team has an institutional understanding of the debt capital markets and regulatory landscape in the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$100 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series A, B, and C funding led by Valar Ventures with participation from Susquehanna, Winklevoss Capital, Fidelity, Galaxy Digital, Akuna Capital, and Morgan Creek&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$350 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series D funding led by Bain Capital Ventures, partners of DST Global, Pomp Investments and Tiger Global&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are moving quickly and have already deployed substantial capital into the space, proving our ability to execute and capture customer demand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For information about how we&amp;nbsp;collect, use, or otherwise handle your Personal Information, please see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a class=&quot;c-link&quot; href=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-stringify-link=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; data-sk=&quot;tooltip_parent&quot;&gt;Privacy&amp;nbsp;Policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/o92zit2jRO0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockfi/jobs/5698818002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/553492/blockfi-logo-512x512.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockfi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7eefa976-25ba-4497-9343-24e88aecb41f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Manager, Figure Marketplace]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Figure]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://figure.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Figure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Figure is transforming the trillion dollar financial services industry using blockchain technology.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In three short years, Figure has unveiled a series of fintech firsts using the Provenance blockchain for loan origination, equity management, private fund services, banking and payments sectors - bringing speed, efficiency and savings to both consumers and institutions. Today, Figure is one of less than a thousand companies considered a unicorn, globally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our mission requires us to have a creative, team-oriented, and supportive environment where everyone can do their absolute best. The team is composed of driven, innovative, collaborative, and curious people who love architecting ground-breaking technologies. We value individuals who bring an entrepreneurial mindset to every task and will embrace our culture of innovation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every day at Figure is a journey in continuous learning yet a daily focus on getting work done that makes a difference. Join a team of proven leaders who have already created billions of dollars in value in the FinTech space!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/americas-best-startup-employers/#6535f31b6527&quot;&gt;Forbes America’s Best Startup Employers&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/michaeldelcastillo/2020/02/19/blockchain-50/?sh=60e7347c7553&quot;&gt;Forbes Top 50 Blockchain Companies&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20210520005738/en/Figure-Raises-200-Million-Series-D-Co-Led-by-10T-Holdings-and-Morgan-Creek-Digital&quot;&gt;Figure Series D Announcement&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for a Product Manager for our Marketplace business unit to join our growing team!&amp;nbsp; As a Product Manager, you will help build the technology that delivers innovative financial products and services.&amp;nbsp; You will work across the company and with our talented leadership and engineering teams to execute on our blockchain strategy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Do&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help build and lead the product roadmap for the universal blockchain enabled marketplace for digital assets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be responsible for the user experience for investors and issuers on Figure’s blockchain enabled digital marketplace including investor and asset onboarding, dashboards, digital wallets, and marketplace storefront&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Synthesize feedback from investors and issuers on Figure Marketplace into deliverable product improvements across digital asset lifecycle including primary capital raises and secondary trading for companies, funds, and SPVs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Clearly define and communicate strategy, priorities, and key performance indicators with all stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive new feature development from start to finish - write specs, work cross-functionally with design and engineering, launch features, analyze results, synthesize learnings, and iterate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support strategy development, analysis of profitability drivers, product integration, technology and product development for various components of the wealth business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work cross functionally with the Engineering, Data, Business, Legal, and Marketing teams to align product efforts across the company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analyze the product workflow to predict and mitigate complex issues, and develop creative and practical, scalable solutions to streamline business efforts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create, monitor, and assess success metrics, and present findings to the leadership team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Iterate through product development, shipment, and maintenance by applying a deep knowledge of Figure’s business and customer requirements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Look For&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years working on a Product Team for a FinTech company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree or equivalent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of and experience with blockchain technology and digital wallet functionality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of and experience of digital marketplaces&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven history of successfully working on cross-functional projects&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Self-starter with a strong business intuition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong organizational skills and attention to detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to represent the firm professionally with internal and external contacts including product demos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborative team player with the ability to work effectively in a team or independently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excited by fast paced environment and accountability that comes with owning large projects&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong Analytical Skills: You can look at a complex set of data or user research learnings, synthesize them, and make them accessible to engineers, designers, and executives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Customer-first Mindset: You obsess about how to make product experiences intuitive and ensure that you are prioritizing the consumers best interest in product decisions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong Design Sense: You have a high bar for quality product, and can work through design challenges to make a great product&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Technical Chops: You speak intelligently with engineers and know how to build incrementally with a focus on the future&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An Analytical Approach: You can properly evaluate the success or failure of features and use data to guide next steps&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with green-field product development, shipping net-new features&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits and Perks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and growth opportunities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Company quarterly performance based bonus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equity stock options package&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employer funded comprehensive health, vision, dental insurance and wellness program for employees and their dependents&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employer funded life and disability insurance coverage&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Company HSA, FSA, Dependent Care, 401k, and commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Up to 12 weeks paid family leave&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In office, remote, and hybrid work location options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Home office and technology stipend for those working outside of a traditional office more than 75% of the time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible time-off plan to empower employees to take the time off that they want and need&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Continuing education reimbursement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Routine Team swag deliveries!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your residential location certain laws might regulate the way Figure manages applicant data. California Residents, please review our&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drive.google.com/file/d/1eDhTkvbpFETeAvGpsB8e6KzaXES4BWNB/view?usp=sharing&quot;&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;California Employee and Prospective Employee Privacy Notice&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for further information. By submitting your application, you are agreeing&amp;nbsp; and acknowledging that you have read and understand the above notice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Figure is unfortunately unable to provide sponsorship for this position. In compliance with federal law, all persons hired will be required to verify identity and eligibility to work in the United States and to complete the required employment eligibility verification form upon hire.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/WgGXwItJTPE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/figure/jobs/5726859002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/174795/figure.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[figure@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f8d02b76-9066-4951-b8c2-8a565502edd0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Figure]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[HR Operations Manager (APAC)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 10pt">About the Role:</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">Our People team is called the Krakenite Experience (KX) team, and we aim to become a world leader in People Experience. We are now hiring a People Operations Manager (APAC) to join our diverse and forward‐thinking global company.&nbsp; The People Operations Manager will add value to Kraken by ensuring that the Krakenite Experience is world class from their first days as a Krakenite all the way through their entire Kraken lifecycle. The People Operations Manager will have top level support to iterate on or build from scratch awe inspiring, best-in-class people programs and initiatives.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10pt">This is a great opportunity for an HR professional who has already thrived in creating the best‐in‐class people experiences in high‐growth organizations and who wants to get involved in an industry that is changing the world!</span>&nbsp;</div><br/>The KX Operations Manager will oversee, build, and coach a team on the following core areas:<br/><li>HR General Requests (i.e. HR ticketing system)</li><li>HR Policy and Compliance Management</li><li>Workday maintenance and streamlining alongside the HRIS team</li><li>Public readiness initiatives as they relate to HR</li><li>Offboarding &amp; Exit Interviews</li><li>Research, development, and execution of our global workforce strategy&nbsp;</li><li>HR Investigations and Conflict Resolution&nbsp;</li><li>Visa/Immigration and Global Mobility</li><li>Additional programs/policies/processes relating to the mid and end of the Krakenite life cycle</li><br/>Responsibilities: <br/><li>Supervise, coach, and develop a distributed HR operations team&nbsp;</li><li>Create, enhance, and successfully communicate global and regional policies, as appropriate, for disciplinary procedures, internal investigations, and a plethora of other high impact domestic and international employment policies and procedures</li><li>Drive the Ops team to create in-depth analyses of feedback and outcomes that demonstrate a forward thinking, action oriented, and flexible approach to iterations</li><li>Conduct and&nbsp; oversee investigations to ensure the successful resolution of Krakenite Relations issues in a timely, well-documented manner&nbsp;</li><li>Maintain the highest level of integrity, professionalism, fairness, and confidentiality regarding HR personnel matters and job performance</li><li>Foster productive relationships with other departments (especially Legal, Finance, Security, and Business Operations &amp; Strategy)&nbsp;</li><li>Provide proactive thought leadership on best practices when it comes to people systems and operations that enhance the overall Krakenite experience&nbsp;</li><li>Drive the development of a world class, collaborative, analytical, and people centric HR operations team&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Partner and collaborate with the international HR Operations team&nbsp;</li><li>Assist in the research, development, and execution of our global workforce strategy, as needed, ensuring we support our global workforce in a consistent manner while mitigating any unacceptable risk&nbsp;</li><li>Own, enhance, and manage a best in class team to deliver exceptional customer service to all Krakenites via our KX Service Desk</li><li>Ensure that in all things the Krakenite Experience is at the forefront</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>5+ years of HR operations leadership experience</li><li>Thorough knowledge of employment-related laws, regulations, and compliance requirements&nbsp;</li><li>Proven experience in HR policy and procedural documentation development, drafting, and maintenance</li><li>Understanding of HRIS systems design, HR reporting, workflow, and auditing requirements (experience with Workday strongly preferred)</li><li>Ability to manage multiple critical priorities/projects without losing attention to detail or a positive attitude</li><li>Completely at ease in an ever changing fast paced ambiguous environment</li><li>Extremely flexible, open-minded, and creative when it comes to developing and maintaining HR protocols</li><li>Relentlessly devoted to the ‘people experience’ in all things&nbsp;</li><li>Excellent interpersonal, negotiation, and conflict resolution skills</li><li>Tech-savvy with an appreciation for privacy, security, “crypto values”, sound money, and can get along well with other Krakenites&nbsp;</li><div>Location Tagging: #APAC</div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/40c0b284-d62b-485a-95a9-f65b83f44b17/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Affiliates Product Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ledger]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ledger.fr/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Paris]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As part of its strong growth, Ledger - a technology leader in digital assets and crypto-security solutions - is looking for an Affiliates Product Specialist. Within the E-commerce Team, you will be in charge of animating a network of affiliates.</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">This position is highly strategic as you’ll represent Ledger in front of big players in the crypto industry.</span></div><br/>Missions<br/><li><b><u>&nbsp;Increase affiliate revenue</u></b></li><li>Develop strong relationships with top affiliates by understanding their businesses, the priority they give to Ledger as affiliates, and why they are recommending Ledger products</li><li>Work with the affiliate recruitment team to optimize the affiliates onboarding process</li><li>Manage the relationship with our partners to improve our affiliate program</li><li>Decrease churn and increase activation of affiliates</li><li>&nbsp;<b><u>Manage and Improve Ledger’s in-house affiliate program</u></b></li><li>Give affiliates the best experience with our program</li><li>&nbsp;Improve UX and features of the affiliate program&nbsp;Manage data collection to better analyse fraud and scams</li><li>Adapt the affiliate program to compete against other affiliates programs in the crypto realm&nbsp;</li><li><b><u>Reporting and analyses&nbsp;</u></b></li><li>Own channel KPIs, report results and trends, and proactively work to optimise program effectiveness.</li><li>Communicate results and recommendations based on data-driven analysis and align with internal teams to maximise impact: creative, product, sales, tech, as well as other team members in marketing.</li><li>Quantify and prioritize high-impact opportunities with clear understanding of cost and revenue drivers. </li><br/>Profil<br/><li>3-4 years experience in an affiliate marketing position for a tech company or within a startup environment</li><li>Data-driven (knowledge of analytical tools such as Google Analytics is a plus)</li><li>Interested in cryptocurrencies</li><li>Knowledge of social media and influencer marketing</li><li>Excellent communication skills and fluent in English</li><li>Autonomous, rigorous and creativeNotions in marketing automation</li><li>Any additional language is a plus</li><li>An experience in product management would be a plus</li><br/>Location<br/><li>Location: Paris</li><li>Contract: CDI/Permanent</li><br/>Benefits<br/><li>Competitive compensation package and ESOP according to Company policy</li><li>Flexible working hours, remote-friendly environment, casual office atmosphere</li><li>Strong focus on personal development Internal talks, technical meetups and hackathons</li><li>Comprehensive health insurance policy offering extensive medical, dental and vision care coverage</li><li>Employee discount on Ledger products</li><div><b>Ledger guarantees equal opportunity for all during the recruitment process, without any distinction of gender, ethnicity, religion, sexual orientation, social status, disability or age.</b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/5Ss7xnFP9AM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/ledger/0b4ea0f8-d0de-4c43-a7ef-673dcf1019d3/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/142943/ledger.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ledger@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[83f3aace-4751-47ca-bbcd-26157dd3bc4a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ledger]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Community Operations Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Immutable]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://immutable.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sydney, Australia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 18px"><b>A bit about the role:</b></span></div><div><br></div><div>NFTs (unique digital assets stored on a blockchain), are exploding into a global asset class at rapid speed. The biggest companies in the world in gaming, finance, digital art, and collectables are either actively building or strategising their entry into the market.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>However, blockchain assets right now are highly illiquid: transactions take minutes or hours to confirm, Ethereum can process fewer than 5 asset trades per second for the whole world combined, and the UX is very challenging for mainstream users.</div><div><br></div><div>To solve this problem, we have built Immutable X: the leading open-ecosystem scaling solution to trade and create NFTs on Ethereum. We’re a protocol: that means we enable other businesses to create and trade NFTs with no gas fees, completely carbon neutral, and in a truly decentralised manner.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are hiring for a Community Operations Lead to build the Immutable X community, from developers to end-users, from the ground up! You will create systems, processes and hire resources to ensure community sentiment and happiness remains high. This is an exciting opportunity to join one of Australia’s fastest-growing startups and play a key role in positioning Immutable X as the go to solution for scaling NFTs.&nbsp;</div><br/>You will have the opportunity to:<br/><li>Advocate for the needs of community members to the business—making sure decisions are made that’s best for the community</li><li>Find and recruit community members to become moderators</li><li>Deploy scalable support solutions like bots, community forums and knowledge articles</li><li>Ensure the trust and safety of our community members from scammers, bots, spammers, and negative behavior</li><li>Expand scope of support from Discord to all social channels</li><li>Engage external agencies to help support the community as needed</li><li>Iterate on the support escalation process to balance between getting core developer support versus achieving desired SLAs to community members</li><li>Extract, analyse, and present insights to the entire business to enable product improvement, new engagement initiatives and more</li><br/>We would love you to have:<br/><li>Proven success building and managing a community in a B2C facing role</li><li>Proven capabilities at being the public face of a product e.g. interviews, podcasts, public events</li><li>Exceptional written, oral, interpersonal, and storytelling skills to express messages concisely and compellingly</li><li>Capable of writing email newsletters /copy, etc.</li><li>Demonstrated ability to understand a complex technical subject matter and to simplify and explain it to a broader audience</li><li>Confidence working in a fast-paced environment; ability to deliver a quality product under time-bound and high stakes circumstances</li><li>Ability to keep up to date with the latest news and discoveries in the blockchain and technology space</li><li>Passion and strong understanding of the blockchain and NFT space </li><br/>Some extra skills that would be awesome:<br/><li>Experience working on Crypto, SaaS or fintech companies</li><li>Success interacting and growing a community in a B2B facing role</li><li>Management experience </li><br/>Some of the things we can offer you:<br/><li><b>Competitive Salary and Employee Stock Options:</b> Everyone in our team contributes to the success of our game-changing products, which is why we share all our wins company-wide. As we continue to succeed, stock options and a competitive salary mean you get to enjoy the upside!</li><li><b>Flexible working life and $750 WFH set up allowance:</b> Work-life balance is important. Whether you want to work from home or come to our new, shiny, Sydney office the choice is yours. To help you get comfortable working from home we’ll assist with a $750 contribution</li><li><b>Paid Parental Leave: </b>We celebrate our growing Immutable family!</li><li><b>Employee Assistance Program:</b> A 24/7 service that includes unlimited counselling for you and your family</li><li><b>EOY and Birthday Leave: </b>You can enjoy 2 additional paid annual leave days at EOY and a paid day off for your birthday</li><li><b>Internet and Phone Allowance</b>: $900 annually to put towards your mobile and internet expenses</li><li><b>Learning and Development: </b>We are dedicated to your professional development. You’ll get access to thousands of online learning courses via Go1, Udemy and Naspers. Immutable will also contribute between $1500-$2000 annually for you to invest in your continued education</li><li><b>Wellness Benefits</b>: Work-life balance and your wellbeing are important to us. We will contribute $1200 annually to put towards anything that contributes to your mental or physical wellbeing</li><li><b>Diversity and Inclusion</b>: We are committed to building a diverse and inclusive community for everyone. We’ve joined the Project F initiative aimed at removing the systemic barriers to achieving gender-balanced technology teams</li><li><b>Personal perks: </b>Perkbox benefits including premium access to Aura, Calm, an online fitness portal and discounts at major retailers</li><li><b>Ideal office location: </b>On-top of the Apple store on King Street, Sydney, CBD</li><li><b>Social events</b>: Fun and regular company events to relax and connect with teammates</li><div><b>Additional Information:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Immutable is committed to building and fostering an inclusive, diverse workplace. We believe in incorporating everyone’s perspectives and experiences as this has been a significant driver in our success so far.</div><div><br></div><div>For this reason, we strongly encourage candidates of all backgrounds to get in touch. Even if you don’t meet all the requirements of a job listing, do yourself (and us) a favour by still applying! It’s highly likely you’ll bring something to the workplace that we haven’t thought of yet, and we would love to hear from you.</div><div><br></div><div><b>We are a 2021 Circle Back Initiative Employer – we commit to respond to every applicant.</b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fT1YFjzry3k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/immutable/d5da8a8c-c885-4816-95d2-faedc7b890f9/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/364981/Immutable.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[immutable@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f8630842-e278-44a1-80ce-2963904a6243]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Immutable]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Community Management ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
