<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Global Business Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[f2pool & stakefish]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://stake.fish/en/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>We are looking for an experienced Business Manager to lead and oversee the work of employees in our company. You will be responsible for ensuring the efficiency of business operations as well as setting strategic goals for the future. The ideal candidate will be well-versed in all matters business. They will be a competent leader able to provide guidance that enhances performance in a manner which incorporates the company’s vision and culture. The goal will be to ensure the profitability of our company’s activities to drive sustainable development and long-term success.<br></p><h3><br></h3><h3></h3><h3>What will you do?</h3><ul> <li>Search global power resource and mining construction cooperation matters, and complete communication, coordination, and project implementation independently</li> <li>Design and implement business plans and strategies to promote the attainment of goals</li> <li>Develop Business with existing customers and establish new customers through participation in local/regional industry events, organizations, and affiliations</li> <li>Maintain relationships with partners/vendors/suppliers</li> <li>Keep abreast of trends and changes in the business world.</li> <li>Supervise the work of employees and provide feedback and counsel to improve efficiency and effectiveness</li> <li>Assess overall company performance against objectives</li> <li>Ensure adherence to legal rules and guidelines</li> </ul><h3></h3><h3></h3><h3>What excites us about you?</h3><ul> <li>BSc/Ba in Business Management or relevant field; MSc/MA will be a plus</li> <li>Excellent service mind and strong understanding of blockchain(crypto) minder mind</li> <li>Excellent organizational and leadership skills</li> <li>Outstanding communication and interpersonal abilities</li> <li>International experienced required, Asia experience preferred</li> <li>Proficient spoken and written English skills</li> <li>Resident in the United States, Canada, Kazakhstan, Russia, Australia, Dubai, or have a visa for the above countries</li> </ul><h3></h3>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/stakefish/j/D0AB92D458/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/732239/f2pool_stakefish.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[f2pool@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[33981a68-3968-406e-a0b6-0c8956f5810a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[f2pool & stakefish]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Enterprise Sales Manager - APAC]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.elliptic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore, South West, Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>As digital assets and cryptocurrency become more widely adopted every day,, our products are essential to ensure cryptocurrency is safe and accessible to all.  Our solutions help to prevent financial crime and allow cryptocurrencies to be used for good. Our products are used by some of the world’s leading cryptocurrency exchanges, financial institutions and government agencies to screen over $1 billion of transactions every single week.  </p> <p>The company has offices in London, UK, New York City, Singapore and Tokyo. We are backed by Evolution Equity Partners, SoftBank, SBI Group, Albion VC, Octopus Ventures, SignalFire, Paladin Capital, Santander InnoVentures, and Digital Currency Group. </p><p>To achieve our mission, we depend on our incredible team of Elliptites.  <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/life-at-elliptic" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Our values</a> are reflected in everything we do and every decision we make, both internally and outwardly to our customers.  We actively encourage Elliptities to challenge the status quo and allow the freedom to innovate and learn every day.  We encourage new ideas and learning, whether that’s through collaboration, our curiosity sessions, or utilising your professional development budget - personal growth is important to us all. </p><strong>Are you a passionate and enthusiastic Enterprise Sales Manager with a wealth of experience selling SaaS solutions to enterprise companies? Are you looking for your next challenge in an emerging and exciting market? If yes then we want to hear from you!</strong><p><strong>The impact you will have: </strong><br></p><p>You will join our global Commercial team, and champion uncovering and developing new customer relationships across the APAC region. As an Enterprise Sales Manager you will become an expert in Elliptic’s value proposition, helping our prospective customers navigate and enter the cryptocurrency market with your knowledge and understanding of our product and compliance and regulatory environments. </p> <p>You will manage the full sales cycle including prospecting, qualifying leads, negotiating terms, developing custom proposals and closing business to ultimately deliver profitable revenue growth and exceed your targets.</p> <p>This is an exciting opportunity for an experienced individual looking for a role where you can make an impact not just on the company you work for but also on the market you work in. Fascinating and challenging work is the norm - working at Elliptic is never boring!</p><p><strong>What you’ll do: </strong></p><ul> <li>Develop net new business and cross sell opportunities</li> <li>Build out strategic market penetration plan, prospect, and manage full sales cycle</li> <li>Prospect and generate high quality leads</li> <li>Develop custom proposals based on customer requirements</li> <li>Conduct presentations and product demos</li> <li>Negotiate terms and close the business</li> <li>As applicable, work alongside our Customer Engagement team to develop deeper relationships and upsell to set and hit aggressive revenue goals</li> <li>Meet and exceed quarterly and annual quota</li> </ul><p><strong>You will be a great fit here if you:</strong></p><ul> <li>Can understand the customer’s business model, and how digital assets fit into their strategy </li> <li>Have the ability to analyse data to identify market trends and opportunities for cryptocurrency and compliance</li> <li>Can evaluate customer needs and preferences in relation to pricing, product terms and conditions to ensure that client requirements are addressed in commercial proposals</li> <li>Have a collaborative mindset</li> <li>Address problems immediately and can work across functions to solve problems </li> <li>Enjoy working with pace and energy, building team spirit and cultivating unity and commitment among the team</li> <li>Have an understanding of complex B2B sales methodologies</li> <li>Are flexible, adaptable and comfortable with changing priorities </li> </ul><p><strong>Our ideal candidate has: </strong></p><ul> <li>5+ years full sales cycle experience selling Enterprise SaaS solutions</li> <li>Strong outbound prospecting skills, with track record of generating net new business</li> <li>Demonstrated track record of success and quota over achievement - top 10% performer at your last company</li> <li>A strong work ethic and an entrepreneur’s mindset. You’re comfortable creating value in a low structure environment while being agile and resilient</li> <li>Interest and curiosity about digital assets and the crypto economy</li> </ul><p><strong>Bonus Points for:</strong></p><ul> <li>Intimate understanding of AML/KYC and Forensics space, either in cryptocurrency or traditional financial environments</li> <li>Experience selling SaaS solutions to Financial Services</li> <li>Borderline obsession with emerging technology</li> </ul><ul> <li>Share Options</li> <li>Holiday - 24 days of annual leave in addition to Singapore gazetted holidays</li> <li>Health insurance</li> <li>Quarterly full-day off-sites &amp; annual company 3-day offsite </li> <li>Personal training budget &amp; LinkedIn Learning subscription</li> <li>Laptop + equipment you need</li> <li>Home office allowance </li> <li>Full access to Spill Mental Health Support</li> </ul><p>We know Diversity and Inclusion is much deeper than just hiring, but it’s important for us to mention it here.  We welcome and embrace individuals of all backgrounds and identities at Elliptic, and this is an ongoing priority for us.  We know incredible people don’t all think in the same way.  We want to be challenged every day.  We believe our diverse team of individuals underpins this by bringing creative thinking and innovation to Elliptic every day.  We are committed to creating a diverse, inclusive and equitable workplace, so we welcome applications from everyone, even if you may not think you fit all of the requirements of our roles.  We foster an environment of psychological safety, where everyone feels comfortable to bring their whole self to work. </p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ebOLNjlYiNg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/elliptic/j/8F22E9D348/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145877/elliptic.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[elliptic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[fefe721f-d5ba-4eb0-9b9b-f4156a27cb2b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Elliptic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitcoindepot.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Dallas, Texas]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As Bitcoin Depot&#39;s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Technical Project Manager &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, you&#39;ll be a hands-on member of the product team who will bring best-in-class Blockchain services to market. You&#39;ll help manage and deliver Bitcoin Depot’s product roadmap, strategy, requirements, and problem definition. This is a one-of-a-kind opportunity to make a huge impact on Bitcoin Depot.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Depot is one of the largest multi-cryptocurrency ATM Networks in the world offering users the ability to buy and sell Bitcoin, Litecoin, and Ethereum instantly at over a thousand locations. Our mission is to provide the most secure, convenient, and fastest cryptocurrency transaction. Our vision is to bring the cryptocurrency market to the masses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are proud to be an Atlanta Journal-Constitution Top Work Place for 2021.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help oversee Bitcoin Depot’s technical project development roadmap, forecast resource needs, manage it to meet deliverables for the business&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Organize and manage technical team meetings and function as the primary point of contact for internal and external technical teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analyze, plan and develop requirements and standards in reference to scheduled projects&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with Product and technical teams in managing requirements, priorities, and deliverables&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work cross-functionally with internal Engineering/IT, Marketing, Operations, and Sales to identify, test, execute timely project delivery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage a development process to meet deadlines and assure the project quality.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Document and report progress across all working components of assigned projects&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor budget, billings and accounting for technical projects.&amp;nbsp; Initiate and escalate corrective actions when variances are identified.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Research and evaluate technology options and weigh cost/benefits analysis when making or recommending purchases on behalf of the company&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years experience in technical project management or product management, developing software preferably within a SaaS organization. Some start-up experience is greatly preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in project/product managing software related, payment processing, blockchain or FinTech&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Agile methodologies, Jira, and roadmap-management tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;20% Travel Required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track record of managing the entire project life cycle and successfully bringing new software products to market&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of credit/debit card processing, money transfers flows, payment settlement, and AML/KYC/Compliance in a Fintech environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in a high-level collaborative environment and promoting a teamwork mentality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Highly organized and detail-oriented, yet can deal with change and fast paced environment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Salary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous PTO&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Health benefits offered with a company contribution towards premiums&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Wellness benefits&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401K Matching&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Revenue Sharing Plan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Casual dress environment when in office&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monthly company celebrations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Advancement opportunities based on results&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly catered lunches&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Premium coffee and tea provided by Buckhead Beans&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Depot is an equal opportunity employer that is committed to diversity and inclusion in the workplace. We prohibit discrimination and harassment of any kind based on race, color, sex, religion, sexual orientation, national origin, disability, genetic information, pregnancy, or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state, or local laws.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This policy applies to all employment practices within our organization, including hiring, recruiting, promotion, termination, layoff, recall, leave of absence, compensation, benefits, training, and apprenticeship. Bitcoin Depot makes hiring decisions based solely on qualifications, merit, and business needs at the time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/VuS6XCo53DU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitcoindepot/jobs/4762925003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/556151/bitcoin-depot-image-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitcoindepot@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[49753fb8-b518-4786-89b5-9d1bf0e19ac0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Events Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Eco]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://eco.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere (U.S. timezones preferred)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Eco puts your money back to work for you — creating the first consumer fintech product whose creators are aligned with its users. Financial infrastructure hasn&#39;t changed since the 1970s. All we&#39;ve gotten are shinier products built on the same broken systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Eco App changes that, starting by building the best place to save and spend your dollars. We combine high-yield savings with rewarded spending in a single, compounding balance that&#39;s easy to manage. Soon we&#39;ll let you pay your bills and put your financial life on autopilot. And through all of this — unlike every other fintech company — we don&#39;t skim from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;That’s only possible because we’re building Eco Points, a new rewards currency for the Eco community. Eco Points keep us—our company, App users, and the community of people already building for Eco—aligned to win together. And this is just the beginning. New Points features are emerging every month as we think about how Eco can fundamentally upgrade traditional money. And in case you’re wondering: there’s much, much more to Points than meets the eye.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Every day, we&#39;re working on difficult and impactful problems which demand solutions at the intersection of technology, product, marketing, and advocacy. To achieve our mission and realize our vision, we’ve put together an incredible team and are selectively adding to it. We hope you’ll consider joining us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As Events Manager at Eco, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manager and/or supervise all production aspects of in person and virtual eventsan event&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Formulate and execute ideas and concepts that will make Eco events stand out&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform venue and AV inspections&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Find and hire all appropriate vendors for the successful execution of an event&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Oversee and get “into the weeds” to make an event go off without a hitch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re looking for you if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You define yourself as an event manager by your creativity &lt;/span&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;and&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; attention to detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have strong interpersonal skills and can turn feedback into decisive action&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have the ability to view and understand situations from a variety of perspectives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have at least two years of event production and/or management experience in both in person and virtual events&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You consider yourself open and vulnerable, sharing your true perspective because you know that’s the path toward building relationships that last&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have the ability to multitask and prioritize assignments in a fast-paced environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have excellent decision making skills and the ability to both trust yourself and others&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You thrive in collaborative environments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/econetwork/jobs/5772250002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/644968/eco-200x200.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[eco@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d703e4ac-536e-4837-8c22-e10df11c25af]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Eco]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[UAT Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[ADDX]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://addx.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>Who are we?</b></div><div>Here at ADDX, we believe in a future where everybody can access financial ecosystems easily, fairly, and safely. That is why we’ve built the world’s first fully regulated platform for digital securities, licensed by the Monetary Authority of Singapore.</div><div><br></div><div>In 2021, we raised USD 50 million in Series A funding led by Japan Investment Corporation and Development Bank of Japan. Among other esteemed investors, we are backed by Singapore Exchange and Heliconia, a subsidiary of Temasek.</div><div><br></div><div>We have gone through a total re-brand and promise this to be an exciting time. An integral part of a fast-growing team enabling investments in unicorns, pre-IPO companies, and hedge funds, your role is to innovate and discover new solutions.</div><div><br></div><div>If you believe in a future of fair financial markets, just like we do, we’ve been waiting for you at ADDX.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Who are we looking for?</b></div><div><br></div><div>We are seeking a dynamic <b>Platform Change Analyst</b> to be part of the <b>Business Operations </b>team, responsible for managing changes to ADDX platform processes, features, and functionality on web &amp; mobile front.&nbsp; You will enjoy working in a fast-paced environment, and with a group of exceptionally product focused team who want to make a difference. If you are inspired to take on the challenge of building the Exchange of the future, we would love to speak with you!</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>To collaborate with the Product, Engineering and QA team to define the UAT scope, effort and timeline for the web and mobile platform feature.</li><li>To plan, create and execute UAT test plan, script, and scenario based on the web and mobile platform feature scope and releases</li><li>To support UAT on ad-hoc releases for hot fixes</li><li>To create and document platform user covering Admin, Issuer, Investor and EAM platform user</li><li>To conduct training for platform user to familiarize with the platform feature</li><li>To manage the platform admin user’s on ADDX platform </li><li>To support relationship manager with creation of “how to videos”</li><li>To work with the Product team to implement platform enhancement identified during UAT</li><li>To support client service team to respond to client’s queries on platform usage</li><div><br></div><div>The primary responsibility is to collaborate with the Product, Engineering and Quality Assurance team to manage and execute the User Acceptance Testing on ADDX web and mobile platform covering the functional, performance, and user interface on enhancement or new feature rollout.</div><br/>Requirements<br/><li>3-6 years of practical experience in platform or software testing.</li><li>Strong understanding in system testing, UAT testing and execution in functional and non- </li><li>Experience working with business users to understand the UAT scope and plan the UAT support and reporting</li><li>Experience in reporting test progress and using test management tool JIRA</li><li>Experience in preparation of system user manual documentation.</li><li>Good communication skills with users on platform usage and queries.</li><li>Plan UAT resource support around the feature releases and perform actual UAT &nbsp;</li><li>Essential Attributes - Drive, good team player and determination</li><div>Due to our limited capacity, we regret that only shortlisted candidates will be notified. </div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/7ErT7T4wgYI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/addx/79a14825-ddcb-45fa-9ff9-c25c000f5a7a/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/413784/addx-istox-logo.jpeg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[addx@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b82fa9b1-c059-434f-82d6-6cb949f49699]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[ADDX]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Power Procurement Coordinator (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitfury.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Oslo, Oslo, Norway]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;div id=&quot;header&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at Bitfury:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is a leading emerging technologies company. &amp;nbsp;At Bitfury, you can build the solutions of the future, with the most significant technologies of the millennium, in a modern and flexible workplace. We work a bit faster, and a bit smarter, so we can make the world a bit better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of Working at Bitfury:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Experiences &amp;amp; Global Impacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is an international company with 200+ team members in more than 16 countries. No matter your assignment, your work will support global technology initiatives and best-in-class security operations in North America, Asia and Europe, as well as help us fulfil our mission to make the world more trusted and secure.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building the Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe big data, artificial intelligence, blockchain technology, tokenized economies and cryptocurrencies are the future of our digital, global economy. Bitfury is building this future through our products that offer digitised security, asset management, government services and more. We consider ourselves first and foremost a technology company. We are a diversified organisation, with operations across multiple facets of the AI, blockchain, and digital currency sectors. If you are passionate about emerging technologies, you can build your future at Bitfury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Your Career&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is growing fast and looking for the next generation of leaders and entrepreneurs to help us. At Bitfury, you will be expected to create the future – not just execute it. If you are a self-starter, driven and collaborative team member, you can create a dynamic future for yourself and your career at Bitfury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modern Workplace with Intelligent Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury lets you work in the way you need to work to make your work faster, smarter and better. We will give you the resources you need to succeed – competitive pay and benefits, educational support, intellectual challenges, professional advancement, personal accommodations including remote work, and more. We pride ourselves on being less bureaucratic and a lot more impactful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start-up Culture with Established Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with the world’s leading experts and engineers, you will have the opportunity at Bitfury to pursue results that will power your success as well as lead to the adoption of game-changing technologies. Our teams work every day to make the impossible possible, to change the game, to be agile and effective, and most of all – to empower the rest of the world to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ersonal and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rofessional&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;haracteristics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We at Bitfury ensure our team members possess the ability to think out of the box and make the impossible possible. We are self-motivated and result-oriented, and we have an “owner of the company” mindset. We are constantly self-educating and developing. We are able to work in a team and collaborate. We have a “do good” mindset and are not afraid to dream big. And of course, we always deliver in time what we promised and with extreme attention to detail — because if we are not able to do the little things right, we will never be able to do big things right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The role consists in optimisation of daily power procurement processes and support in identifying, securing power procurement contracts for the development of Bitfury’s data centers in Norway/Sweden and Canada.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties and responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Permanent review of Company’s current contract prices;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identification of market opportunities and potential new suppliers, execute contract re-negotiations;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define tactics and methods:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Define and refine electricity purchase tactics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refine methids of electricity cost reporting and analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop tactics and methods implementation plan (e.g. propose additional electricity suppliers);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop hedging policy (electricity and certificates):
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform historical price analysis;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepare risk profile assessment and proposal for hedging portfolio content, including time horizons. PPA opportunity mapping;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Developing hedging instructions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implementing hedging plan.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Daily power procurement (EU, North America)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support with search for new promising sites for future Data Centers with cheap energy and available power.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support with paper work, managing external consultants and/or subcontractors (certified estimates for applications, preliminary design, etc), upon request;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span lang=&quot;EN-US&quot;&gt;Specific knowledge, skills and abilities: &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Must:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5-year minimum experience in the power sector;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of power market structures, rules and ancillary services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding the power generation, transmission and distribution mechanisms as physically, as commercially.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to breakdown and model grid tariffs and ancillary services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial mindset and ability to work autonomously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As-a-plus:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Basic understanding of Bitcoin blockchain and mining economics;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Power trading experience;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong network across power generating companies in Europe and North America.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/DtkFJoj24rE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitfury/jobs/5793868002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145862/bitfury.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitfury@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bff43dfe-8ac3-4757-8a78-7559c9e9e327]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.mastercard.us/en-us.html]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:left"><span><b>Our Purpose</b></span></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p>We work to connect and power an inclusive, digital economy that benefits everyone, everywhere by making transactions safe, simple, smart and accessible. Using secure data and networks, partnerships and passion, our innovations and solutions help individuals, financial institutions, governments and businesses realize their greatest potential. Our decency quotient, or DQ, drives our culture and everything we do inside and outside of our company. We cultivate a <a href="https://www.mastercard.us/en-us/vision/who-we-are/diversity-inclusion.html" target="_blank">culture of inclusion</a> for all employees that respects their individual strengths, views, and experiences. We believe that our differences enable us to be a better team – one that makes better decisions, drives innovation and delivers better business results. </p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:left"><b>Job Title</b></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p>Principal Software Engineer<p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p>Mastercard is looking for brilliant, passionate and innovative software developers. In this role, you will be a key member of a highly agile group driving hard to create innovative payment solutions in Mastercard’s R&amp;D Lab.<br><br>Overview<br><br>- This team will have a diverse focus both in terms of geography and variety of technology challenges driving hard to bring innovative payment solutions to market.<br>- Love coding? Have a track record of designing and building robust, flexible, scalable backend systems?<br>- Enjoy a fast paced, start-up culture?<br>- Have a strong desire to deliver world class solutions?<br><br>Role<br><br>- Design, build and launch robust, flexible, scalable, enterprise Blockchain solutions<br>- Ensure all services can be readily published as APIs on the Mastercard Developers platform<br>- Keep up to date on technology trends and assess relevance in the payments space<br>- Must be solutions oriented – ultimately find and implement the ‘best fit’ solution to address the requirement on time.<br>- Experience in Agile development.<br><br>All About You<br><br>- Expert software development skills<br>- Expert in distributed computing<br>- Expert knowledge of security protocols and encryption<br>- Understanding of Blockchain technology<br>- Expert in a functional language: Erlang, Scala, Elixir,<br>- Expert in Java and Spring (preferably Spring Boot, Spring Cloud)<br>- Worked with multiple databases (relational, no-SQL etc.) e.g. Postgres, Oracle, MySQL, Hadoop, Elastic<br>- Experience implementing APIs and SDKs<br>- Experience with Swagger and familiar with Docker an advantage<br>- Knowledge of payment protocols an advantage<p></p><p></p><p><span>Due to COVID-19, most of our employees are working from home. We’ve implemented a virtual hiring process and continue to interview candidates by phone or video and are onboarding new hires remotely. We value the safety of each member of our community because we know we’re all in this together.</span></p><p></p><p><i>Mastercard is an inclusive Equal Employment Opportunity employer that considers applicants without regard to gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, race, ethnicity, disabled or veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.​</i></p><p></p><p><i>If you require accommodations or assistance to complete the online application process, please contact </i><a href="mailto:reasonable.accommodation&#64;mastercard.com" target="_blank"><i><span><span><span>reasonable.accommodation&#64;mastercard.com</span></span></span></i></a><i> and identify the type of accommodation or assistance you are requesting.  Do not include any medical or health information in this email. The Reasonable Accommodations team will respond to your email promptly.</i></p><p></p><p><i>  </i></p><p><b><span>Corporate Security Responsibility</span></b></p><p><br /><span>Every person working for, or on behalf of, Mastercard is responsible for information security. All activities involving access to Mastercard assets, information, and networks comes with an inherent risk to the organization and therefore, it is expected that the successful candidate for this position must:</span><br /><br /><span>• Abide by Mastercard’s security policies and practices;</span><br /><span>• Ensure the confidentiality and integrity of the information being accessed;</span><br /><span>• Report any suspected information security violation or breach, and</span><br /><span>• Complete all periodic mandatory security trainings in accordance with Mastercard’s guidelines.</span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/w7FvjIQx_tg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://mastercard.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/CorporateCareers/job/New-York-City-New-York/Principal-Software-Engineer_R-145379?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143560/mastercard.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[mastercard@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5e2069a0-e8ad-4538-a4a1-79d2ab62d9aa]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Protection Officer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Brave]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://brave.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div&gt;Brave is hiring a full-time Data Protection Officer, reporting to the Chief Security Officer. We are looking for someone with a passion for online privacy to help keep our millions of users safe.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Responsibilities will include:&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● Maintaining Brave’s registry of data processing.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● Advising on Brave’s data protection disclosures.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● Responding to data rights requests from Brave users or partners.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● Teaching colleagues how best to deliver on the objectives of the GDPR.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● Advising on vendors’ data protection arrangements, and on related agreements between Brave and them&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● Doing privacy reviews to ensure compliance with our privacy policy / updating the privacy policy if needed&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● Working closely with the privacy and security engineering teams to come up with privacy-preserving solutions&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● And such tasks as may be required to fulfill the duties of a Data Protection Officer set out in Article 39 of the GDPR:&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;○ “to inform and advise the controller or the processor and the employees who carry out&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;processing of their obligations pursuant to this Regulation and to other Union or Member&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;State data protection provisions;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;○ to monitor compliance with this Regulation, with other Union or Member State data&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;protection provisions and with the policies of the controller or processor in relation to the&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;protection of personal data, including the assignment of responsibilities, awareness-&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;raising and training of staff involved in processing operations, and the related audits;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;○ to provide advice where requested as regards the data protection impact assessment&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;and monitor its performance pursuant to Article 35;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;○ to cooperate with the supervisory authority;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;○ to act as the contact point for the supervisory authority on issues relating to processing,&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;including the prior consultation referred to in Article 36, and to consult, where&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;appropriate, with regard to any other matter”.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Required qualifications:&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● A thorough knowledge and understanding of European data protection law, including the&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;GDPR, ePrivacy Directive, and relevant case law of the European Court of Justice, and the&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;opinions and guidance of Article 29 Working Party and European Data Protection Board.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;● The ability to communicate in simple terms the full substance of complex data protection&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;matters to millions of people who use Brave products.&lt;br&gt;● Technical background is a plus.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Benefits&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;PTO is unlimited in U.S., 20 days + your birthday in Canada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous health and retirement benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Stock option grant&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel and conference budgets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commuters benefit (SF only)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flexible remote work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/kLiLOkzLetE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/brave/jobs/2262081?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145908/brave.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[brave@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d9771ed5-e81b-4920-bc38-de085de85437]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Brave]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Designer (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://swissborg.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Milan]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We are SwissBorg, a FinTech startup headquartered in Lausanne, Switzerland.</div><div><br></div><div>Our flagship product, the SwissBorg app, offers over 550,000+ users the best price and liquidity across 16 fiat and 17 cryptos, as well as giving them the opportunity to earn passive income with our Smart Yield account. Our community is growing fast, with over $1.5 billion in assets under management, a weekly volume of over 250 million, and over 18,000 Premium users.</div><div><br></div><div>This is just the start in our mission to democratise wealth management by building products that allow individuals to manage their crypto assets at the touch of a finger. Whether you’re in Andorra or Zimbabwe, whether your portfolio is worth one dollar or a million, SwissBorg gives you the best tools to learn about digital currencies and manage your wealth.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to join a team of revolutionaries on a mission to decentralise nations? We want to hear from you!</div><div><br></div><div><b><i>Please note this is a fully remote role for a candidate who can be based anywhere in European timezone. </i></b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 15px">#LI-Remote</span></div><br/>What you might be doing:<br/><li>Create assets for product marketing campaigns, including banners for social media, articles, email and in-app notifications</li><li>Designs for presentations and one-pagers for various teams across the business</li><li>Designs for information-heavy content, such as infographics and reports, alongside supporting assets (call-out quotes and banners for social media and email)</li><br/>What you might bring:<br/><li>Degree in visual artsStrong Photoshop / Adobe Creative Cloud skills</li><li>Presentation design skills</li><li>Experience in both digital and print design</li><li>Excellent oral and written communication skills in English</li><li>Highly motivated team player with good organisational skills</li><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Why you should apply: </b></div><div><br></div><div>- Freedom to build the company of your dreams</div><div>- Learn with (super cool) experts in finance, engineering, AI, psychology and business</div><div>- CHSB bonus based on our meritocratic system</div><div>- We'll provide you with a MacBook and a cutting edge tech stack to help you do your best work</div><div>- Flexible work hours</div><div>- Annual team retreats with colleagues around the world</div><div>- Continuous learning and development opportunities</div><div><br></div><div>Oh and are you planning on having a kid? That’s great! We have a bunch of those: you’ll get time off to enjoy that (other) adventure!&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><i>At SwissBorg, we embrace diversity. We strongly believe that getting to the best outcomes requires different perspectives and backgrounds. We’re committed to openness, curiosity and creating an inclusive culture as we know that diverse teams build better products and generate better ideas. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status.</i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/02lonwc5XE4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/swissborg/17168c8f-f671-40c4-9624-2ae891ce8775/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/440178/Swissborg-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[swissborg@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f4703261-2e7b-4b75-af19-fbdfc5e62c02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Associate Portfolio Manager - Rates]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[DRW]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://drw.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRW&lt;/strong&gt; is a technology-driven, diversified principal trading firm. We trade our own capital at our own risk, across a broad range of asset classes, instruments and strategies, in financial markets around the world. As the markets have evolved over the past 25 years, so has DRW – maximizing opportunities to include real estate, cryptoassets and venture capital. With over 1,200 employees at our Chicago headquarters and offices around the world, we work together to solve complex problems, challenge consensus and deliver meaningful results. It’s a place of high expectations, deep curiosity and thoughtful collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a motivated macro rates trader to contribute his/her market expertise in trading USD, EUR and GBP securities and derivatives. The associate PM is expected to evaluate market opportunities, generate trade ideas and assist the PM in managing the overall portfolio. He/she must be a strong communicator with the broker-dealer community and is able to actively source relevant information in a timely manner to stimulate discussion among team members.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish good relationships with dealers&amp;nbsp;to facilitate frequent discussions&amp;nbsp;regarding&amp;nbsp;market conditions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Source relevant market information to team&amp;nbsp;in a timely manor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor portfolio performance and associated risk exposures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create trade ideas that will produce PnL, but also stimulate&amp;nbsp;discussion among team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guide junior team member in gaining market knowledge and project execution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 Years of trading experience in US, Europe and UK rates, including bonds and derivatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Complete understanding of macro factors driving interest&amp;nbsp;rate markets, including fundamental economic data, central bank policy actions, and short-term flow dynamics&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong foundation in&amp;nbsp;fixed income analytics for&amp;nbsp;bonds, futures, swaps as well as risk analytics&amp;nbsp;and PnL components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of exchange-traded options and swaption risks including&amp;nbsp;greeks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hands-on programming experience in Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborative mindset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong communicator with proven relationship management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Efficient and capable of working independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor degree in a Finance, Economics or a quantitative field such as Math, Science, or Engineering&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based in New York or London&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about DRW&#39;s processing activities and our use of job applicants&#39; data, please view our Privacy Notice at &lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;California residents, please review the&amp;nbsp;California Privacy Notice&amp;nbsp;for information about certain legal rights at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#LI-SK1&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MdwEImeQcx8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/drweng/jobs/3789496?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145892/drw.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[drw@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bf32acf8-cf47-410b-aa59-74974c4d6afd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[DRW]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Accounting Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Eco]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://eco.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere (U.S. timezones preferred)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Eco puts your money back to work for you — creating the first consumer fintech product whose creators are aligned with its users. Financial infrastructure hasn&#39;t changed since the 1970s. All we&#39;ve gotten are shinier products built on the same broken systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Eco App changes that, starting by building the best place to save and spend your dollars. We combine high-yield savings with rewarded spending in a single, compounding balance that&#39;s easy to manage. Soon we&#39;ll let you pay your bills and put your financial life on autopilot. And through all of this — unlike every other fintech company — we don&#39;t skim from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;That’s only possible because we’re building Eco Points, a new rewards currency for the Eco community. Eco Points keep us—our company, App users, and the community of people already building for Eco—aligned to win together. And this is just the beginning. New Points features are emerging every month as we think about how Eco can fundamentally upgrade traditional money. And in case you’re wondering: there’s much, much more to Points than meets the eye.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Every day, we&#39;re working on difficult and impactful problems which demand solutions at the intersection of technology, product, marketing, and advocacy. To achieve our mission and realize our vision, we’ve put together an incredible team and are selectively adding to it. We hope you’ll consider joining us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As an Accounting Manager at Eco, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Oversee day-to-day accounting operations, inclusive of accounts payable, payroll, vendor / consultant management, and banking operations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own and manage the General Ledger, inclusive of daily transaction coding, chart of accounts structuring, balance sheet reconciliations and everything in between&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Constantly be looking for gaps in operational processes, and solving for maximum throughput/efficiency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Liaise, support and work cross-functionally with People Operations, Legal, Compliance and Payment Operations on a regular basis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re looking for you if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are super passionate about accounting; monthly reconciliations bring you to your happy place&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a proven track record of executing under tight time constraints with limited resources and information&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Scaling a hypergrowth, early-stage startup does not intimidate you&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are excited to pursue a career in crypto, blockchain and/or fintech&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;--&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please note that we are committed to equal employment opportunity regardless of race, background, religion, gender identity, national origin, sexual orientation, age, citizenship status, marital status or disability. We also consider for employment qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records. If you have a disability or special need that requires accommodation, please feel free to let us know.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/econetwork/jobs/5802596002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/644968/eco-200x200.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[eco@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d703e4ac-536e-4837-8c22-e10df11c25af]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Eco]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Junior Strategic Finance Analyst - Data]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,400+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 12pt">About the Role</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">The Strategic Finance Analyst role will support all of Kraken’s strategic finance needs including modeling business scenarios, tracking performance metrics, and working with leaders to make strategic company decisions. You are an ambitious individual who is excited by the challenge of solving tough, often ambiguous problems in this dynamic space. You are able to make well-informed recommendations based on data and analysis. You can communicate your findings and recommendations verbally and in concise and actionable reports. Intellectual curiosity and a desire to learn everything cryptocurrency are a requirement for this role. The data focused analyst role will dedicate more time in gathering and driving insights through large datasets and work on automation projects to improve efficiency of our team and our company. </span></div><br/>Who you are:<br/><li>Strong academic background in Finance or a quantitative field (mathematics, economics, physics, engineering, etc) preferred.</li><li>At least 1 years of work experience in finance, tech, or related fields.</li><li>Extensive experience working with large datasets using Excel (advanced formulas and VBA macros) and reading/writing SQL queries.</li><li>Proficiency in programming (especially Python or C++) an advantage.</li><li>Strong understanding of accounting, financial, and valuation&nbsp;</li><li>Attention to detail with a drive to solve problems, investigate issues, and creative thinking.</li><li>Ability to multi-task in a fast-paced, deadline driven environment.</li><li>Ability to navigate ambiguous situations and deliver results.</li><li>Intrinsic motivation with a strong desire to make a positive impact on the organization.</li><br/>What you'll do:<br/><li>Leverage extremely large databases maintained by the Data teams to create advanced reports &amp; data visualizations to communicate Kraken’s performance and advise ongoing projects. </li><li>Assist team members in sourcing/scripting additional datasets and conducting detailed quantitative analysis to drive deep insights and generate impact.&nbsp;</li><li>Develop and maintain automation models to improve proficiency and accuracy of internal processes.</li><li>Perform financial and operational deep dives across products, regions, business lines to understand ROI, margins, opportunity cost, and valuation impact.</li><li>Assist the Strategic Finance team in preparing presentations and other updates for our executives, the board, and investors.</li><li>Effectively build financial models to both understand the quantitative and qualitative aspects of what’s happening, and communicate findings &amp;&nbsp; recommendations to the team.</li><li>Build and maintain annual budget models and ongoing quarterly forecasts in collaboration with all the functions across Kraken globally.</li><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</b></div><div><br></div><div><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link"><b>Follow us on Twitter</b></a></div><div><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link"><b>Catch up on our blog</b></a></div><div><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link"><b>Follow us on LinkedIn</b></a></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/eb04b844-b16a-44aa-88b9-60cb00fe6a58/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Front-end / Data Visualisation Developer (100% remote, part-time).]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Maker]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://makerdao.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<h3><span style="font-size: 14px;"><span style="font-size: 16px;"><span style="font-size: 18px;">About us</span></span></span></h3>
<p>MakerDAO is an unbiased global financial system. A Decentralised Autonomous Organization (DAO) that manages an Ethereum-based protocol that issues the Dai stablecoin and facilitates collateral-backed loans.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>We are the Data Insights core unit. We provide free and <em>permissionless</em> datasets to the entire community. Our goal is to enable every user to access and interact with on-chain and off-chain data related to the MakerDAO protocol. We are currently a 3 person team, a product manager and data engineers, based in different countries in Europe 🇪🇺 .</p>
<p>You can read more about our core unit in our <a href="https://forum.makerdao.com/t/mip39c2-sp22-adding-data-insights-core-unit-din-001/10208" rel="noopener">MIP mandate post</a>.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<h3><span style="font-size: 14px;"><span style="font-size: 16px;"><span style="font-size: 18px;">What we need</span></span></span></h3>
<p><br /></p>
<p>We are looking for a frontend developer to create a platform(s) to visualise our data.</p>
<p>We are a small team mainly focused on data engineering, so the ideal candidate is looking for independence and wants own the end-to-end frontend, including design, implementation and improvement.</p>
<p>We want to further improve the value we deliver the community by creating the best possible user experience. While we already provide datasets to some of the core systems of MakerDAO, we want to expand our each by creating rich visualisations for users of all skills to interact with them.</p>
<p>We are technology agnostic with a preference for popular frameworks. The backend team works with:</p>
<ul>
<li>Github (version control)</li>
<li>AWS (hosting)</li>
<li>Snowflake (structured database)</li>
<li>Python (data pipeline, analysis)</li>
<li>FastApi (public api)</li>
<li>gSheet (input/output)</li>
</ul>
<p>While also making use of any interesting set of tools, such as Flask, Tableau Public and Streamlit, among others.</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>You can take a look at <a href="https://data.makerdao.network/roadmap" rel="noopener">our roadmap</a> to get a better idea of what we are planning to do.<span style="font-size: 18px;"><br /><a href="https://beta.mcdgov.info/" rel="noopener"></a></span><span style="font-size: 18px;"></span><span style="font-size: 18px;"><br /></span></p>
<h3><span style="font-size: 16px;"><span style="font-size: 18px;">You will</span></span></h3>
<ul>
<li>Work with the PM and data engineers to build the user-facing web applications</li>
<li>Designing the feel and look of UIs</li>
<li>Deciding the best way to showcase data</li>
<li>Implementing the designs into fully workable products</li></ul>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong><span style="font-size: 18px;"><span style="font-size: 20px;"><span style="font-size: 24px;"><span style="font-size: 18px;">Current assets</span></span></span></span></strong><strong><span style="font-size: 18px;"><span style="font-size: 20px;"><span style="font-size: 24px;"><span style="font-size: 18px;"><strong><br /></strong></span></span></span></span></strong></p>
<p><a href="https://data.makerdao.network/" rel="noopener">The Data Insights website</a> (Notion, Cloudflare)</p>
<p><strong><br /></strong><strong><br /></strong></p>
<p><strong>Previously</strong><strong> created GUIs to support our datasets:</strong></p>
<p><a href="https://beta.mcdgov.info/" rel="noopener">MCD Voting Tracker</a> (Flask)</p>
<p><a href="https://beta.mcdstate.info/" rel="noopener">MCD Vault Tracker</a> (Flask)</p>
<p><a href="https://public.tableau.com/app/profile/tadeo5490/viz/2021MakerDAOGovernance/GovernanceVoting" rel="noopener">Governance Voting Overview</a> (Tableau Public)</p>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong>The community of MakerDAO is diverse and has produced some wonderful GUIs that we look up to:</strong></p>
<ul><li><a href="https://maker.blockanalitica.com/" rel="noopener">Risk Dashboard</a> - created by the Risk CU</li><li><a href="https://makerburn.com/#/" rel="noopener">makerburn</a> - created by the community member @makerburn</li><li><a href="https://daistats.com/" rel="noopener">daistats</a> - created by @nanexcool, maintained by @tbone</li></ul>
<p><br /></p><p><h2>Requirements:</h2></p><p><strong>Required</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Solid experience in the design, development and implementation of data web-apps, including visualizations.</li>
<li>Expertise in user experience, usability and visual communication.</li>
<li>Comfortable working in a remote team.</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Optional</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Experience in crypto/web3/DeFi/TradFi</li>
<li>React</li>
<li>Typescript</li>
<li>D3.js</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Not required</strong></p>
<ul>
<li>Backend</li>
<li>User data input</li>
<li>User management</li>
</ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Gqu9GWcx9Wk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://makerdao.recruitee.com/o/frontend-data-visualisation-developer-100-remote-parttime/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180500/makerdao.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[maker@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[20fdd764-0853-447b-b33c-968fda16a5f4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Maker]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Product Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Consensys]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.consensys.net]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;h3&gt;About ConsenSys&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is the leading Ethereum software company. We enable developers, enterprises, and people worldwide to build next-generation applications, launch modern financial infrastructure, and access the decentralized web. Our product suite, composed of Infura, Quorum, Codefi, MetaMask, and Diligence, serves millions of users, supports billions of blockchain-based queries for our clients, and has handled billions of dollars in digital assets. Ethereum is the largest programmable blockchain in the world, leading in business adoption, developer community, and DeFi activity. On this trusted, open source foundation, we are building the digital economy of tomorrow. To explore our products and solutions, visit &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://consensys.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;http://consensys.net/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Infura&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Infura’s development suite provides instant, scalable API access to the Ethereum and IPFS networks. Our world-class infrastructure ensures that developers can reliably scale their decentralized application to meet user demand. It’s powered by a cutting-edge microservice-driven architecture that dynamically scales to support our APIs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thousands of developers are actively using Infura every day. The strength, reliability and stability of Infura’s infrastructure service makes the brand an essential pillar of the Ethereum ecosystem and the leading blockchain infrastructure provider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Product Manager at Infura you will do the following,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define the product specifications for new products, product updates, and new product features. This includes detailed outlines of the product goals, UX requirements, pricing structures, target audience, and strategy for analyzing product performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the release/launch plan for new products, product updates, and new product features. This includes working directly with Project Management, Engineering, Design, Marketing, QA, and Customer Support to ensure all teams are aligned on the launch requirements, timelines, and post release monitoring.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build complex data analysis and monitoring dashboards for everything from service level metrics to product specific usage which you will use to help guide the team&#39;s strategic decisions and priorities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work directly with the Product Design and Customer Support teams to build user research plans and to be the lead pulse tracker of our customers. This includes direct customer research and community engagement for feature requests, bug reports, and general customer feedback.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Developers are our customers therefore being closely tied in with the engineering team is critical. You will be working together to understand customer needs, the complexity of the technology we serve, and the limitations of specific features or products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the business outcomes of the products and features you manage.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BS or higher degree in computer science, math, economics, statistics, or related technical field&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience on a full development cycle through launch on a developer targeted product or service&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience building in depth product specifications and strategy for technical products or services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong analytical skills and experience with data pipelines and data analysis tools such as, SQL, Grafana, Tableau, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Effective and powerful communicator who excels with a team that values autonomy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working on a major cloud service provider and or software as a service provider&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Detailed understanding of project management pipelines and coordinating complex products across all project disciplines&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have led or actively participated in a process for engaging customers on product feedback and thrive on interacting deeply with your product’s audience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience participating in the full development cycle from proposal through live operations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in using SQL, Python, Go or ETL systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Don&#39;t check all of the boxes? Don&#39;t sweat it. We’re passionate about building a diverse team of humans and as such, if you think you&#39;ve got what it takes for our chaotic-but-fun, remote-friendly, start-up environment—apply anyway. While we have a pretty good idea of what we need, we&#39;re ready for you to challenge our thinking on who needs to be in this role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join ConsenSys?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are some of the perks of being part of a unique organization like ConsenSys&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the most recognized tech companies in the blockchain ecosystem globally.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; A work experience at ConsenSys is a tremendous reference for your future career. ConsenSys alumni have moved on to become tech entrepreneurs, CEOs, and team leads at tech companies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The forefront of a revolution.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; We fundamentally believe blockchain is a next generation of technology that can lay the foundation for a more just and equitable society. You can be a part of building the digital economy of tomorrow and radically transforming our society for the better.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A dynamic startup environment with deep roots.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; We are one of the earliest blockchain companies and a leader in the space.&amp;nbsp; You’ll join a network of entrepreneurs and technologists that reaches the edge of our ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep technical challenges.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; Blockchain&amp;nbsp; technology is just over 10 years old. Ethereum itself is still a toddler. There is much to be done before these platforms can scale to the order of millions or billions of users. We are building the tools, infrastructure and applications l that are pushing the technology forward.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous learning and improvements.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; You’ll be constantly exposed to new concepts, ideas and frameworks from your peers and as you work on different projects — challenging you to stay at the top of your game.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is an equal opportunity employer. We encourage people from all backgrounds to apply. We are committed to ensuring that our technology is made available and accessible to everyone. All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, national origin, ancestry, sex, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age, genetic information, religion, disability, medical condition, pregnancy, marital status, family status, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is aware of fraudulent recruitment practices and we encourage all applicants to review our best practices to protect yourself which can be found &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consensys.net/careers/best-practices-to-avoid-recruitment-fraud/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/PTVt2eg0FTA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://consensys.net/open-roles/gh_jid?gh_jid=3677963&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/341584/consensys.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[consensys@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[1036a9a0-3cf5-4e0b-bfa9-5c096c0d3a02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Consensys]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Application Security Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Veem]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.veem.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Ottawa, Ontario, Canada]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Veem empowers small and medium businesses who spend too much time and money dealing with inefficient payment systems. Our transparent, relationship-based payments model makes it easy to build trust with your vendors, contractors and customers by providing a quick and seamless payable and receivable process. We make the process even easier for these clients by supporting integration with major accounting software including QuickBooks, Netsuite, and Xero. Backed by top investors such as Truist Ventures, Google Ventures, Goldman Sachs, Kleiner Perkins and a global syndicate of tech-forward banks based in the US, Japan, China, Australia, and the Middle East, Veem is a fast-growing financial technology company that is changing the way companies pay and get paid.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Product/Application Security Engineer at Veem, you will play an important role in maturing a nascent security practice and improving the security of Veem’s products. In this role you will collaborate closely with designers, engineers, analysts, product managers and other cross-functional team members within the organization to ensure that our products are designed with privacy, security, compliance - without compromising on our commitment to user delight. Veem considers this position a key to building world-class products that embed security into every aspect of the development process, integrates automated security testing, and maintains a strong security compliance posture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in design discussions with product and engineering teams, advocate for secure design/practices, and relay unvarnished information to the rest of the security team from these discussions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Take charge of identifying and remediating security flaws in our application stack, in collaboration with members of the engineering team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Increase test coverage in sensitive areas of our codebase and mature Security Testing and Signoff (SAST, SCA, IAST, DAST, RASP) that help us continually verify that our security program is working.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Instill confidence within product and engineering teams to build in security and privacy by design.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help implement Secure Software Development Lifecycle (SSDLC) practices and improve automation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform security tasks including threat modeling, developer training, static code analysis, dynamic runtime fuzzing, software security testing and participate in code reviews&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work on fixing vulnerabilities, building in security telemetry/instrumentation, and adding security features to our products/applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with the product and engineering teams to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;prioritize fixes for vulnerabilities and release these fixes with minimal disruption, factoring in dependencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design tooling and frameworks to make incorporation of security best practices into our codebase easier for engineers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help product managers prioritize roadmap items in order to balance security and business risks and design Security as a Feature in Product&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Identify cross-cutting security concerns and work with security and engineering teams to develop common solutions and infrastructure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Integrate automated security testing (including both static and runtime) capabilities into an evolving CI-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;CS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;-CD program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Update, maintain, and deploy new training programs for new engineering hires, annual certification, and expert-level developers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and deliver consistent automated metrics, KPIs and KRIs aligned to OKRs, covering key aspects of the software security program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Take charge of identifying and remediating security flaws in our application stack,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase test coverage in sensitive areas of our codebase, and implement penetration testing tools that help us continually verify that our security program is working.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage scope, scheduling, and remediation of vulnerabilities found as part of pen testing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Knowledge, Skills &amp;amp; Abilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to perform security triage and analysis of security flaws, including Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) metrics scoring, Common Weakness Enumeration (CWE) categorization, and Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) assignment processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working knowledge of Open Web Application Security Project (OWASP) Top 10 Web Application Security Risks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of Industry Security Standards , Framework and Compliance such as PCI-DSS, C2M2, NIST, ISO27001, SOC2, GDPR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work experience in Payments industry shall be considered an asset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Professional experience with web applications and microservice architecture shall be considered an asset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Software Engineering or related field,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years experience delivering application security programs or combination of higher education, certifications &amp;amp; experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Software Application Development experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Sound knowledge of all procedures, standards, and regulations for authorization and authentication, applied cryptography, and security vulnerabilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expert understanding of product engineering and expert knowledge of coding, in Java.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 5 years development experience in Java and Springboot a must&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong familiarity with multiple software security paradigms including MSSDL, BSIMM, and CSSLP.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working knowledge of all vulnerability classes on the OWASP Periodic Table of Vulnerabilities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Requires the ability to function in a fast-paced environment, be available off hours as needed by business priorities, self-starter and able to work well under stress&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent interpersonal communication skills and organizational Savvy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Indispensable - A sense of humour!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COVID-19 considerations:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;Office has masking and social distancing protocol in place. Subject&lt;br&gt;to legal restrictions, all employees will be required to provide proof of vaccination to be&lt;br&gt;regularly in the office.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive Salary&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive Benefits Package (Health, Dental, Medical, Vision) from Day 1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Group RRSP Plan (after 3 months)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3 weeks vacation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Friday afternoon unwind&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Professional Development (Growth - Learning &amp;amp; Development)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/dS1UG-tkpOk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.veem.com/careers/openings/?job=3796097&ref=crypto-careers.com#apply]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180175/veem.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[veem@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[becca71c-87c8-4577-a6b7-2a065bfaaf63]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Veem]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Architect]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://blockfi.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi’s mission is to provide liquidity, transparency and efficiency to digital financial markets by creating products that meet the needs of consumers and corporations across the globe. We build bridges between traditional finance and digital markets that enable growth for all participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re a team of builders and strivers, proud to champion financial inclusivity and offer economic opportunities around the globe. We provide the same inclusivity to our team members. BlockFi is a place where diversity is celebrated, individuality is recognized, and every single team member is valued. We are changing the status quo to be the first financial company that people love, and we rely on our people to make it happen!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is looking for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Architects&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to join our growing team!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Your Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At BlockFi, Software Architects play a crucial role in designing and communicating company-wide architectural strategy and setting architectural guidelines across the engineering organization. Our architects work collaboratively with stakeholders and developers to influence the architecture of systems running in production and act as integral &amp;amp; embedded members of the engineering teams they interact with.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Software Architect, you’ll work closely with several engineering teams to help clarify and improve the architecture of their systems as well as designing and communicating company-wide architectural strategy. We are looking for architects who have real world distributed systems experience, who still consider themselves hands on engineers and are passionate about solving complex software architectural challenges.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure architecture and design decisions are aligned with business vision, and that our systems are built for availability, reliability, scalability, and security from the ground up.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enable early and continuous delivery of business value, integrating across technical (development, infrastructure, security, QA, SRE, etc.) and non-technical functions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Guide tech leads and team members in carefully considering business goals, trade-offs, quality attributes, cross-cutting concerns, and risks prior to committing to design decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support conversations with stakeholders, together with product managers, to understand the problem domain, business goals, quality attribute requirements, and timelines for committing to architectural decisions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop a thorough understanding of the technical and design challenges teams are facing, and regularly communicate this back to the Architecture Team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Document architecture and architectural decisions, explicitly outlining tradeoffs, quality attributes, and alternatives considered.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate cross-team and cross-functional communication. And explain architecture and decisions to both business stakeholders and developers, justifying those decisions in terms they understand.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a member of the Architecture Team, contribute to the development of engineering-wide standards and initiatives to continuously raise the bar for engineering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Though working hours depend on your time zone, for this role you will need to be available daily for meetings between 9:00-12:00 US Eastern Time, and sometimes later.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Expertise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience designing software architecture and implementing high-quality software.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Solid industry experience working with, designing, and building distributed systems at scale.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to explain complex ideas to stakeholders of varying levels of technical expertise.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Desire to help those around you grow and learn from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to work independently while maintaining transparency and collaboration with a larger team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrable experience with establishing strong relationships with technical and nontechnical stakeholders, integrating a variety of perspectives (end users, product, engineering, etc.).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage multiple priorities across multiple teams that are geographically dispersed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent communication, presentation and interpersonal skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We benefit from the great work our employees do each day. That is why we are committed to providing a variety of awesome benefits to help them live their best lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive salary &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because we value your experience and expertise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unlimited vacation / sick days &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because everyone deserves time for R&amp;amp;R&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employer&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;contribution towards health coverage &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(including vision &amp;amp; dental) because your physical health and well-being is important to us&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Various fringe benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; such as 401k, Parental Leave, FSA/HSA, and Employee Assistance Programs because health coverage is more than just choosing your yearly plan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible work environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; because we are a geographically dispersed team and we believe in balance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pet insurance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; because all of your beloved family members should have coverage too&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly lunch stipend &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because there is such a thing as a free lunch!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A close-knit team &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;of enthusiastic, collegial and driven people to work alongside in a highly meritocratic environment because teamwork makes the dreamwork&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi has experienced incredible growth since our launch in August 2017. Our client base has grown to more than 225,000 (and counting), and the company now boasts more than $15 billion in assets on our platform. We recently completed a Series D funding round placing the company&#39;s valuation at $3 billion, and our team now has more than 500 people worldwide. We have established ourselves as a crypto market leader, and as we expand our product suite and geographic footprint, we expect our addressable market to grow exponentially.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi&#39;s leadership team has decades of experience in the traditional financial services and banking world, and we take a conservative approach to regulation that will position us well for sustainable long-term growth and expansion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team is comprised of highly motivated professionals from diverse backgrounds. We are aiming to become the leading lender in crypto and are poised to redefine the global financial ecosystem for the better. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is one of the first companies to ever offer crypto-backed loans and the only company whose founding team has an institutional understanding of the debt capital markets and regulatory landscape in the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$100 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series A, B, and C funding led by Valar Ventures with participation from Susquehanna, Winklevoss Capital, Fidelity, Galaxy Digital, Akuna Capital, and Morgan Creek&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$350 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series D funding led by Bain Capital Ventures, partners of DST Global, Pomp Investments and Tiger Global&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are moving quickly and have already deployed substantial capital into the space, proving our ability to execute and capture customer demand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For information about how we&amp;nbsp;collect, use, or otherwise handle your Personal Information, please see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a class=&quot;c-link&quot; href=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-stringify-link=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; data-sk=&quot;tooltip_parent&quot;&gt;Privacy&amp;nbsp;Policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/o92zit2jRO0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockfi/jobs/5813602002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/553492/blockfi-logo-512x512.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockfi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7eefa976-25ba-4497-9343-24e88aecb41f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer, USA, Exchange Infrastructure]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Block One]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://block.one]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><b><i>Block.one is a global software company specializing in high performance blockchain software. Its flagship product EOSIO is a free, open-source protocol designed to bring speed, scalability, and ease of use to the secure and transparent fundamentals of distributed databases. Block.one invests in companies, projects, and developers around the world leveraging EOSIO technology through its EOS VC initiative. </i></b></p><p></p><p></p>
<p></p>
<p></p>
<p></p><p style="text-align:left"><b>Reports to:</b></p>Manager, Cloud Services, Exchange Infrastructure<p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p>Role &amp; Responsibilities </p><p></p><p>To Work on an agile team to design, build, implement, and maintain platforms, processes, tools, and related infrastructure. Ensure a high level of build health through monitoring and continuous improvement and high levels of uptime for critical systems.</p><p></p><p>Experience/Qualifications</p><p></p><p>5&#43; years of relevant work experience in software development. Experience using cloud products, especially AWS and Google, and CI/CD pipelines. Proficiency with infrastructure as code patterns using tools such as terraform. Experience with Linux and bash scripting. A technologically flexible approach to making software, with a focus on patterns over tools. Proficiency in at least one modern language. A basic understanding of probability and the scientific method and how they might apply to developing high quality software. Ability to work independently with minimal guidance on tasks. Embrace of agile and iterative processes.</p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/sE-skx8Hfoo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://blockone.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Blockone/job/Arlington-Office/Software-Engineer--USA--Exchange-Infrastructure_JR2000631-12]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141852/block_one.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockone@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[05d30dd1-6ec5-427e-804b-57912c461835]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Block One]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crypto Ecosystem Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Wyre]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.sendwyre.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>In order to port over the next billion people into a secure and open financial system, you’re going to need a network of applications that connect to the fiat world… Wyre’s APIs make that happen.<br></p> <p>Wyre's on a mission to bring crypto to the masses - <strong>we're pumped about building the infrastructure that will be used to build the future.</strong></p><p>For visionary developers who want to build the next great crypto company, Wyre is the crypto stack that brings together the most powerful payment APIs in one place. To accomplish this mission, we’ve built a simple set of tools that allows fintech projects to materialize their visions.  (1) Our instant Fiat-to-Crypto Checkout gateway is now being used by hundreds of applications (ie. MetaMask, Opera, Ledger) to offer the best way to convert card payments into crypto, and (2) Our flexible APIs (Transfers API, Custody API, Users API), allow projects to build e-wallets, merchant processing services, and money transfer platforms from the ground up.</p> <p>As of December 2021, Wyre has raised over $55M in funding and currently is the backbone to over 1,200 partners and 7.6M accounts. </p> <p>Wyre is looking for a highly strategic Crypto Ecosystem Manager with a strong background in either technical account/partner/program management with a deep understanding of Web3, payments, and the broader crypto ecosystem. You will be responsible for maintaining our current crypto ecosystem relationships (protocols/exchanges) and will be building new ways that Wyre could connect our technologies to the crypto ecosystem to drive growth. You must be comfortable helping create the partnership from the ground up, including documenting the key processes, defining scalable programs, and setting up the tools to track partner performance. </p> <p>Successful candidates for this position will be highly logical thinkers, and curious learners, with broad experience using Defi, engaging in crypto-native communities, and following emerging crypto trends.</p> <p>This role reports to the Head of Business.</p><ul> <li>6+ years working in partner management, sales, sales operations, and/or business development</li> <li>Strong understanding of blockchain, protocols, Defi, NFTs, DAOs, and other crypto-native technologies and communities</li> <li>BA / BS degree or equivalent practical experience</li> <li>Excellent communication and presentation skills. We're looking for attention to detail and a strong habit of writing</li> <li>Passion for solving complex problems, and building scalable processes</li> <li>Comfort working in a high growth, constantly changing environment</li> <li>A technical background, either working for Web3, SAAS, or a highly technical product startup</li> <li>Proactive, self-starter with a solid ability to self-manage</li> <li>An ability to use and understand analytics to drive strategy</li> </ul><p><br></p><p>Don't think you match the bullets above? No worries. We're a mission driven team that is looking for great people to join us. If you think you've got something to add, let us know what we're missing and how you can help.</p><ul> <li>An opportunity to build the future and freedom to work wherever you want<br> </li> <li>Health, dental, and vision benefits for you and your family</li> <li>Life insurance and disability benefits</li> <li>Equity options for all full-time employees</li> <li>401(k) plan with corporate matching</li> <li>Unlimited paid time off to relax and recharge</li> <li>Enjoy a highly fulfilling, mission-driven culture</li> <li>You are an owner! We offer stock options to each of our employee</li> <li>Fair pay, no matter where you live along with a competitive benefits package</li> <li>Flexible work hours</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/XF10lmj4V1M" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/wyre/j/B508D81D82/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/195911/SendWyre-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[wyre@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[819988b2-62bb-4397-8af0-2a6f483e05ef]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Wyre]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Back-End Web Developer (NodeJS/Shopify)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ledger]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ledger.fr/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Paris]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Founded in 2014, Ledger is a leader in security and infrastructure solutions for cryptocurrencies and blockchain applications.</div><div>Headquartered in Paris, Vierzon, Montpellier, Grenoble, London, Singapore and New York, Ledger has a team of 500+ professionals developing a variety of products and services to safeguard cryptocurrency assets for individuals and companies – including the Ledger hardware wallets line already sold in +200 countries.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>To accelerate the company's growth, Ledger is looking for an experienced talent to join the Ecommerce teams.&nbsp;</div><div>Reporting directly to the Lead Developer, you will be responsible for the Wordpress backend development to support multiple web and mobile clients.</div><br/>Missions<br/><li>Investigate new topics and come up with MVPs</li><li>Build embedded apps for Shopify</li><li>Has a deep understanding of Shopify Storefront API and Billing</li><li>Collaborate with infrastructure and Security teams to ensure stability and security</li><li>Make use of webhooks to interact with external API/Apps</li><li>Mentor less experienced developers on the team</li><li>Write high quality, reusable and documented code</li><br/>Requirements and qualifications<br/><li>3+ years experience working in a development role</li><li>Can create API’s REST and/or GraphQL</li><li>The ability to work well in a team environment</li><li>Excellent knowledge of NodeJs and data structures</li><li>Experience with ReactJs would be a plus</li><li>Comfortable working with AWS, SQL and No SQL databases</li><li>A passion to learn and constantly improve your skills</li><li>Experience with Docker and containerization</li><br/>Benefits<br/><li>Competitive compensation package and ESOP according to the Company policy</li><li>Strong focus on personal development including internal/external trainings and attendance to conferences</li><li>Internal talks, technical meetups and hackathons</li><li>High performance office equipment</li><li>Flexible working hours, remote-friendly environment</li><li>5 weeks of paid vacation + 10 days of RTT</li><li>Comprehensive health insurance policy offering extensive medical, dental and vision care coverage</li><li>Meal vouchers with Swile</li><li>Reimbursement for sports and cultural activities</li><li>Annual company outing for Ledgerdary Days plus infrequent parties, snacks and drinks</li><li>Employee discount on Ledger products</li><br/>Hiring Process<br/><li>An HR interview (30min)</li><li>A Team Fit interview with developers from the team (45min)</li><li>A Technical Test to be done at home (2-3h approx.)</li><li>A Technical interview with the Lead Developer (1h)</li><li>A Final interview with the VP of Engineering (30min)</li><div><b style="font-size: 11pt"><i>Ledger guarantees equity for all during the recruitment process, without any distinction of gender, ethnicity, religion, sexual orientation, social status, disability or age</i></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/5Ss7xnFP9AM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/ledger/1c8676f5-0d67-443c-8a27-f3424820a40d/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/142943/ledger.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ledger@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[83f3aace-4751-47ca-bbcd-26157dd3bc4a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ledger]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Performance and Reward Specialist (Remote - Work from Anywhere)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Xapo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://xapo.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xapo is an international fintech startup on a mission to protect and grow its clients’ life savings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re a fully distributed team that works remotely from 50+ countries around the world. We may come from many different cultures and backgrounds, but it’s our values, our resourcefulness, and our drive that makes us Xapiens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We work hard, think globally, and inspire each other to grow every day. If you’re the best at what you do and share our passion, we want you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us, wherever you are, and help us build a digital bank worthy of the digital age at Xapo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Position overview&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for a Performance and Reward specialist to join our team.&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Reporting into the Chief People Officer, you will own and manage performance management, compensation, recognition and reward. You will lead on all compensation activities including salary benchmarking and implementing annual and off-cycle salary increase processes. You will lead on people analytics, and provide relevant dashboards and reports.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Although we are headquartered in Gibraltar, this is a full time, 100% remote position. Work from anywhere!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Salary benchmarking to ensure we are competitive across the market and there is internal equity in order to attract and retain the best talent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide insight and data to inform management decisions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with the broader HR team to implement recognition and engagement&amp;nbsp; programmes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage job evaluations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead the performance management management process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive consistency (where appropriate) of reward by role and performance&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Skills needed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Benchmarking and market analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Contemporary approaches to performance management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Incentive and LTIP design and management including share options&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience of synthetic equity programmes would be highly desirable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enjoys a challenge and is comfortable with change&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Resilient, positive and calm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great eye for detail, accuracy and quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A flexible team player with a high level of initiative, happy to ‘have a go’ at anything&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Other requirements&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A dedicated workspace&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A reliable internet connection with the fastest speed possible in your area&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Devices and other essential equipment that meet minimal technical specifications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Alignment with Our Values.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY WORK FOR XAPO?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPACT GLOBALLY, WORK REMOTELY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shape the Future: Improve lives through cutting-edge technology, work 100% remotely from anywhere in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own Your Success: Receive attractive remuneration, enjoy an autonomous work culture and flexible hours, apply your expertise to meaningful work every day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expect Excellence: Collaborate, learn, and grow with a high-performance team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT XAPO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We founded Xapo to address two of the biggest issues with Bitcoin adoption: accessibility and security. In a matter of years, we developed an industry-leading platform that introduced cryptocurrency into the daily lives of millions worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, we’re bringing our expertise to all facets of our users’ finances. Because no matter who we are or where we’re from, we all deserve more options, more control, and more peace of mind where our money is concerned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re an Equal Opportunity Employer – we believe that diversity is critical to our success as a global company. An inclusive workplace is the foundation of Xapo – it allows us to create products that cater to clients around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/xapo61/jobs/4889141003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175504/xapo500x500.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[xapo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f1ade05b-4c67-4366-b825-57e86b9f373d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Xapo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Associate Counsel, Republic Deal Room]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Republic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://republic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 11pt">Republic</b><span style="font-size: 11pt"> is a financial technology firm that allows everyone to invest in private markets. Republic operates several distinct business lines including a retail investment platform, a private capital division, and a blockchain advisory practice. The Republic ecosystem has deployed over $800 million in investments, has supported over 800 companies, and is comprised of a community of over 1.5M users across 100 countries. Republic is backed by dozens of leading investment firms and financial institutions and its affiliated entities have co-invested with the best names in venture and private equity. Founded in 2016, Republic is headquartered in New York City with offices worldwide.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Associate Counsel for Republic's Deal Room will advise and support all aspects of our venture capital investment fund formation and direct investment in support of the firm’s specialized syndicated funds and investment advisory businesses. </span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We are looking for an Associate Counsel with a  strong working knowledge and experience of private capital markets including fund formation, private offering exemptions, limited partnerships, Investment Advisers Act and Investment Company Act, tax and ERA compliance matters will be critical for success. This position will report to Republic’s Legal Department and the Managing Director of the Republic Deal Room, providing legal services for the benefit of Republic’s Private Deal Room division as well as Republic Retail related legal matters.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></div><br/>What you'll do:<br/><li>Draft, review and negotiate private fund limited partnership agreements and amendments; investment management / advisory agreements; private placement memoranda; subscription documents; side letters; placement agent agreements; and administration agreements</li><li>Familiarity with syndicates and managed accounts.</li><li>Ensure compliance with all applicable securities and tax laws and regulations, regarding specialized fund offerings.</li><li>Understanding tax sensitivities of various investor classes is a plus.</li><li>Collaboratively coordinate with internal key stakeholders across the firm.</li><li>Oversee fund’s investment and closings.</li><li>Handle and coordinate US regulatory filings and applications.</li><li>Manage efficiently the use and costs of fund formation and finance outside counsel.</li><li>Other projects and tasks as they arise from time to time.</li><br/>What we're looking for<br/><li>Juris Doctorate from an accredited U.S. law school and licensed to practice in at least one state</li><li>4+ years of experience at a reputable law firm or investment fund with significant private equity fund formation and private investments, with strong familiarity of capital markets and securities law.</li><li>Exhibits sound practical judgment with a client-service and commercial orientation</li><li>Strong interpersonal skills and a positive work ethic and able to be flexible to deliver under higher pressure and tight deadlines</li><li>Proven analytical and organizational skills with the ability to handle projects from inception to conclusion; subject matter expert with quality decision-making; and, fostering a collaborative team environment</li><li>Communicate complex ideas in an understandable manner with all levels of Republic’s operations.</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Qy1lzYTV6Uc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/republic/b4a343dd-c7e2-4754-8e4b-303bd40231b5/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/211719/Republic.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[republic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b024f433-5745-442c-98f6-a3b65ac4a9b0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Republic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer - NFT/Blockchain Engineering (Remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Recur]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.recurforever.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Recur is building the future of digital collectibles on-chain, known as Non-Fungible Tokens (NFTs) – the newest Unicorn industry.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;RECUR needs a Principal Software Engineer to help architect and build our NFT platform from the ground up.&amp;nbsp; You will be a member of the founding engineering team and will have significant influence on the technologies we use and how we build software at RECUR.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;The primary focus of our team is backend blockchain integration. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If working directly with blockchains is what you want to do, then this role is for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do we at RECUR believe makes a great engineering team?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here are our core beliefs:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;It’s important to have team members that care about the team’s results more than their own individual achievements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;It’s important for leadership to be tolerant of making mistakes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;It’s important that the team members help, teach, and mentor one another&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;It’s important not to place blame on individuals when things go bad but instead to evaluate as a team how we do it better the next time&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;It’s important to be clear on what that mission is and minimize the distractions on the teams executing on that mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Small teams execute better than big ones, empower small teams with ownership and minimize the dependencies between them&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;It’s important to encourage self-directed innovation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section page-centered&quot;&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will do at RECUR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Architect and code everything from small components to big systems.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive decisions on what technologies we use and the software practices we adopt&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be a technical lead on small to large sized projects&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work on a small agile team of software engineers and product managers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coach less experienced teammates to become better software engineers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Set an example and define our standards for how we code and deliver our software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help us grow our team of talented software engineers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you bring to RECUR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have 8+ years of experience developing software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience building and deploying software in the cloud, preferably AWS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have built and maintained highly scalable and reliable internet applications or platforms accessed by hundreds of thousands of users on a daily basis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have designed and maintained highly transactional databases that store lots of data and handle heavy loads&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are a very experienced programmer in at least two languages and know how and when to apply functional and object oriented concepts (i.e. JavaScript, Go, Java, Python)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are an experienced technical lead, that can direct and guide a team of engineers through building platforms/products and solving big, complex, open ended problems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience building and maintaining ecommerce, payment, auction, trading platforms, or similar &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;where security and keeping customer funds safe is imperative&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You know how to break down a big, complex problem into smaller components and coordinate your team to iteratively deliver high quality software&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a passion for testing your code through unit testing and automation&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You strive to be a productive engineer and use the latest tools and techniques to achieve this goal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have experience building applications with node.js, preferably as serverless services, especially with typescript.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have an interest in blockchain, cryptocurrency, and NFTs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are a legally eligible to work in the USA or Canada&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits &amp;amp; Perks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to being a remote-first company &amp;amp; embracing remote work best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Company sponsored Health, Dental and Vision Benefits, 401K with 2% match&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3 weeks paid vacation, 10 company holidays and fully paid parental leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry focused lunch &amp;amp; learns, swag, and the flexibility to get the tooling you need&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work with incredibly passionate people on a mission to shape an industry!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-REMOTE&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/recur/jobs/4169768004/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/828978/recur-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[recur@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c3f0772a-1403-43f6-89c3-599030254b64]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Recur]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Global Brand Media Strategy]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing. We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual, and we want to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno welcomes crypto lovers and crypto newbies. You - just like everyone in the world - are on your own unique crypto-learning journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a mission-driven cryptocurrency company that is building more open and equal access to the future of money. You don’t have to know lots about crypto to be interested in joining us, you just have to feel that upgrading the world to a fairer financial system matters, and that you’d like to be part of this global change. We’re a passionate and committed team taking on a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;working together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with unusual skill, focus and determination. We need the best team on board for our mission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If that sounds like a culture you’d thrive in, then we are excited to hear from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little bit about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno means moon in Esperanto, we chose the name because at night, wherever you are in the world, you look up at the same moon. We believe in the power of working together, as one team, across borders, with clear focus and shared purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our popular mobile app and website helps people around the world grow and manage their money using the world&#39;s most mature cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum and USDC. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve processed over &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$21 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Over 7 million customers across 40 countries have chosen to hold their crypto wallets on Luno because we offer a delightfully simple experience and bank-grade security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re part of the Digital Currency Group, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;named in 2021 as one of TIME magazine’s 100 Most Influential Companies, in the “Disruptors” category alongside Tesla, AirBnB, SpaceX, Peloton. TIME noted that DCG is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/collection/time100-companies/5953752/digital-currency-group/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;“mainstreaming cryptocurrency”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re proud to be one of the world’s most international cryptocurrency teams, with colleagues from 43 different nationalities working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria, Australia and Singapore. Financial inclusion is part of our mission, but on a deeper level, inclusion is a way of life, and a way of work for us. It is part of who we are as a company, and a group of human individuals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role in a nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A key senior leader for our global marketing team, your focus will be the effective deployment of our significant brand marketing budget across all of our global markets. Your knowledge, experience and work will help shape our global ATL marketing strategy &amp;amp; execution as we aggressively invest in growing our top-of-funnel. To succeed you will love being both coach and player and your wide scope will stretch from supporting local market decision-making and negotiations, to guiding experiments and implementing matrix management processes for budget approvals, results tracking, learning &amp;amp; knowledge sharing etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In this role you will&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with our regional marketing leaders to help&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;drive global brand planning and media buying strategy across all Above The Line paid channels including television, radio, print, out-of-home in all our markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; This will include: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;evangelizing ATL media buying &amp;amp; negotiation best practices; d&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;eveloping processes, repeatable methodologies and frameworks that support efficient ATL media buying across all markets; d&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;riving ATL channel analysis (efficiency, feasibility and scalability) and fostering knowledge-sharing across global markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support the management of local media buying agencies to sense check commercial value and ensure that we always deliver against global brand and business objectives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define and own global ATL performance reporting. Track brand uplift and implement holdouts, collaborate with our Head of Growth and Growth Fleet on attribution.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Leverage insights, learnings, and modeling to develop recommendations on ATL channel mix, planning and budget allocation in every market.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner and align with the Performance Marketing Team &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;to drive Through The Line marketing excellence (particularly in planning and reporting)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help create a pipeline of new ideas and methods of marketing including “test and learn” plans and analyze relative ROI possibilities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal Lunaut for this role will have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are a marketing expert industry-leading experience in paid media planning/buying, channel mix decisions and iteration through strong reporting. Desirable experience also includes:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;global experience, working across multiple markets, with a deep understanding of media price variations and opportunities by market and channel.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;experience partnering with in-house performance marketing, data scientists, marketing sciences or analytics experts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;experience working with new brands in rapid growth, disruptors or those defining a new category.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Possess excellent collaboration skills, and can work effectively within a matrixed functional organization in close partnership with key business partners, internal and external.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Posses killer commercial acumen, with strong negotiation skills and a proven track record of driving strong commercial decision-making for real business impact.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are analytical and metrics-driven, are comfortable working with data and (in addition to deep ATL expertise) have a good understanding of performance digital marketing and full-funnel execution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Life at Luno&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno is a ‘remote but reachable’ company! At Luno, we trust that people can do their work effectively anywhere and provide Lunauts with the flexibility to decide where they do their best work. For some of us, that’s at home for the majority of the time, for others, that might mean joining other Lunauts in person at one of our Luno workspaces more often. Luno is built on our relationships, so we still value in-person connection and have a minimum expectation of spending time in person once a quarter.&amp;nbsp; So as long as you are based in one country with a Luno workspace, we want to hear from you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not negatively discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3799573?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[DeFi Partnerships Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ankr]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ankr.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, California, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>ABOUT ANKR</strong></p><p>Ankr provides Web3 infrastructure for the easy, accessible and affordable deployment of blockchain nodes, API’s, decentralized staking infrastructure and Layer 2 scaling solutions, designed to lower the entry barrier for everyday people, enterprises, and developers to contribute to blockchain ecosystems.</p><p><strong>Check us out at </strong><a href="https://www.ankr.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external"><strong>https://www.ankr.com/</strong></a></p><p>Ankr was founded in 2017 in Berkeley, California. Its founding team and headquarters are based in San Francisco. Ankr’s distributed team of 50+ people operates from offices in San Francisco, Shanghai, Moscow, and Amsterdam</p><p>The ideal DeFi Partnerships Manager for this role will have account management and business development experience, as we are looking for someone that can engage with DeFi communities and showcase expert knowledge using DeFi in a multi-chain environment</p><p>In this role, you will take ownership of structuring/forming partnerships and sell liquid staking to exchanges.</p><p><strong>In this role your responsibilities will be but not limited to:</strong></p><ul> <li>Research DeFi project needs, develop a comprehensive list of potential partners and pitch those providers on joining StakeFi</li> <li>Establish relationships with key stakeholders across providers including: partnership and business development teams, technical escalations, entitlements and operations</li> <li>Work closely with projects to expand partnerships</li> <li>Educate the internal marketing and sales teams on the staking offerings available</li> <li>Participate and coordinate StakeFi marketing strategy implementation with the marketing team</li> </ul><p><strong>We are looking for someone who has:</strong></p><ul> <li>Strong background in account management, sales or business development and alliances experience in Crypto or in tech-driven businesses</li> <li>A expert understanding of the DeFi landscape and trends in data and technology</li> <li>Genuine interest in the blockchain industry and understanding of the ecosystem</li> <li>Excellent presentation abilities and composure presenting to all levels of technical and business audiences</li> <li>High EQ and demonstrated experience engaging with and expanding business partnerships</li> <li>Excellent written and verbal communication skills</li> <li>A self-starter mentality, able to work independently and proactively to resolve issues</li> <li>Must thrive in an environment of rapid change, moving targets, and high intensity</li> </ul><p><br></p><p>ANKR is an equal opportunity employer. All applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, religion, color, national origin, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, age, status as a protected veteran, or status as a qualified individual with a disability.</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/ankr/j/8FDF905DFB/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/746707/ankr-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ankr@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3b58522a-6fba-41ac-b017-94bbed42523c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ankr]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Brand Integrated Media Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,400+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b>About the Role</b></div><div><br></div><div>Do you obsess communities and stories that sit at the intersection of tech and culture? We at Kraken are building a world class brand marketing org and are looking for people who understand how to build community and brand reputation in compelling, creative and innovative ways. We believe the future is paved by crypto and it will have creativity and culture at the center.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a passionate and experienced marketing and advertising executive to join our team to lead our brand integrated media team. This is the team that leverages data and sophisticated modeling to work with traditional and non-traditional media platforms to ensure we are driving the business objectives through paid advertising. This includes TV, Print, OOH, Social, OTT, Display, Audio, Transportation and guerrilla marketing.</div><div><br></div><div>You are always curious, seeking to solve problems and finding new ways to connect people around stories. Your team will be responsible for using data and research to develop clear strategic strategy and execution of media plans to drive brand narrative and campaigns. You will work closely with the Growth Marketing team to ensure these brand campaigns result in clear success KPIs that drive business results. You are a leader that can adapt to your situation and will always be there for your team. We focus on quality in our storytelling and we are thoughtful and calculated with our big bets. Finally, we aim to have fun.</div><div><br></div><div><b>This is a fully remote role.</b></div><div><br></div><div><b>Responsibilities</b></div><div>- You are the global lead that oversees the integrated media team.</div><div>- Set strategic vision for integrated media and build quarterly plans that support and accelerate the Brand Strategy offense.</div><div>- Work back with other key brand marketing leaders in brand strategy, partnerships and operations to orchestrate full brand initiatives </div><div>- Good grasp of art and science when it comes to the consumer and development of culture.</div><div>- Make data-driven decisions when framing hypotheses, determining product-market fit, evaluating campaign performance, and setting goals.</div><div>- An expert in all things paid media, including measurement tools, data backends, privacy policy and relationships in the media world.</div><div>- Understand and communicate data baselines for success metrics and ensure dashboards/reports are socialized and adopted at key checkins.</div><div>- Understand the evolving landscape of integrated media and have a firm grasp of how to drive a full funnel approach across online and offline platforms.</div><div>- Manage large scale, sophisticated budgets and operate with precision and creativity.</div><div>- Take a diplomatic leadership approach to involve stakeholders early and get cross-functional work done; be a proactive leader and decision-maker.&nbsp;</div><div>- Create and share intel on competing products and marketing; summarize what is working well and what is not and how we will differentiate ourselves.</div><div>- Be an owner: step up and take the lead on challenging, ambiguous work.&nbsp;Ship. We are in hyper growth and everyone is on board this rocketship to drive impact.</div><div>- Be on the forefront of culture and innovation in marketing.</div><div>- Understand emerging space of culture and embrace new opportunities where advantageous.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Requirements</b></div><div><br></div><div>- 10+ years of previous experience in digital marketing, media agency, premium brands, digital platforms.</div><div>- Has executed large media plans for a premium brand.</div><div>- Understand segmentation strategy and how to target consumers in key touchpoint.</div><div>- You understand how to communicate complex datasets for executives, but can get into the weeds with your direct reports to ensure we are measuring effectively.</div><div>- Has worked on consumer research projects to identify opportunities and help coordinate plans to achieve objectives.</div><div>-Concise speaker, storyteller, and writer: you can slice, dice, and distill a narrative from a complex data set into an executive summaryGood grasp on relationship building with larger parters, agents, organizations</div><div>- You have built and led sophisticated, matrixed teams that are distributed globally.</div><div>- An amazing pulse on what is relevant in culture and can understand how&nbsp;</div><div>- Understand persona work and how to grow a brand through strategic planning and&nbsp;Previous crypto experience not required but certainly a plus!</div><div><br></div><div><b>Nice to Have</b></div><div>- Geo-specific, global client experience in North America, Europe, Asia-Pacific, EMEA, or Latin America&nbsp;</div><div>- You’ve got a couple of moonshot ideas for transforming marketing in crypto</div><div>- You’ve got an ease about you: you address urgency head-on and handle difficult, ambiguous situations with a clear, cool head and an open mind</div><div>#EU #US #LI-AG1 #CANADA</div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</b></div><div><br></div><div><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link"><b>Follow us on Twitter</b></a></div><div><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link"><b>Catch up on our blog</b></a></div><div><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link"><b>Follow us on LinkedIn</b></a></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/dae315f9-4201-41b1-89d0-6bfdd0979530/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[General Manager - Germany]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://blockchain.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Germany]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;page&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;layoutArea&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General Manager - Germany&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain.com is on a mission to empower anyone in the world to control their own money. As a crypto industry leader since 2011, Blockchain.com plays a role in almost every major crypto business: from trading, to the most widely-used bitcoin wallet, to a foundational source of crypto data, to a robust global institutional business with billions in flow.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We are looking for a seasoned leader to join the Blockchain.com team as the General Manager (GM) for our operations in Germany. Reporting to the Chief Business Officer, the GM - Germany has one of the most demanding positions the company has to offer; as the leader of Blockchain.com in a country, the GM is responsible for the development and growth of our business in one of our most critical international markets. You are literally bringing the financial system for the internet to Germany.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The GM-Germany role requires operational excellence and will focus on maintaining Blockchain.com quality throughout the customer experience, product localization, regional business development and marketing and public relations oversight. Additional key responsibilities include building and strengthening regulatory relations, active participation in M&amp;amp;A opportunities, exploring partnerships and building the German team and operations processes from the beginning.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the development of Blockchain.com’s business throughout Germany and continue to grow revenues and customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit a world class team to execute the global business strategy in market, including hiring and managing additional German sales executives as the business grows.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and execute strategy for retail and institutional product localization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate product/process needs to company leadership team and work with the product and engineering teams to deliver on them.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help scale our other markets through developing and sharing best practices.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Initiate creative local marketing strategies and user growth campaigns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide strategic input into global brand marketing moments, ensuring market resonance and impact across Germany.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Represent Blockchain.com at local events and with the media as the face of Blockchain.com Germany.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with the marketing team to develop the Blockchain.com institutional brand and marketing materials.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Engage, onboard, and cover institutional clients in Germany to drive volumes across custody, trading, and lending.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage relationships with our most important German institutional clients to source new opportunities and increase the overall amount of business we do together, including identifying, contacting, and building relationships with key strategic partners and potential customers. The universe of companies could include crypto exchanges, neobanks, fintech apps, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide client feedback and market intelligence to the head of institutional product management to help develop new products and features.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be the voice of the region, with an understanding of market forces, regulatory landscape, and consumer demand for financial services products, and a particular focus on working with regulators and our internal legal and compliance teams to acquire and comply with all required licenses to grow the institutional business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage local regulatory concerns and local politics, pulling in support as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work in unison with the the company business team to support partnership opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with our community team to ensure cultural competence in our customer interactions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate local preferences back to teams at headquarters. Help them further enhance the product to deliver the best experience possible for our customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;page&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;layoutArea&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;page&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;layoutArea&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;7+ years of experience in management consulting, investment banking, operational leadership and/or other relevant experience in tech, startup, corporate or entrepreneurship.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A relentless &amp;amp; optimistic attitude, dedication to detail, and passion for crypto finance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly organized, and a systems thinker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Curious and passionate about new concepts, businesses, and more.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to analyze complex topics, find the signal in the noise but communicate simply.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Execute on projects quickly and with a high quality bar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Can work cross-functionally with a diverse management team and other key stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Thrives on ambiguity. Prefers to work on problems using data.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mobile, ready to live on the internet with a willingness to take on any challenge, no matter how seemingly small, or impossibly difficult.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deep knowledge of the regulatory environment and ability to interface with regulators and governments.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Desire to build robust processes and procedures to support the growth of this business unit.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail, and ability to communicate clearly with engineers, finance, and counterparties.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Positive attitude and mature interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPENSATION &amp;amp; PERKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited vacation policy; work hard and take time when you need it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple equipment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full-time salary based on experience and meaningful equity in an industry-leading company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive health benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote-first environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ground floor opportunity: shape the strategic direction of the company in Germany and continental Europe&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make a difference: we’re not just another crypto company: we’re the financial system for the internet and changing the future of finance we have access to an amazing list of advisors and investors in Germany that we actively engage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;layoutArea&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;page&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;layoutArea&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;APPLICATION&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email LinkedIn profile and resume to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:nita@blockchain.comi&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;nita@blockchain.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Include link to Github, StackOverflow, personal website and/or blog (if applicable).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;When you apply to a job at Blockchain.com, the personal data contained in your application will be collected by one or more of the following subsidiaries of Blockchain Luxembourg S.A (each, a “Controller”):&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;Blockchain Access UK Ltd. Blockchain (GB) Limited Blockchain (US), Inc. Blockchain (LT), UAB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;You may contact our Data Protection Officer by email at dpo@blockchain.com. Your personal data will be processed for the purposes of managing Controller’s recruitment related activities, which include setting up and conducting interviews and tests for applicants, evaluating and assessing the results thereto, and as is otherwise needed in the recruitment and hiring processes. Such processing is legally permissible under Art. 6(1)(f) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation) as necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Controller, which are the solicitation, evaluation, and selection of applicants for employment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;Your personal data will be shared with Greenhouse Software, Inc., a cloud services provider located in the United States of America and engaged by Controller to help manage its recruitment and hiring process on Controller’s behalf. Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, your personal data will be transferred to the United States once you submit it through this site. Because the European Union Commission has determined that United States data privacy laws do not ensure an adequate level of protection for personal data collected from EU data subjects, the transfer will be subject to appropriate additional safeguards under the standard contractual clauses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;Your personal data will be retained by Controller as long as Controller determines it is necessary to evaluate your application for employment. Under the GDPR, you have the right to request access to your personal data, to request that your personal data be rectified or erased, and to request that processing of your personal data be restricted. You also have the right to data portability. In addition, you may lodge a complaint with an EU supervisory authority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;page&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;section&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;layoutArea&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain/jobs/3798984?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180745/blockchaininc.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchaininc@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5457bd3d-b464-4d43-bfd6-5c9d9e62930e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Marketing Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.okcoin.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who We Are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okcoin is one of the world’s largest and fastest-growing cryptocurrency exchanges. We help millions of&lt;br&gt;people buy and sell bitcoin, and over 50 other crypto assets every day — but our work is a whole lot more&lt;br&gt;than that. We’re building an inclusive future of finance, one that opens new opportunities to learn financial&lt;br&gt;literacy, store value, and build wealth for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;Ready to help the next billion people experience the future of finance with us? Come on board. We have&lt;br&gt;offices in San Francisco, Miami, Malta, Hong Kong, Singapore, and Japan. Even though this role is listed&lt;br&gt;in San Francisco, we are remote-friendly and believe in you working wherever you work best.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Product Marketing tells our product’s story to the market. We have a small, mighty team that we are&lt;br&gt;looking to grow. We work closely with product and marketing to turn value propositions into compelling&lt;br&gt;messages for customers and prospects&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Opportunity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;The successful candidate will be critical to the successful development, launch, and maintenance of&lt;br&gt;products and capabilities. This candidate will think big about the future of crypto and how you can bring&lt;br&gt;individual investors and institutions into the crypto economy more quickly. As a key contributor within the&lt;br&gt;Marketing team, you’ll be tasked with developing effective marketing strategies and plans through&lt;br&gt;strategic proven marketing strategies; developing positioning, messaging, competitive differentiation, and&lt;br&gt;enabling the Sales and Marketing teams to ensure they are aligned and work efficiently to generate and&lt;br&gt;close opportunities. Most importantly, as our dedicated marketer you’ll drive results and significantly grow&lt;br&gt;the adoption of Okcoin products and features.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Be Doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;● Support Growth through delivery of new products and improve upon GTM strategies for existing&lt;br&gt;products&lt;br&gt;● Execute and track program deliverables, milestones, action items, dependencies, risks, and&lt;br&gt;mitigation plans&lt;br&gt;● Develop solid working relationships with cross-functional teams to best understand and deliver on&lt;br&gt;business goals and priorities.&lt;br&gt;● Track performance of campaigns to provide data-backed insights to optimize campaigns and find&lt;br&gt;new opportunity areas&lt;br&gt;● Prepare presentations and clearly communicate findings from initiatives to management and to&lt;br&gt;the broader organization&lt;br&gt;● Be the voice of the customers and Influence Product Design and Product pipeline to satisfy user&lt;br&gt;needs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Look For In You:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;● 3+ years of GTM experience with a track record of managing all aspects of a successful product&lt;br&gt;launch.&lt;br&gt;● Proven in orchestrating a wide range of marketing initiatives - everything from strategic planning -&lt;br&gt;to content marketing - to go-to-market implementation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;● Excellent written and verbal communications skills; ability to translate strategy into clear&lt;br&gt;actionable plans&lt;br&gt;● Ability to solve complex problems and rapidly formulate a clear point-of-view&lt;br&gt;● Excellent prioritization skills and willingness to roll up one&amp;amp;#39;s sleeves to get the job done&lt;br&gt;● Thrive when working in a collaborative and cross-functional environment and inspire others&lt;br&gt;around you&lt;br&gt;● Solid analytical, problem-solving, and decision-making skills&lt;br&gt;● Experience with Wordpress, Hubspot, Google Analytics&lt;br&gt;● BA/BS degree; preferably in marketing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;● You either are already or are eager to become an expert in the blockchain and cryptocurrency&lt;br&gt;landscape and will understand how speculators, traders, digital asset exchanges, blockchain&lt;br&gt;money services businesses and financial institutions operate.&lt;br&gt;● Experience working in a disruptive technology, successfully launching products, ideally, within&lt;br&gt;FinTech, eCommerce, SaaS, AdTech, or Digital Wallet business experience&lt;br&gt;● A history (and preference) of being both strategic, analytical and execution-oriented&lt;br&gt;● MBA preferred, but not required&lt;br&gt;● Experience working with teams across offices and time zones.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights of Perks and Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;● Market competitive total compensation package&lt;br&gt;● Comprehensive insurance package including medical, dental, vision, disability &amp;amp; life&lt;br&gt;● insurance (Company pays 100% for employee/80% for dependents)&lt;br&gt;● 401K with company contribution&lt;br&gt;● Flexible PTO policy, company paid holidays, and flexible hours&lt;br&gt;● UberEats Program&lt;br&gt;● Paid Parental Leave&lt;br&gt;● Employee Referral Bonus Program paid in BTC&lt;br&gt;● Company Donation Match&lt;br&gt;● More surprises when you join!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Okcoin Statement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Okcoin is committed to equal employment opportunities regardless of race, color, genetic information,&lt;br&gt;creed, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, lawful alien status, national origin, age, marital&lt;br&gt;status, and non-job related physical or mental disability, or protected veteran status. Pursuant to the San&lt;br&gt;Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance, we will consider for employment qualified applicants with arrest and&lt;br&gt;conviction records.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xAd9NClUmZY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okcoin/jobs/4898195003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/551872/OKCoin_400x400.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okcoin@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[57e0c7fc-df31-4da2-b52b-befd9a7f36e9]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[General Application]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Nifty's]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://niftys.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT NIFTY’S, Inc.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Nifty&#39;s is the eco-friendly home for NFTs (non-fungible tokens) from your favorite brands and creators on the blockchain. Nifty&#39;s, based in Miami FL, brings together premium publishers, brands and creators with collectors, curators and the communities of fans that will emerge around them. Offering an easy-to-use interface, the innovative platform will allow members to collect, discover, and curate the most important digital art and other collectibles from across the rapidly expanding NFT universe. Nifty&#39;s will provide creators with a premium, powerful, flexible and safe platform to launch their NFTs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other things to note:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nifty’s, Inc. strives to be a best-in-class and equal opportunity employer.  All qualified applicants &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, religion, color, national origin, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, age, status as a protected veteran, among other &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;things, or status as a qualified individual with disability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This job posting highlights the most critical responsibilities and requirements of the job. Other duties may be assigned as needed. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nifty&#39;s, Inc. Privacy Policy can be found here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://niftys.com/privacy-policy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;https://niftys.com/privacy-policy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/niftysinc/jobs/4091887004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/943210/niftys.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alexander+niftysinc@cryptocareers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6167914b-84e3-41bb-934a-cdb803281ce7]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Nifty's]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Documentation Engineer (Flow, Developer Experience)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.axiomzen.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We're looking for a passionate Documentation Engineer to help us build the Flow documentation platform which will empower developers via exceptional learning materials that make Flow the most accessible blockchain in the world.</div><div>The ideal candidate has full-stack engineering skills, takes pride in coaching people to learn new concepts &amp; technologies, and is excited about bringing documentation and content to the next level.</div><div><br></div><div><b>A little about us:</b></div><div>Flow is the blockchain for builders. Created by Dapper Labs, the team behind CryptoKitties, Flow blockchain is designed for a new generation of consumer apps, games, and the digital assets that power them. Flow helps developers build the kinds of applications people want to use, with a focus on consumer-friendly onboarding and the ability to handle mainstream scale.</div><div><br></div><div>The Flow team is a humble and curious bunch of builders and scientists who share a passion for blockchain technology and the new kinds of software it enables. Our people are our greatest strength: our diverse team flourishes in an environment where personal autonomy and professional growth are encouraged. We value our culture above else; regardless of where you came from or what you studied, your role here will necessitate both a high level of creativity and strategic thinking on complex issues.</div><br/>What we’ll accomplish together:<br/><li>Transform existing Flow documentation site into a learning hub for all audiences</li><li>Educate developers with concise and well-structured documentation</li><li>Empower Flow enthusiasts by creating accurate, discoverable, and high-quality documents</li><li>Promote best practices and new features by producing new documentation that highlights both</li><br/>A little about you:<br/><li>Adept at collaborating with technical and non-technical stakeholders to produce learning materials</li><li>Experience with developing applications of any kind using JavaScript, Go, Python, Java, or any modern programming languages</li><li>Has strong desire to continuously improve existing documentation</li><li>Experience with extracting knowledge from subject matter experts and translating that into clear and structured documentation</li><li>Experience with HTML, Markdown, and/or Markdown Extension</li><li>We value your past work: if you have produced any learning materials that you are proud of, please share them with us!</li><div><b>More about Dapper Labs:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Dapper Labs is the world's first blockchain entertainment company. We are the creators of industry-leading experiences including CryptoKitties and NBA Top Shot, as well as Dapper Wallet, the simplest way to manage your assets and use the blockchain. We are also the original developers behind Flow, a new decentralized blockchain designed from the ground up for scalability and ease of use.</div><div><br></div><div>Our mission at Dapper Labs is to make the world a more open, empowering, and enjoyable place through consumer adoption of decentralized technologies. We have raised over $600M from leading VCs including Fred Wilson (USV) and Chris Dixon as well as Venrock, Samsung, Google Ventures, Coatue, NBA players, and global artists, among others. Dapper Labs partners include the NBA and NBPA, the NFL-PA, Ubisoft, Warner Music, Turner, Dr. Seuss, Genies, and the UFC, as well as 100+ others.</div><div><br></div><div>Visit our website to learn even more about Dapper Labs, including <a href="https://www.dapperlabs.com/careers#benefits" class="postings-link">information about benefits and perks</a>.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Vvp75OCtwa0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axiomzen/bb179b12-5ee3-49e0-b0d6-bb7dcaa36d74/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194192/axiomzen1.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axiomzen@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5da21464-b527-48a0-a501-0b4f2e445537]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Specialist, Compliance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Block One]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://block.one]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Gibraltar]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Block.one is a software publisher specializing in high performance blockchain technologies. Its<br />first project, EOSIO, an open-source blockchain protocol designed to enable secure data<br />transfer and high-performance decentralized applications, has received global recognition as<br />the first performant blockchain platform, following its introduction in May 2018.</p><p><br />Through its affiliate, Block.one Gibraltar provides software development and consultancy<br />services through its office in Gibraltar. We are continuing to look for global and local<br />talent to join us in Gibraltar to offer creative solutions based on the latest technological<br />innovations and trends.</p><p>                               </p><p style="text-align:left"><b>Responsibilities &amp; Qualifications:</b></p><p style="text-align:inherit">   </p><p>Role &amp; Responsibilities<span> </span></p><p></p><p>Subject matter expert and AML/KYC second line specialist<br />Alert and rule management and escalation<br />Internal and external reporting preparation and case management<br />Supporting the business to build and achieve excellent financial crime controls.<br />Delivering as an individual and also as part of a team.</p><p></p><p>Experience/Qualifications</p><p></p><p>Demonstrated and relevant experience in KYC/AML compliance<br />Excellent communication skills<br />Fluency in English</p><p>Fluency in other languages an asset</p><p style="text-align:inherit"><span class="WE41">                        </span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/sE-skx8Hfoo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://blockone.wd3.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/Blockone/job/Gibraltar/Specialist--Compliance_JR2000368]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141852/block_one.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockone@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[05d30dd1-6ec5-427e-804b-57912c461835]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Block One]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Junior Global Investigation & Monitoring Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sofia, Sofia, Bulgaria]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>We are Foris Europe - the operational power of Crypto.com.</p><p><br></p><p>Crypto.com is redefining how money is being moved, spent and invested. Crypto.com is democratizing blockchain technology by designing beautiful, simple and useful financial services that have a lasting, positive impact on people’s lives.</p><p><br></p><p>For our Sofia office the Compliance team is looking for a dynamic Junior AML Analyst. You will work alongside with the Compliance Manager and support a top-of-class Compliance program. </p><p><br></p><p>In this role, you will:<br></p><ul> <li>Monitor, investigate and act upon compliance-related alerts;</li> <li>Analyze complex cases reported by other teams within the organization focusing on suspicious transactions patters and their analysis;</li> <li>Work with sophisticated tools in the cryptocurrency realm that allow for investigation of suspicious transactions;</li> <li>Draft internal and external SARs and maintain a proper record-keeping;</li> <li>Prepare customer activity reports in accordance to local regulatory requirements and obligations with the Company's partners;</li> <li>Conduct enhance due diligence on high-risk customers;</li> <li>Provide support and knowledge-sharing to cross functional teams such as Customer Care and Risk teams;</li> <li>Maintain a working knowledge of AML/CTF best practices, internal control and risk management practices;</li> <li>Participate in writing AML/CTF related policies and procedures.</li> </ul><p>You will know we are looking for you, if you have:</p><ul> <li>Experience in the AML/CFT space in a financial institution/fintech company;</li> <li>Working knowledge of anti-money laundering and terrorist financing analysis techniques;</li> <li>Ability to be a self-starter, work under minimal supervision, and meet all goals within SLA;</li> <li>Experience with blockchain analysis  (Blockchain explorer, Etherscan) and rule-engine tools preferred;</li> <li>Past experience with technologies for individuals' verification execution (KYC, PEP / Sanction, blacklists,...);</li> <li>An eye for synthesizing details and connecting the dots between complex data relationships;</li> <li>1+ years of experience preferred;</li> <li>Proficiency in verbal and written English</li> </ul><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech;</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you;</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team;</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing a brand-new product from scratch alongside with a talented team.</li> </ul><p><br></p><p>If you meet the requirements above and feel ready to dive into our challenging dynamics, by joining the Foris Europe's team on a permanent contract basis, we are looking forward to receiving your CV in English by applying below.<br></p><p>Only shortlisted candidates will be contacted with information on the next steps of our application process.<br></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/E42550BABA/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Customer Success - PayDay]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Revolut]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.revolut.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">ABOUT THE TEAM</b></div><div>Since 2015, Revolut has introduced over 20 million customers to a new way to handle their money.</div><div>We approach sales at Revolut the same way that we approach everything else. We take complex issues, and create extraordinary solutions that our customers love. From&nbsp;on-boarding&nbsp;flows to sales processes, our goal is to both inform and delight.&nbsp;</div><div>Put simply, we build things we want to use ourselves, that we’re proud to show to our friends and families.</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">ABOUT THE ROLE</b></div><div>Your mission is to build and lead a world class Customer Success team from scratch, relentlessly focusing on providing the fastest and most streamlined onboarding experience for clients and partners, driving exponential growth in product usage in your client book, and driving a high-performance culture in your team.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Revolut is the UK’s most valuable ever private tech company, and we achieved this by continually questioning the status quo when it comes to finance. With On-Demand Pay, we’re challenging the way that salaries are paid, and putting our users in control of when they receive their wages.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>More than half of all employees experience cash flow issues every 2-4 months or more, and financial stress is the number one reason they are likely to leave their job. As Head of Customer Success, you will help companies globally solve this problem by helping them implement Revolut On-Demand Pay and promote employee financial wellbeing with the usage of Revolut’s full suite of financial products.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>You will be at the forefront of our mission to Revolutionise financial well-being, democratising cash-flow cadence and inspiring thought leadership at the world’s most influential corporations.</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">WHAT YOU'LL BE DOING</b><b>:</b></div><div>• Manage a team of customer success managers and manage hiring for the customer success team</div><div>• Oversee the onboarding process of customers and partners, including project management for GTM and technical integration. Ensure that all the customer and internal stakeholders are aware of what is expected from them and when</div><div>• Manage strategic and key accounts and partners with Payday</div><div>• Engaging employers and persuading them to market Payday to their employees </div><div>•  Implement a system to document and communicate product feedback to relevant teams including Product, Engineering, Sales, Marketing, and Operations</div><div>• Build and maintain internal and external knowledge base for customers and internal teams to reference including self-service instructions</div><div>• Implement a process to prioritise and manage customer requests </div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">WHAT SKILLS YOU’LL NEED </b></div><div>• 3+ years experience in customer success / excellence; ideally in top tech companies</div><div>• Experience of hiring and building a customer success team</div><div>• Experience of developing trusted relationships with new clients</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">NICE TO HAVE</b></div><div>• Expertise in project managing launch and GTM plans with clients</div><div>• Expertise in launching employee outreach campaigns and educating employees in benefits or wellbeing</div><div>• STEM background</div><div>• Past experience in Tier-1 or tier-2 strategy consultancies or investment banks</div><div><br></div><div><b>Please note - you have to be based in one of the following countries: UK, Ireland, Spain, Portugal, France, Germany, Lithuania, Poland, Romania</b></div><div>#remote </div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 11pt">A little about us…</b>When Revolut was founded in 2015, we had a vision to build a sustainable, digital alternative to traditional big banks. Our mission now is to help our customers improve their financial health, empower them to have more control, and promote financial cohesion across the communities in which we operate. Launching into 2021 with 15 million Personal customers and over half a million Business customers only reinforced our belief in the vast need across the world for better financial services. </div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 11pt">What we’re looking for…</b>Revolut is being scaled up by people all around the world who share our vision. We’re looking for people who align with our five core values: we believe that we Get it Done because we Think Deeper and are strongly rooted in the Dream Team. We Never Settle hence why we always Deliver Wow. You want to join a community of forward-thinking people - we are here for you. We believe in empowering our Revoluters in their work, giving them autonomy and ownership of what they do. We want everyone at Revolut to own their story and their successes - working with us means you’re not just another cog in the machine.</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">THE BENEFITS</b></div><div>• Competitive salary</div><div>• All the latest tech you need</div><div>• Roll with a free Revolut Metal subscription</div><div>• Pension plan</div><div>• Private health insurance</div><div>• Start the day properly with fresh fruit and cereals</div><div>• Rest up with 29 days’ holiday per year</div><div><br></div><div><i style="font-size: 15px">By applying for the above role, you confirm that you have reviewed our&nbsp;</i><a href="https://www.revolut.com/legal/data-privacy-for-candidates" class="postings-link"><i style="font-size: 15px">Data Privacy Notice for Candidates</i></a><i style="font-size: 15px">.</i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EE2yoffomOc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/revolut/a429699d-7d03-4272-93fe-a2684e7062c2/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/215308/revolut.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[revolut@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bc6bf986-f138-47a8-a964-82b24f8843a0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Revolut]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Development Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKEx]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.okex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This is a fully remote role and the candidate does not have to be based in Singapore&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibility:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expand P2P merchants in key Asia countries and continuously increase the number of active merchants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the operation and management of Asia P2P core merchants, building their operation system and strategies, and improving their service experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Improve the trading activity of merchants and users and increase trading volume through refined operation and service&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Based on industry understanding and analysis, provide localised user feedback and competitive information, and put forward optimisation suggestions for product experience upgrading&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor degree or above&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in Crypto P2P merchant channels, able to independently develop new merchants or explore merchants from competitors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experienced in operation, able to build merchant trust and enhance merchant activity through service and daily management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional communication, presentation and cross-functional stakeholder management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/x9kSkBMcOuo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okex/jobs/4900070003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175406/okex.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bcbc2afc-a2fd-45d8-bba3-e7ce4b53b3d8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKEx]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
