<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Mobile Developer - Android]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celer Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.celer.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Mountain View, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>If you are into blockchain: combine passion and work.</p><p>Get your hands on a series of amazing and creative products.</p><p>Be a blockchain pioneer and quickly become one of the most influential technologists in the industry.</p><p>Join a diverse team and have fun.</p><p>Participate in a unique and prestigious experience, work with a bunch of top-notch engineers and PhDs.</p><p>Succeed together.</p><p>Job Description:</p><p>Team Celer Network is growing and we want you to join us! We’re looking for a talented and creative Android developer to join our mobile team. Every engineer works on exciting, meaningful projects, and defines our technical and product strategy. We move fast, have fun, and help each other out.</p><p>What You’ll Be Doing:</p><p>- With our lead mobile developer’s careful training, develop from scratch the Android mobile app, while being proactive on the features and improvements to our product</p><p>- Prototype and implement new features for our app.</p><p>- Participate in the overall maintenance of the app.</p><p>- Follow closely the app KPIs and report it to the rest of the team</p><p>You will be responsible to lead part of the Android development, and enable usability of blockchain technology and bring day-to-day users to the brave new blockchain world.</p><p>Requirements:</p><p>- App development experience on Android, with prior experience in Java or Kotlin</p><p>- Deep understanding of client/server technologies.</p><p>- Experience with scaling a mobile application to a large user base.</p><p>- Experience with API design and development.</p><p>- Experience with unit and functional testing, debugging, and performance tuning.</p><p>- Capable of owning projects and working closely with other engineers</p><p>- Excited to develop, release and run large-scale applications</p><p>- Reliable and professional</p><p>- Obsessed with code quality</p><p>This is a full-time or internship position in our Mountain View (CA, US) office.</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Pf5UJ5mNvdk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celer-network.breezy.hr/p/1dbddd72d11f-mobile-developer-android/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/331010/Celer.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celler@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[ea786b9c-9f8e-456b-ac42-76c62c195322]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celer Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Spring Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.springlabs.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Los Angeles, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About Spring Labs:</b></div><div>Spring Labs is redefining how data is exchanged for the new age of data sharing, security, and consumer privacy through decentralization. Our Spring Protocol Tech Stack, which includes the use of Blockchain and Cryptography, allows institutions to share information among themselves to verify identities and reduce fraud - all while protecting consumer data.</div><div><br></div><div>Working at Spring Labs is about being part of a collaborative team, comprised of some of the most talented people in the industry. You would be welcomed into a fun, inclusive environment where we care as much about our employees as we do about our product.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div>Product Managers, at Spring Labs, are responsible for leading the development of strategy and vision for our products, while defining and managing&nbsp; the product roadmap and facilitating in-depth discussions, with stakeholders,&nbsp; to drive product clarity.&nbsp;&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>This is a customer interfacing role, therefore it requires a high level of collaboration, creative problem solving, and the ability to effectively communicate and influence at all levels of an organization.</div><div><br></div><div><br></div><br/>What you'll do<br/><li>Be responsible&nbsp; for the&nbsp; end-to-end&nbsp; process, as well as the overall success and performance of the product</li><li>Manage prioritization, and trade offs, by balancing end user needs, product scope and time to market</li><li>Define, analyze and take action on metrics that measures product success</li><li>Create functional and technical specifications for the development teams</li><li>Maintain and groom product backlog</li><li>Perform validation, of product features, against product objectives and acceptance criteria</li><li>Manage product launches, both internally and externally</li><li>Actively work on product and process improvements that drive product and business value post launchLead, without authority, by building relationships within the organization</li><li>Leverage external networks to stay connected with technology and business trends. </li><li>Use knowledge to drive product innovation</li><br/>About you<br/><li>2+ years of experience in product management, in an agile environment</li><li>2+ years of experience in end to end product delivery</li><li>Bachelor’s degree in Engineering, Business or related field</li><li>Financial Services experience is a plus</li><li>Ability to to use data and metrics to build&nbsp; a comprehensive business caseAdvanced technical aptitude, with the ability to&nbsp; contribute in discussions, with Engineering, in regards to technology decisions</li><li>Successful track record in end to end product delivery</li><li>Experience in data products involving Big Data, ML/AI, complex data pipeline, and APIs</li><li>Demonstrated ability to manage and execute projects end to end, including project management, data gathering and modeling, problem solving, conflict resolution, communications and recommendations</li><li>Ability to conceptualize and effectively articulate to a variety of audiences</li><li>Strong, leadership presence, with exceptional presentation skills</li><li>Critical thinking, with balanced decision making</li><li>Experience in the Fintech industry is highly desirable</li><div><br></div><br/>Perks<br/><li>Casual Work Environment</li><li>Fully Stocked Kitchen </li><li>Free Gym</li><li>Weekly Office Events</li><li>Flexible PTO</li><li>Comprehensive Medical/Dental/Vision</li><li>FSA and DCSA</li><li>401(k)</li><div>Equal Opportunity Statement:</div><div>We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/springlabs/d1d57d52-2a07-4907-8fef-4bafeaca526e/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/736396/spring-labs.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[spring@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7a0f7116-a6a1-4890-aa85-36ecb2160387]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Spring Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Customer Success Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Immutable]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://immutable.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sydney, Australia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">A bit about us:</b></div><div><br></div><div>NFTs (unique digital assets stored on a blockchain) are exploding into a global asset class at a rapid speed. The biggest companies in the world in gaming, finance, digital art, and collectables are either actively building or strategising their entry into the market.</div><div><br></div><div>However, blockchain assets right now are highly illiquid: transactions take minutes or hours to confirm, Ethereum can process fewer than 5 asset trades per second for the whole world combined, and the UX is very challenging for mainstream users.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We have built Immutable X, which is the leading open-ecosystem scaling solution to trade and create NFTs on Ethereum. We’re a protocol: that means we enable other businesses to create and trade NFTs with no gas fees, completely carbon neutral, and in a truly decentralised manner.</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">About the role:</span></b></div><div><br></div><div>As a Senior Customer Success Manager, you will own end-to-end relationship accountability for key partners as they integrate, launch, and build an ongoing business on Immutable X. You will have the opportunity to shape what the customer success function looks like to our customers, and work closely with technical solutions engineers to ensure a seamless launch.</div><div><br></div><div>You will work closely with our product and engineering teams to facilitate success and feedback from customers and be a constant internal advocate for our customers, ensuring an exceptional experience throughout their integration into Immutable X.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>If you want to work in one of the most exciting success roles in the world, advising everyone from multi-billion dollar enterprise gaming companies to fintech, to NFT startups on how to maximise their business on Immutable X, this role is for you!</div><br/> You will have the opportunity to:<br/><li>Grow our customer’s businesses on Immutable X</li><li>Lead customers through our integration experience and help consult them on their blockchain/NFT designs to build the most successful business possible</li><li>Deeply understand our customers business and their needs, and help them maximise the success of their NFT business on Immutable X</li><li>Create a scalable playbook for customer success, working with our internal gaming and NFT content</li><li>Be a constant advocate for business customers of Immutable X</li><li>Directly manage relationships with Immutable X’s customers</li><li>Be accountable for customer retention and expansion, increasing the lifetime value of existing customers through client management, forecasting, and driving growth through a variety of creative means (partnerships, connecting to ecosystem partners and investments, technical advice and design, relationship management, etc)</li><br/>We would love you to have:<br/><li>4+ years in customer success within an API based SaaS company</li><li>Enterprise account experience ($1B + in value)</li><li>Previously held full relationship/customer lifetime value accountability</li><li>Exceptional communication skills, with a positive and practical approach</li><li>Proven ability to manage and execute business strategies and plans globally</li><li>A keen interest in NFTs!</li><br/> Some extra skills that would be awesome:<br/><li>B2B2C software company customer success experience</li><li>Crypto knowledge/background&nbsp;</li><br/>Some of the things we can offer you:<br/><li><b>Competitive Salary and Employee Stock Options: </b>Everyone in our team contributes to the success of our game-changing products, which is why we share all our wins company-wide. As we continue to succeed, stock options and a competitive salary mean you get to enjoy the upside!</li><li><b>Flexible working life and $750 WFH set up allowance</b>: Work-life balance is important. Whether you want to work from home or come to our new, shiny, Sydney office the choice is yours. To help you get comfortable working from home we’ll assist with a $750 contribution</li><li><b>Paid Parental Leave:</b> We celebrate our growing Immutable family! New parents will receive 12 weeks (primary) and 2 weeks (secondary) paid parental leave</li><li><b>Employee Assistance Program</b>: A 24/7 service that includes unlimited counselling for you and your family</li><li><b>EOY and Birthday Leave: </b>You can enjoy 2 additional paid annual leave days at EOY and a paid day off for your birthday</li><li><b>Internet and Phone Allowance:</b> $900 annually to put towards your mobile and internet expenses</li><li><b>Learning and Development:</b> We are dedicated to your professional development. You’ll get access to thousands of online learning courses via Go1, Udemy and Naspers. Immutable will also contribute between $1500-$2000 annually for you to invest in your continued education</li><li><b>Wellness Benefits:</b> Work-life balance and your wellbeing are important to us. We will contribute $1200 annually to put towards anything that contributes to your mental or physical wellbeing</li><li><b>Diversity and Inclusion</b>: We are committed to building a diverse and inclusive community for everyone. We’ve joined the Project F initiative aimed at removing the systemic barriers to achieving gender-balanced technology teams</li><li><b>Personal perks:</b> Perkbox benefits including premium access to Aura, Calm, an online fitness portal and discounts at major retailers</li><li><b>Ideal office location: </b>Penthouse office on-top of the Apple store on King Street, Sydney, CBD</li><li><b>Social events:</b> Fun and regular company events to relax and connect with teammates</li><div><b>Additional Information:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Immutable is committed to building and fostering an inclusive, diverse workplace. We believe in incorporating everyone’s perspectives and experiences as this has been a significant driver in our success so far.</div><div><br></div><div>For this reason, we strongly encourage candidates of all backgrounds to get in touch. Even if you don’t meet all the requirements of a job listing, do yourself (and us) a favour by still applying! It’s highly likely you’ll bring something to the workplace that we haven’t thought of yet, and we would love to hear from you.</div><div><br></div><div><b>We are a 2021 Circle Back Initiative Employer – we commit to respond to every applicant.</b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fT1YFjzry3k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/immutable/b8834f7f-5654-423b-bca5-444327f1acae/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/364981/Immutable.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[immutable@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f8630842-e278-44a1-80ce-2963904a6243]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Immutable]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sanctions Investigator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.robinhood.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Denver, CO OR Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Join a leading fintech company that’s democratizing finance for all.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Robinhood was founded on a simple idea: that our financial markets should be accessible to all. With customers at the heart of our decisions, Robinhood is lowering barriers, removing fees, and providing greater access to financial information. Together, we are building products and services that help create a financial system everyone can participate in.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Just as we focus on our customers, we also strive to create an inclusive environment where our employees can thrive and do impactful work. We are proud of the world class products and company culture we continue to build and have been recognized as:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A Great Place to Work&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A CNBC Disruptor 50 in 2019 and 2020&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A LinkedIn Top Startup in 2017, 2018, 2019 and 2020&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Robinhood is backed by leading investors that include DST Global, Index Ventures, NEA, Ribbit Capital, Thrive Capital, and Sequoia.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Check out life at Robinhood on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.themuse.com/profiles/robinhood&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; The Muse!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Financial Crimes Organization is looking to fill full time investigator roles to grow our team. The Sanctions Investigators will manage all aspects of investigation including the in-depth analysis of internal and external data sources.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your day-to-day will involve:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Review and analyze alerts of potential matches of Robinhood customers to denied parties&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage the investigative process from initial detection to disposition and reporting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Annotate findings providing proof of evidence and a final decision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Escalate any matches that you cannot resolve to Sanctions Investigation management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Escalate any true positive matches to the Sanctions Officer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Some things we consider critical for this role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s Degree&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years experience working in financial crimes investigations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;1+ years experience investigating cryptocurrency coin transactions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written and oral communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Keen attention to detail, organization, and process improvements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to search internet and social media resources to provide facts in the case&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Self-starter with ability to work independently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to effectively manage multiple priorities and adapt to a changing environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blocked Property Report filing experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CAMS/CGSS certifications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Chainalysis experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Colorado Residents Only: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In accordance with Colorado state law, Robinhood provides an estimate of the pay range associated with this role. In Colorado, the target salary for this position is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$69,000 - $81,000&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Pay is based on several factors, including but not limited to education, work experience and certifications.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for more growth-minded and collaborative people to be a part of our journey in democratizing finance for all. If you’re ready to give 100% in helping us achieve our mission—we’d love to have you apply even if you feel unsure about whether you meet every single requirement in this posting. At Robinhood, we&#39;re looking for people invigorated by our mission, values, and drive to change the world, not just those who simply check off all the boxes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Robinhood promotes diversity and provides equal opportunity for all applicants and employees. We are dedicated to building a company that represents a variety of backgrounds, perspectives, and skills. We believe that the more inclusive we are, the better our work (and work environment) will be for everyone. Additionally, Robinhood provides reasonable accommodations for candidates on request and respects applicants&#39; privacy rights. To review Robinhood&#39;s Privacy Policy please visit rbnhd.co/applicant-privacy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Robinhood&#39;s benefits include generous time off, 401(k) participation with employer match, comprehensive health coverage, a health savings account (HSA), wellness benefits, backup childcare and education stipends (all benefits are subject to applicable taxes and based on eligibility).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://robinhood.com/us/en/careers/openings/?gh_jid=3421105&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/291512/RH_SmallSizeIcon_RGB_Green_101019.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[robinhood@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[732b93c1-0bb0-4236-9a2c-e38e1d6cfe18]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Robinhood]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Financial Operations Controller (Oracle)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://blockchain.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Miami, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p class=&quot;p1&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BLOCKCHAIN.COM FINANCIAL OPERATIONS CONTROLLER (ORACLE)&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p3&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Miami, Remote (US)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p4&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain.com is the world&#39;s leading software platform for digital assets. Offering the largest production blockchain platform in the world, we share the passion to code, create, and ultimately build an open, accessible and fair financial future, one piece of software at a time.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p5&quot;&gt;We are growing our Finance team and implementing Oracle Cloud (Fusion) as a part of a large finance transformation. We are looking for an experienced Oracle ERP Systems Consultant to be the Financial Operations Controller (Oracle). This person will work closely with our Head of Consolidation &amp;amp; Financial Reporting and other team leaders, and will be responsible for leading and supporting the ERP implementation, including General Ledger and sub-ledgers in Oracle Cloud, as well as designing and managing overall operational functionality related to Blockchain.com’s Finance ERP system.&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Directly responsible for the build out an ongoing operation of the core finance ERP system globally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Manage ERP implementation project collaborating with third party vendors, ERP implementation consultants and internal stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Capture current state and future state environments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Works closely with business users to research, describe and design Business Requirements for system functionality for the global ERP solution.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s4&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Manage design of a Security Model for ERP System, data conversion model, data migration testing, System testing working with external implementation partner and internal stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Support the Integration testing with other core systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Create Training Program for ERP application&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Work with the finance and accounting leadership team and other key participants in the accounting process, ensuring that their input and feedback is incorporated into key initiatives.&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Develop new or improved methods of data mapping to accounting systems for the most efficient accounting and reporting of transactions.&lt;span class=&quot;Apple-converted-space&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Support the establishment of governance approaches for the projects to result in clear communication and issue resolution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Support the establishment of a risk-based approach to designing accounting processes to ensure adherence to audit compliance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Identify and implement process improvements to enhance the efficiency and accuracy of the monthly, quarterly and annual reporting process&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Partner with operations teams to ensure record from user experience through to financial statements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p5&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;The foremost quality for this position or any position at Blockchain.com is integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;CPA or Chartered Accountant preferred, but not required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;8-10 years of experience in project management with a strong background in IT and accounting/finance functions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Experience with Oracle implementations required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;Experience with distributed ledger technology preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p5&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPENSATION &amp;amp; PERKS:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;Unlimited vacation policy; work hard and take time when you need it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;Apple equipment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;Full-time salary based on experience and meaningful equity in an industry-leading company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li5&quot;&gt;US Benefits: Medical, Dental, Vision, 401K, Flexible Spending Account, Commuter, Life, Short Term &amp;amp; Long Term Disability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p class=&quot;p5&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;APPLICATION:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li7&quot;&gt;Resume/CV and LinkedIn profile.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li5&quot;&gt;Your favorite GIF.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain/jobs/3662561?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180745/blockchaininc.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchaininc@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5457bd3d-b464-4d43-bfd6-5c9d9e62930e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[People Operations Manager (m/f/d)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.parity.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Lisbon, Lisboa, Portugal]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Parity’s mission is to provide open source infrastructure to build a better future internet, aka Web 3.0. Blockchains are a key component in this future Web 3 stack and Parity is a leader in the blockchain space. It is the creator of two ambitious new blockchain projects, Polkadot and Substrate, that makes it easier to experiment and innovate with new ideas for sharding, encryption and governance. Parity is creating an open source creative commons that will enable people to create better institutions through a new wave of peer-2-peer technologies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Parity envisions the future of the Web as decentralised and secure, giving users more autonomy so that they can verify the systems that they are increasingly relying on, instead of trusting the current services’ providers. Parity is an international team composed of more than 180 members from over 30 countries, with of&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;fices in &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Germany, the UK and Portugal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We continue to undergo huge growth and are currently seeking a dedicated and well-organised, energetic individu&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;al to take initial ownership of People Operations for Parity’s new Lisbon office. Y&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ou are a real self-starter, have gathered hands-on experience with running People Operations autonomously and ideally have been involved in bootstrapping an office (or even company) in Portugal in the past. You successfully liaise with external partners and government institutions and have a solid working knowledge of Portuguese Labor Law. As Parity is a successful, rapidly growing company, we expect you to have an “all hands on deck” mentality, and you should expect your role to evolve during your time here.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We encourage you to also have a look at other open positions to get a feeling for the current needs at Parity.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RESPONSIBILITIES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate and execute the initial setup of People Operations processes and documents for Parity’s new Lisbon branch. This includes setting up payroll with an external provider or in-house, finalizing contract templates and tailoring Parity’s existing policies to local law and best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own core People Operations tasks and processes (e.g. contract creation, onboarding, offboarding) for all team members based in Portugal, in alignment with the People Operations team at Parity’s HQ&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Act as the main contact person for Parity employees based in Portugal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ongoing coordination with external consultants, government offices and service providers on topics like employment law, social security, and payroll&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support relocation of Parity team members to Portugal, including visa support, with the help of external consultants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support core People Operations areas for our other entities (UK &amp;amp; Germany) as needed, such as employee data management, absence tracking, employee requests, and reporting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Initiate and work on exciting new People Operations projects together with the People Operations team in Berlin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THIS JOB IS FOR YOU IF YOU…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have 2-4 years of experience in the field of People Operations / HR&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are a real self-starter who has hands-on experience with running People Operations autonomously&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have a solid working knowledge of Portuguese Labor Law&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are keen to work independently and proactively and are a great team player too&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Successfully liaise with external partners, such as consultants, payroll providers, and government institutions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Show great attention to detail&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Speak both English and Portuguese fluently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are comfortable working with Admin tools / HR systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Possess great communications skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NICE-TO-HAVES&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have been involved in bootstrapping an office (or even company) in Portugal in the past&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interest and/or experience in Blockchain technology&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BENEFITS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Because we value initiative and learning, we&#39;ve defined a generous personal development budget for each employee&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We offer a very remote-friendly company setup (even before Corona!)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will have the option to work from our newly established work space in Lisbon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bringing the team together is something we value a lot, so we used to regularly go on team retreats and are planning to do so again, once the international health regulations allow it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;To apply to this position, we ask you to answer a few questions in the application form. This helps us get a better feeling for your knowledge surrounding the role and expedite the hiring process on our end. For the most part there is no hard ‘right’ or ‘wrong’ to those questions, so please give explanations with your answers. Also please add a paragraph telling us a little bit about yourself in a cover letter.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We handle personal information in accordance with our privacy policy &lt;a href=&quot;https://workable.com/nr?l=https%3A%2F%2Fparitytech.io%2Flegal%2F&quot;&gt;https://paritytech.io/legal/&amp;nbsp;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LZd6z7HiTLw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/parity/jobs/4833701003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/378609/parity.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[parity@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6edef434-1785-497e-a19b-ce6d949ad50a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Backend Engineer, Crypto Transfers]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://blockfi.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi’s mission is to provide liquidity, transparency and efficiency to digital financial markets by creating products that meet the needs of consumers and corporations across the globe. We build bridges between traditional finance and digital markets that enable growth for all participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re a team of builders and strivers, proud to champion financial inclusivity and offer economic opportunities around the globe. We provide the same inclusivity to our team members. BlockFi is a place where diversity is celebrated, individuality is recognized, and every single team member is valued. We are changing the status quo to be the first financial company that people love, and we rely on our people to make it happen!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is looking for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Backend Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to join our Crypto Payments Engineering team!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Senior Engineer on the Crypto Payments Team, you’ll help build out the part of the BlockFi platform that handles all crypto transfers for retail clients. This includes integration with various crypto custodians as well as building fault-tolerant and scalable systems to handle all the deposits and withdrawals that occur on the BlockFi platform. We provide the glue between what the client sees within the BlockFi experience and what occurs on the blockchain. Navigating complex technical problems and providing insight, technical direction, and technical execution will be your day-to-day. The ability to build a solid working relationship with our custodian team and others including fraud, and compliance is a must.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build and maintain BlockFi’s crypto asset transfer platform services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with various teams including Custody, Security, Fraud, Risk, and Data Science.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide technical input and knowledge to the planning, design, and requirements process for new products and features.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Research complex topics around specific blockchain networks including consensus algorithms, economic models, and node/network topology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactively identify and prioritize improvements to the team’s processes, codebases and best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Expertise:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have at least 7 years of experience in software engineering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve designed, built, scaled and maintained production services, and know how to compose a service oriented architecture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Advanced proficiency in at least one language and open to learning new languages&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong communication (written and verbal) and interpersonal skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge and interest in the crypto asset ecosystem and underlying technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with the finance industry, payments, crypto, asset custody, trading and/or exchange systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bonus Points For:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with functional programming languages&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience driving initiatives at a broader level across an organization or company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We benefit from the great work our employees do each day. That is why we are committed to providing a variety of awesome benefits to help them live their best lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive salary &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because we value your experience and expertise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unlimited vacation / sick days &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because everyone deserves time for R&amp;amp;R&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employer&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;contribution towards health coverage &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(including vision &amp;amp; dental) because your physical health and well-being is important to us&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Various fringe benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; such as 401k, Parental Leave, FSA/HSA, and Employee Assistance Programs because health coverage is more than just choosing your yearly plan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible work environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; because we are a geographically dispersed team and we believe in balance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pet insurance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; because all of your beloved family members should have coverage too&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly lunch stipend &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because there is such a thing as a free lunch!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A close-knit team &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;of enthusiastic, collegial and driven people to work alongside in a highly meritocratic environment because teamwork makes the dreamwork&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi has experienced incredible growth since our launch in August 2017. Our client base has grown to more than 225,000 (and counting), and the company now boasts more than $15 billion in assets on our platform. We recently completed a Series D funding round placing the company&#39;s valuation at $3 billion, and our team now has more than 500 people worldwide. We have established ourselves as a crypto market leader, and as we expand our product suite and geographic footprint, we expect our addressable market to grow exponentially.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi&#39;s leadership team has decades of experience in the traditional financial services and banking world, and we take a conservative approach to regulation that will position us well for sustainable long-term growth and expansion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team is comprised of highly motivated professionals from diverse backgrounds. We are aiming to become the leading lender in crypto and are poised to redefine the global financial ecosystem for the better. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is one of the first companies to ever offer crypto-backed loans and the only company whose founding team has an institutional understanding of the debt capital markets and regulatory landscape in the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$100 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series A, B, and C funding led by Valar Ventures with participation from Susquehanna, Winklevoss Capital, Fidelity, Galaxy Digital, Akuna Capital, and Morgan Creek&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$350 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series D funding led by Bain Capital Ventures, partners of DST Global, Pomp Investments and Tiger Global&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are moving quickly and have already deployed substantial capital into the space, proving our ability to execute and capture customer demand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For information about how we&amp;nbsp;collect, use, or otherwise handle your Personal Information, please see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a class=&quot;c-link&quot; href=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-stringify-link=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; data-sk=&quot;tooltip_parent&quot;&gt;Privacy&amp;nbsp;Policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/o92zit2jRO0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockfi/jobs/5726275002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/553492/blockfi-logo-512x512.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockfi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7eefa976-25ba-4497-9343-24e88aecb41f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Assistant/Sales Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CertiK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://certik.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 12pt">Why Us?</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">CertiK is the leading blockchain security company. Our clients include leading projects such as Aave, Polygon, Binance Smart Chain, Terra, Yearn, and Chiliz. We just raised over $60 million in Series B and B+ funding rounds in 2021. Our investors include top VCs like Tiger Global, Coatue Management, Shunwei Capital, and Hillhouse Capital as well as industry leaders like Coinbase Ventures and Binance.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 12pt">About Team/Role:&nbsp;</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">CertiK is experiencing exponential growth. Our BD team needs an exceptional Assistant/Sales Specialist to help us to scale. You will support the Business Development team for day-to-day operations, assist in implementing and initiating systems/tools that will drive sales efficiency. You will have plenty of opportunities to assist in other ad hoc projects and work collaboratively with cross-functional stakeholders.</span></div><br/>About you (responsibilities):<br/><li>Assist our BD teams with daily data input for new sales inquiries, sales status, ongoing sales cases, and case follow-up</li><li>Analyze sales trends, business opportunities, and market trend&nbsp;</li><li>Support data-driven business decisions by tracking and providing ongoing reporting and analysis support to our BD team and other cross-functional stakeholders</li><li>Ad hoc projects assigned by hiring manager to help operation efficiency and market expending</li><br/>Job Requirements<br/><li>Bachelor's degree in Marketing and Business Administration is a plus</li><li>Minimum 1 year of experience in BDR/SDR experience with enterprise SaaS/Blockchain</li><li>Strong analytical skills&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Strong customer service, detail-oriented, well organized, and thrive to work under pressure and in different time zones</li><li>Effective communication skills</li><li>Highly collaborative, an active listener, and strong interpersonal skills</li><li>Excellent written and verbal communication skills in English, bilingual in Chinese/Mandarin is a must</li><br/>Bonus Points<br/><li>Financial, blockchain, cybersecurity, or crypto industry experience</li><li>Passionate about Cryptocurrency/Defi/Blockchain is a plus</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/aEn2UaqeHho" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/certik/4a021ca0-6fe4-4049-8c41-76712b2d363f/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/452745/CertiK-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[certik@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f6c22067-35b7-4b78-a01c-cb1e9232298a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CertiK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Security DevOps Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>Crypto.com was founded in 2016, Crypto.com today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest growing crypto app, along with the Crypto.com Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the Crypto.com Exchange and Crypto.com DeFi Wallet. Recently launched, Crypto.com NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment and sports.</p><p>Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, CCSS Level 3, ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks.</p><p>With over 3000 people in offices across the Americas, Europe and Asia, Crypto.com is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a href="https://crypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com</a></p><p><br></p><p><strong>Responsibilities</strong></p><ul> <li>Maintain and support blockchain infrastructure</li> <li>Review and propose configuration of blockchain software and network setup of nodes running the blockchain software</li> <li>Develop deep understanding of the Blockchain technology (specifically public Blockchain) </li> <li>Develop and share with others on security threats of various blockchain technology</li> <li>Define and maintain team continuous devops lifecycle and automation</li> <li>Design and maintain cloud computing workload, manage cloud security posture</li> <li> Software engineers or system administrators with an interest in blockchain/automation/infrastructure are welcomed to apply.</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>Degree in Computer Science or Engineering or similar discipline</li> <li>3 - 5 years working experiences in devops or system administration or related area, applicants with less experience will be considered for a Junior position</li> <li>Experience in deploying in various cloud (Azure, Google, Amazon)</li> <li>Experience in building, deploying and maintaining monitoring tools (Grafana, Prometheus, etc)</li> <li>Experience in deploying and maintaining container infrastructures (Kubernetes, docker-compose, etc)</li> <li>Experience in building, deploying and maintaining logging tools (Fluentd, ElasticSearch, Kibana, etc)</li> <li>Experience in developing and deploying infrastructure as code (Kubernetes, Terraform, Docker, Ansible, etc)</li> <li>Understand basic blockchain (a plus if has experience in deploying blockchain)</li> <li>Good understanding of traditional security ops areas of expertise: Linux, Networking, Firewall, IDS/IPS</li> <li>Able to troubleshoot and debug issues, and demonstrate a methodical approach to root cause analysis</li> <li>A team player</li> <li>Eager for constant learning from both success and failure, remaining open to change and continuous improvement</li> <li>Enthusiastic about the future of blockchain</li> <li>Curious and comfortable with ambiguity</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of FinTech and distributed ledger technology.</li> <li>Significant and meaningful responsibilities from Day 1. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment, part of an international team</li> <li>You will drive multiple global projects alongside a talented team of professionals</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/D20FA759CF/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[careers@crypto.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Academy Operations Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Consensys]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.consensys.net]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;ConsenSys is the leading Ethereum software company. We enable developers, enterprises, and people worldwide to build next-generation applications, launch modern financial infrastructure, and access the decentralized web. Our product suite, composed of Infura, Quorum, Codefi, MetaMask, and Diligence, serves millions of users, supports billions of blockchain-based queries for our clients, and has handled billions of dollars in digital assets. Ethereum is the largest programmable blockchain in the world, leading in business adoption, developer community, and DeFi activity. On this trusted, open source foundation, we are building the digital economy of tomorrow. To explore our products and solutions, visit &lt;a href=&quot;http://consensys.net/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As Academy Operations Lead you will:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Are you someone who finds joy in a well put together spreadsheet? Do you take pride in taking care of the small details? Is building and maintaining a strong, well-functioning team exciting to you? Then this is the position for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Academy runs the best-in-class blockchain education experience. We currently run Bootcamps, produce content, run webinars and assist with enterprise trainings. A Lead Operations person will be able to handle the communications and logistics underpinning Academy’s educational offerings.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Main responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own incoming Academy communications. Being able to sort between the different demands of external requests from customers and students as well as internal requests from teams requiring educational content or exposure to developers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing communications from the Academy email account&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Streamlining operational processes for the Academy team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assisting and coordinating on research efforts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinating meetings/project management with other departments for cross functional projects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing ConsenSys Academy events and conferences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Providing support on special projects and initiatives&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Characteristics:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Past Experience dealing with a wide variety of operational tasks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working Proficiency with professional email communications, manipulation of basic data via spreadsheets&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rigorous Prioritizer Demand will always outstrip capacity in this role, should be able to clearly prioritize and manage tasks with competing importance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Structured Problem Solver who can bring process and prioritization to the table&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analytical Can break down problems to the core issue and come to conclusions on how to proceed from the problem point&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow-Through Being able to commit to good estimations around time and ability on tasks. Can also signal as soon as things look like they will take longer than expected.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Communications Ace&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strategic thinker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Hubspot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in teaching institutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in a start-up environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join ConsenSys?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Here are some of the perks of being part of a unique organization like ConsenSys&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One of the most recognized tech companies in the blockchain ecosystem globally&lt;/strong&gt;. A work experience at ConsenSys is a tremendous reference for your future career. ConsenSys alumni have moved on to become tech entrepreneurs, CEOs, and team leads at tech companies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The forefront of a revolution&lt;/strong&gt;. We fundamentally believe blockchain is a next generation of technology that can lay the foundation for a more just and equitable society. You can be a part of building the digital economy of tomorrow and radically transforming our society for the better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A dynamic startup environment with deep roots&lt;/strong&gt;. We are one of the earliest blockchain companies and a leader in the space.&amp;nbsp; You’ll join a network of entrepreneurs and technologists that reaches the edge of our ecosystem.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deep technical challenges&lt;/strong&gt;. Blockchain technology is just over 10 years old. Ethereum itself is still a toddler. There is much to be done before these platforms can scale to the order of millions or billions of users. We are building the tools, infrastructure and applications l that are pushing the technology forward.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous learning and improvements&lt;/strong&gt;. You’ll be constantly exposed to new concepts, ideas and frameworks from your peers and as you work on different projects — challenging you to stay at the top of your game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;ConsenSys is an equal opportunity employer. We encourage people from all backgrounds to apply. We are committed to ensuring that our technology is made available and accessible to everyone. All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, national origin, ancestry, sex, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age, genetic information, religion, disability, medical condition, pregnancy, marital status, family status, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;ConsenSys is aware of fraudulent recruitment practices and we encourage all applicants to review our best practices to protect yourself which can be found&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consensys.net/careers/best-practices-to-avoid-recruitment-fraud/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/PTVt2eg0FTA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://consensys.net/open-roles/gh_jid?gh_jid=3648456&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/341584/consensys.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[consensys@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[1036a9a0-3cf5-4e0b-bfa9-5c096c0d3a02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Consensys]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[IT Vendor Management Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[MoonPay]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.moonpay.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote (US)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MoonPay&lt;/strong&gt; builds payments infrastructure for cryptocurrencies. Our on- and off-ramp suite of products provides a seamless experience for converting between fiat and crypto using all major payment methods in over 160 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;a class=&quot;c-link&quot; href=&quot;https://www.moonpay.com/blog/the-moonpay-mission&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-sk=&quot;tooltip_parent&quot;&gt;Our mission&lt;/a&gt; is to make cryptocurrencies accessible to over a billion people by 2030! 🚀 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are trusted by 250+ leading wallets, websites, and applications. Some of the biggest crypto brands in the world, including &lt;a class=&quot;c-link&quot; href=&quot;http://bitcoin.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-sk=&quot;tooltip_parent&quot;&gt;Bitcoin.com&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dapperlabs.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Dapper Labs&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://opensea.io/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;OpenSea&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.argent.xyz/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Argent&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://zengo.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;ZenGo&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://trustwallet.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Trust Wallet&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.spot-bitcoin.com/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Spot&lt;/a&gt;, rely on our technology. Through these partnerships alone, our products are used by over 5 million users worldwide. 🌎 &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;One of the great things about working at MoonPay is that we are remote first. Our global team spans 25+ countries, and we pride ourselves on having a connected and inclusive culture that empowers people to do their best work. We give our team autonomy to move fast, innovate and take responsibility. Join us in our mission to build a better financial world!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are very proud of our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.moonpay.com/blog/moonpay-values&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;values&lt;/a&gt; and expect all those who join us to help us proactively drive and improve our culture, aligned to these values.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;B - Be Humble&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;L - Lead with Empathy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;O - Own It&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;C - Communicate Clearly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;K - Kaizen &lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Information Technology (IT) Team ❤️&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Principal IT Systems Engineer, you’ll join our Information Technology (IT) team to provide quality technology solutions for MoonPay which are state of the art and secure, but always ensure that user experience is the priority.&amp;nbsp; This role will report directly to the Director of Information Technology.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ideal candidate is a highly motivated, inquisitive individual with a background in SaaS solutions, who is extremely customer focused and enjoys solving problems. We are currently looking for candidates in the US / UK / EMEA / APAC regions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll do 👀&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build a quality and comprehensive technology infrastructure.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish and maintain effective operational processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deliver quality, prompt, cost effective and reliable technology services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create best in class IT technology solutions which will enable MoonPay to deliver on its vision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Always put the end user first!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You should apply if ✅&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A passion for harnessing the power of digital currency and blockchain technology and services built on top of it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years experience at a financial institution, ideally in FinTech.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;8+ years of experience with SaaS or Technology Solutions within Financial institution a positive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years of experience in IT Architecture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with vendor management and contract negotiations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to take lead on cross functional teams, to assess and develop full end to end architecture for SaaS solutions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Act as Technical advisor to other IT teams to assess full technology stack to avoid technical debt from incomplete solutions design.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to work well independently or as part of a team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Customer oriented in your approach.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An innovative and creative mind looking to suggest new solutions to old problems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong organizational and analytical skills with great attention to detail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills in English. Additional languages will be considered an asset.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;First-rate decision making skills, bias for action and sound judgement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to maintain a strong operational focus with the capacity to manage time sensitive workflows across competing priorities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;B.A./B.S. degree; quantitative or technical degree a plus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with TRM and/or Chainalysis is a plus.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbr.org/2014/08/why-women-dont-apply-for-jobs-unless-theyre-100-qualified&quot;&gt;Research&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;has shown that women are less likely than men to apply for this role if they do not have solid experience in 100% of these areas. Please know that this list is indicative and that we would still love to hear from you even if you feel you only are a 75% match. Skills can be learnt, diversity cannot.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;We promote a diverse and inclusive culture at MoonPay.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Logistics 🛠&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unfortunately, we are unable to offer visas of any kind at this time!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our interview process takes place on Zoom and tends to consist of the following stages:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Hiring Manager Screen (20-30 minutes)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Technology screen (20-30 minutes)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Culture Screen (20-30 minutes)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Final interview (20-30 minutes)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please let us know if you require any accommodations for the interview process, and we’ll do our best to provide assistance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits 💰&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Stock options 📈&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Unlimited holidays 🏝&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Home office equipment allowance of $600 USD (or local equivalent) 🪑&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working in a disruptive and fast-growing industry where the possibilities are endless 🚀&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully remote: your life, your way of working 🌎&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Freedom, autonomy and responsibility 💪&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Annual company retreat 🧘‍♀️&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/moonpay/jobs/4848408003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/622286/MoonPay-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[moonpay@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[2f99944a-a6fb-4f79-a155-1bfc3312339e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[MoonPay]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer Intern - US]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[internship]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[f2pool & stakefish]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://stake.fish/en/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Palo Alto, California, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>As our intern, you will have the opportunity to learn about a wide range of technologies at stake.fish, including blockchain protocols, smart contracts, node.js based backend systems, and react/js based frontend apps. You will work closely with a group of talented product managers, UX designers, and other backend/frontend engineers. Let us know your interest and passion, and we may even be able to tailor-make an internship specific to you!<br></p><h3><br></h3><h3>What will you do?</h3><p>Some possible responsibilities depending on our passion and skill set<br></p><ul> <li>Build new backend services using node.js and Typescript</li> <li>Develop smart contracts and services that interact with the smart contracts</li> <li>Build data ETL pipelines using Python</li> <li>Build frontend apps that are beautiful, simple, and delightful</li> </ul><h3></h3><h3><br></h3><h3>What excites us about you?</h3><ul> <li>You are currently in a reputable Bachelors or Masters program in the US</li> <li>You are passionate about blockchain technology and a decentralized future, and you are familiar with the technologies behind blockchains.</li> <li>You are familiar with one of the following: solidity/smart contracts, node.js, or React</li> <li>Able to work independently and set up an efficient development environment </li> </ul><h3><br></h3><h3>What will be great to have?</h3><ul> <li>You are contributing to the open-source community</li> <li>You have previous internship experiences</li> <li>You have experience with smart contracts / solidity (this is a plus but not required, and we will be happy to bring you up to speed on the job)</li> </ul><h3><br></h3><h3>Why are we awesome you ask?</h3><p>We are truly at the forefront of the crypto ecosystem as maintainers of the infrastructure layer of blockchain networks! We practice the crypto team mentality by assembling a truly global and diverse team (with even pseudo anonymous team members). We collectively represent more than 12 different countries and are united in a single mission: building out the future of decentralization. Crypto is here to stay, having introduced novel ideas such as DeFi, NFTs and DAOs. At the core of all this are teams like us working relentlessly to build the necessary tools and applications that help run and secure blockchains. Here are some other reasons why you should join us:</p> <ul> <li>We are one of the top staking service providers with over $3B of assets staked across our validators. E.g. Our staking market share for Cosmos rivals that of Binance and Coinbase.</li> <li>Curious about how protocols like Solana and Cosmos have exploded into the juggernauts they are today? We have front row seats to observe and learn how protocols evolve, going from idea to adoption. You will get opportunities to learn about and work very closely with a wide range of blockchain networks.</li> <li>We are crypto nerds at heart. Some people are power DeFi users and some others are intense NFT collectors. You can learn and debate everything on crypto with our teammates.</li> <li>We have some people who have been around this space for ages. They’ll casually drop a few interesting history lessons along the way. Did you know Bitcoin was actually double spent at one point in time?</li> <li>We are a very well capitalized and already profitable startup.</li> </ul> <p>We are looking for fun, curious, and committed individuals to swim with us!</p><p>Requirements</p><p>Benefits</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/f2pool-stakefish/j/0ADB9C0A00/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/732239/f2pool_stakefish.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[f2pool@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[33981a68-3968-406e-a0b6-0c8956f5810a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[f2pool & stakefish]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[International Benefits Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt"><b>About the role&nbsp;</b></span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">We are growing rapidly and expanding our footprint into new markets globally. To support our expansion we are building a world class HR and People Operations function that will enable us to both recruit and retain top talent by offering best in class Benefits that are relevant to individual territories.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">You will join a global benefit team working together to identify and implement scalable Benefits solutions for our 18+ countries and ensure we keep pace with our expansion plans and employee needs in line with our&nbsp; mission, values and culture.</span></div><br/>What you will do:<br/><li>Provide counsel to key internal stakeholders on benefits guidelines and the nuances of regions, territories and specific countries as well as build external relationships with key benefits partners</li><li>Support the Director of Global Benefits by executing all aspects of the annual benefits management process including health and welfare, retirement (pension) and ancillary benefits for the international region (all countries except for US)</li><li>Work with the Global Benefits and People Operation team to support the development, implementation and administration of benefits programs for the international region (all countries except US) including health and welfare, retirement, leave of absence,&nbsp; and wellness programs</li><li>Partner with the Workday team to improve administration efficiency through automation and employee self-service</li><li>Conduct regular analysis to monitor the regulatory compliance and on-going effectiveness of benefits programs to ensure external competitiveness and internal equity are maintained. Shares recommendations regarding changes to existing programs with Director of Global Benefits</li><li>Regularly monitors local works council, labor union, and acquired rights requirements to ensure company adherence to local laws</li><li>Provide assistance on one-off benefits projects</li><br/>What we're looking for:<br/><li>BS/BA, preferably in a business field</li><li>Minimum of 8 +&nbsp; years benefits experience. High-Tech experience preferred</li><li>Experience with Workday HRIS</li><li>Excellent prioritization and organization skills</li><li>Strong attention to detail</li><li>Knowledge of international (local country) laws pertaining to benefits; ability to find answers where there is a lack of knowledge</li><li>Interpersonal/Influencing/Negotiating skills</li><li>Independent, self-managed, and self-starter personality</li><li>Be able to provide solutions and clarity in times of ambiguity</li><div><span style="font-size: 15px">Location Tagging: #EU #International</span></div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/29e99958-8ab8-4ba7-a4e3-e97ce2a2a7af/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase has built the world&#39;s leading compliant cryptocurrency platform serving over 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries. With multiple successful products, and our vocal advocacy for blockchain technology, we have played a major part in mainstream awareness and adoption of cryptocurrency. We are proud to offer an entire suite of products that are helping build the cryptoeconomy and increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for signals that a candidate will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, disrupt ourselves, and expect sustained high performance because we play as a championship team. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people with the desire and capacity to build and share expertise in the frontier technologies of crypto and blockchain, in whatever way is most relevant to their role.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;6rt44-0-0&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;1npem-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;1npem-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;1npem-0-0&quot;&gt;Coinbase Product Managers play a critical role in building the next generation of crypto products. You will work &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span id=&quot;1npem-1-0&quot; class=&quot;suggestion-span&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;1npem-1-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;1npem-1-0&quot;&gt;closely&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;1npem-2-0&quot;&gt; with engineering, design and cross-functional teams to build products and new experiences. You’ll play a pivotal role in shaping the future of cryptocurrency and help us achieve our mission of creating an open financial system for the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;4iede-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;4iede-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;4iede-0-0&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;6vv09-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;6vv09-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll be doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-ul&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;337hi-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-reset public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;337hi-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;337hi-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;337hi-0-0&quot;&gt;Own product development from conception to launch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;1dehm-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;1dehm-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;1dehm-0-0&quot;&gt;Collaborate cross-&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span id=&quot;1dehm-1-0&quot; class=&quot;suggestion-span&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;1dehm-1-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;1dehm-1-0&quot;&gt;functionally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;1dehm-2-0&quot;&gt; with engineering, design and cross-functional teams to develop and steer product roadmap&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;fp3c7-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;fp3c7-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;fp3c7-0-0&quot;&gt;Define and analyze metrics to guide product development &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;e68i6-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;e68i6-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;e68i6-0-0&quot;&gt;Align teams on a shared vision and steer execution on that vision.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;8t66-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;8t66-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;8t66-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we look for in you:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-ul&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;8k6a2-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-reset public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;8k6a2-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;8k6a2-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;8k6a2-0-0&quot;&gt;5+ years of product management experience &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;e5upc-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;e5upc-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;e5upc-0-0&quot;&gt;Exceptional interpersonal communication, relationship management and organizational skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;fti5j-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;fti5j-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;fti5j-0-0&quot;&gt;Deep analytical, prioritization and problem solving skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;889bl-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;889bl-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;889bl-0-0&quot;&gt;Previous experience working in software product management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;3u66a-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;3u66a-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;3u66a-0-0&quot;&gt;Demonstrated passion for cryptocurrency, financial markets, and the Coinbase mission&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-unorderedListItem public-DraftStyleDefault-depth0 public-DraftStyleDefault-listLTR&quot; data-block=&quot;true&quot; data-editor=&quot;dukh8&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;euo8b-0-0&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;public-DraftStyleDefault-block public-DraftStyleDefault-ltr&quot; data-offset-key=&quot;euo8b-0-0&quot;&gt;&lt;span data-offset-key=&quot;euo8b-0-0&quot;&gt;An entrepreneurial mindset with the ability to succeed in a fast-paced environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations@ coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Please contact accommodations@ coinbase.com for additional information or to request accommodations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3008134?gh_jid=3008134&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Executive Assistant to CTO]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Tampa]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Executive Assistant to CTO</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">This position will be responsible for supporting CTO with various tasks including calendar management, meeting coordination, and drafting correspondence. The Executive Assistant will also be responsible for traditional administrative support and general office manager support at the Tampa, Florida office. This is a fantastic opportunity for an experienced and proactive Executive Assistant to join a company with an industry-leading Board of Directors, Management Team, and who is willing to roll up his/her sleeves with significant potential to transform the industry. The ideal Executive Assistant has a high level of curiosity, intelligence, and ability to work independently and provide outstanding support to the executive team for a leading cryptocurrency company. Responsible for traditional administrative support while tackling complex projects in a fast paced high-growth company.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Actively manage calendars to ensure no conflicts; proactively address issues with little direction</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Assist the CTO and Technology leadership team in building out an operating model on how they operate as a leadership team and a framework for highly functioning effective team management through proactive management of the agendas, internal/external events.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Preparing for and attending discussions and decisions, and ensuring accountability among the executives for follow-up action items.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Setting up meetings and conference calls, often involving internal and/or external parties, encompassing the use of equipment technologies.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Coordinate and book executive travel arrangements, meetings, and events.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Office management responsibilities will be part of the job: ordering and keeping track of office supplies, managing office vendors, and liaising with property management teams at the local Tampa, FL office.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Must be able to prioritize and manage multiple projects simultaneously</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Handle confidential material with appropriate discretion</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Provide administrative backup coverage as designated in the Administrative Team. (e.g. during vacations, sick time)</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">SKILLS AND QUALIFICATIONS:</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Prior experience working with and supporting an executive team on corporate matters, preferably exceeding 3 years.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Ability to build strong relationships with co-workers of various backgrounds and expertise in the Company and to also in still the Company’s culture and values.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">A bachelor's degree is strongly preferred.  </span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Demonstrated experience with project management that is cross-functional in nature.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">High integrity and business ethics.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Experience in planning study kick-off meetings, ad boards, and off-sites</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Ability to function at a high level in a team setting whether leading the group or acting as an individual contributor</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Advanced proficiency in relevant office-based software and data applications, including Google Suite, Slack, MS Office</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">PREFERRED ATTRIBUTES:</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">A high level of curiosity, intelligence, ability to work independently, a “can do” attitude, and the ability to work cross-functionally. Strong initiative and follow-through are essential for this job.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Excellent verbal and written communication and skills.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Analytical thinking with problem-solving skills and the ability to adapt to changing priorities and deadlines.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">A commitment to excellence.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">Self-motivated and enthusiastic; fast learner who can identify the core project challenges and expeditiously change course as required in a fast-paced organization.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Arial;">High emotional intelligence and the ability to represent the Company when interacting with Company executives, Board members, staff, and external third parties (collaborators, investors, regulators, etc.) as circumstances may require.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xW6QWaNfysw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=469&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/731816/celsius_network.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celsius@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5fa72b05-b42d-48a9-806e-c3fdccb06776]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Administrative / Office Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Owner - Crypto Wallets]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bittrex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Bellevue, WA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Bittrex, a Seattle-based cryptocurrency exchange,&amp;nbsp;is hiring a Product Owner over crypto wallets. Founded by three cybersecurity engineers in 2014,&amp;nbsp;we build our products with security first, offering&amp;nbsp;access to over 100 cryptocurrencies in the United States along with lightning-fast trade execution and dependable digital wallets.&amp;nbsp;We believe in the potential of blockchain and its ability to provide game-changing solutions, and we’re looking for talented and passionate individuals to join our exceptional team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a Product Owner with strong technical skills that understands and has experience with 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; party API integrations. As a Product Owner you will be working alongside talented developers, designers, and our Crypto Wallets Product Manager to expand blockchain project integrations (Coins &amp;amp; Tokens) into our Bittrex crypto wallet infrastructure. Crypto Wallets are a critical and highly impactful area to our organization and can positively impact both our internal teams and our external customer experience. You will be the voice of the customer, and imperative in eliminating customer pain points. You will be seen as a subject matter expert who can answer engineering team questions and communicate effectively with support teams. This role is an ideal opportunity for someone who is excited to get their hands dirty, is detail oriented and skilled at executing 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; party integrations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be the bridge between product and development teams - Translate the understanding of the product manager’s vision and what each product area is designed to do for its users.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translate the Product Managers’ strategies and business requirements into well-defined product requirements including features, user stories, and acceptance test criteria.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to explain the “how” and “why” behind all the user stories and other tasks.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand the market and customer needs to be useful in translating the strategic plan into the right execution steps.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run the team daily standup.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build, edit, maintain the team backlog by working closely with PM, Dev, and support teams to ensure technology needs and business needs are adequately represented in priority order.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Establish and own the Product backlog grooming meetings.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Guide the engineering team in establishing normalized estimation practices and work towards an accurate understanding of team capacity and velocity so that delivery estimates are practical.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sprint Planning- Coordinate dependencies with other Product Owners. Communicate story level detail and priorities to the team and ensure the team aligns and agrees on a final sprint plan. Ensure team focus is divided adequately between strategic items, maintenance/bugs, and discretionary needs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Answer dev questions about user stories or tasks throughout the sprint.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Accept &amp;amp; Validate Stories- work with team to agree on definition of done. Validate stories to ensure they meet acceptance criteria.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Backlog Priority- Work outside the normal scrum meetings with the business stakeholders/ Product Mangers to continually review and update the product backlog priority&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate the team end of sprint demos&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coordinate the team sprint retrospective&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be part of the first line of defense for Production Support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Make decisions- the product owner role is a decision-making role. You will be responsible and accountable for the product and making decisions daily. These decisions range from what items to include in the product backlog, how to triage production issues, how to prioritize requests, and how to best communicate the same to the engineering and support teams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience as a Product Owner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3+ years of experience in software development planning, resource management, and product delivery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent at breaking down business requirements into user stories and acceptance criteria.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organized and thorough in following best practices for stand ups and sprint planning.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating with third party platforms&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled at communicating with business support teams and development teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Well versed in risk analysis and making complex business/risk trade-off recommendations and decisions.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Agile SDLC and Change Management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to thrive in a fast-paced startup environment where you sometimes need to wear multiple hats and step outside your box of responsibilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written, verbal, and storytelling communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Able to collect and analyze information, solve complex problems rationally, and make decisions on time for enhanced productivity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience as a Product Owner over API integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with cryptocurrencies, blockchain technology, and digital assets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with Azure Dev Ops for user story and content management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with financial technology, investment banking, trading, or similar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience integrating 3&lt;sup&gt;rd&lt;/sup&gt; party vendors and managing the lifecycle of API products.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of REST APIs, Web Sockets, Asp.net, Javascript and/or Azure.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bittrex is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to age, ancestry, color, family or medical care leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran status, race, religion, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by applicable laws, regulations, and ordinances.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/wPebbTGCUCQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bittrex/jobs/5751881002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175858/bittrex.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bittrex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[80244eca-7fc4-4796-8431-8d6255bccb6c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bittrex]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of Advertising]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[directorvp]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Republic]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://republic.co]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We are looking for a Director of Advertising to join our team! You will be responsible for overseeing the creation, execution &amp; optimization of digital marketing campaigns in Facebook ads manager, Google Ads manager, and many other social media platforms. Having in-depth experience with email marketing is required as well. Knowledge of Google Analytics and data analysis is a prerequisite for this job.&nbsp;</div><br/>What you'll do:<br/><li>Oversee the creation, execution &amp; optimization of multiple digital marketing campaigns across multiple digital platforms such as Facebook ads manager &amp; Klavyio</li><li>Develop detailed paid advertising strategies across lead generation, traffic &amp; website conversion ad campaigns</li><li>Coordinate the development of digital marketing campaigns with our internal team (graphics, copywriting, analytics, and more)</li><li>Review and manage marketing budgets per client per campaign. Ensure that marketing budgets are met with each account</li><li>Monitor and report to the client &amp; internal team weekly on the progress of all digital marketing campaigns</li><li>Work as our Director of Advertising to create strategies that increase Return on Ad Spend (ROAS) as we are a growth marketing agency that spends a lot of money on Facebook, Google, Instagram, TikTok, LinkedIn and programmatic</li><br/>What we're looking for:<br/><li>2-3 years of previous experience in digital marketing running paid ad campaigns and optimizing campaigns based on incoming data</li><li>Experience in a managerial role running internal teams and communicating professionally with clients</li><li>Strong project management skills to ensure the timely launch &amp; completion of multiple digital marketing campaigns that are being run at the same time</li><li>Strong leadership qualities to work in a fast paced environment with multiple team members and multiple clients across multiple time zones</li><li>(Must have) Knowledge of Google Drive </li><li>(Must have) Ability to learn in a fast paced environment </li><li>(Must have) Knowledge of a task management tool such as Asana or Trello</li><li>Deadline and detail-oriented as we are managing A LOT of work. We use Asana, Slack, Google Drive &amp; Dropbox to stay organized!</li><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Qy1lzYTV6Uc" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/republic/1400c492-fef2-4987-9195-108058a169e1/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/211719/Republic.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[republic@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b024f433-5745-442c-98f6-a3b65ac4a9b0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Republic]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Backend Developer (Go, Solidity)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitfury.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;div id=&quot;header&quot;&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at Bitfury:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;content&quot; class=&quot;&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is a leading emerging technologies company. &amp;nbsp;At Bitfury, you can build the solutions of the future, with the most significant technologies of the millennium, in a modern and flexible workplace. We work a bit faster, and a bit smarter, so we can make the world a bit better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits of Working at Bitfury:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;International Experiences &amp;amp; Global Impacts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is an international company with 200+ team members in more than 16 countries. No matter your assignment, your work will support global technology initiatives and best-in-class security operations in North America, Asia and Europe, as well as help us fulfil our mission to make the world more trusted and secure.&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Building the Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe big data, artificial intelligence, blockchain technology, tokenized economies and cryptocurrencies are the future of our digital, global economy. Bitfury is building this future through our products that offer digitised security, asset management, government services and more. We consider ourselves first and foremost a technology company. We are a diversified organisation, with operations across multiple facets of the AI, blockchain, and digital currency sectors. If you are passionate about emerging technologies, you can build your future at Bitfury.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accelerate Your Career&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury is growing fast and looking for the next generation of leaders and entrepreneurs to help us. At Bitfury, you will be expected to create the future – not just execute it. If you are a self-starter, driven and collaborative team member, you can create a dynamic future for yourself and your career at Bitfury.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Modern Workplace with Intelligent Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitfury lets you work in the way you need to work to make your work faster, smarter and better. We will give you the resources you need to succeed – competitive pay and benefits, educational support, intellectual challenges, professional advancement, personal accommodations including remote work, and more. We pride ourselves on being less bureaucratic and a lot more impactful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start-up Culture with Established Results&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Working with the world’s leading experts and engineers, you will have the opportunity at Bitfury to pursue results that will power your success as well as lead to the adoption of game-changing technologies. Our teams work every day to make the impossible possible, to change the game, to be agile and effective, and most of all – to empower the rest of the world to do the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ersonal and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;P&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;rofessional&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;C&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;haracteristics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We at Bitfury ensure our team members possess the ability to think out of the box and make the impossible possible. We are self-motivated and result-oriented, and we have an “owner of the company” mindset. We are constantly self-educating and developing. We are able to work in a team and collaborate. We have a “do good” mindset and are not afraid to dream big. And of course, we always deliver in time what we promised and with extreme attention to detail — because if we are not able to do the little things right, we will never be able to do big things right.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Project Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Clarity is an exciting new data oriented decentralised crypto protocol designed to enhance safety and maximise inclusion for the decentralised economy. This is a rare chance to join a greenfield project that has backing from established players within the industry at the pre-launch phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position Summary:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Senior backend developer will join a team of Blockchain developers working closely with the tech lead and product lead to design and implement a market-leading data protocol based on crypto/blockchain tech.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Duties and responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with development teams and product managers to ideate software solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficiency coding using Golang, must submit work example&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design client-side and server-side architecture&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build the front-end of applications through appealing visual design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write effective REST APIs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Write technical documentation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing efficient, scalable, robust, and maintainable code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Writing unit and end-to-end test scripts for required modules/packages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Technologies you will be using:
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cosmos SDK&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solidity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Golang, Protobuf&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Database: MongoDB, MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Source control: Git&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of backend development experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in smart contract development, Cosmos SDK and Solidity&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and interest in crypto projects covering areas such as DeFi, NFTs, and DAOs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organizational skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An analytical mind&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having good knowledge of Algorithms, Data structures, and Networking&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working in a collaborative team environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear and concise written and oral English communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An excellent team player and humble&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having good problem-solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would be a plus:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Slightly obsessed crypto nerd&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working on decentralized protocols&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/DtkFJoj24rE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitfury/jobs/5752800002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145862/bitfury.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitfury@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bff43dfe-8ac3-4757-8a78-7559c9e9e327]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitfury]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[General Interest]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Salt]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://saltlending.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Company&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SALT is the pioneer of crypto-backed lending and offers crypto-focused financial services for individuals and businesses. Our mission is to build products that increase access to financial opportunities and give people more control over their ability to generate wealth long term. Committed to fostering adoption of blockchain technology, we’re working to bridge cryptocurrency with traditional finance. With an emphasis on security and customer service, we provide the technology, infrastructure, and tools that make it easy for crypto holders, businesses, banks, and governments across the globe to participate in the blockchain economy. SALT operates a blockchain-based platform that facilitates the issuance of consumer and commercial asset-backed loans secured with cryptocurrency and provides asset management services. The platform is a wholly-owned subsidiary of Salt Blockchain Inc. SALT is a remote first organization with a dynamic workforce. For more information, please visit saltlending.com.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are passionate about what we do and seek others that are excited to be in this cutting-edge space!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opportunity:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interested in working with SALT but don&#39;t see an open position that is a fit? Apply here! We are always looking for top talent to join our team it would be great to have your information on hand as we continue to grow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in it for you:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work Remotely:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;no commute/traffic, enjoy more flexibility and improved work/life balance, live where you want anywhere within the U.S. and work where you want - comfort of your home, favorite coffee shop, the beautiful outdoors - you pick!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Health Insurance &amp;amp; Benefits:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;medical, dental and vision health insurance with options for the company to pay 100% of the monthly premiums for employees and all their eligible dependents, health care and dependent care flexible spending account options, virtual health options, robust 24/7 employee assistance program, and company-paid short-term and long-term disability insurance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paid Time Off:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;12 company paid holidays and unlimited paid time off - work hard / play hard!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Retirement Savings:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;401(k) with company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Company Equity:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;receive grant of company stock options - build and share in our success!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Perks &amp;amp; Recognition Program:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;monthly allowance of SALTcoin to spend on gift cards, Visa/Mastercard prepaid cards, donation to charities, use to recognize / gift to others, and more!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Work Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;monthly stipend to use towards home internet, cell phone, and work supplies expenses. A generous payment to use towards your home office set up, in addition to a company-provided tech package - laptop, mouse, keyboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Matching Gifts Program:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;company match of your charitable contributions - we support the causes important to you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Great Culture:&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;partner with an engaged, collaborative team and enjoy our informal culture and fun virtual events.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/saltlending/jobs/5750236002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/142025/salt.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[salt@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[cdde14b6-345a-4b6a-b17d-e800f51b5eef]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Salt]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Eco]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://eco.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere (U.S. timezones preferred)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Eco puts your money back to work for you — creating the first consumer fintech product whose creators are aligned with its users. Financial infrastructure hasn&#39;t changed since the 1970s. All we&#39;ve gotten are shinier products built on the same broken systems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Eco App changes that, starting by building the best place to save and spend your dollars. We combine high-yield savings with rewarded spending in a single, compounding balance that&#39;s easy to manage. Soon we&#39;ll let you pay your bills and put your financial life on autopilot. And through all of this — unlike every other fintech company — we don&#39;t skim from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s only possible because we’re building Eco Points, a new rewards currency for the Eco community. Eco Points keep us—our company, App users, and the community of people already building for Eco—aligned to win together. And this is just the beginning. New Points features are emerging every month as we think about how Eco can fundamentally upgrade traditional money. And in case you’re wondering: there’s much, much more to Points than meets the eye.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every day, we&#39;re working on difficult and impactful problems which demand solutions at the intersection of technology, product, marketing, and advocacy. To achieve our mission and realize our vision, we’ve put together an incredible team and are selectively adding to it. We hope you’ll consider joining us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;--&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a Data Engineer at Eco, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with all business functions to identify and scope data needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design and build scalable data pipelines for our products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help us design and build our data warehouse to support reporting, analytics, and model generation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’re looking for you if:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have 5+ years practical work experience as a software engineer, with 2 or more focused on data engineering&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a natural curiosity and interest in data engineering best practices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You stay up-to-date with state-of-the-art and industry trends, and seek to apply the latest and greatest in your work.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You possess a strong understanding of security and privacy. Preserving user trust is a high priority for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You learn fast, are collaborative by default, and have outstanding communication skills (especially written).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;JavaScript/Typescript experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of cryptography fundamentals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fintech experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competent in multiple programming languages, for example: JavaScript/TypeScript, Go, C++, Python, Java, Rust, Ruby, Scala&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/econetwork/jobs/5751602002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/644968/eco-200x200.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[eco@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d703e4ac-536e-4837-8c22-e10df11c25af]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Eco]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Research Engineer - Brave Browser]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Brave]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://brave.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;pre class=&quot;c-mrkdwn__pre&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;pre&quot;&gt;We are hiring a member of the Brave browser research and engineering team to work on browser privacy and security.

As a research engineer, your responsibilities will include:

- Prototyping, measuring, and implementing novel privacy enhancing technologies in Brave browser
- Assisting and / or conducting publication-focused research on Web privacy and security
- Building and maintaining crawlers for Web measurement and privacy-focused list curation purposes 
- Modifying our open source fork of Chromium to improve performance

Required qualifications:

- Proficiency in C++ and JavaScript. At least 5 years of experience is preferred
- Proficiency working with Git
- Comfortable working with a geographically-distributed software development team.
- Familiarity with Web technologies and the Web security model.
- Be comfortable diving into an unfamiliar and complex codebase

Preferred qualifications:

- Experience contributing to open source codebases and/or participating in open source communities. (Almost all of our work at Brave is done in the open on Github.)
- Contributions to other browsers
- Familiarity with Chromium&#39;s architecture.
- Experience auditing C++ code for security issues.
- Ability to write clear technical documentation.
- Be excited about privacy, anonymity, and censorship resistance!
- Interest or experience with research and publications 

This is a full-time role and would report to the Direct of Privacy and the Chief Scientist.&lt;/pre&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/kLiLOkzLetE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/brave/jobs/3721493?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145908/brave.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[brave@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d9771ed5-e81b-4920-bc38-de085de85437]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Brave]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer - Backend]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Stacked Invest]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://stackedinvest.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Chicago or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Stacked is looking to add to its dynamic group of professionals that are dedicated to simplifying crypto investing and helping as many people as possible to take part in the greatest investment opportunity in history. </div><div><br></div><div>Based in Chicago, Stacked is a venture-funded crypto company with less than 100 employees. It provides automation technology to help investors more easily manage their cryptocurrency investments and strategies. Founded out of a personal need, Stacked has grown quickly and has facilitated tens of millions of trades, billions of dollars of volume, and helped tens of thousands of users. Visit <a href="http://www.stackedinvest.com" class="postings-link">www.stackedinvest.com</a> to learn more.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>And, while work experience and educational preparation are certainly important, we don’t hire resumes.&nbsp; We hire talented individuals based on our culture and values that can help us drive innovation and get us to the next stage of our business.</div><br/>Your Core Contributions To The Team<br/><li>Collaborate with key internal partners to determine how to scale and implement backend functionality, APIs, and data pipelines.&nbsp;</li><li>Define, prototype and implement best practices across the backend team.</li><li>Perform code reviews and define characteristics of high quality coding standards.&nbsp;</li><li>Use your understanding of the product and our business goals to build proven and high quality solutions inline with our long-term strategy</li><li>Challenge yourself to keep growing as a engineer</li><br/>About You<br/><li>8+ years of experience in software development.&nbsp;</li><li>You have expert knowledge of system design, data structures, algorithms and understand how to apply them to craft pragmatic solutions.</li><li>Mastery of Node.js and cloud based solutions</li><li>Experience with agile development methodologies such as SCRUM or Kanban.</li><li>Ability to work collaboratively in teams and develop meaningful relationships to achieve common goals&nbsp;</li><li>A passion for investing and the crypto-currency space</li><div><span style="font-size: 10px">#LI-Remote</span></div><div><br></div><div><b>What We Provide You</b></div><div>Stacked works hard to provide benefits that make your life better. We offer a comprehensive benefit program that features:</div><div><br></div><div>- Health coverage for you and your family through medical, dental, and vision plans.</div><div>- A 401(k) plan with a company match.</div><div>- Free gym access in the Chicago office.</div><div>- A generous paid time off program.</div><div><br></div><div><b>All The Other Stuff</b></div><div>Stacked is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace dedicated to pursuing and hiring a diverse workforce. We are committed to building an environment of mutual respect, free of discrimination and harassment, where opportunities are available to everyone based on business needs, job requirements, and individual qualifications.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>The job functions listed above represent the primary duties and responsibilities of this job and in no way states or implies that these are the only duties to be performed by you. Other duties and responsibilities within the scope of this job may be assigned.&nbsp; You will be required to follow all instructions and to perform all duties requested by your manager; subject to reasonable accommodations and within the scope of the position.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/stacked-invest/fad5c187-977a-4ac8-8d04-f00a27ad079b/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/943211/stacked_invest.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alexander+stacked@cryptocareers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f165af66-d59c-48cc-9832-2dc642e4bdb9]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Stacked Invest]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
