<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Daml Application Runtime]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Digital Assets Holding]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://digitalasset.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Zürich, New York, London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Digital Asset&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset helps companies of all sizes and across industries get distributed applications to market faster, and stay there longer. At the core of our service offering is Daml (daml.com), the open source and platform-independent smart contract framework that enables developers to write an application once and deploy it anywhere. Today, we work with some of the largest companies in the world to harness the transformative power of smart contracts - a component of the distributed ledger technology (DLT) stack - and change the way applications are developed, deployed and used to solve real-world business challenges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset is a global company with offices in New York, London, Budapest, Zurich, Hong Kong, and Sydney.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As we grow our team, we will maintain the dynamic, collaborative and pragmatic way of working that has grounded our efforts from the beginning.&amp;nbsp; If you seek to develop solutions others have yet to contemplate, this opportunity may be right for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Daml Application Runtime team is responsible for all software and tooling used in the development of Ledger client applications. This ranges from JavaScript code generation and libraries used in UIs, to frameworks that abstract over common tasks and provide simpler APIs to users to services, and APIs to implement and deploy ledger automation.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a software engineer on the Daml Application Runtime team, you have the unique opportunity to build an ecosystem of tools that enable an exciting new class of smart contract, distributed ledger applications. You’ll develop the tools, APIs and frameworks used in the development of smart contract applications. You will get to extend and improve existing software as well as develop entirely new services to address the issues faced by Daml users in their applications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work on frameworks and tooling used directly by customers in their ledger client applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deliver high quality and well-tested code efficiently and at pace in a Scala-focused codebase&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Address production requirements from customers by making services more reliable and easier to debug&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Criteria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good programming skills in a functional programming language, ideally on the JVM, including, but not limited to, Scala, Haskell, Kotlin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience running services in a production setting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nice to have: Experience working on services deployed to Kubernetes and similar systems and the associated requirements on logging, monitoring and metrics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect With Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a rare opportunity to help define an industry and join a dynamic team of technology innovators.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, national origin, sex, religion, sexual orientation, age, disability, citizenship status, veteran status or any other basis protected by applicable law. If and as required by applicable law, all persons hired to work at Digital Asset will be required to verify identity and eligibility to work in the location for which they have an offer to work and to complete the necessary employment eligibility verification documents upon hire. Applicants with disabilities who require accommodation should contact &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:recruiting@digitalasset.com&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;recruiting@digitalasset.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As part of our commitment to equal opportunity, Digital Asset believes that all employees should receive equal pay for equal work and is committed to this principle in its pay structure. DA also offers family-friendly benefits in addition to flexible work arrangements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/digitalasset/jobs/2334137?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/289153/digital-asset-holdings-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[digitalassets@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b9e3329f-7812-4695-a1f7-5b094cbac58f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Digital Assets Holding]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Software Engineering - Hands-On Architect]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.mastercard.us/en-us.html]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:left"><span><b>Our Purpose</b></span></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p>We work to connect and power an inclusive, digital economy that benefits everyone, everywhere by making transactions safe, simple, smart and accessible. Using secure data and networks, partnerships and passion, our innovations and solutions help individuals, financial institutions, governments and businesses realize their greatest potential. Our decency quotient, or DQ, drives our culture and everything we do inside and outside of our company. We cultivate a <a href="https://www.mastercard.us/en-us/vision/who-we-are/diversity-inclusion.html" target="_blank">culture of inclusion</a> for all employees that respects their individual strengths, views, and experiences. We believe that our differences enable us to be a better team – one that makes better decisions, drives innovation and delivers better business results. </p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:left"><b>Job Title</b></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p>Blockchain Software Engineering - Hands-On Architect<p style="text-align:inherit"></p><p style="text-align:inherit"></p>Who is Mastercard?<br>Mastercard is a global technology company in the payments industry. Our mission is to connect and power an inclusive, digital economy that benefits everyone, everywhere by making transactions safe, simple, smart, and accessible. Using secure data and networks, partnerships and passion, our innovations and solutions help individuals, financial institutions, governments, and businesses realize their greatest potential.<br>Our decency quotient, or DQ, drives our culture and everything we do inside and outside of our company. With connections across more than 210 countries and territories, we are building a sustainable world that unlocks priceless possibilities for all.<br>Overview<br>Mastercard is looking for a talented Hands-On Architect in the Blockchain Software Engineering area to join the Mastercard Blockchain &amp; Digital Asset team in our New York City location.   In this role you will be part of a highly agile team building exiting and innovative products delivered at scale to global markets.<br>Our team is built on a foundation of research and development, mining innovation internally, innovating new product lines with emerging technology, managing new products from inception to market validation and engaging strategically with start-ups to shape the future of commerce with and for our customers. At Mastercard you will help define the future of commerce globally. <br>This team will have a diverse focus both in terms of geography and variety of technology challenges driving hard to bring innovative payment solutions to market.<br>Role<br>This role is the Hands-On Architect for blockchain software engineering that involves working with a team of talented engineers to develop high performance blockchain based solutions. The role would be categorized into these broad areas<br>Architect <br>This aspect of role requires working with Engineering lead and architects <br>-	To lead the architecture, design and development of software systems and applications for a given module or workstream. These solutions &amp; software targeted towards a clients’ specific needs or create products geared for Mastercard. <br>-	Present options, pro’s/con’s for various aspect of design choices to technical standards, such as platforms and coding standards. <br>-	Collaborate to product teams to understand the requirements, identify solution and propose ideas <br>-	Engage with external customers to represent engineering, alongside engineering lead or lead architecture discussion with customers. <br>-	Evaluate and present options/pro’s/con’s analysis of build vs buy solutions<br>-	Document the overall systems/application architecture, help create high level design and provide guidance to the engineering team on low level design <br>Engineer<br>•	Responsible for the analysis, design, and development of software solutions<br>•	Contribute to the requirements for new applications and customizations, adhering to standards, processes, and best practices<br>•	Ensure quality of one or more application codebases and alignment with development standards<br>•	Applies technical capabilities within own discipline to coach and develop junior employees<br>•	Designs highly complex applications, interfaces and integrations<br>•	Integrates at an enterprise level using third-party middleware or messaging products, or by designing and implementing custom interfaces and mapping for those interfaces<br>•	Responsible for performance engineering of the enterprise software architecture, and providing functional guidance, advice, and/or training to other application developers<br>•	Software development, code reviews and day-to-day support duties<br>Project Lead<br>This aspect of role requires working with Engineering lead and architects <br>-	Lead workstream or a given module <br>-	Helps with the scope of the project, assigning tasks to the team, creating a timeline for the project and working with engineering lead doing the estimation of effort<br>-	Engage with partner organization in ensuring that proposed solution meets the corporate standards in creating &amp; operating the applications<br>-	Collaborates with multiple engineering team to achieve the overall objective of the proposed solution <br>Thought Leadership/Mentoring<br>-	Build relationships with technical peers across organization with a focus on our Enterprise Architecture (EA) relationship; socialising new technologies with EA and bringing EA technology and updates back to the group.<br>-	Maintain the common tech stack and integration components. Design a tech stack and blueprints for simplified transitions. Align coding conventions with EA e.g. naming conventions, logging formats.<br>-	Develop and maintain common tools and services for use by the global Blockchain teams.<br>-	Work with Information security and Infrastructure teams to help design infrastructure/cloud environments and a secure application architecture utilizing blockchain technology<br>-	Work with external partners as needed to design or review architectures (e.g. Microsoft).<br>-	Investigate new technologies and architectural domains and apply to Labs projects. <br>-	Provide updates and technical talks to the global blockchain &amp; digital asset engineering teams.<br>-	Promote continuous improvement through tooling and process refinement.<br>-	Researches and evaluates tools and acquisition opportunities to support cross-domain needs<br>Skills<br>•	Proficiency with Java JDK 8 or greater. <br>•	Experience of Tomcat, Spring, Spring Boot, Shell Scripting, JSON. <br>•	Experience with Docker, Kubernetes or other container orchestration solutions.<br>•	Expertise in Junit or other automated unit testing frameworks.<br>•	Expertise in CI/CD principles and tools such as Jenkins, Gradle, Maven. <br>•	Expertise in Source Control Management and working with code in a multi-developer <br>•	Experience with a UI framework such as Angular a plus<br>•	Proficiency with either Besu/Quorum/or R3 technology (Corda and CENM) <br>•	Expertise in cryptography and encryption functions <br>•	Expertise in creating distributed, multi layered, service oriented architecture for global applications that are payment/transaction based.<br>All About You <br>The ideal candidate for this position should: <br>•	Loves creating innovative solutions to problems in a collaborative fun environment<br>•	Advanced knowledge and understanding of modern software engineering concepts and methodologies  <br>•	Passionate about software development and comfortable in a fluid environment<br>•	Passionate about code quality and coding best practices<br>•	Show initiative and demonstrate a willingness to take on challenging opportunities<br>•	Excellent communication (verbal and written) and strong collaboration skills<br>•	Must be driven, highly motivated and a strong team-player<br>•	Interested in mentoring and helping grow the skills of the next generation of software developers<p></p><p></p><p><span>Due to COVID-19, most of our employees are working from home. We’ve implemented a virtual hiring process and continue to interview candidates by phone or video and are onboarding new hires remotely. We value the safety of each member of our community because we know we’re all in this together.</span></p><p></p><p><i>Mastercard is an inclusive Equal Employment Opportunity employer that considers applicants without regard to gender, gender identity, sexual orientation, race, ethnicity, disabled or veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.​</i></p><p></p><p><i>If you require accommodations or assistance to complete the online application process, please contact </i><a href="mailto:reasonable.accommodation&#64;mastercard.com" target="_blank"><i><span><span><span>reasonable.accommodation&#64;mastercard.com</span></span></span></i></a><i> and identify the type of accommodation or assistance you are requesting.  Do not include any medical or health information in this email. The Reasonable Accommodations team will respond to your email promptly.</i></p><p></p><p><i>  </i></p><p><b><span>Corporate Security Responsibility</span></b></p><p><br /><span>Every person working for, or on behalf of, Mastercard is responsible for information security. All activities involving access to Mastercard assets, information, and networks comes with an inherent risk to the organization and therefore, it is expected that the successful candidate for this position must:</span><br /><br /><span>• Abide by Mastercard’s security policies and practices;</span><br /><span>• Ensure the confidentiality and integrity of the information being accessed;</span><br /><span>• Report any suspected information security violation or breach, and</span><br /><span>• Complete all periodic mandatory security trainings in accordance with Mastercard’s guidelines.</span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/w7FvjIQx_tg" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://mastercard.wd1.myworkdayjobs.com/en-US/CorporateCareers/job/New-York-City-New-York/Blockchain-Software-Engineering---Hands-On-Architect_R-142937?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143560/mastercard.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[mastercard@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5e2069a0-e8ad-4538-a4a1-79d2ab62d9aa]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Mastercard]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of People]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Forte Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.forte.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We believe in treating people right to build a great team for the journey ahead. If there’s something important to you that’s not on this list, talk to us! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive compensation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Remote and/or flexible work arrangements. We believe in bringing on the best people to our team, no matter where they are in the world&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A dynamic startup environment where you will constantly be challenged and exposed to new ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Forte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Forte is building economic technology for games. Its end-to-end platform enables the emergence of community economics, a system where the interests of game developers and players are aligned,&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;leading to healthier, sustainable game communities. The team is composed of longtime industry members (Unity, ngmoco, Riot Games, Electronic Arts, Sony, and Rockstar Games, among others). Forte is currently working with over thirty acclaimed game developers from across the industry to reimagine the economics of games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/K378r1KeRio" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/forte/jobs/4900482003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/511563/forte-labs-logo_Cropped.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[forte@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[509e5842-f758-4b3e-8b54-bfc3ca4c2a98]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Forte Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Institutional Senior Sales - Electronic Trading]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://blockchain.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, San Francisco, Miami, New York,  Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Institutional Senior Sales - Electronic Trading&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;at Blockchain.com &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(View all jobs)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;London, San Francisco, Miami, New York,&amp;nbsp; Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Blockchain is the world&#39;s leading software platform for digital assets. Founded in 2011, we provide the world’s largest and most trusted production blockchain platform, powering more than 80 million wallets. Together with our platform of liquidity and execution services, we share the passion to build an open, accessible and fair financial future, one piece of software at a time.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for an experienced senior sales professional to drive volumes on our exchange by&amp;nbsp; building and maintaining strong relationships with market makers, liquidity aggregators and other institutions active in providing liquidity within the crypto ecosystem. The Senior Electronic Trading Sales Executive will take a long view of building out deep relationships while finding new opportunities for Blockchain.com to partner. As a key member of the Institutional Client Services team, this person will play a significant role in driving the growth of Blockchain.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL DO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define and drive Blockchain.com’s partnership strategy with crypto market makers, liquidity aggregators and other venues to drive institutional flow on the Blockchain.com exchange..&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Operationalize and scale up our partnerships strategy working collaboratively with the Sales team, Corporate Partnerships group and the infrastructure functions of the organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build strategic relationships with market makers, liquidity aggregators and other sources of flow to generate liquidity on the exchange as well as the cash and derivatives OTC trading desks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish appropriate measurement criteria for the enablement function and report quantifiable progress over time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU WILL NEED&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A passion for crypto and blockchain ecosystems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years business development, partnerships or sales experience in an traditional finance role with an exchange or broker-dealer, ideally with 2+ years experience in crypto&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A proven track record of leading and closing impactful partnerships or transactions&amp;nbsp; in a product-centric environment with significant internal and external dependencies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience negotiating commercial deals with organizations of all sizes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team player with strong interpersonal skills, ability to interact effectively with partners and colleagues from various cultural backgrounds&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Highly organized, analytical thinker who thrives in a fast-paced, high growth environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelors degree in finance related field. MBA, CFA or similar qualification would be an advantage, as would present or prior financial industry regulatory registrations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;COMPENSATION &amp;amp; PERKS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Unlimited vacation policy; work hard and take time when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Apple equipment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Full-time salary based on experience and meaningful equity in an industry-leading company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Make a difference: we’re not just another crypto company: we’re the financial system for the internet and changing the future of finance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;When you apply to a job on this site, the personal data contained in your application will be collected by one or more of the following subsidiaries of Blockchain Luxembourg S.A (each, a “Controller”):&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain Access UK Ltd.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain (GB) Limited&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain (US), Inc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain (LT), UAB&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You may contact our Data Protection Officer by email at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;dpo@blockchain.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Your personal data will be processed for the purposes of managing Controller’s recruitment related activities, which include setting up and conducting interviews and tests for applicants, evaluating and assessing the results thereto, and as is otherwise needed in the recruitment and hiring processes. Such processing is legally permissible under Art. 6(1)(f) of Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (General Data Protection Regulation) as necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the Controller, which are the solicitation, evaluation, and selection of applicants for employment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your personal data will be shared with Greenhouse Software, Inc., a cloud services provider located in the United States of America and engaged by Controller to help manage its recruitment and hiring process on Controller’s behalf.&amp;nbsp; Accordingly, if you are located outside of the United States, your personal data will be transferred to the United States once you submit it through this site. Because the European Union Commission has determined that United States data privacy laws do not ensure an adequate level of protection for personal data collected from EU data subjects, the transfer will be subject to appropriate additional safeguards under the standard contractual clauses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your personal data will be retained by Controller as long as Controller determines it is necessary to evaluate your application for employment.&amp;nbsp; Under the GDPR, you have the right to request access to your personal data, to request that your personal data be rectified or erased, and to request that processing of your personal data be restricted. You also have to right to data portability. In addition, you may lodge a complaint with an EU supervisory authority.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockchain/jobs/3830792?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180745/blockchaininc.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockchaininc@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5457bd3d-b464-4d43-bfd6-5c9d9e62930e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Blockchain, Inc.]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Front-End Web Developer (Remote - Work from Anywhere)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Xapo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://xapo.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Anywhere]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Xapo is an international fintech startup on a mission to protect and grow its clients’ life savings.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re a fully distributed team that works remotely from 50+ countries around the world. We may come from many different cultures and backgrounds, but it’s our values, our resourcefulness, and our drive that makes us Xapiens.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We work hard, think globally, and inspire each other to grow every day. If you’re the best at what you do and share our passion, we want you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Join us, wherever you are, and help us build a digital bank worthy of the digital age at Xapo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Position overview&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a Senior Front-End Web Developer who is motivated to combine the art of design with the art of programming. Responsibilities will include the translation of design wireframes to actual code that will produce visual elements of the application. You will work with the product designer and bridge the gap between graphical design and technical implementation, taking an active role on both sides and defining how the application looks as well as how it works.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Although we are headquartered in Gibraltar, this is a full time, 100% remote position. Work from anywhere!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop new user-facing features&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build reusable code and libraries for future use&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure the technical feasibility of design, from a visual and experience standpoint.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Optimize application for maximum speed and scalability&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assure that all user input is validated before submitting to back-end&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with other team members and stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Skills needed&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient understanding of web markup, including HTML5, CSS3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Basic understanding of server-side CSS pre-processing platforms, such as LESS and SASS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient understanding of client-side scripting and JavaScript frameworks, including jQuery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of advanced JavaScript libraries and frameworks, such as AngularJS, KnockoutJS, BackboneJS, ReactJS, DurandalJS etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of asynchronous request handling, partial page updates, and AJAX&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Basic knowledge of image authoring tools, to be able to crop, resize, or perform small adjustments on an image. Familiarity with tools such as Figma and Lokalise is a plus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient understanding of cross-browser compatibility issues and ways to work around them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient understanding of code versioning tools, such as Github&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of SEO principles and ensuring that application will adhere to them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent attention to detail &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Other requirements&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A dedicated workspace&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A reliable internet connection with the fastest speed possible in your area&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Devices and other essential equipment that meet minimal technical specifications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Alignment with Our Values.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHY WORK FOR XAPO?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IMPACT GLOBALLY, WORK REMOTELY.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shape the Future: Improve lives through cutting-edge technology, work 100% remotely from anywhere in the world.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Own Your Success: Receive attractive remuneration, enjoy an autonomous work culture and flexible hours, apply your expertise to meaningful work every day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Expect Excellence: Collaborate, learn, and grow with a high-performance team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ABOUT XAPO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We founded Xapo to address two of the biggest issues with Bitcoin adoption: accessibility and security. In a matter of years, we developed an industry-leading platform that introduced cryptocurrency into the daily lives of millions worldwide.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, we’re bringing our expertise to all facets of our users’ finances. Because no matter who we are or where we’re from, we all deserve more options, more control, and more peace of mind where our money is concerned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We’re an Equal Opportunity Employer – we believe that diversity is critical to our success as a global company. An inclusive workplace is the foundation of Xapo – it allows us to create products that cater to clients around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/xapo61/jobs/4915977003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175504/xapo500x500.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[xapo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f1ade05b-4c67-4366-b825-57e86b9f373d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Xapo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Graphic Designer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOTA Foundation]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.iota.org]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The IOTA Foundation is a not-for-profit organization established in 2017 and headquartered in Berlin, Germany. The Foundation’s mission is to drive the development and standardization of new distributed ledger technologies (DLTs) that enable permissionless innovation ecosystems. To realize this potential the IOTA Foundation is actively building a collaborative of developers, start-ups, private enterprises, and government, civil society and academic institutions.</span></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Concretely, we engage in engineering, research and community organizing efforts around the IOTA Tangle – a new generation of DLT specifically designed to be the open and free trust layer for the Internet-of-Things (IoT).</span></p>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Mission: </span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="color: #091e42;">As a Graphic Designer you</span><span style="color: #222222;"> will create visual communications to convey messages in an effective and aesthetically pleasing manner.</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Responsibilities:</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Concepting and finalizing Brand Design, UI Design &amp; Logos</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Conceptualizing creative ideas with the Team</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Testing and improving the design of the website</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Developing design guidelines, standards, and best practices</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Develop creative concepts for brand initiatives and campaigns across a variety of media</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Provide design support and thinking in presentations, strategic documents, corporate communication</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Present creative work to the team, as well as directly to clients</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Your personality</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Superb design skills supported by strategic thinking</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Ability to verbally illustrate, rationalize and present design</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Innate ability to think conceptually</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Stamina to push the work towards excellence</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Your expertise</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">At least 5 years of experience in design both in web and print is required</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Fantastic Knowledge of design, typography and production of web and print products</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Proficiency with Figma, Adobe Illustrator/Affinity Designer, Adobe Photoshop and other relevant Creative Suite Products</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #1d1c1d; font-size: 15px;">Proficiency with Google Slides &amp; Powerpoint</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #091e42;">When applying, please provide a portfolio of your work explaining your approach and decision-making as part of the research and design process.</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">What we offer</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The opportunity to work with the brightest minds in the industry</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The opportunity to make a true difference</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Culture of trust, empowerment and constructive feedback</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">A flexible and agile organization with a flat hierarchy</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Independence and responsibility from day one</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The IOTA Foundation is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity and are committed to creating an inclusive environment for all employees.</span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LVY9DzwyzdU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://iota.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=189&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180020/iota.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iota@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[89e42fc6-4d4d-416c-82b4-a1443bc5e101]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOTA Foundation]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Partnerships Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.parity.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role will be focused on building and managing a strong set of partners with the key goals of increasing partner adoption of Substrate/Polkadot and developing high-value partnerships/initiatives.&amp;nbsp; With a sense of urgency and determination you will break down complex problems to make decisions that best serve stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with the ecosystem, BD, partnership team and partners to define and execute joint go to market programs to drive partner success through the development of chains, applications and professional services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage and drive joint engagements between the partner and Parity teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage the partners’ field sales organization, channels, and end customers to create and drive opportunities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish and run partner account planning meetings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Engage closely with sales and technical pre-sales teams to develop a pipeline and in support of RFPs, projects/pilots&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Closely collaborate with platform, services and legal teams for end-to-end partnership engagement, from the initial agreement to launch&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Accountable and responsible for activating, onboarding and managing ISV’s, SI’s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Nurture existing partnerships to deliver ongoing mutual value, evolve relationship&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Prepare and deliver business reviews to the senior management team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years of experience in partnerships or business development in the software/technology industry with a history of exceeding performance metrics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of blockchain ecosystems and commercial acumen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong program management skills, including advanced problem solving and decision-making skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience engaging senior executives and familiarity with decision-making processes across enterprise customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills, as well as the ability to work across internal and external organizations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work experience in Web3/blockchain projects with enterprises and regulators&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Structuring and leading large complex technology platform partnerships&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Structuring and leading large complex partnerships among public/private institutions&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;To see how we use your data please see our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.parity.io/applicant-notice/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applicant Notice.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LZd6z7HiTLw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/parity/jobs/4916488003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/378609/parity.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[parity@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6edef434-1785-497e-a19b-ce6d949ad50a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Public-Goods-Funding Software Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://protocol.ai/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>Key Summary:</b></div><div>We seek a full-stack engineer who will develop, deploy, and iterate on novel mechanisms for funding public goods and the tools to measure their outcomes.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Public-Goods Funding at Protocol Labs:</b></div><div>Protocol Labs doesn’t just build core protocols for the decentralized web. We think engineers and researchers should work on a variety of high-leverage goals for the betterment of humanity.&nbsp; For that reason, we're developing a lab to develop and deploy better methods of funding the creation and maintenance of public goods.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As part of our public-goods team, you’ll be enabling outcomes at the forefront of our mission. Our team is granted both the freedom to develop knowledge by working on novel applications and a responsibility to contribute those skills toward advancing the mission of Protocol Labs.&nbsp; You’ll feel at home working with us if your knowledge and optimism enable you to craft creative solutions working around evolving needs.</div><br/>As a software engineer at Protocol Labs you will…<br/><li>Be an early engineer and “go-to” contributor of the growing public-goods funding team</li><li>Work alongside a cross-functional team including research, product, and operations</li><li>Work with team to evaluate the technical feasibility of funding mechanisms and associated internal measurement / analysis tools</li><li>Design and prototype multiple tools and implementations of funding mechanisms to distribute significant amounts of funding to the Protocol Labs ecosystem</li><li>Design, prototype and implement small scale user-facing web tooling and platforms</li><li>Develop prototypes into production-ready implementations</li><li>Collaborate with ecosystem and external teams exploring new and out-of-the-box approaches to designing and implementing next-gen funding mechanisms.</li><li>Gain high-level exposure across the PL stack (IPFS, Filecoin, LibP2P, etc.)</li><li>Help build a team, mentoring, leading, and developing more junior engineers as the team grows</li><li>Work in a fully asynchronous and remote team.</li><br/>You may be a fit for this role if you have...<br/><li>BA/BS or MS degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering, related field or equivalent practical experience</li><li>Experience building internal or external full-stack applications with high ownership across the product from proposal to launch (e.g., docs, support, metrics)</li><li>Experience with developer tooling projects</li><li>Background in an agency or consultancy environment with diverse project types</li><li>A proven track record of independently driving technical projects in a fast-paced environment with minimal oversight or guidance</li><li>Adept at starting new software projects interacting with complex systems single-handedly, if necessary</li><li>Strong analytical, problem solving, and interpersonal skills</li><br/>Bonus points if you have...<br/><li>Experience with and the desire to improve the funding systems for public goods</li><li>Experience building applications in Go, Rust, and/or JavaScript</li><li>Familiarity with Web3 technology and concepts (smart contracts, blockchain, P2P networking)&nbsp;</li><li>Prior project or development experience in the Web3 ecosystem or prior experience in implementing funding mechanisms / operations.</li><li>Familiarity with Protocol Labs stack (IPFS, Filecoin, LibP2P) through project work or open-source contributions</li><li>Technical familiarity with relevant flavors of economics (behavioral economics models, cryptoeconomic models, decentralized governance tooling).</li><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">What’s it like to work at Protocol Labs?</span></b></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Protocol Labs mission is to improve humanity’s most important technology, the Internet. We build protocols, systems, and tools to improve how it works. Today, we are focused on how we store, locate, and move information. Our projects include IPFS, Filecoin, libp2p, and more.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As a distributed team, we hire anywhere in the world, and at various levels of experience (entry, senior, staff). We look for people with unique perspectives and diverse backgrounds.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We have a great benefits package, including parental leave, contributions to your retirement, competitive pay, and unlimited time off. For U.S.-based employees, we also provide platinum-level health, dental, and vision coverage for you and your family.</span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EClPAFPeXIQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/protocol/ce7372f9-88c4-42e0-a4ec-5e4afdb8e72a/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/207125/protocol_loabs.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[protocollabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c4028873-6454-47fc-a65d-6c6d1ed8cb1f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Protocol Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Smart Contract Developer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Wintermute]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.wintermute-trading.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London / Singapore / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Wintermute</b></div><div><br></div><div><a href="https://www.wintermute.com/" class="postings-link">Wintermute</a> is one of the largest algorithmic trading firms in digital assets globally. We manage billions in assets and trade more than $5B+/day across dozens of different trading platforms. Wintermute provides liquidity algorithmically across most CeFi and DeFi exchanges and via OTC.&nbsp;Wintermute was one of the earliest adopters of DeFi and is a big supporter of decentralized finance. We are widely known to be one of the largest and most advanced liquidity providers in DeFi. We support all major DEX, trading platforms, AMMs, RFQs, aggregators and we work with most major chains. Wintermute is an official market maker for many of the most prominent blockchain projects and we actively support the DeFi ecosystem: we invest in and help scale early stage DeFi projects, we actively participate in governance of various protocols and cooperate with projects of building the missing pieces of the eco-system.&nbsp;Wintermute is a hyper-growth highly profitable business with a very ambitious vision and roadmap. We are backed by <a href="https://medium.com/lightspeed-venture-partners/wintermute-makes-sure-you-dont-get-ripped-off-when-you-buy-crypto-63aa96dcb983" class="postings-link">Lightspeed</a>, <a href="https://panteracapital.com/" class="postings-link">Pantera Capital</a>, <a href="https://www.sinoglobalcapital.com/" class="postings-link">Sino Global Capital</a>, <a href="http://blockchain.com/" class="postings-link">Blockchain.com</a> Ventures, Avon Ventures by <a href="https://www.fidelity.com/" class="postings-link">Fidelity Investments</a>, <a href="https://defialliance.co/" class="postings-link">DeFi Alliance</a> and other top tier investors. We are run as a technology company, not a financial service provider, and we build our culture around <a href="https://www.wintermute.com/join-us/" class="postings-link">core values</a> of ambition, collaboration, entrepreneurship, transparency and meritocracy. </div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 13.5pt">Working at Wintermute DeFi team</b></div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a smart contract developer to design/build secure and reliable dApps in Solidity. You will get a lot of independence and responsibility right away, and you'll learn at an unprecedented speed! A great advantage of this position is that it is varied and it is also up to you to shape it in the direction that matches your talents and company needs. </div><br/>Responsibilities and projects may include:<br/><li>Design/implement secure and reliable applications in Solidity</li><li>Collaborate with full-stack, front-end developers and quantitative developers to bring products to life</li><li>Development of automated testing code bases and audit of smart contracts</li><li>Providing tech support internally for optimal execution of trading strategies</li><li>Researching dApp protocols and providing a vision for the space</li><li>Optionally, longer term researching/developing rust smart contracts</li><br/>Hard skills requirements <br/><li>Deep understanding of EVM, solidity, and popular decentralized protocols</li><li>Programming fundamentals in e.g. C++, Python Java; OO, design patterns, etc.</li><li>Blockchain fundamentals: consensus, nodes, miners, forks, transactions, web3</li><li>2-3 years development of smart contracts and working on DeFi projects and protocols is an advantage, but if you are a self-taught genius or a DeFi enthusiast working on own projects, that may work too</li><li>Knowledge and experience of test-driven development</li><li>Familiar with the common smart contract vulnerabilities (we will test!)</li><br/>Nice to have skills <br/><li>Knowledge of other chains (Solana, Polkadot) is an advantage</li><li>Trading knowledge isn’t required but curiosity to learn algorithmic, quantitative, market making trading would be a huge plus, as well as understanding of DeFi native trading (farming, liquidity mining, liquidations, etc)</li><br/>Culture fit requirements <br/><li>Love coding, love problem solving, building things and seeing your products work</li><li>Curious about algorithmic trading and financial markets</li><li>Determined, ambitious yet humble, willing to work hard, give and take feedback</li><li>Like meritocracy and being judged by what you deliver</li><li>Owner mentality: focused on doing what it takes to achieve important results, prepared to work non-standard working hours, no 9-to-5 mentality</li><li>Like working in a team environment closely collaboration both within and outside the team</li><br/>Wintermute offer <br/><li>A unique opportunity to work on very interesting projects, get the level of responsibility and ownership that would be unlikely at any other project or trading firm</li><li>A unique opportunity to join one of the strongest and most successful DeFi teams globally</li><li>With Wintermute you don’t make a bet on a single product, platform, chain or technology; we’ll win if DeFi wins as a whole</li><li>Great company culture: informal, non-hierarchical, ambitious, highly professional yet collaborative and entrepreneurial&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Option to work from London or Singapore offices, as well as remotely; we generally prefer at least 50% working from the office but are open to remote candidates</li><li>Weekly team events, such as team lunches, team dinners, team board games and Dota playing sessions; these are not obligatory in any sense, but this is what we like to do</li><li>Aligned incentive structure: high upside from performance-based variable pay with very transparent bonus system</li><li>We offer standard perks too, like pension, private health insurance, free food and office gym, but that’s probably not the right reason to join us</li><li>We offer UK work permits and help in relocation; we prefer Singapore candidates who have PR or citizenship but are able to arrange permits too for the best candidates</li><br/>Tips for successful application <br/><li>Only apply to us if you are genuinely interested or curious about this role and DeFi space; this is not for someone who is just looking for "a job"</li><li>Do some research: look at our website and social media channels</li><li>Write us a short, honest, and direct message if you'd like to apply. Tell us about why you are interested in DeFi in general and in Wintermute in particular. Do not send us generic copy paste applications, we are looking for authentic people who share our interests, values and ambitions!</li><li>If you don't have an obviously matching experience or skills, make sure you state very clearly what you can bring or how your experience is relevant (but note, we do require deep blockchain development expertise)</li><li>Prepare to be tested on your blockchain knowledge. We do not care as much about your credentials (university or prior employer), but we care a lot about your knowledge and ability to get things done</li><li>Unfortunately, we won't be able to proceed if you simply press "submit button"; we do promise to reply to everyone who puts time and effort in making the application relevant!</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/wintermute-trading/b8dc6891-b177-496d-bc27-17524ab2e0ee/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637352/wintermute-trading.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[wintermute@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b33e8b5-6d52-4368-8eea-e8c0ac3382ff]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Wintermute]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Web3 Relations Lead (Remote possible)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Keyrock]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.keyrock.eu/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Brussels,]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keyrock is expanding!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keyrock was founded in 2017 and has quickly grown from 3 to over 50 people today. As an industry recognized liquidity provider and market maker, Keyrock is a leading European creator of algorithmic trading technology in the digital asset space. With VC backing, a constantly expanding global client base and revenues growth 13x in 2021, Keyrock is one of Belgium’s fastest-growing fintech companies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;We’re currently active on over 80 exchanges and count numerous marketplaces and asset issuers among our clients, including some of the best-known companies in the crypto space.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keyrock&#39;s beating heart is its technical team filled with crypto and DeFi natives, software engineers, digital scientists and PhDs, who themselves are supported by university professors, industry-leading experts and a strong management team. Over the years Keyrock has become a company that is both idealistic and practical.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;We are looking for:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;DeFi community participant and expert who lives and breathes Web3. Ideally, you are skilled in leveraging brand and community relations in order to increase Keyrock brand equity among DeFi projects and communities through thoughtful participation. Your core mission will be ensuring positive recognition of Keyrock brand as a “top-of-mind”, leading liquidity provider through positive participation in project communities.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Job description:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0;&quot;&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Positively interacting with DeFi projects communities and key drivers and engaging in governance discussions for key protocols&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Positive, constructive and genuine participation in social media&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Participation in community-driven decision making according to governance rules of each protocole&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Promoting Keyrock values across DeFi ecosystem&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Staying on top of development and proposals &amp;nbsp;within projects to be aware of potential profitable partnerships&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Working closely with Keyrock’s defi, treasury and venture teams in order to position Keyrock as a leading DeFi player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Competences and skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0;&quot;&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Good understanding of DeFi and decentralised projects ecosystem&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Project management and communication skills including the ability to oversee implementation of complex projects&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Problem-solving and decision-making skills, with the ability to analyse complex information to identify the key issue/action and drive resolution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Understanding of sales process and public relations dynamics and ability to translate it into action plan within realms of digital assets and DeFi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Operational excellence&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Strong analytical capabilities under pressure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Team player&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Able to thrive in an autonomous environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Basic coding skills and ability to pull blockchain data is a big plus (ideally experience with Dune Analytics or similar)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;General good understanding of capital markets is a strong plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Strong written and spoken communication skills,&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;fluent in written and spoken English&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:7pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Have a minimum of 3 year of professional experience or at least 1 year professional &amp;nbsp;experience in companies of crypto space&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;margin-left: 36pt;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:7pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:underline;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Our recruitment philosophy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;We believe the most important aspect of our recruitment process is self-awareness: we are looking for people who have a clear understanding of themselves and what they are looking for in their professional career. That means that we expect to work with people who not only have the right skills, but who have also made the conscious decision to look for a company in our industry and with our characteristics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:underline;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Our offer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0;&quot;&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;A competitive salary package, including benefits that you choose and manage according to your needs and those of your family (car/bike, meal vouchers, phone and internet subscription, health insurance, 25 days &amp;nbsp;off, etc.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Complete autonomy in your time management thanks to flexible working hours and the opportunity to work remotely&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;The freedom to create your own entrepreneurial experience by being part of a team of people in search of excellence who all receive stock options from the first year&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:7pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;A ton of fun in a thriving and multicultural environment, with colleagues enjoying regular team building activities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keyrock offers you both a career and a large range of benefits that we will gladly discuss in the course of the application process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://keyrock.freshteam.com/jobs/mGzlMO2v-r5T/web3-relations-lead-remote-possible?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/831880/keyrock-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[keyrock@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5b5712b4-ea1b-4843-8efd-ea04303877b0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Keyrock]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Quantitative Developer - Systematic Commodities]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[DRW]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://drw.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Greenwich]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRW&lt;/strong&gt; is a technology-driven, diversified principal trading firm. We trade our own capital at our own risk, across a broad range of asset classes, instruments and strategies, in financial markets around the world. As the markets have evolved over the past 25 years, so has DRW – maximizing opportunities to include real estate, cryptoassets and venture capital. With over 1,200 employees at our Chicago headquarters and offices around the world, we work together to solve complex problems, challenge consensus and deliver meaningful results. It’s a place of high expectations, deep curiosity and thoughtful collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Quantitative Developer&lt;/strong&gt;, you will work directly on a systematic commodity trading team to help support the entire quantitative trading process. You will have the opportunity to solve challenging problems in a dynamic environment. The ideal candidate will be entrepreneurial and passionate about exploring new ideas and improving current processes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will do in this role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop analytic and investment tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maintain and improve code-base in both Rust and Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze and clean large datasets.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Run day-to-day processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support research and development of investment strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conduct commodity fundamental research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will need in this role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong preference for math, engineering&amp;nbsp;or computer science degrees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong quantitative foundation, including understanding of time-series analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong programming skills with experience in both scripting and strongly-typed languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to successfully research ideas given broad direction.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to respond to requests quickly and manage multiple work streams.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energetic and goal oriented.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creative and independent thinker.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interest in financial markets and trading, with prior financial experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with commodities is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For more information about DRW&#39;s processing activities and our use of job applicants&#39; data, please view our Privacy Notice at &lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;California residents, please review the&amp;nbsp;California Privacy Notice&amp;nbsp;for information about certain legal rights at&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;#LI-SK1&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MdwEImeQcx8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/drweng/jobs/3853756?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145892/drw.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[drw@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bf32acf8-cf47-410b-aa59-74974c4d6afd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[DRW]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Writer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[NEAR]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://nearprotocol.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About NEAR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;NEAR Protocol is a developer-first blockchain that emphasizes convenience and speed of development on the NEAR platform while minimizing the entrance barrier for developers coming from the blockchain ecosystem, as well as regular web and mobile development space.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a talented, meticulous, and productive person who loves working in an energetic and free-thinking environment, feels comfortable challenging opinions, and most importantly who shares with us the same desire to make the web free again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage people of all backgrounds to apply. NEAR is committed to creating an inclusive culture, and we celebrate diversity of all kinds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About The Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Are you a strong writer who loves to share what you know with the world? Do you enjoy building prototypes and proofs of concept while you learn about a technical topic? Have you published your work online as video, audio or text tutorials and workshops to wide acclaim?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a key member of the Developer Relations team at NEAR, you will be working as a knowledge bridge between our internal teams and the rest of the world. You share the key responsibilities of growing our community of developers and entrepreneurs as well as enabling their success as they use the platform to build DApps of their own.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role is a good fit if you are a disciplined and shameless content factory, are genuinely curious and driven to learn and share what you learn about DApp development using NEAR and compulsively share your work online via social media channels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You&#39;ll Be Doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Plans, directs, and coordinates preparation of project documentation, such as engineering drawings, production specifications and schedules&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Determines documentation required for each phase of a project, applying knowledge of engineering processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Schedules due dates for drawings, specifications, software, technical manuals, and other documents.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitors status of project to ensure documentation is submitted according to schedule.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Reviews and verifies project documents for completeness, format, and compliance with requirements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Submits project documentation to management for approval, and transmits approved documents to customers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Confers with engineers, managers, the community, and others to discuss projects, prepare documents, or modify schedules&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key metrics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Active and engaged learners who consume your content&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Student &quot;time to ship&quot; from first touch to a working, meaningful DApp&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We’re Looking For:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Significant experience designing, developing and publishing learning content online&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Some familiarity with blockchain and its ecosystem is helpful&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Well versed in technical topics, especially web based software development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working with open-source projects and their documentation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of open-source documentation tools such as Markdown, Git, Docusaurus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We’d Love If You Have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with coding in languages such as JavaScript, Rust, C, Java&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Anywhere in the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Working at NEAR&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Roles are posted to this portal on behalf of the companies that make up the NEAR Collective and are typically located anywhere in the world because most of the companies are fully remote. Some hubs are located in Switzerland, Germany, Russia, the US and China. Regardless of where you work, this is a high performance culture that values ownership, execution and professionalism but pairs it with curiosity and experimentation. The vision is big but the right team is behind it.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/-hOWM-o7N5k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/near/jobs/5862335002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/291590/near-protocol-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[near@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[968fe95d-e05d-452b-ab80-880386c33b67]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[NEAR]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Developer Marketing - Remote]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tendermint]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tendermint.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berlin]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About us:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Formed in 2014, Tendermint is a core contributor to the Cosmos network, a rapidly growing ecosystem of independent interconnected blockchains. We are a software engineering company that focuses on developing state-of-the-art frameworks for blockchain development, including the Cosmos SDK and Starport. Over $130 billion of digital assets are secured by the 250+ blockchains and applications built with our technology.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We’re passionate, self-driven industry leaders whose vision is to empower people to create a more transparent and accountable world through open, distributed, and interoperable networks. We believe that the technology we're building will have a major positive impact on how humans connect and coordinate globally. Join our growing international team and help us build the most popular multi-blockchain ecosystem in the world.</div><div><br></div><div><b>How we work:</b></div><div><br></div><div>We have team members working worldwide in more than 35 countries, from North America and Europe to the Middle East and Asia. We leverage agile methodologies to move quickly and stay focused. Communication is vital to us, and we rely heavily on Slack, Google Workspace, Notion, and GitHub to help us stay in sync. All the technology we build is free and open source.</div><div><br></div><div>This role is a full-time remote position, and you’re free to work from anywhere. However, most team meetings occur between 8 am and 12 pm Pacific Time (UTC-8/-7). If you're applying from a location where these hours are outside your usual working hours, we would expect you to adapt to attend our meetings.</div><div><br></div><div><b>About the position:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Tendermint is seeking a talented and motivated Head of Ecosystem Growth to accelerate the growth of the ecosystem to make Starport the standard for launching blockchain-based dApps. You’ll take full ownership of our growth initiatives on the developer acquisition and engagement fronts. You will manage a talented team of 6, with more members to recruit this year. This strategic position reports directly to the VP of Growth, with the opportunity to contribute to the broader strategy for the company.</div><div><br></div><div>Your scope will be quite broad and you have the opportunity to continue growing in responsibility over time.</div><div><br></div><br/>What you will be doing:<br/><li>Build and lead a high-performing team to create and implement strategic growth initiatives across various channels including lead generation, CRM, social media, and video marketing.</li><li>Increase our product awareness, adoption, and advocacy across various technical audiences, primarily crypto developers.</li><li>Oversee retention initiatives to ensure developers within our ecosystem are onboarded smoothly, get access to useful resources, and receive the support they need to be successful using our line of products.</li><li>Use data and analytics for decision making, measure marketing effectiveness, and create a culture of structured experimentation and iteration to drive growth.</li><li>Manage the developer acquisition budget to drive sustainable bottom-line growth with the goal to fuel our developer acquisition pipeline.</li><li>Develop a deep familiarity with our product and the technology behind it to ensure that developers understand their functionalities at their full potential.&nbsp;</li><li>Define, measure, and report the performance of growth actions and assess them against KPI goals</li><br/>What we expect:<br/><li>Strong passion for and understanding of blockchain ecosystems</li><li>8+ years of related experience in the blockchain industry or have worked in the ecosystem development or developer marketing in a fast-paced environment</li><li>Analytic skills: You love analyzing your team’s actions to make data-driven decisions</li><li>Ability to present and speak in public to both technical and non-technical audiences&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Ability to take initiative and work independently</li><div><br></div><br/>Nice to have:<br/><li>Experience managing a growth or ecodev team</li><li>Familiarity with programming languages (Golang preferred)</li><br/>What we offer:<br/><li>The opportunity to be part of building the future of the Internet</li><li>Flexible work schedule</li><li>Excellent benefits like educational budget, fitness, and wellbeing spend</li><li>Flexible PTO</li><li>Healthcare, Dental, and Vision insurance 100% covered for employees in the US</li><li>401K Match in the US</li><li>Competitive salary, including equity.</li><div>Tendermint in the news:</div><div><br></div><div><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2019/03/17/welcome-to-the-hub-of-all-hubs/" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://techcrunch.com/2019/03/17/welcome-to-the-hub-of-all-hubs/</a></div><div><a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cross-platform-blockchain-project-cosmos-launches-first-hub-after-17-million-ico" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://cointelegraph.com/news/cross-platform-blockchain-project-cosmos-launches-first-hub-after-17-million-ico</a></div><div><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/a-blockchain-to-connect-all-blockchains-cosmos-is-now-officially-live" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://www.coindesk.com/a-blockchain-to-connect-all-blockchains-cosmos-is-now-officially-live</a></div><div><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/how-to-turn-a-17-million-ico-into-104-million-the-cosmos-story" class="postings-link">https://www.coindesk.com/how-to-turn-a-17-million-ico-into-104-million-the-cosmos-story</a></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/oJ4WG3SelT0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/tendermint/bc705be1-b4b5-4d8b-88f6-11dc87e56e88/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145907/tendermint.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tendermint@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7560c97e-86cc-40b9-b8e0-09ef50cbd9ef]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tendermint]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[German Customer Service Agent]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://swissborg.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Lisbon]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We are SwissBorg, a FinTech startup headquartered in Lausanne, Switzerland.</div><div><br></div><div>Our flagship product, the SwissBorg app, offers over 550,000+ users the best price and liquidity across 16 fiat and 17 cryptos, as well as giving them the opportunity to earn passive income with our Smart Yield account. Our community is growing fast, with over $1.5 billion in assets under management, a weekly volume of over 250 million, and over 18,000 Premium users.</div><div><br></div><div>This is just the start in our mission to democratise wealth management by building products that allow individuals to manage their crypto assets at the touch of a finger. Whether you’re in Andorra or Zimbabwe, whether your portfolio is worth one dollar or a million, SwissBorg gives you the best tools to learn about digital currencies and manage your wealth.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to join a team of revolutionaries on a mission to decentralise nations? We want to hear from you!</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 14.6667px">Due to the growth of our business, SwissBorg is offering an opportunity for a CS Agent to join our Community Success team in Lisbon. If you like to help others, seek to understand and are hard working experienced customer service agents speaking German, it’s your chance to join and be part of the new financial era from behind the scenes.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>What you might be doing:<br/><li>Get to know our product and the crypto world if you're not familiar with it yet</li><li>Play around with our app and the Crypto Challenge app to be able to relate to our users with ease&nbsp;</li><li>Offer top notch customer service for our community members in German and English</li><li>Help our users via e-mail or chat thread</li><li>Work based on a 24/7 rotating shift pattern with the flexibility to work from home during night shifts etc. when possible</li><li>Organise your daily work and occasional projects or project based tasks efficiently</li><li>Be a great team player - we’re all in this together; our community is not just our users, it’s all of us</li><li>Report all the important feedback to relevant teams</li><li>Report bugs to relevant channels</li><li>Be ready to get in contact with our users when needed in German and in English (our working languages)</li><br/>What you might bring:<br/><li>Multilingual: Fluency in English and German is a must; French, Spanish or other languages are a bonus</li><li>Working in customer-centric and customer-facing environment</li><li>Listening and reading to fully understand&nbsp;</li><li>Finding the best solution for users concerns and questions</li><li>You are well adaptive in a changing environment (we are developing and improving every day, this means that the way we work also changes)</li><li>You are tolerant and empathic and good at finding win-win solutions</li><li>Organising your time and tasks and being on time</li><li>You are good at thinking outside the box&nbsp;</li><li>You are interested in FinTech and are generally tech savvy</li><li>You are able to take the initiative in improving the processes and systems</li><li>You are able to well evaluate the situation and take best possible decisions in unexpected situations</li><li>Ability to work on multiple tasks independently with minimal supervision</li><li>Good understanding of Blockchain ecosystem is an advantage</li><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Why you should apply: </b></div><div><br></div><div>- Freedom to build the company of your dreams</div><div>- Learn with (super cool) experts in finance, engineering, AI, psychology and business</div><div>- CHSB bonus based on our meritocratic system</div><div>- We'll provide you with a MacBook and a cutting edge tech stack to help you do your best work</div><div>- Flexible work hours</div><div>- Annual team retreats with colleagues around the world</div><div>- Continuous learning and development opportunities</div><div><br></div><div>Oh and are you planning on having a kid? That’s great! We have a bunch of those: you’ll get time off to enjoy that (other) adventure!&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><i>At SwissBorg, we embrace diversity. We strongly believe that getting to the best outcomes requires different perspectives and backgrounds. We’re committed to openness, curiosity and creating an inclusive culture as we know that diverse teams build better products and generate better ideas. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status.</i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/02lonwc5XE4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/swissborg/449a42d8-64fe-4ee1-a22c-282cd9078e2b/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/440178/Swissborg-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[swissborg@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f4703261-2e7b-4b75-af19-fbdfc5e62c02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[QA Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.axiomzen.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>*Please note this role is only open to North America remote work*</div><div><br></div><div>How’d you like to join the team that broke the Ethereum blockchain with cute kitties? Dapper Labs, the creators of CryptoKitties, is at an inflection point in our journey and it might be the perfect time for you to join us. Less than 6 months ago we launched NBA Top Shot on the new Flow blockchain and it is already on track to be the fastest-growing marketplace in history. Over $200 million in sales in the past 30 days and nearly 300k active users driven by organic growth. We're now profitable and ready to invest in building out the ecosystem so everyone can benefit.</div><div><br></div><div>We're looking for a full-time<b> QA Analyst </b>to help us guarantee the excellence of our next generation of blockchain collectible and gaming products for world-renowned brands like the NBA and Dr. Seuss.</div><div><br></div><div>The ideal candidate will have experience building a QA function from the ground up. QA is young at our organization and we're looking for the right person to lead its growth!</div><br/>What you will help us accomplish:<br/><li>You will assist our current QA Analyst in performing manual QA on our NBA Topshot and Dapper products. It will be a feather in your cap if you can help us move towards automation of often repeated tests. The position will see you:</li><li>Analyze our acceptance criteria and software specification to create detailed manual tests plans.</li><li>Work with our product and engineering team to collect criteria to keep the test cases up to date.</li><li>Identify edge cases in our implementation through thorough black box testing.</li><li>Estimate, prioritize, plan and coordinate testing activities between different product teams.</li><li>Find, record, document and track issues.</li><li>Perform manual acceptance and regression testing to verify issue resolution.</li><li>Help us determine how to move towards more automated testing in the future.</li><br/>A little about you:<br/><li>You have 3-5 years (or more) of experience performing manual QA on web and mobile applications.</li><li>You have a strong knowledge of software QA methodologies, tools and processes</li><li>You are capable of applying your skills across a variety of use cases; inflexible specialists need not apply.</li><li>We believe in processes and the power of planning, but you will often&nbsp; have to roll with the punches and prioritize the most impactful tasks on&nbsp; the fly.</li><li>You have a passion for finding bugs and pointing them out to the development teams.</li><li>You are familiar with basic API interactions, writing simple SQL&nbsp; queries and understanding the basics of front-end and back-end web&nbsp; development technologies.</li><li>You have a fundamental understanding and experience in the automation of front and back end applications.</li><li> You will blow us away if you have done work in Javascript UI test automation.</li><li> You will blow us away if you have knowledge of blockchain technologies.</li><div><b>More about Dapper Labs:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Dapper Labs is the world's first blockchain entertainment company. We are the creators of industry-leading experiences including CryptoKitties and NBA Top Shot, as well as Dapper Wallet, the simplest way to manage your assets and use the blockchain. We are also the original developers behind Flow, a new decentralized blockchain designed from the ground up for scalability and ease of use.</div><div><br></div><div>Our mission at Dapper Labs is to make the world a more open, empowering, and enjoyable place through consumer adoption of decentralized technologies. We have raised over $600M from leading VCs including Fred Wilson (USV) and Chris Dixon as well as Venrock, Samsung, Google Ventures, Coatue, NBA players, and global artists, among others. Dapper Labs partners include the NBA and NBPA, the NFL-PA, Ubisoft, Warner Music, Turner, Dr. Seuss, Genies, and the UFC, as well as 100+ others.</div><div><br></div><div>Visit our website to learn even more about Dapper Labs, including <a href="https://www.dapperlabs.com/careers#benefits" class="postings-link">information about benefits and perks</a>.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Vvp75OCtwa0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axiomzen/c943e64d-cc98-4b1b-b4e6-e9259ca3a550/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194192/axiomzen1.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axiomzen@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5da21464-b527-48a0-a501-0b4f2e445537]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Alchemy]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://alchemyapi.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco & New York]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><a href="https://www.alchemy.com/company" class="postings-link">Our mission</a> is to bring blockchain to a billion people. The Alchemy Platform is a world class developer platform designed to make building on the blockchain easy. We've built leading infrastructure in the space, powering over $45 billion in transactions for tens of millions of users in 99% of countries worldwide. </div><div><br></div><div>The Alchemy team draws from decades of deep expertise in massively scalable infrastructure, AI, and blockchain from leadership roles at leading companies and universities like Google, Microsoft, Facebook, Stanford, and MIT. </div><div><br></div><div>Alchemy recently raised a <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/10/28/aws-for-blockchain-alchemy-boost-valuation-to-3-5b-with-250m-raise/" class="postings-link">Series C</a> led by a16z at a $3.5B valuation, having previously raised from Coatue, Addition, Stanford University, Coinbase, the Chairman of Google, Charles Schwab, and the <a href="https://alchemy.com/company#investors" class="postings-link">founders and executives</a> of leading organizations.</div><div><br></div><div>Alchemy powers the top blockchain companies globally and has been featured in <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/04/28/alchemy-raises-80m-at-a-505m-valuation-to-be-the-aws-for-blockchain/" class="postings-link">TechCrunch</a>, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ninabambysheva/2021/06/08/the-future-of-crypto-and-blockchain-fintech-50-2021/?sh=6791bad153b1" class="postings-link">Forbes</a>, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-21/nfts-mushroom-into-billion-dollar-market-with-help-from-alchemy?srnd=premium" class="postings-link">Bloomberg</a>, and <a href="https://www.alchemy.com/newsroom" class="postings-link">elsewhere</a>.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">The Opportunity</b></div><div><br></div><div>As a Product Specialist at Alchemy, you will be pushing the entire blockchain industry forward by helping developers and companies accelerate their product development. You will use your first-hand knowledge and work closely with Alchemy's customers to ensure a great user experience to help them maximize the value they get from the platform. You will collect product feedback, share learnings with the entire team, and help inform our roadmap .</div><div><br></div><div>In a nutshell, this role is meant for someone with a technical background who is looking to work with multiple sides of the business, with the main focus on understanding customer needs and shaping feedback into product decisions.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Interact with customers to solve their needs</li><li>Be the front line for customers</li><li>Collect and organize product feedback across our entire customer base</li><li>Be the voice of the customers</li><li>Perform analysis reports on qualitative and quantitative data + present to team</li><li>Inform product strategy and roadmap prioritization based on customer feedback</li><li>Make informed suggestions to create a stellar customer experience</li><li>Understand customer needs and how to meet unique challenges and goals</li><li>Work cross-functionally to drive long term solutions / product development decisions</li><br/>What we're looking for<br/><li>Knowledge and passion for the crypto/blockchain industry</li><li>A technical or educational background in engineering, computer science, or MIS</li><li>Self-starter attitude and the ability to execute new ideas with autonomy</li><li>Excellent listening, verbal and written communication skills</li><li>Capable of understanding of customer pain points, requirements and correlating potential business to value that can be provided by technical services</li><li>Experience managing numerous requests and time demands concurrently</li><li>Be able to work in a quickly changing environment</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/alchemy/88b57af2-b0b5-448b-9e63-01bff7f7d632/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637333/alchemy-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alchemy@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[2216d58c-1ece-4465-a4f9-6c8eafa52f36]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Alchemy]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Engineering Manager II - Design Systems]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As one of the largest and most trusted </span><b style="font-size: 11pt">digital asset platforms</b><span style="font-size: 11pt"> globally, we are empowering people to experience the life-changing potential of crypto.&nbsp;Trusted by over 8 million consumer and pro traders, institutions, and authorities worldwide - our unique combination of products, services, and global expertise is helping tip the scales towards mass crypto adoption.&nbsp;But we’re only just getting started. We want to be pioneers in crypto and add value to the everyday lives of billions. Now is not the time to sit on the sidelines. Join us to bring crypto to the world.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">About the Role</b></div><div><br></div><div>We’re looking for an engineering manager to lead a squad of engineers chartered with developing Kraken’s next-generation Design System that will power our Mobile and Web platforms. You will be partnering closely with design to translate a design language into tangible code that empowers engineers to ship beautiful industry-leading UI faster and with greater confidence. This role will require an individual who is comfortable being a player-coach — capable of both crafting a strong technical vision and strategy as well as providing day-to-day coaching and career guidance to your reports. In addition to the UI libraries, you will be responsible for developing the tooling, processes, and automation infrastructure that enables a high bar for quality and reliability. Finally, you will influence and execute a strategy to drive adoption of the Design System across the entire engineering org through close collaboration with Product, Design and Engineering leaders.</div><br/>Basic Qualifications<br/><li>6+ years of full-time professional engineering experience</li><li>2+ years of experience building and running highly effective software engineering teams</li><li>2+ years of experience planning Software Engineers' careers, coaching them to promotion</li><li>Deep knowledge of software development and delivery best practices, you know when a team isn’t moving fast enough and you know how to fix it</li><li>Experience hiring talented engineers, you have a clear understanding of what it takes to be an excellent Software Engineer</li><li>Clear passion for software engineering, design, and Crypto</li><div><br></div><br/>Preferred Qualifications<br/><li>8+ years of full-time engineering experience within a large technology organization or fast growing startup</li><li>4+ years of experience building and running highly effective software engineering teams within a large technology organization or from the ground up at a fast growing startup</li><li>Proven track record partnering with Design &amp; Product stakeholders, preferably on Design Systems</li><li>Experience working with design systems and/or UI libraries at scale</li><li>Familiarity with accessibility principles and inclusive design best practices</li><li>Understands the importance of aligning code to design and the impact it has on quality assurance</li><li>Has had success in independently driving adoption of innovations across large organizations</li><li>Deep knowledge of HTML, CSS, TypeScript, React (or React Native)</li><li>Understanding of scalable JavaScript architecture patterns and client side systems design</li><div>Location Tagging: #EU #US #LI-LM1</div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/2d7a653c-015e-41e2-b96f-e7cb55e4e7a9/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Associate Manager, Customer Experience]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berlin, Germany]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re Coinbase. We’re the world’s most trusted way to join the crypto revolution, serving more than 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/our-mission-strategy-and-culture-18a92a3bb0fa&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web 3.0 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture. We’re a remote-first company looking to hire the absolute best talent all over the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve got positive energy. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This role requires the successful individual to &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;relocate&lt;/span&gt; to Ireland or the UK. A relocation package will be offered.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a CX Retail Operations Associate Manager,&amp;nbsp; you will lead a team of highly motivated customer support professionals whose performance is critical to Coinbase achieving its mission. Using your customer support, operations and team management skills you will play a crucial role ensuring we deliver an outstanding customer experience globally.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Support domains vary across areas such as account, payment and crypto operations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage team of FTE Agents:&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Schedule and attend agent 1:1s&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Schedule and lead team meetings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Approve agent payroll timecards&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Approve agent holiday requests&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage agent adherence to weekly schedule, and ad hoc requests/leave etc&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Check-in against agent targets, and handle performance improvement plans as the need arises&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Schedule and lead career development sessions (quarterly)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Complete and deliver performance reviews (biannually)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage business related tasks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor team weekly metric run rate and deep dive into outliers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Update various trackers and report on pillar metrics in relevant meetings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attend wider team/org meetings&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attend Coinbase wide meetings/Office Hours as the need arises&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Manage personal projects:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attend 1:1s with manager&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attend project meetings/stand ups/deep dives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Update career development plan and attend career development sessions with manager (quarterly)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Project work - Deliver on specific project deliverables and identify team SMEs to take on project related tasks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we look for in you (ie. job requirements):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passionate People Leader&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong metrics driven management experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable working with ambiguity / self starter&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fluent German speaker is essential&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Salesforce experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Crypto knowledge / experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Analytical mindset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*This role requires the successful individual to &lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;relocate&lt;/span&gt; to Ireland or the UK. A relocation package will be offered.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ID: P33171&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please note that for employees based in the US, Philippines, Canada or Singapore, if your role requires you to be present in a Coinbase office or if you choose to be physically present in a Coinbase office or sponsored location, participate in any in-person gathering (including offsites) or engage in business travel sponsored by Coinbase, you will be required to be fully vaccinated (as defined by applicable law).&amp;nbsp; If you receive an offer, you will receive additional information about the grounds and process for an exemption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations[at]coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3876229?gh_jid=3876229&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Marketing Lead (NFL ALL DAY)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.axiomzen.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote or Vancouver, BC]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>NBA Top Shot caught lightning in a bottle, bringing in over one million users to the blockchain in a matter of months. We’re looking for a Product Marketing Lead to take our growth trajectory to the next level.&nbsp;We're looking for an experienced product marketer who can bring a data-driven approach to support the Product team with new feature launches, liveops events, ongoing user growth, and who can test and optimize USPs, user flows, and conversion from a Marketing perspective. The ideal candidate has grit and a test-and-learn approach to their process.</div><div><br></div><div>Location: Remote OK, traveling to Vancouver when needed</div><br/>Jobs to be done:<br/><li>Optimizes FTUE working collaboratively with UX, Product, and Data teams.</li><li>Creates strategies and initiatives that support business objectives for Growth.</li><li>Works with Channel owners to create best-in-class campaigns that hit every type of audience ALL DAY is meant for.</li><li>Aggressively finds new opportunities and edges to increase product adoption and sustainable success.</li><li>Validates hypotheses for USPs, offerings, and liveops events.</li><div><b>More about Dapper Labs:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Dapper Labs is the world's first blockchain entertainment company. We are the creators of industry-leading experiences including CryptoKitties and NBA Top Shot, as well as Dapper Wallet, the simplest way to manage your assets and use the blockchain. We are also the original developers behind Flow, a new decentralized blockchain designed from the ground up for scalability and ease of use.</div><div><br></div><div>Our mission at Dapper Labs is to make the world a more open, empowering, and enjoyable place through consumer adoption of decentralized technologies. We have raised over $600M from leading VCs including Fred Wilson (USV) and Chris Dixon as well as Venrock, Samsung, Google Ventures, Coatue, NBA players, and global artists, among others. Dapper Labs partners include the NBA and NBPA, the NFL-PA, Ubisoft, Warner Music, Turner, Dr. Seuss, Genies, and the UFC, as well as 100+ others.</div><div><br></div><div>Visit our website to learn even more about Dapper Labs, including <a href="https://www.dapperlabs.com/careers#benefits" class="postings-link">information about benefits and perks</a>.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Vvp75OCtwa0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/axiomzen/2275955f-834f-4845-b8c6-34262e0e1a64/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194192/axiomzen1.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[axiomzen@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5da21464-b527-48a0-a501-0b4f2e445537]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[AxiomZen]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Compliance Model Design and Validation Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Circle]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.circle.com/de/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Boston - will also consider remote in US]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Circle is a global financial technology firm that enables businesses of all sizes to harness the power of digital currency and public blockchains for payments, commerce and financial applications worldwide. Circle platforms and products provide a suite of internet-native financial services for payments, treasury infrastructure and capital formation. Circle is also a principal developer of USD Coin (USDC), which has become the fastest growing dollar digital currency in the world. USDC has grown to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;over 47 billion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in circulation and supported over&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; $1.6 trillion&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in transactions in the past year. Circle’s payments and treasury infrastructure services available through the Circle Account and APIs helps bridge the legacy financial system and digital currency and blockchain based finance.&amp;nbsp; Circle’s SeedInvest service brings internet-native fundraising and capital formation to startups and growth companies.&amp;nbsp; Combined, Circle’s suite of services helps companies to participate in a more open, global and inclusive financial system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be part of:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;With the mission “To raise global economic prosperity through the frictionless exchange of financial value,” Circle was founded on the belief that the internet, blockchains and digital currency will rewire the global economic system, creating a fundamentally more open, inclusive, efficient and integrated world economy.&amp;nbsp; We envision a global economy where people and businesses everywhere can more freely connect and transact with each other with new technologies for digital money and internet-native finance. We believe such a system can raise prosperity for people and companies everywhere. Our mission is powered by the values we espouse and which we expect all Circlers to respect. We are Multistakeholder, serving the needs of our customers, our shareholders, our employees and families, our local communities and our world. Furthermore, we are also Mindful, Driven by Excellence, and High Integrity.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be responsible for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Circle is looking for an experienced Financial Crime Compliance Model Design and Validation expert to help us build out a new global compliance function. This is a critical new role and you will be empowered to design and build the best in class controls to support the Global Compliance Program in delivering exceptional results. This will be achieved through ensuring the integrity of the data used on a day-to day-basis, developing program insights and analytics tools and tuning models to support compliance officers in making informed decisions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll work on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Compliance Program leadership and cross-functional teams to set strategy and develop the Compliance Model Design and Validation program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and maintain an effective model management program that meets regulatory requirements.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create detailed plans with Compliance Program team and Product &amp;amp; Risk Analytics team to facilitate the technology controls design conversations for AML, Sanctions and KYC controls&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Compliance engineering teams to oversee the implementation of transaction monitoring rules within various AML monitoring and OFAC/sanctions screening technology and analytics solutions systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Architect the strategy for enhancing and automating compliance reporting solutions, including data collection, aggregation, governance, and reporting.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ensure appropriate documentation is in place for all technical aspects of the Compliance program, which can be reviewed by regulators and external examiners; Including AML transaction monitoring rules, sanctions screening systems, and risk scoring models as well as detailing data lineage and model/rule assumptions and parameters for all models&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Use continuous improvement techniques to drive maturity and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;drive automation and process efficiency gains&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform analysis of structured and unstructured data to solve complex business and department problems utilizing advanced statistical techniques and analysis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You will aspire to our four core values:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Multistakeholder - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you have dedication and commitment to our customers, shareholders, employees and families and local communities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mindful - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek to be respectful, an active listener and to pay attention to detail.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Driven by Excellence - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you are driven by our mission and our passion for customer success which means you relentlessly pursue excellence, that you do not tolerate mediocrity and you work intensely to achieve your goals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;High Integrity - &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;you seek open and honest communication, and you hold yourself to very high moral and ethical standards.&amp;nbsp; You reject manipulation, dishonesty and intolerance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you&#39;ll bring to Circle:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BS/BA in Information Science, Computer Science, Engineering or relevant field.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;7+ &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;years of data management and analytics experience in either banking, consulting, or cryptocurrency. Experience at RegTech or FinTech companies preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with programming for data analysis; ideally Python, SQL, or R.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working hands-on with other cross-functional team leaders, such as lawyers, engineers, product managers, data scientists and operations teams in improving compliance processes and systems.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven experience preparing model documentation to support compliance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience and comfort working in an ever-changing industry and the flexibility to quickly react to changing demands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with the application of external AML and sanctions software, including LexisNexis Bridger. Experience with on-chain transaction monitoring solutions preferred.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency in Google Suite, Slack and Apple MacOS preferred. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;equal opportunity employer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and value diversity at Circle. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h6 style=&quot;text-align: right;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h6&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/KEvenCaIq70" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/circle/jobs/5866053002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143132/circle.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[circle@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[e4722b14-c590-4410-b876-45bc581c49c8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Circle]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Team Lead Front-End - Ledger Live]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ledger]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ledger.fr/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Founded in 2014, Ledger is a leader in security and infrastructure solutions for cryptocurrencies and blockchain applications. Headquartered in Paris, Vierzon and London, Ledger has a team of 500+ professionals developing a variety of products and services to safeguard cryptocurrency assets for individuals and companies – including the Ledger hardware wallets line already sold in 180 countries.</div><div><br></div><div>Ledger Live is an application to manage all your blockchain-backed assets. It’s built in React.js (Electron on Desktop and React Native on mobile) and supports multiple blockchains (coins &amp; NFTs) as well as provides multiple services by integrating DApps and offering a SDK for 3rd parties to integrate. Finally, all this is backed by our hardware wallets which Ledger Live allows you to manage.</div><div><br></div><div>To sustain the company's growth, Ledger is looking for a new talent,&nbsp;to work on Engineering team management, evolution &amp; performance.&nbsp;</div><div>Reporting directly to the Ledger Live Engineering Manager, you will be responsible for a team of engineers to build an entire part of the Ledger Live software.</div><br/>Missions<br/><li><b>Management</b></li><div>- Lead your team of engineers and be the link with other teams</div><div>- Focused on and responsible for the team's productivity and collective impact</div><div>- Drives recruitment, performance assessments, training, and career development</div><div>- Helps individuals set goals and works to ensure employee growth and retention goals</div><div>- Drives a constant improvement to team practices</div><div><br></div><li><b>Tech</b></li><div>- Developed in React.js professionally and is able to drive a project from end-to-end</div><div>- Well versed in engineering best practices (e.g. reviews, pair programming, branching strategy, tests)</div><div>- Understands and practices scrum software development and management</div><div>- Actively participates in the sprint delivery</div><div>- Accounts for quality, performance and security into deliverables</div><div>- Responsibility for the team's tech monitoring</div><div>- Consistently comes up with innovative solutions and elicits innovative thinking from others</div><div>- Team lead to ensure technical alignment with company</div><div><br></div><li><b>Delivery</b></li><div>- Scales themselves by delegating effectively; ensures tasks are completed as specified without micromanaging</div><div>- Involved in planning</div><div>- Manage clear expectations of the team's delivery and communicate changes in a timely way</div><div>- Leverage process to ensure the team is predictable</div><div>- Ensure practices are followed to meet acceptance criteria and Ledger’s quality bar</div><div>- Protect team processes to maintain sustainability and team moral</div><div><br></div><li><b>Leadership &amp; Communication</b></li><div>- Positive “can do” attitude and role model for others</div><div>- Communicates the vision helping making it a reality</div><div>- Actively learning how to handle difficult management situations</div><div>- Meets regularly with their direct reports to provide frequent feedback on their work</div><div>- Tracking and Communicating progress/risk/issues to stakeholders</div><br/>Knowledge & Experience<br/><li>2+ years of experience in managing software teams</li><li>Strong experience in React.js development, tools and libraries</li><li>B.S. Computer Science degree, or equivalent professional experience</li><li>You love developing and growing people</li><li>Good knowledge of React Native</li><li>Knowledge of UI/UX practices in software development</li><li>Team player with excellent interpersonal skills and ability to work cross-functionally</li><li>Enthusiast about hiring new talent and building a team</li><li>Excellent presentation and written communication</li><li>Passionate about blockchains and interested in cryptocurrencies is a plus</li><br/>Benefits<br/><li>Competitive compensation package and ESOP according to the Company policy</li><li>Flexible working hours, remote-friendly environment</li><li>Strong focus on personal development including internal/external trainings and attendance to conferences</li><li>Internal talks, technical meetups and hackathons</li><li>High performance office equipment</li><li>Comprehensive health insurance policy offering extensive medical, dental and vision care coverage</li><li>Annual company outing for Ledgerdary Days plus infrequent parties, snacks and drinks</li><div><i><b style="font-size: 16px">Ledger guarantees equal opportunity for all during the recruitment process, without any distinction of gender, ethnicity, religion, sexual orientation, social status, disability or age.</b></i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/5Ss7xnFP9AM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/ledger/ee740043-4d66-4ffe-871c-4d0547b7582a/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/142943/ledger.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ledger@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[83f3aace-4751-47ca-bbcd-26157dd3bc4a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ledger]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Developer , Finance Digital Transformation - Global Fintech startup]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Crypto.com</strong></p><p>Crypto.com was founded in 2016 on a simple belief: it's a basic human right for everyone to control their money, data and identity. With over 10+ million users on its platform today, Crypto.com provides a powerful alternative to traditional financial services, turning its vision of "cryptocurrency in every wallet" into reality, one customer at a time. Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level compliance. Crypto.com is headquartered in Singapore with a 3000+ strong team. For more information, please visit www.crypto.com.</p><p><strong>Responsibilities</strong></p><ul> <li>Provide technical leadership and expertise for architecting new scalable data platform</li> <li>Design &amp; Develop batch and streaming solutions using various technologies</li> <li>Responsible for evaluating technologies and approaches for ingestion, transformation and storage</li> <li>Mentor engineers on data architecture and promote best practices</li> </ul><ul> <li>Experience with application containerization (Docker / Kubernetes / AWS ECS or EKS)</li> <li>Experience with CI/CD in particular with AWS managed services: CodeCommit, CodeBuild, CodeDeploy, CodePipeline and CodeArtifact.</li> <li>Experience with ETL processing in a cloud environment (nice to have would be AWS Glue and Athena experience). Important here would be Python experience with Pandas libraries. Also nice would be PySpark.</li> <li>Cloud storage in particular AWS S3. Knowledge about storage formats such as Parquet and JSON. Schema specifications languages like Avro would be good also.</li> <li>Streaming and integration technologies such as Apache Kafka or AWS Kinesis</li> <li>Security experience with AWS IAM</li> <li>Airflow or Amazon Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow (MWAA), experience would also be good.</li> </ul><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing brand new products from scratch using latest technologies alongside with a passionate and talented team</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/B25AD4B9E7/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxful]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://paxful.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, New York, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Paxful&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxful is the people-powered marketplace for money transfers with anyone, anywhere, at any time. Imagine a world where everyone has equal access to finance, no matter who they are, or where they’re from. We&#39;re building it. Our mission is to empower the forgotten four billion unbanked, so they have control of their money in a way they&#39;ve never had before.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working across three offices in different time zones, the Paxful team serves our amazing community of 4 million strong. We build for people, not profits, and consider ourselves to be everyday heroes who don’t wear capes or masks. That’s why we launched Built with Bitcoin, a charitable initiative that aims to build 100 schools, water facilities, and entrepreneurial incubators in emerging markets all over the world. We want to show that bitcoin can have a positive impact and make real changes in the lives of people everywhere.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paxful is looking for a Senior Data Analyst who will be responsible for promoting &amp;amp; growing the Analytics footprint at Paxful. They must be proficient at the tool/technology level (developing, maintaining, and improving databases, dashboards and other business intelligence and visualization systems). They must be able to work with Business stakeholders to promote the benefit of the platform and try to solve business problems. This position will also be responsible for helping to teach, train, and help grow the skill set of BI developers/Junior Analyst in the team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a key member of our team, your responsibilities will entail:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide innovative analytical insights to Internal/external stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Conduct detailed data analysis on data used across business units to evaluate business processes and improve on/create new feature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Respond to data and product related inquiries in real-time to support business and technical teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform various data analytics in SQL , python , R and MS Excel using statistical models or industry accepted tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide relational database expertise to construct and execute SQL queries to be used in data analysis activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide data solutions, tools, and capabilities to enable self-service frameworks for data consumers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide expertise and translate the business needs to design; and develop tools, techniques, and metrics, and dashboards for insights and data visualization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Responsible for developing and executing tools to monitor and report on data quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Responsible for establishing appreciation and adherence to the principles of data quality management, including metadata, lineage, and business definitions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desired Skills &amp;amp; Qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering, Math, Statistics or other quantitative field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong data management skills including Excel, SQL, R, SAS or other Statistical Packages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years of experience in BI tools like (Tableau, superset,power BI etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Exceptional analytical, quantitative, problem-solving, and critical thinking skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understanding of Big data and related technologies (Redshift, clickhouse) is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in Product, FinTech or Crypto etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, both written and verbal, with people at all levels of an organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Comfort working with stakeholders across different time zones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great relationship building qualities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to manage multiple tasks while working independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A strong sense of urgency and commitment to get the job done quickly and with high quality&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive insurance plans, commuter benefits, flexible spending account, and 401(k) with 4% company matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible working hours and generous paid time off&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Gym membership, massage, chiropractor, or other reimbursements (personal training, dance classes, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Learning and development reimbursement (including online courses, certifications, conferences, seminars, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;One day a year to volunteer and serve your community&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Parental leave, including a one-time bonus to support a newborn, adoption, or foster placement&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxful&#39;s COVID response: remote work, company-wide online events and weekly meal credits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Diversity &amp;amp; Inclusion at Paxful&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Paxful, we know that a diverse workforce fuels our individual and collective success. We encourage applicants of different backgrounds, cultures, genders, experiences, abilities and perspectives to apply. We are actively working to increase the diversity of experience and perspectives on our team and are looking for someone who can help continue to lead that process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EEOC and&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Accommodations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxful is committed to diversity in the workplace and we’re proud to be an equal opportunity employer. We do not hire on basis of race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, marital status, pregnancy, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation, citizenship, or any other basis protected by local, state or federal law.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re also committed to providing accommodations to people with disabilities. If you need any kind of accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, you can reach out to careers@paxful.com and let us know how we can best help you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other privacy laws may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full Privacy Notice is available at https://paxful.com/privacy-notice. By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/JvYoQb4qyg4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/paxful/jobs/4858125003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/353334/paxful-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxful@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[0cd1eea2-97ef-4cc0-9d15-01fa1a8ce9ca]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxful]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Principal Applied Scientist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;Ripple’s mission is to enable payments every way, everywhere for everyone. We believe connecting traditional financial entities like banks, payment providers and corporations with emerging blockchain technologies and users is the path to an open, decentralized, and more inclusive financial future. This Internet of Value gives any internet-enabled person, application or device access to financial services that are transparent, fast, reliable, and cheap. Delivering this vision is a challenge of massive scale spanning $155 trillion in annual cross border fiat payments and the $1.5 trillion market of digital assets that has grown 10X in the last year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a principal scientist to join a growing team charged with determining and delivering optimal liquidity for every customer in the world in a cost-effective, robust and scalable manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU’LL DO&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subject matter expert on models for supply and demand of liquidity&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide technical expertise on models for inventing forecasting, planning, routing, risk management, and experimentation to scalably and reliable deliver best-in-class liquidity to our customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor team and advocate for best practices (technical implementation, design, modeling expertise)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be an entrepreneurial leader, managing the roadmap, requirements and deliverables, while partnering closely with machine learning and software engineering teams. Initially, you will spend up to a quarter of your time as a contributor as we grow out your team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lead the vision for creating models to improve and automate frontend and backend services to constantly improve our customers experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mentor and guide the professional and technical development of your team members. Help develop their careers and assign them to projects tailored to their skill levels, personalities, work styles, and professional goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Instill a spirit of continuous improvement in the team’s inventions and processes so we can rapidly deliver innovations for customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE’RE LOOKING FOR&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in computer science or other quantitative field; masters or PhD preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10+ years applied science experience, 5+ years in lead/manager role preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Broad machine learning experience including statistical modeling, time series analysis/forecasting and experimentation, bonus if in finance and trading domains, especially FX&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Python or Java, and machine learning frameworks like scikit-learn, TensorFlow, or PyTorch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills, demonstrated through experience working with technical and non-technical teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Track record of recruiting and mentoring a team of world-class scientists&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice &lt;/a&gt;and our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/ca-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;California Applicant Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; for reference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3880752?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Mining Loan Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://blockfi.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi’s mission is to provide liquidity, transparency and efficiency to digital financial markets by creating products that meet the needs of consumers and corporations across the globe. We build bridges between traditional finance and digital markets that enable growth for all participants.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re a team of builders and strivers, proud to champion financial inclusivity and offer economic opportunities around the globe. We provide the same inclusivity to our team members. BlockFi is a place where diversity is celebrated, individuality is recognized, and every single team member is valued. We are changing the status quo to be the first financial company that people love, and we rely on our people to make it happen!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is looking for a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mining Loan Associate&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to join our growing team!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Your Team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mining Loan Associate within the Principal Credit &amp;amp; Crypto Team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with Sales to screen potential opportunities and write call reports for management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Structure loan transaction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Model financials&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Assess risk/return&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create term sheets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Negotiate covenants and credit agreements&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate with other stakeholders in the organization and provide information required to complete their processes&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage loan closings&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enhance and execute portfolio monitoring processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Perform market and competitor research&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create presentations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Expertise&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Two or more years of experience in fundamental credit analysis, either on the sell or buy side&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Hands on experience negotiating credit agreements, preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Some familiarity and aptitude with Crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Undergraduate degree required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Perks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We benefit from the great work our employees do each day. That is why we are committed to providing a variety of awesome benefits to help them live their best lives.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive salary &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because we value your experience and expertise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Unlimited vacation / sick days &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because everyone deserves time for R&amp;amp;R&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Employer&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;contribution towards health coverage &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(including vision &amp;amp; dental) because your physical health and well-being is important to us&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Various fringe benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; such as 401k, Parental Leave, FSA/HSA, and Employee Assistance Programs because health coverage is more than just choosing your yearly plan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexible work environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; because we are a geographically dispersed team and we believe in balance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Pet insurance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; because all of your beloved family members should have coverage too&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weekly lunch stipend &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;because there is such a thing as a free lunch!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A close-knit team &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;of enthusiastic, collegial and driven people to work alongside in a highly meritocratic environment because teamwork makes the dreamwork&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why BlockFi?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi has experienced incredible growth since our launch in August 2017. Our client base has grown to more than 225,000 (and counting), and the company now boasts more than $15 billion in assets on our platform. We recently completed a Series D funding round placing the company&#39;s valuation at $3 billion, and our team now has more than 500 people worldwide. We have established ourselves as a crypto market leader, and as we expand our product suite and geographic footprint, we expect our addressable market to grow exponentially.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi&#39;s leadership team has decades of experience in the traditional financial services and banking world, and we take a conservative approach to regulation that will position us well for sustainable long-term growth and expansion.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team is comprised of highly motivated professionals from diverse backgrounds. We are aiming to become the leading lender in crypto and are poised to redefine the global financial ecosystem for the better. In addition:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BlockFi is one of the first companies to ever offer crypto-backed loans and the only company whose founding team has an institutional understanding of the debt capital markets and regulatory landscape in the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$100 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series A, B, and C funding led by Valar Ventures with participation from Susquehanna, Winklevoss Capital, Fidelity, Galaxy Digital, Akuna Capital, and Morgan Creek&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$350 MM&lt;/strong&gt; of Series D funding led by Bain Capital Ventures, partners of DST Global, Pomp Investments and Tiger Global&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are moving quickly and have already deployed substantial capital into the space, proving our ability to execute and capture customer demand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For information about how we&amp;nbsp;collect, use, or otherwise handle your Personal Information, please see our&amp;nbsp;&lt;a class=&quot;c-link&quot; href=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot; data-stringify-link=&quot;https://blockfi.com/privacy&quot; data-sk=&quot;tooltip_parent&quot;&gt;Privacy&amp;nbsp;Policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/o92zit2jRO0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/blockfi/jobs/5861433002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/553492/blockfi-logo-512x512.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[blockfi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7eefa976-25ba-4497-9343-24e88aecb41f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BlockFi]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[ADDX]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://addx.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>Who are we?</b></div><div>Here at ADDX, we believe in a future where everybody can access financial ecosystems easily, fairly, and safely. That is why we’ve built the world’s first fully regulated platform for digital securities, licensed by the Monetary Authority of Singapore.</div><div><br></div><div>In 2021, we raised USD 50 million in Series A funding led by Japan Investment Corporation and Development Bank of Japan. Among other esteemed investors, we are backed by Singapore Exchange and Heliconia, a subsidiary of Temasek.</div><div><br></div><div>We have gone through a total re-brand and promise this to be an exciting time. An integral part of a fast-growing team enabling investments in unicorns, pre-IPO companies, and hedge funds, your role is to innovate and discover new solutions.</div><div><br></div><div>If you believe in a future of fair financial markets, just like we do, we’ve been waiting for you at ADDX.</div><div><br></div><div><b>Who are we looking for?</b></div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a Product Manager to&nbsp;join our dynamic&nbsp;Product team. By liaising with the other Product Managers, Engineers, Designers and business stakeholders you will support the team in defining, managing and executing the Product roadmap.</div><div>&nbsp;</div><div>You will&nbsp;play&nbsp;a key role in driving&nbsp;the development of our client-facing portals taking it from its current state into a high performing user-centric experience; based on user feedback. You will work alongside all stakeholders to identify new opportunities, areas of improvement and address issues as they arise to define the best user experience for our users.&nbsp;</div><div>&nbsp;</div><div>To be successful in this role, you&nbsp;must&nbsp;be hands-on, open-minded&nbsp;and&nbsp;be&nbsp;able to turn ideas into value-adding features.&nbsp;You should have a&nbsp;good&nbsp;understanding about user experience and you need to be able to think outside of the box and find alternative solutions to traditional processes.&nbsp;You have a proven ability to solve problems and you have an interest in continuous learning and doing research into different financial products and processes.&nbsp;</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Support the Product team in the execution of the Product roadmap and build consensus on prioritization of new features alongside</li><li>Take ownership of product features relating to our users</li><li>Understand user needs and gather product requirements</li><li>Build alignment across product teams and cross-functional stakeholders (Sales, Marketing, Operations)</li><li>Goal setting, spec writing, technical requirements, managing project execution</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>1-2 years of Product Management experience building user-facing apps&nbsp;</li><li>Ability to quickly absorb technical concepts and communicate them to a non-technical audience</li><li>Entrepreneurial drive and demonstrated ability to achieve goals in an innovative and fast-paced environment</li><li>Strong interpersonal skills; your team members proactively seeks your input and guidance</li><li>Excellent presentation, verbal and written communication skills</li><br/>Bonus<br/><li>Previous experience with fintech, crypto or trading products</li><div>Due to our limited capacity, we regret that only shortlisted candidates will be notified. </div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/7ErT7T4wgYI" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/addx/215ec79a-ddf5-4086-9298-3fe65dd14de1/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/413784/addx-istox-logo.jpeg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[addx@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b82fa9b1-c059-434f-82d6-6cb949f49699]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[ADDX]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Lead DevOps]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Delta]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://delta.app/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Ghent, Flanders, Belgium]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>We're looking for a talented and experienced <strong>lead DevOps'er</strong> to join the Delta team!</p><p>You will be working on building, maintaining, and scaling the infrastructure powering our Delta platform. Our applications run on Docker containers in either ECS or k8s. Data is persisted on MySQL and derived data is stored in Redis, depending on the use case. Using Github Actions &amp; CircleCI, our code gets tested, formatted and scanned for security issues before it gets deployed to production, which can happen multiple times per day. All this lives in the AWS cloud, leveraging infrastructure as code using Terraform. In short, you'll be responsible for the infrastructure powering the Delta apps, <strong>serving massive amounts of users</strong>. The full requirements are listed in full below.</p><p>You'll be working remotely or in our office in Ghent, Belgium. We're located right in the city center in a gorgeous historic building, which is pretty cool. Psst... no worries if you can't speak Dutch, we're used to communicating in English.<br></p><p>You'll be part of a start-up which is part of a big company (eToro). Which means you'll be working within the Delta start-up mentality, surrounded by lots of experience and the empowering structure of a bigger entity. Win-win!</p><p>What else? Delta is aiming to be one of the household names in fintech, so you'll be growing an app that is already <strong>used today by millions of dedicated investors</strong>, every day. We get lots of feedback and even more love from our users, which is really motivating and makes everybody here even more driven to keep adding value. Recently we’ve launched a full-fledged investment tracker that allows investors to keep tabs on their stocks, indices and even funds. Our main goal is to become one of the best and most-used platforms and a household name in the fintech space. If you're up for that challenge, you'll fit right in.</p><p>Career:</p><ul> <li>BS (or higher, e.g. MS or PhD) in Computer Science or equivalent technical experience</li> <li>Ability to diagnose technical problems, debug code and automate routine tasks</li> <li>Analytical approach coupled with solid communication skills and a sense of ownership</li> </ul><p>Good knowledge of and/or experience with:</p><ul> <li>NodeJS, MySQL, Redis</li> <li>AWS platform, Linux</li> <li>Github Actions, Terraform, Kubernetes</li> </ul><p>Other non-required pluses:</p><ul> <li>Python</li> <li>Vault</li> <li>TimescaleDB, PostgreSQL</li> <li>Blockchain development</li> </ul><p>Well, we already mentioned the exquisite office in the city centre of Ghent. We'll always make sure everybody in the team is compensated like they should be. On top of that competitive salary, we offer the following extra benefits:</p><ul> <li>Laptop &amp; phone*</li> <li>Fully paid phone subscription*</li> <li>Healthcare benefits plan (DKV)*</li> <li>Meal vouchers*</li> <li>Some slick Delta swag</li> <li>Soft-drinks, coffee, water, all to your hearts content!*</li> <li>Team drinks and events</li> </ul><p><em>*Only applicable to team members who work from Ghent on our payroll</em></p><p>More info about how awesome it is to work at Delta, <a href="https://jobs.delta.app/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">please check out our company page</a>!</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/joindelta/j/8C59721377/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/548875/delta-logo-400x400.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[delta@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9ad75421-50ad-41fc-b2ee-63671ba64f0a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Delta]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sr. Data Scientist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Solana]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://solana.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco CA, Chicago IL, NYC, or United States-Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re looking for an experienced and entrepreneurial Data Lead to help lead efforts to define our ecosystem, partnership and business success metrics, and build the goals and dashboard that help us scale. This individual will be the first data hire at Solana Labs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What You’ll Be Doing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working with leadership to define the right metrics to measure the success of our ecosystem and the business&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Determine the most important metrics to gauge partnership success and make the right decisions on where to deploy time and resources&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help drive the goal-setting strategy, build dashboards and reporting systems for enhanced insight into our operations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Act as a strategic thought partner across the company on how to use data effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build strong relationships with our ecosystem data products and companies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Scale our insights through improving systems and automating where possible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design communication structure and cadence with team members; synthesize data takeaways (success or failures) into compelling narratives and communicate them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with data engineering team to build data stack and data pipelines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What We Are Looking For&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of experience in fast-paced environments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in Python, R, SQL, NoSQL and BigQuery (or any other Big data/Cloud equivalent)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Efficiency in pulling data from disparate sources: (no)SQL, graphs, and basic parsing of dirty data&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Background and experience with statistical analysis.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with data visualization tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in dashboards, goal-setting, storytelling and executive presentations.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong cross-functional skills and ability to operate under ambiguous and fast moving problem spaces.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A passion for, and understanding of, blockchain technologies and applications. (Prior experience in crypto data is preferred, but not required)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Potential to grow into a leadership position as the team expands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent ability to communicate complicated and nuanced insights in accessible language to relevant stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Relevant degrees (not required) include Computer Science, Data Science, Statistics, Finance, Mathematics or similar field&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/7UE5UFd-b2c" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/solana/jobs/4321224004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/195920/solana.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[solana@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[e4e1a69e-be02-4e13-be37-5d03fb7d383f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Solana]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Data Engineer - Web Scraper]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[CertiK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://certik.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York / Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt"><b>About the Company</b></span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Founded in 2018 by professors of Yale University and Columbia University, CertiK is a pioneer in blockchain security, utilizing best-in-class AI technology to secure and monitor blockchain protocols and smart contracts. CertiK’s mission is to secure the cyber world. Starting with blockchain, CertiK applies cutting-edge innovations from academia into enterprise, enabling mission-critical applications to be built with security and correctness.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">CertiK is one of the fastest growing and most trusted companies in blockchain security and has become a true market leader. To date, we have collectively worked with over 1800 enterprise clients, helped secure over $90 billion worth of digital assets, and detected over 31,000 vulnerabilities in blockchain code. Our clients include leading projects such as Aave, Polygon, Binance Smart Chain, Terra, Yearn, and Chiliz. Our Q1 2021 revenues have more than quadrupled the revenue of the full 2020 year. Since Q1 2020, our team size has more than doubled, and this rate of growth will continue in 2021, creating a highly effective, remote-friendly culture with talents located worldwide.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">CertiK just raised over $140 million in Series B, B+, and B2 funding rounds over four months in 2021, putting the company close to unicorn status at nearly $1 Billion in valuation. Our investors include top VCs like Sequoia, Tiger Global, Coatue Management, Shunwei Capital and Hillhouse Capital as well as industry leaders like Coinbase Ventures and Binance.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt"><b>About the Role</b></span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As a Web Scraping focused Data Engineer, you will be responsible for extracting and ingesting data from websites using web crawling tools, and building and maintaining infrastructure to support those tools.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">In this role you will own the creation process of these tools, services, and workflows to improve crawl/ scrape analysis, reports and data management. We will rely on you to test the data and the scrape to ensure accuracy and quality. You will own the process to identify and rectify any issues with breaks as well as scale scrapers as needed.</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Building and managing targeted web scrapers, including but not limited to ad-hoc scraping tasks and production level regularly recurring scraping jobs.</li><li>Managing the pipeline and storage for the data of those scrapers.</li><li>Working closely with Data Scientists and Product Team to build and develop future data pipelines as defined by the business.&nbsp;</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Experience running large scale web scrapers; ideally some familiarity with a big data stack (e.g. Airflow, Spark, Hadoop, MapReduce, Hive, Impala, Kafka, Storm, and equivalent cloud-native services)</li><li>Solid Python knowledge, Java, C are ideal</li><li>Hands-on experience with cloud services and tools required for designing cloud architectures and websites like AWS, Google Cloud, Azure, Linux/UNIX, regex, GraphQL, HTTP, HTML, Javascript, typescript, and Networking protocols</li><li>Familiarity with techniques and tools for crawling, extracting and processing data (e.g. Scrapy, pandas, mapreduce, SQL, BeautifulSoup, etc).</li><li>Familiarity with Search APIs</li><li>Strong database creation and administration knowledge; Mysql and nosql (elastic, postgres, graph-dbs)</li><li>Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science or a related field or the equivalent demonstrated experience</li><br/>Bonus Points<br/><li>Experience in developing data &amp; analytics platforms / applications on cloud and experience with cloud native container technologies such as Kubernetes, Jenkins, OpenShift, Docker (experience with Terraform, Ansible, Chef, and Puppet is preferred)</li><li>Experience with streaming data sources and RESTful interfaces including familiarity with extracting data from publicly available API endpoints</li><li>Knowledge of CICD best practices like designing and building automated solutions for building, testing, monitoring, and deploying applications in a continuous delivery environment</li><li>Familiarity with social media apis and scraping&nbsp;</li><li>Experience with system monitoring/administration tools</li><li>Experience with version control, open source practices, and code review</li><li>Experience with applications designed to display archived web content</li><li>Knowledge of entity resolution best practices and ontology creation</li><div>CertiK is proud to offer medical, vision, and dental insurance, 401(k) plan with company matching, life and accidental death and dismemberment insurance, HSA (with high deductible plan), FSA, and other benefits to all full-time employees, along with flexible paid time off and holidays.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>In compliance with federal law, all persons hired will be required to verify identity and eligibility to work in the United States and to complete the required employment eligibility verification form upon hire. </div><div><br></div><div>CertiK is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. We will not discriminate against any applicant or employee on the basis of age, race, color, creed, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity or expression, medical condition, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, marital status or civil partnership/union status, physical or mental disability, pregnancy, childbirth, genetic information, military and veteran status, or any other basis prohibited by applicable federal, state or local law.</div><div><br></div><div>CertiK will consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with local and federal requirements.</div><div><a href="https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf" class="postings-link">https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf</a></div><div><br></div><div>All CertiK employees are expected to actively support diversity on their teams, and in the Company.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/aEn2UaqeHho" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/certik/eda5d618-8d6c-45dc-a3f9-70f904b5a92c/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/452745/CertiK-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[certik@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f6c22067-35b7-4b78-a01c-cb1e9232298a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[CertiK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Data Science ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Technical Writer - Blockchain and DeFi]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ankr]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ankr.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Dubai, Dubai, United Arab Emirates]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>{Fully remote]</p><p><br></p><p><strong>ABOUT ANKR</strong></p><p>Ankr provides Web3 infrastructure for easy, accessible and affordable deployment of blockchain nodes, API’s, decentralized staking infrastructure and Layer 2 scaling solutions, designed to lower the entry barrier for everyday people, enterprises, and developers to contribute to blockchain ecosystems. Check us out at <a href="https://www.ankr.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://www.ankr.com/</a></p><p>Ankr was founded in 2017 in Berkeley, California. Its founding team and headquarters are based in San Francisco. Ankr’s distributed team of 50+ people operates from offices in San Francisco, Shanghai, Moscow, and Amsterdam.<br></p><p>This highly creative Technical Writer will lead the way in writing documentation for Defi and promoting Ankr’s staking product offerings.</p><p>You will have an interest in or experience writing documentation for Defi —you are passionate about the needs of users in relation to these and communicating related concepts clearly. Our ideal candidate can comprehend blockchain concepts quickly and understand the user journey from multiple perspectives.</p><p>You will work closely with our product managers and directly with our user base (institutional/enterprise or crypto/Defi developers) to identify key recurring areas of confusion and create corresponding content, whether written, visual, or webinars, and be able to partner with community contributors on documentation through wikis and other means. </p><p><br></p><p><strong>What you will do:</strong></p><ul> <li>Write high-quality documentation such as staking documentation, technical/architecture documentation, user guides, FAQs, video tutorials, and technical support docs for key aspects of our open-source software</li> <li>Have an in-depth understanding of the product and what customers/developers need </li> <li>Proactively identify gaps in the documentation or knowledge base articles</li> <li>Work with product managers, and other subject matter experts in a collaborative editing environment</li> <li>Edit and review content created by others for technical accuracy and clarity</li> <li>Provide feedback to the product team on how our products might be made easier to use</li> <li>Assist the marketing team in creating other resources and thought leadership including tear sheets, case studies, and white paper</li> </ul><ul> <li>Excellent written and verbal Russian and English communication skills</li> <li>3+ years experience working on software documentation, ideally in the fintech and/or blockchain space</li> <li>Great teaching skills that translate into amazing written work</li> <li>Teamwork, flexibility, initiative, communication and organisation</li> <li>Ability to share knowledge, train other developers</li> <li>Developer community experience and/or evangelism</li> <li>Willingness to constantly learn and improve, challenging yourself to stay at the top of your game</li> <li>Passion for blockchain</li> </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/ankr/j/7F728D7F57/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/746707/ankr-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ankr@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3b58522a-6fba-41ac-b017-94bbed42523c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ankr]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of IT]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[FTX US]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ftx.us]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>FTX US is a US-regulated cryptocurrency exchange, built from the ground up. Its mission is for FTX US to grow the digital currency ecosystem, to offer US and international traders a platform that inspires their loyalty, and to become the market leading US regulated cryptocurrency exchange by volume within the next two years. We are looking for talented individuals to join our fast paced team to help us on this mission!&nbsp;&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>FTX US is seeking a Head of Global IT to set up and manage our current and future network security, networking, SOC compliance audits, infrastructure, technology, and employee hardware and software needs. As in line with our company ethos, this will be at least in part an individual contributor role. You will provide technology vision and leadership for developing and implementing IT initiatives to increase productivity, manage corporate &amp; user security, create and implement user policies and processes, manage IT vendor relationships, and develop proof of concept plans to evaluate new technical solutions.</div><br/>What we're looking for:<br/><li>Ability and flexibility to travel at various times throughout the year throughout the US and internationally as required</li><li>Experience working with a fast-growth company</li><li>Minimum 6-8 years of experience in IT management, with experience both setting up IT infrastructure from the ground up and managing the infrastructure at a scaled business</li><li>Successful track record of technology leadership, execution, and delivery.</li><li>Willing to be hands-on and “do”, in addition to manage</li><li>Prior experience with SOC certification and audit process</li><li>Experience helping a business grow at a fast pace through thought leadership and professional excellence.</li><li>Strong understanding of cyber security and networking.</li><li>Ability to work effectively with multiple teams </li><div><i>FTX US is an equal opportunity employer.</i></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/FTXUS/7b439efa-d7bb-4517-a344-dc2a510162c1/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/895260/FTX_US_Logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alexander+ftxus@cryptocareers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c9e0623d-b701-44f9-a750-6c25cdb03096]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[FTX US]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crypto Program Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re Coinbase. We’re the world’s most trusted way to join the crypto revolution, serving more than 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/our-mission-strategy-and-culture-18a92a3bb0fa&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web 3.0 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture. We’re a remote-first company looking to hire the absolute best talent all over the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve got positive energy. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for a Crypto Programs Manager to join the Crypto Intelligence Team within the Business Development organization to roll out efficient and repeatable processes, enable cross-functional alignment and collaboration, and deliver initiatives on time through consistent planning and tracking.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What you’ll be doing:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work directly with the Manager of the Crypto Intelligence Team and other team members.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Utilize professional and crypto experience to collaborate closely with cross-functional teams including Listings, Product Management, Business Development, Data Science, Legal, Compliance, Security and others to implement new crypto-related programs and improve systems and processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Establish and maintain workflows to support a “Monitoring Command Center” program while identifying scaling vectors and supporting internal adoption across cross-functional partners.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support various programs in the crypto asset lifecycle, including but not limited to: asset reviews/re-reviews/prioritizations, Day-1 listings and crowd-fundraising platform product.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Leverage crypto forward knowledge to spin-up pioneering (yet-to-be-defined) programs around DApps, Wallet and NFTs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead efforts to improve data integrity across crypto-programs to measure process performance, and identify process improvement opportunities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate stakeholder alignment to create short-term and long-term program roadmaps to support business needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create executive-facing reports and presentations regarding team KPIs and accomplishments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;What we look for in you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years program, project or growth experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor&#39;s degree from an accredited university&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven track record of handling large-scale projects across a variety of cross-functional teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Solutions oriented with a curious &amp;amp; analytical mindset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated data-driven decision making or quantitative analysis skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent communicator who can influence a wide range of partners, facilitate training to large groups, and is comfortable presenting to senior leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working at a tech company or has a track record of quickly ramping up on complex projects/environments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to handle multiple stakeholders and priorities simultaneously&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to thrive in ambiguous environments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven “crypto-forward” knowledge or demonstrated passion/curiosity and ability to ramp into crypto quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Notice for Colorado applicants as required by sb19-085 (8-5-20). Target annual salary for this role performed in Colorado, is &lt;span data-sheets-value=&quot;{&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;:3,&amp;quot;3&amp;quot;:170850}&quot; data-sheets-userformat=&quot;{&amp;quot;2&amp;quot;:21443,&amp;quot;3&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;:2,&amp;quot;2&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;\&amp;quot;$\&amp;quot;#,##0&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;3&amp;quot;:1},&amp;quot;4&amp;quot;:{&amp;quot;1&amp;quot;:2,&amp;quot;2&amp;quot;:16770457},&amp;quot;9&amp;quot;:2,&amp;quot;10&amp;quot;:1,&amp;quot;11&amp;quot;:4,&amp;quot;12&amp;quot;:0,&amp;quot;15&amp;quot;:&amp;quot;Lato&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;17&amp;quot;:1}&quot; data-sheets-formula=&quot;=if(R45C6=0,R6C15*index(&#39;[HIDE]  Constants&#39;!R6C17:R18C17,match(R6C16,&#39;[HIDE]  Constants&#39;!R6C16:R18C16,0)),DGET(IMPORTRANGE(&amp;quot;https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/11NK8Qii7CmiOpX_swzo7Ml0cEWE3j-g8se90PW81hhQ/edit#gid=1563110246&amp;quot;,&amp;quot;Comp 3.0!$B$5:$CH$200&amp;quot;),R47C6,{&amp;quot;lookup&amp;quot;;R42C6&amp;amp;R43C6}))&quot;&gt;$144,500&lt;/span&gt;&amp;nbsp;+ target bonus + target equity + benefits (including medical, dental, vision and 401(k)).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ID=P32041&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please note that for employees based in the US, Philippines, Canada or Singapore, if your role requires you to be present in a Coinbase office or if you choose to be physically present in a Coinbase office or sponsored location, participate in any in-person gathering (including offsites) or engage in business travel sponsored by Coinbase, you will be required to be fully vaccinated (as defined by applicable law).&amp;nbsp; If you receive an offer, you will receive additional information about the grounds and process for an exemption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations[at]coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3836485?gh_jid=3836485&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Jr Finance Associate - Compliance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: bold;">About Celsius Network</span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>Celsius addresses the financial needs of today’s consumers worldwide through a democratized reward income and lending platform accessible via a mobile app. With a mission to put unparalleled economic freedom in the hands of the people, and a core belief that financial services should only do what is in the best interests of the community, Celsius is a modern platform where membership provides access to curated financial services that are not available through traditional financial institutions. Crypto holders can earn high-yield compounding interest by transferring coins to their Celsius Wallet and can borrow fiat currency against their crypto collateral at the lowest interest rates in the space.  </span></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span>The Celsius team is committed to doing good and doing well. We believe in the power of disruption and the importance of decentralization to create a new system that acts in the best interest of everyone. Each member of our team brings something unique and innovative to the table, but the common thread that links us together is our passion for blockchain, equality, and leading the next financial revolution that changes the equation to bring power back to the people. </span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>An exciting opportunity has come about for Jr</span><span> Analysts</span><span> to join Celsius Network Compliance team </span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>The Role: Full time and initially Remote - Preferable locations <span style="font-weight: bold;">Las Vegas, NV | Dallas, TX | Tampa, FL </span></span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>The key responsibilities of this Global role will be to support Celsius’ Compliance program, taking ownership of the onboarding processes, undertake lifecycle compliance management, and provide solution led expert advice and guidance for business. </span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>This is an exciting and varied role working alongside our partners and clients to ensure they, and our business, are protected. </span><span></span></p>
<p><span>This is a entry-level role with opportunities to learn and develop alongside an experienced team.</span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>What will you be doing?</span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-weight: bold;">Performing Customer Due Diligence (CDD) on Celsius’ customers - including <strong>Enhanced Due Diligence (</strong>EDD) as well </span></li>
<li><span>Performing customer lifecycle compliance monitoring and re-evaluation on our customers</span></li>
<li><span>Compliance analysis &amp; support as relevant/required, including Lending and partners sales areas, across processes relevant to the role, including:</span><br></li>
<li><span>Internal Reporting – compilation, provision &amp; support of the Global Compliance team</span></li>
<li><span>Maintain sound professional working relationships with other Compliance teams, business development, and management </span><br></li>
</ul>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>We tend to look for people with:</span></p>
<p><span><br></span></p>
<p><span>First and foremost, a positive attitude and a passion for learning along with:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Knowledge, understanding and interest in Cryptocurrency  </span></li>
<li><span>Compliance awareness with a good understanding of the compliance challenges facing the business</span></li>
<li><span>An understanding of the impact of wider compliance issues on the business</span></li>
<li><span>An ability to work flexibly and re-priotise work as appropriate </span></li>
<li><span>Able to present solutions and influence final decision of line manager</span></li>
<li><span>Able to challenge and influence business decisions</span></li>
<li><span>Excellent communication skills – verbal and written</span></li>
<li><span>Manages and plans own work loads</span></li>
<li><span>Ability to translate research and analysis well into reasoned recommendations that informs effectively the decision-making process</span></li>
</ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xW6QWaNfysw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=575&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/731816/celsius_network.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celsius@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5fa72b05-b42d-48a9-806e-c3fdccb06776]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Operations Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.parity.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berlin, Germany]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Parity Technologies builds core infrastructure to power a better internet—one that respects the freedom and data of individuals—and to empower developers to create better services through decentralized tech. Parity’s technologies include Substrate, a flexible framework for building blockchains, and Polkadot, a protocol for connecting and securing blockchains.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As the company rapidly grows we are seeking a competent professional with a passion for organisation, who is ready to handle a wide range of administrative tasks, has experience with company scaling, and the ability to create excellent working environments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your duties will include but are not limited to:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Managing and optimising by scaling our processes to ensure the continuous smooth running of operations and support exponential growth of Parity&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Driving health and safety within the company, being project lead for ongoing pandemic management and our company risk assessment (Gefährdungsbeurteilung/GBU)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Overviewing workplace budgeting (forecasting and expense control)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinating and aligning with team assistants and VPs of Team about our guidelines and policies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working together with our Finance and Legal team on specific projects and tasks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Leading teams of Office Managers and Operations Coordinators&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;REQUIREMENTS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum of 3 years of operations, admin, project or programme management experience or worked in a similar role across multiple locations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A proactive, responsible way of working, even under pressure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great written and verbal communication skills with English on native level and German on intermediate level&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with organization’s P&amp;amp;L management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strategic thinking and problem-solving mindset&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Knowledge of Google Apps (Gmail, Docs, Spreadsheets)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;NICE-TO-HAVES&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with German bureaucracy when it comes to workplace health and safety&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with project management tools like Trello or Asana&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interest in or even experience with blockchain or open-source software (OSS)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BENEFITS&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working at Parity means focusing on the stuff that counts: building the most cutting-edge technology for the future web. Our teams enjoy a high degree of trust, freedom and autonomy to achieve that goal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will have the opportunity to have direct impact on our company growth with your decision making&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Because we value initiative and learning, we&#39;ve defined a generous personal budget to attend conferences or skills courses of your own choosing. We think you know what&#39;s best for you!&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We handle personal information in accordance with our privacy policy&lt;a href=&quot;https://workable.com/nr?l=https%3A%2F%2Fparity.io%2Fprivacy&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;https://parity.io/privacy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LZd6z7HiTLw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/parity/jobs/4939755003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/378609/parity.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[parity@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6edef434-1785-497e-a19b-ce6d949ad50a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Parity Technologies]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Front-End Developer - Remote]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tendermint]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://tendermint.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Berlin]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b>About us:&nbsp;</b></div><div><br></div><div>At Tendermint, we empower people to engage with blockchain advancement and uncover new opportunities presented by this cutting-edge technology. Our diverse talent comes from around the world and together, we ignite change, powering the growth of truly innovative ideas and providing access to next-generation financial systems.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>By developing an innovative suite of products that are optimized for ease of use, including Starport and Emeris, we lead the way in building an open decentralized future. We are focused on creating an environment that allows for permissionless innovation, stemming from our legacy as the creators of Cosmos ($ATOM), the world’s largest cross-chain ecosystem that has secured billions of dollars in digital assets.</div><div><br></div><div>Fueling the advancement of blockchain applications through our user-friendly solutions, we connect technology and creativity to deliver a future where global businesses and individuals can benefit from a transparent ecosystem that is sustainable and interconnected.</div><div><br></div><div>Join our rapidly growing international team and play a meaningful role in this exciting industry, positively impacting global collaboration and prosperity.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div><b>How we work:</b></div><div><br></div><div>True to our vision of a Web3 future, we take a decentralized approach in our team. With team members working worldwide from North &amp; South America, Europe, Africa to the Middle East and Asia-Pacific, we focus on talent rather than location. We understand the importance of open communication and collaboration, leveraging the most optimal tools to operate efficiently and run an open-door policy with the leadership team.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>This role is a full-time remote position, and you are free to work from anywhere. The benefits we offer are carefully considered, aimed to facilitate remote working and maintain team welfare. As a team made up of varied backgrounds, cultures and experiences, we believe everyone has a unique way of contributing, and we fully encourage cross-learning.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Due to the nature of a decentralized team, there is a need to align schedules across different time zones. Having a certain level of time flexibility is therefore required during times of 8 am - 12 noon PST but this also means that you have flexibility in your schedule to best suit your lifestyle.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>At the heart of our work ethics, we value diversity, inclusivity, kindness, and respect.</div><div><br></div><div><br></div><br/>What you’ll be doing:<br/><li>Be a part of the front-end web engineering team building Starport, a developer-focused platform for building and launching sovereign blockchains.</li><li>Implement the user interface for the desktop web and mobile web versions of Starport, based on the high-fidelity mockups produced by our design team.</li><li>Design API client-side libraries that will be generated automatically from the source code of the blockchain.</li><li>Maintain a white-label wallet web app template, an integral part of Starport scaffolding.</li><li>Writing unit tests and integration tests for various features of the Starport web application.</li><li>Ensure our web application and components are accessible, responsive, performant, and bug-free for recent versions of web browsers across all popular platforms.</li><li>Ensure the code you write is readable, maintainable with minimal technical debt.</li><div><br></div><br/>We’re looking for someone who has:<br/><li>An exceptional portfolio demonstrating 6+ years of web development experience.</li><li>Mastery in building component-based web apps in JavaScript and TypeScript using Vue (preferred) or React.</li><li>Deep expertise in client-side state management libraries like Vuex, Mobx, or Redux</li><li>Expert understanding of client-side application architecture</li><li>Excellent knowledge of CSS and experience in writing stylesheets with Sass.</li><li>Experience in using communication protocols such as WebSockets and gRPC.</li><li>Proficient understanding of code versioning tools, such as Git.</li><li>Clear and concise written and oral English communication skills.</li><div><br></div><br/>Nice to have:<br/><li>Experience in using cryptocurrencies, wallets, decentralized exchanges, lending protocols, etc.</li><li>Fascination with blockchain technology</li><div><br></div><br/>What we offer:<br/><li>The opportunity to be part of building the future of the Internet</li><li>Flexible work schedule</li><li>Excellent benefits like educational budget, fitness and wellbeing spend</li><li>Flexible PTO</li><li>Healthcare, Dental and Vision insurance 100% covered for employees in the US</li><li>401K Match in the US</li><li>Competitive salary, including equity</li><div>Tendermint in the news:</div><div><br></div><div><a href="https://techcrunch.com/2019/03/17/welcome-to-the-hub-of-all-hubs/" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://techcrunch.com/2019/03/17/welcome-to-the-hub-of-all-hubs/</a></div><div><a href="https://cointelegraph.com/news/cross-platform-blockchain-project-cosmos-launches-first-hub-after-17-million-ico" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://cointelegraph.com/news/cross-platform-blockchain-project-cosmos-launches-first-hub-after-17-million-ico</a></div><div><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/a-blockchain-to-connect-all-blockchains-cosmos-is-now-officially-live" style="font-size: 15px" class="postings-link">https://www.coindesk.com/a-blockchain-to-connect-all-blockchains-cosmos-is-now-officially-live</a></div><div><a href="https://www.coindesk.com/how-to-turn-a-17-million-ico-into-104-million-the-cosmos-story" class="postings-link">https://www.coindesk.com/how-to-turn-a-17-million-ico-into-104-million-the-cosmos-story</a></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/oJ4WG3SelT0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/tendermint/2c113947-2109-444e-9da4-6b5da33c7985/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145907/tendermint.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tendermint@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[7560c97e-86cc-40b9-b8e0-09ef50cbd9ef]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tendermint]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
