<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Platform Engineer (f/m/d)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Upvest]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://upvest.co/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>We’re looking for fintech enthusiasts to join us in creating the financial infrastructure of tomorrow. We’re building the first European Investment API to enable any financial institution to offer a broad range of investment products in their apps. Our view is backed by Europe's largest tech VCs (Earlybird, Notion Capital, Partech, HV Capital, ABN AMRO Ventures) and by renowned fintech entrepreneurs (including <a target="_blank" href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ACoAAA5D6LAB1cJ1GBRZ8whwsc6ZI78kDf1Ulx0" rel="noopener">Maximilian Tayenthal</a>, founder of N26, and <a target="_blank" href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ACoAAAAAH8AB8C9RXofd6q-Ux6PSMs23ahwpU8U" rel="noopener">Felix Haas</a>, founder of IDnow). </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>We’re based in Berlin but would consider <strong>hiring</strong> <strong>remotely</strong> for this role. If you do want to move to Berlin though, we’re happy to support your relocation.<br /><br /></p>
<p>At Upvest, our vision is <strong>to make investing as easy as spending money</strong>. By enabling any business to offer investment opportunities, our goal is to empower anyone to invest. Today, we count 50+ talented people from 20 different countries. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong>Your mission:</strong><br /></p>
<p>Platform team’s objectives include creating a robust, secure, resilient, and observable infrastructure for our Product Engineering teams to build products on as well as provide all the needed tooling for them to be productive on the Platform. As our next Platform Engineer, you will join our Platform team (together with <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/martinvulprecht/" rel="noopener">Martin</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rokas-petraitis/" rel="noopener">Rokas</a> &amp; <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sergei-gunstvin-59b264192/" rel="noopener">Sergei</a>). You will play an important role in engineering our infrastructure by making it as automated and scalable as possible while maintaining a high degree of security. <br /></p>
<p><br /></p>
<p>Our principles include infrastructure-as-code, security first, zero trust, and least privilege principles but most importantly the Platform team’s job is to enable and empower Product teams to deliver Products on the Platform in a more productive way. The platform team does this by mapping out Product teams’ requirements, formulating a roadmap and plans on what kind of tooling and automation needs to be in place and executing on those plans. </p>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong>This role will give you the opportunity to:</strong><br /></p>
<ul>
<li>Contribute to the development of our infrastructure and architectural decisions</li><li>Gain valuable experience in a high-security and high-stakes fintech environment</li><li>Improve our CI/CD pipeline</li><li>Partner with the product engineering teams to improve services</li><li>Drive DevOps mindset and collaboration within Engineering Department</li><li>Contribute to the platform development in Go with a focus on scalability and stability</li><li>Proactively test the flexibility and resilience of the system (and keep improving our monitoring &amp; observability)</li><li>Establish communication and documentation best practices throughout the entire software development lifecycle (development, deployment, and incident management)</li><li>Provide operational support and engineering for multiple large distributed software applications</li><li>Gather and analyze system metrics to assist in improving performance and finding faults</li></ul>
<ul>
</ul>
<ul><li>Prior experience with Kubernetes, Docker, Vault and Terraform</li><li>Prior experience with Cloud computing (ideally with GCP)</li><li>Deep knowledge of modern monitoring and observability</li><li>Knowledge of operating Kafka in high availability environments</li><li>High level of pragmatism</li></ul>
<p><br /></p>
<p><strong>Nice to have:</strong><strong><br /></strong></p>
<ul><li>Knowledge of our modern tech-stack (Go, Docker, K8S, Postgres, Redis, Kafka), SRE, service meshes, API gateways, and observability</li><li>Experience working in the fintech domain</li></ul>
<p><strong><br /></strong></p>
<p><strong><strong>Why Upvest?</strong></strong></p>
<ul><li>We're working on solving a hard problem: fixing the European securities financial infrastructure that empowers more people to be able to invest. You have the opportunity to contribute to this change.</li><li>We invest in you. From access to a personal coach, development budget and plenty of opportunities to grow in your role.</li><li>We take hiring seriously with a strong focus on keeping a high bar when interviewing (equally important is that we also hire decent people who are passionate about their craft and helping up achieve our shared mission).</li><li>While we're not quite fully-remote, we are committed to being a flexible employer as we understand you don't have to be in the office to do your best work.</li><li>We live a culture of empowerment, trust (that we hire the best people and get out of their way) and openness (there's a greater advantage in sharing information than keeping it to ourselves).</li><li>We ensure we take time to have fun as a team. We're looking forward to having more time in-person again once this becomes possible again.</li></ul>
<p><br /></p>
<div><strong>Our values:</strong><br /></div>
<ul><li><strong>Learn and grow: </strong>We aim high to shape our future. We give and request honest feedback. Everything is a learning opportunity. Progression &gt; Perfection.</li><li><strong>Team first. </strong>We make it easy for others. We value different views, disagree, and commit. We win and celebrate together!</li><li><strong>Own the outcome. </strong>We are proactive and finish the job until it is done. Happy clients &gt; Sales. We take breaks when needed.</li><li><strong>Tell the story. </strong>We always start with the ‘why’. Outcome &gt; Process. We share knowledge to empower others.</li></ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://upvestco.recruitee.com/o/senior-platform-devopssre-engineer-fmd/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/410329/upvest-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[upvest@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[eb868170-dc83-4d10-a530-4995d2a58301]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Upvest]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Strategy & Operations Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Forte Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.forte.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strategy &amp;amp; Operations Analyst&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, you will play a key role in driving growth and business success across the organization. You will leverage your analytical skills to tackle a wide range of different problem spaces -- spanning tech/gaming, blockchain, and finance. You are comfortable diving deep into any task, be it strategic analysis, market research, or financial modeling. Strong candidates possess exceptional business judgement and communication skills to deliver consistent, high quality outcomes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In this role, you will...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrate your quantitative abilities by building and/or maintaining financial models, tracking KPIs, and compiling market analyses&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Leverage your outstanding eye for detail in creating polished, high-impact presentations&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop a deep understanding of market opportunities and trends, with an emphasis on the blockchain and gaming industries&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Communicate data-driven insights to internal stakeholders and the leadership team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage schedules, verify milestones, and execute on goals in collaboration with cross-functional teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ultimately, work on strategic challenges that have major impact on Forte’s products and services, partners, and teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;To be a good fit, you have...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A “roll up the sleeves” attitude that demonstrates a bias towards action and impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A low ego, a desire to take ownership, and intellectual curiosity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Prior experience at a top-tier investment bank and/or management consulting firm&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Intellectual curiosity and a passion for creative problem-solving with incomplete data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BA/BS in Business, Economics, or a related field, and 1 - 3 years of relevant work experience such as consulting, financial services, strategy, business operations or program management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bonus if you also have...&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with financial modeling, data analysis, visualizations and presentations&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An understanding of the fundamentals of blockchain technology, developer platforms, game design, and / or token economics. And, if not, a strong desire to learn!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Forte&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Forte is building economic technology for games. Its end-to-end platform enables the emergence of&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cts.businesswire.com/ct/CT?id=smartlink&amp;amp;url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.forte.io%2F%3Fp%3D507&amp;amp;esheet=52430260&amp;amp;newsitemid=20210520005295&amp;amp;lan=en-US&amp;amp;anchor=community+economics&amp;amp;index=5&amp;amp;md5=47dfe9eadc11aa00eabe6c1dcfa3cc30&quot;&gt;community economics&lt;/a&gt;, a system where the interests of game developers and players are aligned, leading to healthier, sustainable game communities. The team is composed of longtime industry members (Unity, ngmoco, Riot Games, Electronic Arts, Sony, and Rockstar Games, among others), and is currently working with over 20 acclaimed game developers from across the industry to reimagine the economics of games.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/K378r1KeRio" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/forte/jobs/4820003003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/511563/forte-labs-logo_Cropped.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[forte@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[509e5842-f758-4b3e-8b54-bfc3ca4c2a98]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Forte Labs]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Community Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://uniswap.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>The Uniswap Protocol is the largest decentralized trading and automated market making protocol (often called a DEX, “Decentralized Exchange”) on Ethereum.</div><div><br></div><div>The Uniswap Labs team was a major contributor to the Uniswap Protocol and now focuses on building a suite of products to support the Uniswap ecosystem. Our team is one of the most impactful in crypto. We are based out of SoHo in New York City with the option to be partially or fully remote depending on the position.</div><div><br></div><div>The Uniswap community is one of the most impactful groups, inclusive of everyone from developers to traders. We’re looking for a Community Lead with a strong understanding of Ethereum, DeFi fundamentals, decentralized communities and community-building tools to support and engage with the Uniswap community.</div><div><br></div><div>This role will be a highly visible role in the organization and in the broader ecosystem. You will not only manage our day-to-day online presence, you will also be responsible for keeping your finger on the pulse of what’s happening in the DeFi and greater crypto space. You wil help with hiring and training a team of global community managers. You should love community-building and have a knack for developing online relationships. You will be joining a lean team, and this role will have a lot of autonomy-- you should be a self-starter and be capable of self-directed work. This role will be impactful to our ever-growing community - reinventing what a community is at the heart of crypto.</div><div><br></div><div>Most importantly, you should care deeply about the mission of decentralized communities and decentralized finance and always be thinking of creative ways to help spread the word.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Understand Uniswap’s tone and messaging and apply this by engaging with users on twitter and in our discord</li><li>Deep technical understanding of Uniswap’s mechanisms and ability to answer questions and speak to users and integration partners</li><li>Manage support requests</li><li>Attend virtual and in person conferences and hackathons, support hackers, and generally engage with the developer community around Uniswap</li><li>Create fun community engagement programs, such as giveaways or virtual events</li><li>Host a monthly Uniswap community call</li><li>Manage our mailing list and create periodic newsletter updates</li><li>Create dank memes</li><li>Develop new wants of engaging with our users and community</li><li>Work with the business development team to turn community engagement into active BD opportunities</li><li>Thought leadership on issues in the DeFi space via twitter and the Uniswap blog</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Experience working in community management for a crypto project</li><li>Organizational skills</li><li>Self-directed worker</li><li>Ability to respond very quickly across all of our platforms</li><li>Sense of humor </li><br/>Nice to have<br/><li>Degree in computer science/self-taught engineer</li><li>Active following on twitter</li><li>Existing relationships in the crypto space</li><li>Fondness for the color pink</li><li>Love for unicorns :)</li><div>Uniswap Labs welcomes&nbsp;all qualified persons to apply regardless of race, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, disability, age, or veteran status. Compensation will be competitive and commensurate with experience. This is a full time role which includes health insurance and other benefits.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/Uniswap/7f63671e-ea58-4a8f-a7b4-9a5b1981fcd6/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/669325/uniswap-uni-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[uniswap@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b488dfbb-84b8-4efa-9d5d-2ced4e25769e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Community Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Cardano DCF Senior Designer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOHK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://iohk.io]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano is an open source blockchain project committed to a roadmap towards decentralized governance. As part of this journey, IO Global is looking for a Content Editor to help drive forward our Decentralized Consortium Funding program, an exciting new model to expand the developer base for Cardano’s protocol and ecosystem development. </p> <p>In 2021, Cardano has achieved incredible success, but we are still early in this space and have a long way to go.  A big component of the continued evolution of Cardano is IOG’s efforts to fully open source and decentralize the core development of the platform and protocol.  To do this, we will need to build a broad coalition and a consortium of highly qualified and reputable firms that can meaningfully contribute to this effort.  As a Designer at IOG, you are responsible for creating, maintaining, and assessing the beautiful brand assets that communicate the vision, scope, and importance of the Cardano DCF in a visually aesthetic way. As part of the Cardano DCF marketing and communications team, you are also expected to contribute to Google slide presentations, printed collateral, and UI/UX for DCF product prototypes and websites.</p><p><strong>Your mission </strong></p><ul> <li>Create a unique brand architecture and consistent brand language that embodies the ideals of DCF around decentralized development of the Cardano Blockchain Platform &amp; Protocol</li> <li>Work with Cardano DCF Director, DCF communications manager, and other IOG stakeholders to discover communication objectives and translate them into a design philosophy</li> <li>Be the end-to-end implementer for all visual needs (eg. slides, graphics, illustrations, ads, banners, landing pages, presentations, brochures, ebooks, guides, and training materials)</li> <li>Act as a strategist as much as an implementer, bring creative ideas to the table, and uplevel the look &amp; feel of all Cardano DCF material and marketing</li> <li>Be willing to support other IOG MarComms campaigns and branding initiatives</li> <li>Ideate and present slide, web, and print collateral solutions in a team setting</li> <li>Create presentation and document guides and templates for internal and external use</li> <li>Update and maintain external thedcf.io website.</li> </ul><p><strong>Your expertise</strong>  </p> <ul> <li>Minimum of five years of experience in  Graphic and Web Design, preferably with a technology company (crypto, blockchain, gaming, interactive media preferred)</li> <li>Advanced understanding of brand architectures and brand language</li> <li>Design Project Delivery Experience</li> <li>Ability to work independently and under pressure created by deadlines</li> <li>Attention to detail</li> <li>Critical thinking skills.</li> </ul><p><strong>Location</strong></p><p>IOG is a fully distributed organization and therefore this is a remote position. Due to team distribution we are ideally searching for someone in a Central European or Pacific Standard time zone.  </p><p><strong>All Colleagues</strong></p><ul> <li>Flexible schedule</li> <li>Remote work - ability to work anywhere</li> <li>Laptop reimbursement</li> <li>New starter package to buy hardware essentials (headphones, monitor, etc)</li> <li>Learning &amp; Development opportunities</li> <li>Competitive PTO and Sick Leave plan</li> </ul><p><strong>US Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits coverage through Anthem with 100% premium cost covered by IO Global for the employee and dependents</li> <li>Health Savings Account</li> <li>Life Insurance</li> </ul><p><strong>UK Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Monthly Health Stipend to use towards any wellness or medical coverage/service</li> <li>Pension</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EM-XkuQdUq8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/io-global/j/1F393BB59C/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143583/iohk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iohk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b89f946-6d3b-434f-aa32-f0e84ecb2992]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOHK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Sales Manager (Utah)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[PayStand]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paystand.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Draper, Utah, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paystand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paystand is a hungry, fast-growing, Series-C startup with three locations! Nestled in the beautiful Santa Cruz mountains, just south of Silicon Valley is where we started. We have our offices in amazing and historic Guadalajara Mexico and Salt Lake City with the dramatic backdrops of the mountains of Utah.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to unlock capital efficiency for enterprise businesses through our transformative&amp;nbsp;“Payments as a Service” platform. Our smart billing and payment network uses revolutionary internet, blockchain, and FinTech services to digitize receivables, automate processing, reduce time-to-cash, lower transaction costs, and produce new revenue for our clients. Paystand is venture-backed, having been consistently recognized as one of the top innovators in FinTech, and fastest growing companies in the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Paystand&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Paystand is a hungry, fast-growing, Series-C startup with three locations! Nestled in the beautiful Santa Cruz mountains, just south of Silicon Valley is where we started. We have our offices in amazing and historic Guadalajara Mexico and Salt Lake City with the dramatic backdrops of the mountains of Utah.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to unlock capital efficiency for enterprise businesses through our transformative&amp;nbsp;“Payments as a Service” platform. Our smart billing and payment network uses revolutionary internet, blockchain, and FinTech services to digitize receivables, automate processing, reduce time-to-cash, lower transaction costs, and produce new revenue for our clients. Paystand is venture-backed, having been consistently recognized as one of the top innovators in FinTech, and fastest growing companies in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role at a Glance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;Are you a motivated, sales leader looking for an uncapped opportunity to materially change the way businesses and enterprise manage payments? If so, you will be a part of a growing team that is changing the payments industry and commerce ecosystem in a refreshing and disruptive way. This isn’t just any job. We’re looking to create a new category for revenue management in the enterprise and we need upbeat, enthusiastic, movers and shakers to take on the challenge and drive new revenue in this changing landscape! This individual should be committed to maximize sales efforts to produce accelerated goals. Are you a closer who thrives in a fast-paced, dynamic sales environment? Then, this opportunity awards accelerated compensation and career progression for driven, top performers.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roles &amp;amp; Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Achieving growth and hitting sales targets by successfully managing the sales team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clearly articulate and demonstrate our value proposition, creating excitement and enthusiasm among prospects.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cultivate lasting relationships with customers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Designing and implementing a strategic sales plan that expands company’s customer base and ensure it’s strong presence.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help the team exceed their quota.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist the sales team through calls and web-based presentations to maintain product positioning and strategies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing recruiting, objectives setting, coaching and performance monitoring of the team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Present sales, revenue and realistic forecasts to the management team.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-5 years experience as a Sales Manager or Team Lead at a high velocity SaaS company (preferably in the FinTech industry).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clear history of meeting &amp;amp; beating quota&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;B.A. or B.S. preferred&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proficient computer skills and experience with CRM (HubSpot, Google Docs, and Slack)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills; proficient in English-language business writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly organized multi-tasker who works well in a fast-paced environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent time management skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail and problem solving skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Preference for candidates with experience selling ERP or other financial software&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the accounts receivable/payable cycle a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Salary + competitive equity in a high growth-stage startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;401k&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Stock Options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Flexible and Generous PTO (vacations)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Opportunity for advancement &amp;amp; growth in a rapidly expanding team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Mentorship, learning &amp;amp; education programs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Smart, motivated team that likes to have fun&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Mission-driven culture, where your work matters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We understand that no candidate is perfectly qualified for any job. Experience comes in different forms; many skills are transferable; and passion goes a long way. Even more important than your resume is a clear demonstration of dedication, impact, and the ability to thrive in a fluid and collaborative environment. We want you to learn new things in this role, and we encourage you to apply if your experience is close to what we’re looking for. We also know that diversity of background and thought makes for better problem solving and more creative thinking, which is why we&#39;re dedicated to adding new perspectives to the team. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Availability&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;- Bay area/Scotts Valley, CA.&amp;nbsp;Salt Lake City area, UT. Guadalajara, MX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(This is not a remote position)***No recruiters please***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only English resumes will be considered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We understand that no candidate is perfectly qualified for any job. Experience comes in different forms; many skills are transferable; and passion goes a long way. Even more important than your resume is a clear demonstration of dedication, impact, and the ability to thrive in a fluid and collaborative environment. We want you to learn new things in this role, and we encourage you to apply if your experience is close to what we’re looking for. We also know that diversity of background and thought makes for better problem solving and more creative thinking, which is why we&#39;re dedicated to adding new perspectives to the team. We look forward to hearing from you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Availability &lt;/strong&gt;- Bay area/Scotts Valley, CA.&amp;nbsp;Salt Lake City area, UT. Guadalajara, MX.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(This is not a remote position)***No recruiters please***&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Only English resumes will be considered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/z5Oi5cFLSmM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://paystand.com/job-listing/?gh_jid=4895346003&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/188126/Paystand.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paystand@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9713c611-4d29-448b-a71c-3c8d3ca06a70]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[PayStand]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Smart Contract Auditor (Malta)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Saint Julian's, Saint Julian's, Malta]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>About Crypto.com </p><p>Founded in 2016, Crypto.com today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest growing crypto app, along with the Crypto.com Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the Crypto.com Exchange and Crypto.com DeFi Wallet. Recently launched, Crypto.com NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment and sports. Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, CCSS Level 3, ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks. With over 3,000 people in offices across the Americas, Europe and Asia, Crypto.com is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a href="https://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com</a></p><p><br></p><p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p><ul> <li>Establish oneself as DeFi security thought leader with hands-on audit of smart contract and research/sharing of smart contract security</li> <li>Establish best practices for smart contract development</li> <li>Establish DeFi product security rating system (using industry standard or an adapted version) for internal use </li> <li>Establish monitoring and alerting on the DeFi space</li> <li>Understand existing and new and upcoming DeFi products </li> <li>Coordinate and work with external stakeholders, partners and auditors on safe-guarding crypto.com DeFi products</li> <li>Drive the organisation on creating a safer and secure DeFi with well-researched security solutions.</li> <li>Educate others on the trends of DeFi product and smart contract security</li> <li>Keep abreast with new/recent attacks on smart contract/DeFi products</li> <li>Keep abreast with upcoming trends in DeFi such as Layer 2 technologies</li> </ul><ul> <li>Degree in Computer Science or Engineering or Mathematics or similar discipline</li> <li>Expect the candidates to have at least 5 years of working experience (not necessary for the full 5 years in blockchain space, but ideally should have worked in blockchain industry)</li> <li>Understanding and hands-on experience in DeFi ecosystem (specifically in Ethereum)</li> <li>Understanding of Ethereum blockchain, Ethereum Virtual Machine (EVM)</li> <li>Understanding of Layer 2 solutions and cross-chain bridge technologies</li> <li>In depth understand and hands-on experience with Solidity programming language</li> <li>Knowledgeable of smart contract vulnerability and hands-on experience to exploit these vulnerability</li> <li>Experience across common vulnerability classes for smart contract at design or system level</li> <li>Knowledgeable on various security analysis tools on smart contract and hands-on experience to setup and use it</li> <li>Have basic understanding of finance such as trading, lending, automatic market making (AMM), derivatives</li> <li>Ability to communicate across roles to drive security mindset across the organization</li> <li>General programming ability - such as Python, Javascript, Bash, Rust, Go</li> </ul><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of combining cryptocurrency and financial services.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you.</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team.</li> <li>Flexible working</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/4183765BA6/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Security UI/UX Designer (UK)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, England, United Kingdom]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About <a target="_blank" href="http://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Crypto.com</a><br></strong> <br>Founded in 2016, <a target="_blank" href="http://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Crypto.com</a> today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest growing crypto app, along with the <a target="_blank" href="http://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Crypto.com</a> Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the <a target="_blank" href="http://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Crypto.com</a> Exchange and <a target="_blank" href="http://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Crypto.com</a> DeFi Wallet. Recently launched, <a target="_blank" href="http://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Crypto.com</a> NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment and sports. <a target="_blank" href="http://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Crypto.com</a> is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, CCSS Level 3, ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks. With over 3,000 people in offices across the Americas, Europe and Asia, <a target="_blank" href="http://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Crypto.com</a> is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a target="_blank" href="https://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com</a></p><p><br></p><p><strong>About the Role:</strong></p>    <p><a target="_blank" href="https://crypto.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external"></a>The Digital Asset Wallet team is responsible for building a user friendly and intuitive wallet for our internal users. The wallet supports withdrawal and deposit of digital assets, NFT and DeFi protocol. The UI/UX designer will be responsible for turning complex problems into simple, elegant and engaging customer experiences for web and mobile experiences. This role is responsible for design at each stage of the project -  from user research and wireframes to final visual specifications.</p><p><br></p><p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p>  <ul> <li>Analyzing product requirements and create high-quality UX design solutions through sketches, wireframes, designs, flow diagrams, storyboards, site maps; </li> <li>Participating in user research and competitive product analysis </li> <li>Discovering design optimization points, improving design systems, and ensure a smooth implementation</li> </ul><ul> <li>2+ years experience as an UI or UX designer </li> <li>Ability to operate independently, demonstrating creativity, being detail oriented, and delivering results in an organized manner </li> <li>Ability to visualize and execute design concepts and ideas quickly, from ideation to prototyping, to user testing/validation, to execution(MVP) </li> <li>Proficient in Figma and other standard design software </li> <li>Have experience building highly accessible application that work on a broad spectrum of devices</li> <li>Have experience making mobile first design</li> <li>Ability to come up with strong and consistent design language that align with our branding</li> <li>Enthusiastic about the future of blockchain</li> <li>Curious and comfortable with ambiguity</li> </ul><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of combining cryptocurrency and financial services.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you.</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team.</li> <li>Flexible working.</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/5DD0C98B7F/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Events Partner, Celo Foundation]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celo.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Do you love building community and bringing people together? And have an acute attention to detail, an eye for thoughtful design, and a drive to make every event a success? Celo Foundation is hiring an Events Partner to manage events operations. As an Events Partner, you will organize and manage events operations with an eye toward consistency in creativity, quality, sustainability, and brand.</div><br/>You Will:<br/><li>Lead operations for larger scale initiatives including Celo’s annual conference and Tier 1 events</li><li>Work internally to ensure vendors are paid in a timely manner</li><li>Coordinate sponsors and activations at Celo’s annual conference</li><li>Build key relationships across the crypto ecosystem</li><li>Write, edit, and ship weekly community events newsletter - collaboration w/comms</li><li>Work closely with the Social Media Lead for event outreach across Celo social media + relevant community publications</li><li>Create and manage swag plan - with a keen focus on sustainable and local</li><li>Create processes to streamline event requests or opportunities</li><br/>You Have:<br/><li>A proven track record of organizing successful events, both online and in-person</li><li>Experience in copywriting, online marketing/communications</li><li>Project management experience</li><li>Well-organized and is energized by creating order in a startup environment</li><li>An eye for detail and quality</li><li>Enjoyment in crafting experiences that inspire magic and beauty</li><li>Passion for building community&nbsp;</li><li>2+ years experience</li><li>Bonus: Social media expertise</li><li>Bonus: Experience with HubSpot or other CRM system</li><div><span>cLabs ("Celo Labs") started Celo in 2017 and is one of many contributors to the open source project Celo.&nbsp;cLabs builds financial technology to enable prosperity of all beings.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>cLabs is a Teal organization, a method of decentralized management and organizational governance. Roles are defined around the work, not people, and there is a high degree of autonomy. As such, we're all proud to hold the job title of "Partner." For more information on our culture, we encourage you to check out our blog at&nbsp;</span><a href="https://medium.com/celohq/the-future-is-teal-cc264a5d51d3" class="postings-link"><span>https://medium.com/celohq/the-future-is-teal-cc264a5d51d3</span></a><span>.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>To build technology and products that are used and loved by people and solve real-world problems, we need to build a team with many different perspectives and experiences. We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. We encourage candidates from all backgrounds to apply and always consider qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records, in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>Applicants in need of special assistance or accommodation during the interview process or in accessing our website may contact us by sending an email to assistance(at)</span><a href="http://celo.org" class="postings-link"><span>celo.org</span></a><span>. We will treat your request as confidentially as possible. In your email, please include your name and preferred method of contact, and we will respond as soon as possible.</span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vwfHiaVzc2E" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/clabs/fd2829f7-0f04-4bf1-9224-545d6708484f/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145322/celo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c6054e2e-9096-43cc-9ea8-c4a05ab9335a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, Operations and SRE]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chronicled]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://chronicled.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, USA]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Chronicled has established the decentralized MediLedger Network, which connects the pharmaceutical industry and runs mission critical processes. You will be working on the software and infrastructure that connects to and runs the Network. You will take part in building a cutting-edge platform using the latest technological achievements at the intersection of blockchain, distributed computing, network protocols and automated application management.</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 11pt">The opportunity</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">As Director, Operations and SRE you will be responsible for the operations of the MediLedger Network, which supports mission critical functions of the business of Fortune 100 customers.&nbsp; The Network is decentralized and you will collaborate with both internal teams and IT departments of Network participants that are running independent </span><a href="http://nodes.You" class="postings-link"><span style="font-size: 11pt">nodes.You</span></a><span style="font-size: 11pt"> will have the opportunity to work with a highly talented engineering team that uses modern technologies.</span></div><br/>What you'll do: <br/><li>Oversee operations and monitor performance of the MediLedger Network</li><li>Design, build, and operate cloud infrastructure to enable reliable and rapid deployment of services for end customers and internal development team</li><li>Work closely with development teams to make sure applications are production-ready, scalable, and reliable from the ground up</li><li>Champion excellence in SRE practicesWork with the customer success team to support the participants of the MediLedger Network</li><li>Establish and deploy monitoring and alerting on critical components of the application and infrastructure</li><li>Further develop our CI/CD pipelinePromote automation of any repetitive task</li><li>Continuously optimize infrastructure and Cloud costs</li><br/>What you'll need: <br/><li>Experience with enterprise-grade software</li><li>At least two years of experience with Kubernetes</li><li>Experience with GCP, optionally AWS and Azure</li><li>Familiarity with event-driven architectures and microservices-based solutions</li><li>Strong knowledge of networking and related infrastructure (including DNS, reverse proxy, firewall, VPN setup, etc)</li><li>Familiarity with enterprise-grade security aspectsFamiliarity with monitoring, altering and logging solutions (including Prometheus)</li><li>Experience with CI/CDExperience with sizing for complex enterprise-grade solutions</li><li>At least 2 year of experience in a management position, 4 years of experience in a DevOps role and additional 2 years in software development</li><li>Experience building and launching new production systems</li><li>Familiarity with SOC compliance is a plus</li><li>Experience with blockchain is a plus</li><li>BS in Computer Science or equivalent experience</li><div><b>Perks:</b>At Chronicled we take pride in our Total Rewards Package which is available to all full time Chronicled Employees:</div><div><b>Competitive Rewards</b>: Comprehensive and competitive employment and rewards packages for all employees</div><div><b>Equipment</b>: Macbook pro and accessories standard issue.</div><div><b>Flexibility</b>: We believe flexibility comes in multiple forms. Freedom to express yourself with an open startup casual dress code, Flexible schedules. Best of all we have an unlimited vacation policy that allows you to get the rest and relaxation you need to refresh.</div><div><b>Welcoming Culture</b>: We call ourselves a family for a reason. We foster a fun and creative atmosphere where anyone can openly contribute ideas, feel appreciated, and feel empowered to be who they are. Fun is also highly encouraged! Frequent offsite team building events and weekly happy hours.</div><div><b>Recognition</b>: Respect and prominence due to work contributions, working on cutting edge technology. Our employees are celebrated and recognized for their contributions</div><div><b>Variety:</b>&nbsp;Opportunities to experience different job tasks, responsibilities, and project opportunities</div><div><b>Workload</b>: Challenging and fast paced work. There is never a dull moment in our Enterprise Blockchain Laboratory.</div><div><b>Work Importance</b>: The typical Chronicled team member has a bias for action. We do. We build. We step outside of the scope. We believe we will change the world.</div><div><b>Control your own Destiny</b>: Ability to influence others and control one’s own destiny.&nbsp;&nbsp;</div><div><b>Advancement</b>: Opportunities to get ahead both personally and professionally.</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/5MArmZpzU68" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/chronicled-2/af9ba9b0-6e23-4889-a485-5cdae030c140/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/301749/chronicled.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chronicled@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d44ed840-83fb-4e02-8dd2-2347727f060d]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chronicled]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[SEO]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Alchemy]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://alchemyapi.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco & New York]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><a href="https://www.alchemy.com/company" class="postings-link">Our mission</a> is to bring blockchain to a billion people. The Alchemy Platform is a world class developer platform designed to make building on the blockchain easy. We've built leading infrastructure in the space, powering over $45 billion in transactions for tens of millions of users in 99% of countries worldwide. </div><div><br></div><div>The Alchemy team draws from decades of deep expertise in massively scalable infrastructure, AI, and blockchain from leadership roles at leading companies and universities like Google, Microsoft, Facebook, Stanford, and MIT. </div><div><br></div><div>Alchemy recently raised a <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/10/28/aws-for-blockchain-alchemy-boost-valuation-to-3-5b-with-250m-raise/" class="postings-link">Series C</a> led by a16z at a $3.5B valuation, having previously raised from Coatue, Addition, Stanford University, Coinbase, the Chairman of Google, Charles Schwab, and the <a href="https://alchemy.com/company#investors" class="postings-link">founders and executives</a> of leading organizations.</div><div><br></div><div>Alchemy powers the top blockchain companies globally and has been featured in <a href="https://techcrunch.com/2021/04/28/alchemy-raises-80m-at-a-505m-valuation-to-be-the-aws-for-blockchain/" class="postings-link">TechCrunch</a>, <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/ninabambysheva/2021/06/08/the-future-of-crypto-and-blockchain-fintech-50-2021/?sh=6791bad153b1" class="postings-link">Forbes</a>, <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-03-21/nfts-mushroom-into-billion-dollar-market-with-help-from-alchemy?srnd=premium" class="postings-link">Bloomberg</a>, and <a href="https://www.alchemy.com/newsroom" class="postings-link">elsewhere</a>.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 18px">The Role</span></div><div><br></div><div>As Alchemy's first SEO hire, you will have the opportunity to lead SEO efforts within the company. This position is crucial to our company’s success as blockchain development is still a nascent industry and we believe there is a massive opportunity to help drive growth through SEO. We're looking to find a rock-star SEO specialist who will take the lead on our various growth efforts from a SEO perspective. Some of the various initiatives will include: optimizing existing content for improved SEO positioning, creating new pages and content, implementing internal analytics to make data driven decisions, understanding our key SEO growth vectors and how to optimize them, and much more. You'll be working closely with our world-class product, engineering, design, and sales teams to drive the launch and adoption of products that serve millions of users globally today.</div><div><br></div><div>The ideal candidate brings experience in this role for high growth start-ups and has some interest in crypto. Additionally, this person shows a combination of strategic thinking, attention to detail, and project management skills.</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Lead SEO efforts internally to drive customer growth, partnering with Go-to-Market, Product, Developer Relations, and Engineering</li><li>Establish, track, and optimize KPI’s across SEO and take data-driven action to increase performance month over month</li><li>Performing ongoing keyword research and competitor analysis to identify opportunities and assess risks</li><li>Identifying and understanding content gaps and experiment opportunities and drive constant testing and improvements forward</li><li>Help create landing pages and create new/iterate on existing content for search performance</li><li>Tracking search engine algorithm changes and SERP volatility constantly to make sure Alchemy is well positioned for growth</li><br/>What We're Looking For<br/><li>3+ years of proven work experience as a SEO manager or specialist at one or multiple high-growth companies</li><li>2+ years of technical/analytical/quantitative work experience</li><li>Hands on experience with SEO, keyword optimizations, ad campaign platforms, and other growth analytic tools</li><li>High attention to detail</li><li>Ability to understand and write about highly technical topics, for both general and technical audiences</li><li>Stellar written and verbal communication skills</li><li>Experience at early stage startups is a large plus</li><li>Technological background a plus</li><li>Passion for blockchain technologies a plus</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/alchemy/d2386f00-c08c-4c3a-ad00-7249b97f2ef5/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637333/alchemy-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alchemy@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[2216d58c-1ece-4465-a4f9-6c8eafa52f36]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Alchemy]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer, RippleX (New Grad)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We champion the builders of tomorrow by providing the infrastructure, tools, services, programs and support for creation on one of the world’s fastest, most sustainable and consistently reliable public blockchain - XRPL. By supporting an open community of developers, they can advance the solutions and innovation needed to allow businesses, consumers, institutions and governments to fuel the engine of a new digital economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;RippleX operates on the belief that realizing the Internet of Value hinges on how easily new technology works for more people, and how effectively we can change the way the world operates today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;RippleX is helping more people participate in the digital economy through:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Practical support and capabilities to develop applications that move digital value faster and more easily&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Empowering a community that’s democratizing the digital economy&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The expertise of a technology company that is known for vision and pragmatism&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain infrastructure that is supported by RippleX and owned by everyone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We have a big vision and the ambition to match. We are seeking the same in engineers. You also see the huge potential of this technology and have the entrepreneurial spirit and technical excellence to realize the vision we have. There is a lot of work to get there but we are committed to building out the best team to achieve this.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be working on:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work on integration libraries and SDKs to interface with our server and APIs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expose the power of blockchain technology through user-friendly interfaces&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Contribute to an ecosystem of decentralized finance applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Quickly learn and utilize modern development tools and libraries&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build services that aggregate and leverage on-chain data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’re looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s in Computer Science or similar years of hands-on Software Development experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve worked on open source projects, developer platforms, and/or API-driven businesses&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re experienced working with any of Typescript/Javascript, Java, Rust, Go, or Python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re excited about learning about blockchains, the technical details, and the potential benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You seek to deeply understand the low-level details of the technologies you work with and the problems you work on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You look to solve problems with simple solutions, rather than technically perfect ones&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Must be a graduate of 2022, Spring 2021, Winter 2021&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice &lt;/a&gt;and our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/ca-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;California Applicant Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; for reference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3502213?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Content Writer - California]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitcoindepot.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[California]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Content Writer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Depot&lt;strong&gt; (&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://bitcoindepot.com/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;bitcoindepot.com&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;) &lt;/strong&gt;is the world’s leading and fastest growing cryptocurrency ATM company.&amp;nbsp; Based in Atlanta, GA, our business and our teams are rapidly expanding, and we are looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Content Writer&lt;/strong&gt; to join our dynamic Marketing team and help us Bring Crypto to the Masses™.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ideal Content Writer will be that unicorn that’s great at long-form And short form writing.&amp;nbsp; The successful candidate will be able to deliver a killer portfolio of past content for blogs, press releases, emails, social media, ads, signage, etc.&amp;nbsp; This person will report to the Sr. Creative Manager and will be responsible for producing content for multiple Bitcoin Depot external and internal projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you consider yourself a seasoned content writer who has the skills and an incredible work ethic, perhaps this rare opportunity is for you.&amp;nbsp; But I warn you, we’re looking for all-stars, not the average.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our creative team sits in our Atlanta, Georgia office.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The successful candidate must have...&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree in marketing, advertising, journalism, integrated communication or a related field&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-5 years of related experience in a fast pace working environment (i.e. agencies)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must have cryptocurrency experience&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A killer portfolio of copywriting and storytelling&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong work ethic (a “That’s not my job.” attitude will not work at Bitcoin Depot.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;An incredible eye for detail and a “flawless execution always” attitude&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;And it would be a big plus if you had any of these…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with Microsoft Office, Google Suite, and Slack&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Position responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draft on-strategy long-form content for blogs, press releases, emails, scripts, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Draft on-strategy short-form content for signage, social media, ads, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Incorporate SEO keywords into all Bitcoin Depot writing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Edit the content work others produce from internal and external personnel (vendor and agency partners) as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the Sr. Creative Manager and graphic designers to pair content with SEO keywords.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure that all content creation maximizes company SEO and positions leadership as thought leaders in the FinTech industry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the horsepower of our Creative team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be the subject matter expert for all things content related for the entire company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with Marketing leadership to set project deadlines and content goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adhere to creative department and brand standards throughout the Bitcoin Depot organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develops and maintains strong, collaborative relationships across the organization&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Other duties as assigned&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K Matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous PTO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health benefits offered with a company contribution towards premiums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wellness benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Revenue Sharing Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Casual dress environment when in office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly company celebrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advancement opportunities based on results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Weekly catered lunches&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Premium coffee and tea provided by Buckhead Beans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bitcoin Depot is an Equal Opportunity Employer that does not discriminate on the basis of actual or perceived race, creed, color, religion, alienage or national origin, ancestry, citizenship status, age, disability or handicap, sex, marital status, veteran status, sexual orientation, genetic information, arrest record, or any other characteristic protected by applicable federal, state or local laws. Our management team is dedicated to this policy with respect to recruitment, hiring, placement, promotion, transfer, training, compensation, benefits, employee activities, and general treatment during employment.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/VuS6XCo53DU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitcoindepot/jobs/4907119003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/556151/bitcoin-depot-image-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitcoindepot@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[49753fb8-b518-4786-89b5-9d1bf0e19ac0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[People Platform and Automation Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxos]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos is on a mission to enable the movement of any asset, any time, in a trustworthy way. Today’s financial infrastructure is archaic, expensive, inefficient and risky - supporting a system that leaves out more people than it lets in. So we’re rebuilding it. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a regulated blockchain infrastructure company, we use technology to tokenize, custody, trade, and settle assets for enterprise clients like PayPal, Novi, Bank of America, and Interactive Brokers. Paxos is a top-funded blockchain company, with more than $500 million in total funding from leading investors like OakHC/FT, Founders Fund, PayPal Ventures, and Declaration Partners. Together, we empower today’s financial leaders to build a more open, trusted economy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Paxos People team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is always working on creating world class candidate and employee experiences day to day. We are a diverse and collaborative group who want to enable Paxos people to do what they do best! We are at the forefront of growth across the company!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a People Platform and Automation Lead, you’ll get to:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lay the foundation for the people technology platform at Paxos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be the key subject matter expert on platforms and reporting for the people team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Play a key role in scaling the people function at a fast growing transformational company in blockchain infrastructure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with cross functional leaders to create positive hiring and people outcomes. This includes executives, hiring managers, interviewers and the people team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Leverage people data to create insights and to enable decision making&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create training programs and adoption programs to setup stakeholders success with people tooling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define KPIs for people tooling. Report on, measure, and make recommendations based on people tooling KPIs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide stakeholders with support, guidance and troubleshooting for people tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manages permissions, access, personalization, and similar system operations and settings for HR services users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with our procurement and vendor intake team to evaluate, purchase and onboard people tools&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to grow your people platform expertise, build a program at a fast growing company and make an impact on hiring and employee engagement goals&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Immerse yourself in blockchain technology, cryptocurrency for enterprises and investors, our regulation-first approach, and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your experience should include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum of 4 years experience with people analytics, people tooling or comparable field&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent data analytics skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to build reporting and dashboards&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to work with multiple data sets to surface insights&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to drive integrations of tools to create seamless experiences and clear data to action on&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience procuring and implementing people tooling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience training and increase adoption of tooling with stakeholders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage multiple projects and communicate updates to relevant stakeholders&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to drive new initiatives&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to guide and instruct stakeholders on how to best utilize tooling&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Basic understanding of APIs and integrations between tools&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You might also have:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with HRIS tools such as Bamboo or Workday&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with people tools such as Lattice, Peakon&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with talent tools such as LinkedIn enterprise, Gem, Seekout&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with customer success, implementing products, or implementing tooling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of how to procure and implement tools that are best fit for an organization&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity and/or experience with SQL for data mining and analytics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll love about Paxos:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos has consistently been named as a “Best Place to Work” by BuiltIn and was recently listed on the 2021 Forbes Fintech 50. All of our employees have significant ownership and impact on our business, as well as benefits like company equity, health insurance, family leave, a $500 quarterly stipend for development, a $500 stipend for home office setup and unlimited PTO. From team product demos and virtual lounge and learns to care packages and an active Slack #shoutouts channel, there are countless opportunities to connect and make your mark. Help us continue to build a new, open financial system from one of our three offices or right from your home!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h5ar-oLO1VY&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos CEO Discusses Crypto, Blockchain and the Future of Finance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/12/02/mercadolibre-is-creating-the-biggest-crypto-market-in-latin-america-paxos-powers-the-experience/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mercado Libre Creating Biggest Crypto Market in LatAm through Paxos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/11/29/introducing-prex-crypto-powered-by-paxos/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Powers Prex Crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/10/19/usdp-chosen-for-novi-pilot/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;USDP Stablecoin Chosen for Facebook&#39;s Pilot of Novi Digital Wallet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/fintech/2021/#413b4e2631a6&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Forbes Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/13/paxos-supports-interactive-brokers-journey-into-crypto-markets/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Interactive Brokers&#39; Journey into Crypto Markets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/fintech-250-startups-most-promising/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CB Insights Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 250 for Crypto Category&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/30/trust-is-not-an-option-its-a-requirement-paxos-explains-its-unique-approach-to-pioneering-a-new-market/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Flourish Crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/23/paxos-national-trust-receives-occ-conditional-approval-for-de-novo-charter/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos National Trust Receives OCC Conditional Approval for De Novo Charter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/29/paxos-raises-300-million-in-series-d-funding-at-2-4-billion-valuation/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Raises $300M in Series D Funding at 2.4B Valuation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2020/10/21/paypal-launches-new-service-enabling-users-to-buy-hold-and-sell-cryptocurrency/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos &amp;amp; PayPal Bring Crypto to Millions of Users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Paxos team is made up of passionate people from all over the world with different perspectives and experiences. If this opportunity excites you, but your experience doesn’t perfectly match the description…apply! Unique voices help us build a more transparent and open economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;1641574856.002400&quot; class=&quot;c-virtual_list__item&quot; data-qa=&quot;virtual-list-item&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__background c-message_kit__background--hovered p-message_pane_message__message c-message_kit__message&quot; data-qa=&quot;message_container&quot; data-qa-unprocessed=&quot;false&quot; data-qa-placeholder=&quot;false&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__hover c-message_kit__hover--hovered&quot; data-qa-hover=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__actions c-message_kit__actions--default&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__gutter&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__gutter__right&quot; data-qa=&quot;message_content&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__blocks c-message_kit__blocks--rich_text&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message__message_blocks c-message__message_blocks--rich_text&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-block_kit_renderer&quot; data-qa=&quot;block-kit-renderer&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper--first&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_block&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;#LI-JW1&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;1641574863.002600&quot; class=&quot;c-virtual_list__item&quot; data-qa=&quot;virtual-list-item&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__background p-message_pane_message__message c-message_kit__message&quot; data-qa=&quot;message_container&quot; data-qa-unprocessed=&quot;false&quot; data-qa-placeholder=&quot;false&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__hover&quot; data-qa-hover=&quot;true&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__actions c-message_kit__actions--above&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__gutter&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__gutter__right&quot; data-qa=&quot;message_content&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message_kit__blocks c-message_kit__blocks--rich_text&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;c-message__message_blocks c-message__message_blocks--rich_text&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-block_kit_renderer&quot; data-qa=&quot;block-kit-renderer&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper p-block_kit_renderer__block_wrapper--first&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_block&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;#LI-Remote&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com/careers/role/5825658002?gh_jid=5825658002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/215201/paxos.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxos@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c782dc3a-8644-40b8-919b-b98b0cb1b35f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxos]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[French Senior KYC Analyst (Remote in Portugal)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://swissborg.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Porto]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>We are SwissBorg, a FinTech startup headquartered in Lausanne, Switzerland.</div><div><br></div><div>Our flagship product, the SwissBorg app, offers over 550,000+ users the best price and liquidity across 16 fiat and 17 cryptos, as well as giving them the opportunity to earn passive income with our Smart Yield account. Our community is growing fast, with over $1.5 billion in assets under management, a weekly volume of over 250 million, and over 18,000 Premium users.</div><div><br></div><div>This is just the start in our mission to democratise wealth management by building products that allow individuals to manage their crypto assets at the touch of a finger. Whether you’re in Andorra or Zimbabwe, whether your portfolio is worth one dollar or a million, SwissBorg gives you the best tools to learn about digital currencies and manage your wealth.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to join a team of revolutionaries on a mission to decentralise nations? We want to hear from you!</div><div><br></div><div>Mission:</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Due to the growth of our business, SwissBorg is offering an opportunity for a French Senior KYC analyst to join our team in Portugal. If you are motivated, creative and want to learn more about the new financial era, this is your chance to apply!</span></div><br/>What you might be doing:<br/><li>Perform the due diligence on new users, requesting the KYC information, documentation, review and verification of received documentation and making an analytical risk assessment for new users</li><li>Prepare KYC checklists and arrange for review</li><li>Analysis of accounts and user information during review</li><li>Investigate high risk users and reporting where necessary, including Politically Exposed Persons, and obtaining all necessary documentation to complete the user file</li><li>Communicate effectively and efficiently with relevant internal and external parties to obtain KYC documents</li><li>Work on specific projects which may rise from time to time</li><br/>What you might bring:<br/><li>Bachelor degree in law or business administration or country equivalent in a related discipline together with equivalent working experience</li><li>1-2 years of experience in similar position</li><li>Bilingual in English and French</li><li>Strong research and analytical skills</li><li>Sound knowledge of and /or experience in working with FATF Recommendations (Anti-Money Laundering, Countering Terrorism Financing)</li><li>Ability to work on multiple tasks independently with minimal supervision</li><li>Excellent organizational skills required for handling a high volume of work with attention to detail</li><li>Good understanding of Blockchain ecosystem is an advantage</li><li>Experience with AML monitoring and screening is an advantage</li><br/>What you can expect:<br/><li>Competitive salary</li><li>25 days of holidays</li><li>Accident insurance</li><li>Employee premium account</li><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Why you should apply: </b></div><div><br></div><div>- Freedom to build the company of your dreams</div><div>- Learn with (super cool) experts in finance, engineering, AI, psychology and business</div><div>- CHSB bonus based on our meritocratic system</div><div>- We'll provide you with a MacBook and a cutting edge tech stack to help you do your best work</div><div>- Flexible work hours</div><div>- Annual team retreats with colleagues around the world</div><div>- Continuous learning and development opportunities</div><div><br></div><div>Oh and are you planning on having a kid? That’s great! We have a bunch of those: you’ll get time off to enjoy that (other) adventure!&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><i>At SwissBorg, we embrace diversity. We strongly believe that getting to the best outcomes requires different perspectives and backgrounds. We’re committed to openness, curiosity and creating an inclusive culture as we know that diverse teams build better products and generate better ideas. We strongly encourage applications from everyone regardless of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, or disability status.</i></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/02lonwc5XE4" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/swissborg/c7ae7f69-077f-4c93-9b9d-33712eee06a7/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/440178/Swissborg-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[swissborg@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f4703261-2e7b-4b75-af19-fbdfc5e62c02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Swissborg]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[DevOps Lead / Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - United Kingdom, London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div>We are building a centralised DevOps engineering team in Europe to improve, scale and automate our business critical Cloud-based architecture.</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a seasoned DevOps Lead for the Binance Cloud and Infrastructure team who can help to build and cultivate the centralised DevOps engineering team, remaining hands-on and highly-technical in the early days, and driving the solutions and architecture to be highly secure, performant, reliable and automated.&nbsp;</div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Build the team by hiring qualified DevOps engineers and architects to further build and optimise the Binance infrastructure, platform and solutions</li><li>Lead the team to design and implement the DevOps architecture and automation solutions including infrastructure security, automated provisioning, CI/CD pipeline</li><li>Coach your team to drive for results with continuous improvements on technical skills, architectural thinking and communication efficiency</li><li>Ensure performance and availability of infrastructure at all times</li><li>Deploy and operate Kubernetes clusters</li><li>Stay curious and continuously optimise system security, performance, availability and scalability </li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>At least 5 years of experience as senior or principal DevOps engineer (or equivalent role) working on large-scale projects and architecture</li><li>Strong hands-on experience and skills on Docker, Kubernetes, infrastructure design (networking, load balancing, CDN, middleware including message queue - Kafka, RabbitMQ, etc), Automation (Ansible, Terraform, CloudFormation, etc) and CI/CD Pipeline (Jenkins).</li><li>Experience on Infrastructure as Code, GitOps and Cloud Native</li><li>Expert level understanding and hands-on experience with AWS</li><li>Solid experience and mindset on Cloud based security solution and architecture design and implementation</li><li>Corresponding development experiences on micro-services based frontend and backend applications are preferred.</li><li>Ideally 3+ years of experience in team management</li><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">#LI-Remote</span></div><div><br></div><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/b476290e-409d-436b-9dc3-a5e1127fc5b1/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, CBDC, RippleX]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Hyper-Accelerating the Internet of Value.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We champion the builders of tomorrow by providing the infrastructure, tools, services, programs and support for creation on one of the world’s fastest, most sustainable and consistently reliable public blockchain - XRPL. By supporting an open community of developers, they can advance the solutions and innovation needed to allow businesses, consumers, institutions and governments to fuel the engine of a new digital economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;RippleX operates on the belief that realizing the Internet of Value hinges on how easily new technology works for more people, and how effectively we can change the way the world operates today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;RippleX &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;is helping more people participate in the digital economy through:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Practical support and capabilities to develop applications that move digital value faster and more easily&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Empowering a community that’s democratizing the digital economy&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The expertise of a technology company that is known for vision and pragmatism&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Blockchain infrastructure that is supported by RippleX and owned by everyone&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We have a big vision and the ambition to match. We are seeking the same in engineers. You also see the huge potential of this technology and have the entrepreneurial spirit and technical excellence to realize the vision we have.There is a lot of work to get there but we are committed to building out the best team to achieve this.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role is based in San Francisco.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support and create tools and services that surprise and delight the community of developers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with other external entrepreneurs and ecosystem stakeholders to continuously improve the speed, scalability, and functionality of the XRP Ledger and the tooling around it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You love programming!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in the full software development lifecycle, from software design and requirements gathering to unit and integration testing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in either front-end or backend development, preferable both, but must be interested in delivering end-to-end features&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have worked on open source projects, developer platforms, and/or API-driven businesses&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s in Computer Science or similar + 5 years of hands on Software Development experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are experienced working with any of: Typescript/Javascript, Java, Rust, Go, or Python&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are excited about blockchains, the technical details and the potential benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You seek to deeply understand the low-level details of the technologies you work with and the problems you work on&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You look to solve problems with simple solutions, rather than technically perfect ones&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Thrive in autonomy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice &lt;/a&gt;and our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/ca-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;California Applicant Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; for reference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3823757?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[IT Systems Engineer (remote)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Latoken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote Worldwide]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>LATOKEN</strong> is a next-gen crypto exchange focused on the startups’ token market with a current $1.2 T value. We are the Initial Exchange Offering and VC-backed tokens categories leader, serving more than 200 primary placements and 400 VC tokens. Traders gave us 25k 5-star reviews in Google play and Applestore for simplicity to discover and buy startups’ and VC-backed tokens.</p><p><strong><strong>Today, is a great moment to join us as crypto is expanding into mainstream financial market.</strong></strong></p><p><strong>Role:</strong> IT Systems Engineer.</p><p><strong>Unit:</strong> OPERATIONS.</p><p><strong>Role Mission: IT systems are stable, secure, up-to-date, and documented</strong>.</p><ul></ul><ul></ul><ol></ol><p><strong>Details:</strong></p><p><strong>- Story</strong>: Teammates need stable, secure, up-to-date, and documented IT systems that support the company business operations so operations are efficient and not interrupted.</p><p><strong>- Key PROBLEM's</strong>:</p><ul><li>Internal systems uptime, &gt; 99,5% in Q1 2022.</li><li>Average time to repair, &lt;30 minutes in Q1 2022.</li><li>Internal Systems on the latest stable release, &gt;60% in Q1 2022.</li><li>All Initial sowtware setup proccesses documented in Q1 2022.</li><li>Internal Systems on Zabbix monitoring &gt; 99% in Q1 2022.</li><li>Support tasks accounting/management is automated &gt; 80% in Q1 2022.</li><li>Average waiting for support response and fix time &lt; 10 minutes in Q1 2022.</li></ul><p><strong>- How</strong>:</p><ul><li>Deploy and manage business-critical applications</li><li>Collaborate with engineering to coordinate on IT policies</li><li>Build policies and scripts to support infrastructure</li><li>Develop and maintain documentation for supported applications, processes</li><li>Participate in general IT operations and user support</li></ul><p><strong>- Constraints</strong>: The introduction of new systems should be approved by the CEO<br></p><p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p><ul><li>Setting up and supporting Docker compute environments;</li><li>Developing automation workflows and integrations for repetitive or manual tasks;</li><li>Supporting Linux and Windows.</li></ul><ul></ul><p><strong>Requirement skills and experience:</strong></p><ul><li>3+ years of experience administering SaaS and self-hosted applications like Okta, Google Workspace, Slack, Zoom, AmoCRM;</li><li>Experience setting up and supporting Docker compute environments;</li><li>Knowledge of configuration management and source control tools;</li><li>Hands-on experience supporting Linux and Windows;</li><li>2+ years experience with Python for administrative tasks automation.</li></ul><p><strong>Why LATOKEN:</strong></p><ul><li><strong>Build the future</strong>. Level up the financial system. Put it at fingertips, so everybody can use the money to build and be a stakeholder of the future.</li><li><strong>Culture.</strong>Level up your and our culture until we and the world have advancement in culture deserving to be spread with our products. We call it visionary doers culture.</li><li><strong>Raise the bar.</strong>Any hire raises our bar, and you will be the bar raiser for us and newcomers.</li><li><strong>Be stakeholder.</strong>You build a product helping people's success. People pay for it, and you get a stake in these future payments as a LATOKEN shareholder.</li><li><strong>Lead.</strong> We are the largest in the world "IPO" platform for digital assets.</li></ul><p><strong>Feel a great fit—apply now </strong>or forward to a great candidate.</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ikbGulIPQs0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.breezy.hr/p/e0ff7dc78a4d01-it-systems-engineer-remote/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/178323/latoken.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[latoken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[ad8a3cbd-f1ed-4400-b372-af94f5f06cb4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Latoken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Trust & Compliance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BitGo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.bitgo.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[United States, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;BitGo is the leader in digital asset financial services, providing institutional investors with liquidity, custody, and security solutions. In 2020, BitGo launched Prime Trading and Lending, as well as BitGo Portfolio and Tax, providing clients with a full-stack solution for digital assets. In 2018, it launched BitGo Trust Company, the first qualified custodian purpose-built for storing digital assets. BitGo processes over 20% of all global Bitcoin transactions, and supports over 250 coins and tokens. BitGo’s customer base includes the world&#39;s largest cryptocurrency exchanges and institutional investors and spans more than 50 countries. BitGo is backed by Goldman Sachs, Craft Ventures, Digital Currency Group, DRW, Galaxy Digital Ventures, Redpoint Ventures, and Valor Equity Partners.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitGo is looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Senior &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; who will join our Custody Platform Engineering Team and help us build new features and applications for our enterprise clients. BitGo processes a significant amount of cryptocurrency transactions so our applications need to be fast, accurate, scalable and secure. Our integrated platforms interact with a number of exchanges, agencies, and governments around the world, and we use the best technology the industry offers to build them.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This role may be worked remotely from anywhere within the United States.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build strong, resilient, and robust APIs, libraries, and services to power our wallet services: hot and cold wallets, indexing, staking, and SDK services&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own functionality and scalability features by taking responsibility from inception to deployment and customer integration&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expose and document functionality to the UI, third-party developers, and our internal and external tooling&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate closely with all engineering teams to ensure consistency in understanding of technical requirements and overall work quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Provide mentorship to your peers in the broader engineering team through code reviews and education on best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Experience:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for teammates who share and practice our values: open communication, transparency, taking ownership, and high level of craftsmanship. We are looking for coworkers who share our vision and mission: deliver trust in digital assets.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Required&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least 5 years of back-end, server-side software development&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong experience with Node.js&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mongo DB expertise&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Solid experience with RESTful API design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong experience with message brokers (such as Kafka)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great with unit and functional testing and debugging&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in Git/GitHub and branching methodologies, code review tools, CI tools, JIRA, Confluence, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great at algorithm design, problem solving, and complexity analysis&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding and experience working in the financial industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding and strong interest in cryptocurrencies and blockchain industry&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with any of the following: API and SDK services, digital wallets, clearing and settlement, lending, etc.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with Kubernetes, Docker, Golang, TypeScript&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with large-scale, real-time, and distributed applications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong data-redactor-tag=&quot;strong&quot;&gt;Why Join BitGo?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;Disrupting an industry takes vision, innovation, passion, technical chops, drive to deliver, collaboration, and execution. Join a team of great people who strive for excellence and personify our corporate values of ownership, craftsmanship, and open communication. We are looking for new colleagues who bring innovative ways of thinking and problem solving, and who want risks to be part of the team that changes the world’s financial markets.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;Here are some of the benefits of working at BitGo:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Competitive base salary, bonus and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;100% company paid&amp;nbsp;health insurance for employee, partner and dependents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Up to 4% 401k company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Paid parental leave&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Free custom lunches, dinners and snacks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Computer equipment and workplace furniture to suit your needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Great colleagues and inspiring startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li class=&quot;li1&quot;&gt;Benefits may vary based on location&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;Cryptocurrencies are the most disruptive change the financial services industry has seen in years. Join us and you’ll be able to look back and say you were part of the team that transformed investing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: justify;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yGR7NLjXslU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitgo/jobs/5823119002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175514/birgo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitgo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b720d671-6d88-4863-a59d-ea5d1c6feea8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BitGo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Recruiting Coordinator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Digital Assets Holding]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://digitalasset.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Digital Asset&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset helps companies of all sizes and across industries get distributed applications to market faster, and stay there longer. At the core of our service offering is DAML (daml.com), the open source and platform-independent smart contract framework that enables developers to write an application once and deploy it anywhere. Today, we work with some of the largest companies in the world to harness the transformative power of smart contracts - a component of the distributed ledger technology (DLT) stack - and change the way applications are developed, deployed and used to solve real-world business challenges.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset is a global company with offices in New York, London, Budapest, Zurich, Hong Kong, and Sydney.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As we grow our team, we will maintain the dynamic, collaborative and pragmatic way of working that has grounded our efforts from the beginning.&amp;nbsp; If you seek to develop solutions others have yet to contemplate, this opportunity may be right for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Recruiting Coordinator collaborates with the firm’s recruiters and business stakeholders to drive the hiring process forward while ensuring a seamless all-around recruiting experience, both internally and externally.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Recruiting Coordinator at DA, you will work closely with our hiring managers and recruiters to ensure a positive interview experience for all candidates. We’re looking for someone who is resourceful and thrives under pressure. This position will rely heavily on your ability to effectively manage competing priorities. You will be part of a team that is responsible for developing, implementing, and executing on a broad recruiting strategy, with an emphasis on efficiency and overall value generation (i.e., hiring awesome people!).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a self-starter to join our TA team, focusing on coordinating recruiting activities.&amp;nbsp; You will help post job specs, interact directly with candidates, schedule and follow up on interviews, and help us scale our recruiting process as we continue to grow as a global organization. Most importantly, the ideal candidate will support the recruiting team and hiring managers by coordinating high volume interviews while ensuring a strong, positive candidate experience.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ideal candidate might not have any prior recruitment experience, but is looking to break into Talent/Human Resources, is exceptionally detail-oriented, organized and inquisitive.&amp;nbsp; This is a tremendous developmental opportunity for the right person.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate with the internal recruiting team, including hiring managers, to post the job spec and set up the role in our ATS (Greenhouse).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Schedule phone, video and in-person interviews for active searches, and monitor to ensure that everything flows smoothly.&amp;nbsp; Support changes to the schedule, when necessary.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the candidate experience, ensuring timely communication throughout the interview process.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serve as the DA host for candidates interviewing in person in the New York office and coordinate with colleagues in other jurisdictions to ensure a similar experience is provided to the candidates.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track recruiting activities and provide candidate status in a weekly report to help assess and improve the process and results.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Inform hiring managers of progress within their open position.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help act on, develop and maintain our commitment to a diverse and inclusive hiring process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Criteria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At least one (1) year of experience as a recruiting coordinator, admin or intern&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Self-starter, curious and always willing to step in to help the team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Highly organized and detail-oriented&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent time management and ability to multitask&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong verbal and written communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficient with Google docs, Office 365, etc.; able to learn new systems quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills and the ability to interact with professionals at all levels, both internally and externally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Creative and proactive approach to problem solving&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Willingness to take ownership of a wide range of responsibilities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect With Us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a rare opportunity to help define an industry and join a dynamic team of technology innovators.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Digital Asset is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, national origin, sex, religion, sexual orientation, age, disability, citizenship status, veteran status or any other basis protected by applicable law. If and as required by applicable law, all persons hired to work at Digital Asset will be required to verify identity and eligibility to work in the location for which they have an offer to work and to complete the necessary employment eligibility verification documents upon hire. Applicants with disabilities who require accommodation should contact &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;mailto:recruiting@digitalasset.com&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;recruiting@digitalasset.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As part of our commitment to equal opportunity, Digital Asset believes that all employees should receive equal pay for equal work and is committed to this principle in its pay structure. DA also offers family-friendly benefits in addition to flexible work arrangements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/digitalasset/jobs/3819176?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/289153/digital-asset-holdings-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[digitalassets@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b9e3329f-7812-4695-a1f7-5b094cbac58f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Digital Assets Holding]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Technical Product Manager - Data & Analytics]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://mythical.games/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are Mythical Games. A venture-backed next-generation game technology company at the intersection of video games and economics led by industry veterans. Our goal is to lead the industry with the launch of exceptional video game experiences that leverage distributed ledger technology, while also providing a platform of robust tools that will allow any other game developers to do the same.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a highly-skilled &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senior Technical Product Manager, Data &amp;amp; Analytics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to join our growing team of data professionals, working to build best-in-class analytics products for our gaming, marketplace, and brand teams. The Sr. TPM, Data &amp;amp; Analytics role at Mythical Games presents an opportunity for a highly-technical and detail-oriented Product Manager to take their career to the next level by joining the most exciting company at the intersection of Gaming, E-commerce, and Blockchain. In this role, you will work with a diverse set of stakeholders to organize analytical requirements, build a prioritized roadmap for our data products, and see them through to completion and adoption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This role will report to our Head of Data &amp;amp; Intelligence Products.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Guide data product definition, strategy, and long-term vision at Mythical, both internally and externally&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own technical design and implementation of analytic systems and alignment of engineering efforts&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead enablement and drive adoption of analytics products&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with stakeholders to design and run experiments to inform product direction&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create flexible systems and data structures to allow for rapid iteration&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Steward and document comprehensive system design, including integrations with multiple data providers and tracking sources of truth&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Basic Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Academic degree and deep training in a technical discipline such as Computer Science, Mathematics, Statistics, Economics/Finance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2+ years of experience designing and building complex analytic experiences&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Programming experience in a general purpose language, SQL or Python preferred&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience designing ETL pipelines and data interfaces&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Detail-oriented and exceptional problem-solving skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding communication and interpersonal skills: experience collaborating with engineers, product managers, and executives&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Highly-organized with proven ability to manage multiple initiatives simultaneously&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with analytic experiences, data pipelines, and management systems/frameworks such as Docker and Kubernetes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with the GCP suite including BigQuery, Composer, and Cloud Functions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Have previously conducted technology enablement for users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortable operating in cloud-first, *nix-centric environments&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Interest in and proficiency with blockchain solutions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passion for video games&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Past work experience in both larger companies and startups&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our team values diversity and believes that it strengthens our games, products, and communities. We strongly encourage POC, folks with disabilities, those belonging to the LGBTQIA+ communities, and folks across all gender identities to apply.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We offer our team benefits such as (but not limited to) high-quality Vision, Dental, and Health Care, generous Parental Leave, and Unlimited PTO to ensure that they actually take time off without the stress of needing to accrue time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you need assistance around accommodations due to a disability, please reach out to accessibility@mythical.games. We’ll be with you as soon as possible; our goal is to ensure an accessible and equitable interview process for everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/Zfsp0FQ5X8s" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/mythicalgames/jobs/4907487003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/351124/Mythical-Logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[info@mythical.games]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[541f8953-1749-4738-90d8-efd04dd286d1]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Mythical Games]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[MLRO and Compliance Officer (UK-based) ]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Keyrock]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.keyrock.eu/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Brussels,]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Keyrock is expanding!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keyrock SA (the Group) was founded in 2017 and has quickly grown from 3 to over 50 people today. As an industry recognized liquidity provider and market maker, Keyrock SA is a leading European creator of algorithmic trading technology in the digital asset space. With VC backing, a constantly expanding global client base and revenues growth 13x in 2021, Keyrock is one of Belgium’s and Europe’s fastest-growing fintech companies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;We’re currently active on over 80 exchanges and count numerous marketplaces and asset issuers among our clients, including some of the best-known companies in the crypto space. We strive to operate according to highest standards of compliance and integrity - both in spirit and in regulatory scrutiny we succumb to.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keyrock&#39;s beating heart is its diverse, quantitative and technical team filled with software engineers, digital scientists and PhDs, who themselves are supported by university professors, industry-leading experts and a strong management team. Over the years Keyrock has become a company that is both idealistic and practical.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keyrock is setting up an office in London and needs to recruit its first MLRO and Compliance Officer.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;We are looking for:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;An experienced, driven and entrepreneurial MLRO and Compliance Officer to work in our newly opened UK entity and ensure top standard of compliance across the UK business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Job description: MLRO and Compliance Officer (SMF 17, 16)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0;&quot;&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Responsible for the oversight of all compliance and AML activities;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Arial;color:#2d2d2d;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Assist the Board in ensuring the business continues to meet its regulatory obligations;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Managing internal controls activities;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Arial;color:#2d2d2d;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Delivering high-quality compliance advice, oversight and challenge to the business;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Ensuring the firm’s policies and procedures are being communicated effectively to all relevant employees;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Ensuring that appropriate compliance and financial crime trainings are provided to employees;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Managing the relationship and regulatory returns with UK regulatory bodies;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keeping up to date with regulatory developments;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Challenging Keyrock&#39;s systems and controls in respect of risk management;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Reporting to the Board and Group head of regulatory compliance;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Working closely with the Group head of regulatory compliance and other heads of business lines. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Background and experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0;&quot;&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;+5 years in a FCA regulated MLRO/ compliance role;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Arial;color:#2d2d2d;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Experience working in a MiFID Investment Firm or Credit Institution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Deep knowledge of the UK regulatory environment;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Understanding of capital markets and banking systems;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;A relevant degree, preferably &amp;nbsp;in business or law, is required;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;A compliance qualification for example ACAMS or a Masters in a related field would be advantageous.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Competences and skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0;&quot;&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Project management including the ability to oversee implementation of complex projects;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Problem-solving and decision-making skills, with the ability to analyse complex information to identify the key issue/action and drive resolution;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Operational excellence;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Strong attention to details;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Arial;color:#2d2d2d;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.716;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Strong written and verbal communication skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10.5pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Thrive in an autonomous environment;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Team player;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:7pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:#ffffff;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Have a minimum of 5 years of professional experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;margin-left: 36pt;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:7pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:underline;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Our recruitment philosophy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;We believe the most important aspect of our recruitment process is self-awareness: we are looking for people who have a clear understanding of themselves and what they are looking for in their professional career. That means that we expect to work with people who not only have the right skills, but who have also made the conscious decision to look for a company in our industry and with our characteristics.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:700;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:underline;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Our offer&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul style=&quot;margin-top:0;margin-bottom:0;&quot;&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;A competitive salary package, including benefits that you choose and manage according to your needs and those of your family (car/bike, meal vouchers, phone and internet subscription, health insurance, 25 days &amp;nbsp;off, etc.)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Complete autonomy in your time management thanks to flexible working hours and the opportunity to work remotely&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;The freedom to create your own entrepreneurial experience by being part of a team of people in search of excellence who all receive stock options from the first year&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;list-style-type:disc;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;text-align: justify;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:7pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;A ton of fun in a thriving and multicultural environment, with colleagues enjoying regular team building activities&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; style=&quot;line-height:1.38;background-color:#ffffff;margin-top:0pt;margin-bottom:0pt;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-size:10pt;font-family:Roboto,sans-serif;color:#000000;background-color:transparent;font-weight:400;font-style:normal;font-variant:normal;text-decoration:none;vertical-align:baseline;white-space:pre;white-space:pre-wrap;&quot;&gt;Keyrock offers you both a career and a large range of benefits that we will gladly discuss in the course of the application process.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://keyrock.freshteam.com/jobs/k9iaw-O9Dm9E/mlro-and-compliance-officer-uk-based?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/831880/keyrock-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[keyrock@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5b5712b4-ea1b-4843-8efd-ea04303877b0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Keyrock]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Legal & Compliance ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director, Investor Relations & Capital Raising]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[TrustToken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.trusttoken.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York / California]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 18pt">About TrustToken</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>TrustToken is freeing money.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">As traditional finance is being challenged by cryptocurrencies, our team is assembling the fundamental building blocks to deliver the unprecedented opportunity and greater accessibility of decentralized finance to anyone with an internet connection.&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">We're known for two products: TrueFi, the first project to bring collateral-free lending to the blockchain; and TrueCurrencies, the world's most trusted asset-backed stablecoins, in five denominations.&nbsp;</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">TrueFi, launched by TrustToken in November 2020, is the world’s leading uncollateralized lending protocol, offering lenders transparent and competitive earning opportunities and borrowers the ease of fast loans that maximize their capital efficiency. Borrowers build credit scores by using the platform, paving the way for TrueFi’s other innovation: on-chain credit ratings.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">Our TrueCurrencies (TUSD, TGBP, TAUD, TCAD, THKD) are the world’s most trusted stablecoins. Each is fully collateralized and attested live on-chain, leading the way in transparency in our industry. Collectively, these stablecoins now move billions of dollars around the world each month, including across +100 trading partners like Binance, Huobi, and OKEx. TUSD users enjoy lighting-fast transactions, easy minting and redemptions, and obsessive customer service.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">Our team is global with employees based in San Francisco, Ireland and remote, made up of talented people from Google, Facebook, and Coinbase. We're backed by luminaries at a16z crypto, Blocktower, Founders Fund, Alameda Research, Stanford StartX, and other top global investors from North America, Europe, and Asia.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">Our team is on a mission to empower people by opening access to financial opportunities. We believe that new technology will allow us to make financial freedom as accessible as the internet, and each day, we're working on the fundamental elements to make this world possible. It’s going to be a long journey, and we’re just at the beginning.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 15px">TrustToken is seeking to hire a Director of Investor Relations &amp; Capital Raising. In this high impact role, you will be responsible for building and maintaining relationships with family offices, high net worth individuals and institutional investors to originate new investors and lead the fundraising process for portfolios managed on the TrueFi blockchain lending protocol.</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 15px">TrueFi currently manages approximately $1 billion in liquidity and has originated over $1 billion in loans in the last twelve months. </span></div><div><span style="font-size: 15px">While the existing borrower base primarily consists of crypto-focused hedge funds, TrueFi is now onboarding traditional finance borrowers to broadly diversify across both non-crypto and crypto borrower prospects. </span></div><div><span style="font-size: 15px">As the current loan portfolio aggressively expands over the next twelve months, lender/investor fundraising will be critical to support hyper-growth in new loan originations.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Develop and lead the go-to-market strategy to build a family office and institutional investor pipeline.</li><li>Manage the day-to-day organization, execution, and funding of participating investors.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Educate clients and prospects on alternative credit investments and crypto generally.&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Develop a sales projection with defined targets to raise institutional capital on TrueFi.</li><li>Collaborate with business development, sales, product, and engineering teams to communicate and manage client needs, preferences and investment criteria.</li><li>&nbsp;Identify and articulate product enhancements to improve investor experience.</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>7+ years of experience in a fundraising role with a HF, PE, VC or similar fund.</li><li>Extensive network of family office and institutional investor relationships with a proven track record of successfully having raised capital for new and existing funds.</li><li>Deep familiarity with alternative fund products and investment preferences of family office and institutional investor base.&nbsp;&nbsp;</li><li>Experience leading a structured fundraising process including planning, organization and execution.</li><li>Ability to succeed in a remote environment and willingness to safely travel if necessary.</li><div>Does this sound like you? We’d love to hear from you if so.</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 24px">Equal opportunity</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">We’re proud to be an equal opportunity employer. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. Apply today and let us know what makes you unique</span><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 24px">Learn more about TrustToken</span></div><div><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/trusttoken/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></div><div><a href="https://blog.trusttoken.com/" class="postings-link">Check out our blog</a></div><div><a href="http://www.trusttoken.com" class="postings-link">Visit www.trusttoken.com</a></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/lPnbgyc-ZIA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/trusttoken/dd4be7ac-c72d-46ef-b7c5-6ab70ef8b4f2/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/193497/trusttoken.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[trusttoken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[aea100fb-f5aa-4c1e-9fd3-2896483d7f46]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[TrustToken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Marketing]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[ChainSafe Systems]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://chainsafe.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe Systems is currently seeking a Head of Marketing to establish and lead a new marketing department from the ground up. As our first Marketing hire, you’ll have the opportunity to have a tremendous impact, but it is important that you are a self-starter with an entrepreneurial spirit. You will be working very closely with the leadership team to understand our marketing needs across the organization and drive initiatives to address them. You will build the marketing team, both from a processes and hiring perspective, while contributing to critical marketing efforts to help push ChainSafe forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ChainSafe is a unique company in a nascent space that is growing quickly and building a stellar global reputation. &quot;Beyond offering experience across major blockchain ecosystems to our team, we provide an open, inclusive, and supportive environment where we help folks reach their full potential as a human and as a professional.”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Culture fit and alignment to our core values are extremely important to us. We are fueled by an immense intellectual curiosity of what technology can do and the impact it can have. We are building the next generation of web infrastructure and decentralized systems and you will thrive here if you are intensely driven by tackling challenges in a fast-moving enviornment with a tight knit team.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is a very exciting time as Web3 and blockchain technology is continuously pushing the boundaries of what is possible and new opportunities arise on a daily basis. It is a great time to join and this position is both fun and extremely rewarding!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build a new marketing department at ChainSafe from the ground up, including establishing the department’s strategy &amp;amp; best practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Direct the high-level competitive positioning for our innovative Web3 products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with our product teams to help with product marketing, including value propositions, market segmentation and go-to-market strategies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work hands-on for key organizational marketing projects, including product marketing and online marketing initiatives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Recruit, scale, coach and mentor the marketing team as needed to help meet ChainSafe’s marketing needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuously look for ways to improve our marketing practices&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Communicate effectively with leadership and the organization to influence outcomes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and manage marketing budgets &amp;amp; costs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop branding plans &amp;amp; campaigns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s degree or time-equivalent working experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years working at a startup with a role focused on marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of hiring &amp;amp; managing other marketing professionals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated understanding of the techniques and methods of product marketing and online marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to learn multiple functional areas of business – engineering, design, finance, sales, or marketing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to engage with engineers, designers, and company leaders in a constructive and collaborative relationship&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with and passion for Web3&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience doing marketing for a SaaS product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience building and leading a marketing team at a startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Professional experience in development, product management, sales engineering or another technical role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why join us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We offer fast opportunities for personal growth, mentorship, professional development funding, tons of autonomy and responsibility, a results-driven environment, close collaboration with an international team, exposure to a wide array of ecosystems and trailblazing technologies, and flexible work hours.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At ChainSafe, we are a compassionate group of builders and makers, working to bring our ideas to life. You’ll be part of a team that believes in the vital importance of community and contributing to advance humanity with open-source and decentralized technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chainsafe.io/corevalues&quot;&gt;We care deeply about our values and look for these in every team member:&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; A dedication to self-improvement and professional development; a commitment to community and collaboration; a drive for accountability, diligence, and autonomy; and above fostering a place of acceptance, friendliness, and compassion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tell us who you are and learn more about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are ready to join us, assemble your highlights (Portfolio, LinkedIn) and show us your best work. Get ready to have incredible conversations about your work. For our team’s project highlights, explore our &lt;a href=&quot;https://discord.com/invite/xSAwrnCWcg&quot;&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/chainsafe&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://chainsafe.io/projects&quot;&gt;website&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;We welcome your fresh perspectives and ideas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;At ChainSafe, diversity and inclusion is more than a statement; equality and accessibility are guiding principles embedded in who we are - and why we do what we do. Our leadership is committed to continuously improving their own level of education to make the fairest and inclusive hiring and performance decisions from an informed perspective. We recognize the benefits of a diverse team and aspire to embed respect for all people into our culture, values, and day-to-day practices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If at any time we can provide accommodations to facilitate your application and interview process, please let us know. We will strive to meet your needs.&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainsafesystems/jobs/4299467004?gh_jid=4299467004&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/820874/chainsafe-systems-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainsafe@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5f6a040d-27de-4887-98d1-3606d387ad93]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[ChainSafe Systems]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[System Administrator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[BitGo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.bitgo.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div&gt;BitGo is the leader in custody and security solutions with over $60B in assets under custody. Founded in 2013, BitGo is the first digital asset company to focus exclusively on serving institutional clients. In 2018, it launched BitGo Trust Company, the first qualified custodian purpose-built for storing digital assets and established BitGo New York Trust in 2021. BitGo also offers market leading trading, lending, and borrowing services and supports over 400 digital assets on its platform. BitGo provides the security and operational backbone for more than 500 institutional clients in 50 countries, including many of the world’s top cryptocurrency exchanges and platforms.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BitGo is looking for an experienced&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;System Administrator&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;who will join our Security Team in Palo Alto. The System Administrator to maintain, upgrade and manage our software, hardware and networks. Resourcefulness is a necessary skill in this role. You should be able to diagnose and resolve problems quickly. You should also have the patience to communicate with a variety of interdisciplinary teams and users. Your goal will be to ensure that our technology infrastructure runs smoothly and efficiently.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Install and configure software and hardware.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage network servers and technology tools.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set up accounts and workstations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monitor performance and maintain systems according to requirements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot issues and outages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure security through access controls, backups, and firewalls.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upgrade systems with new releases and models.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop expertise to train staff on new technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Build an internal wiki with technical documentation, manuals, and IT policies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BitGo is looking for people who are passionate about their craft, take full ownership for their work and projects, and believe in a transparent and collaborative culture with the goal of making BitGo successful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Main requirements include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proven experience as a System Administrator, Network Administrator or similar role.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with databases, networks (LAN, WAN) and patch management.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of system security (e.g. intrusion detection systems) and data backup/recovery.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to create scripts in Python, Perl or other languages.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with various operating systems and platforms.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Resourcefulness and problem-solving aptitude.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BS/BA in Information Technology, Computer Science or a related discipline; professional certification is a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with monitoring systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Solid networking knowledge. (OSI network layers, TCP/IP)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minimum of 5 years of relevant experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You are a huge fan of blockchain technology and cryptocurrencies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;50% in office, 50% remote&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive base salary, and stock options&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;100% company paid health insurance for employee, partner and dependents&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Up to 5% 401k company match&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paid parental leave, Paid vacation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free commuter/parking pass; 5 min from Caltrain&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free custom lunches, dinners and snacks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Computer equipment and workplace furniture to suit your needs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Great colleagues and inspiring startup environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Benefits may vary based on location.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yGR7NLjXslU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitgo/jobs/5835043002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175514/birgo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitgo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b720d671-6d88-4863-a59d-ea5d1c6feea8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[BitGo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director of Marketing Operations]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxos]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a regulated blockchain infrastructure company, we use technology to tokenize, custody, trade, and settle assets for enterprise clients like PayPal, Novi, Bank of America, and Interactive Brokers. Paxos is a top-funded blockchain company, with more than $500 million in total funding from leading investors like OakHC/FT, Founders Fund, PayPal Ventures, and Declaration Partners. Together, we empower today’s financial leaders to build a more open, trusted economy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos seeks a nimble, data-driven &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Director of Marketing Operations&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to be responsible for all team processes, MarTech solutions and overall digital marketing strategy and execution. As the first Marketing Operations hire, you will be an essential player/coach responsible for building a new function that drives marketing excellence while serving as a bridge between Marketing and Sales. From growth and demand marketing to customer insights and campaign ROI, we have a lot to build and are eager to meet an energetic leader with a point of view.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As the Director of Marketing Operations, you’ll get to:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design and build out initial phase of Operations org; manage a high performing team&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive annual budgeting/planning process in partnership with the VP of Marketing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Stand up marketing technology stack for improved day-to-day team workflow and actionable visibility of end to end funnel&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with Business Development and Sales to establish the correct measurement processes per business line and improve marketing automation&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with cross-functional teams to develop and coordinate campaign execution across acquisition, engagement, and partnership&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive optimization of lifecycle marketing in partnership with Product Marketers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own performance marketing (SEO/SEM, affiliate, display, all paid) and website in partnership with Content Team and IT&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop a best-in-class approach to gather and elevate the right insights from customers, research and data to share throughout the organization&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Immerse yourself in blockchain technology, cryptocurrency for enterprises and investors, our regulation-first approach, and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your experience should include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;10+ years of progressive experience owning operations within a marketing team for a B2B company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience and knowledge of best in class software, B2B lead generation and funnel management, SEO and paid advertising&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You might also have:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An analytical, pragmatic approach and operate without sacrificing speed for perfection&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to thrive in ambiguity and identify opportunities/solutions while driving cross-functional alignment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A passion and desire to mentor and teach by doing&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll love about Paxos:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos has consistently been named as a “Best Place to Work” by BuiltIn and was listed on the 2021 Forbes Fintech 50. All of our employees have significant ownership and impact on our business, as well as benefits like company equity, health insurance, family leave, a $500 quarterly stipend for development, a $500 stipend for home office setup and unlimited PTO. From team product demos and virtual lounge and learns to care packages and an active Slack #shoutouts channel, there are countless opportunities to connect and make your mark. Help us continue to build a new, open financial system from one of our three offices or right from your home!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2022/01/12/2021-was-just-the-beginning-paxos-will-accelerate-mainstream-digital-asset-adoption-in-2022/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;2021 Paxos Year in Review&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.builtinnyc.com/companies/best-places-to-work-nyc-2022/?utm_medium=exreferral&amp;amp;utm_source=3punknown&amp;amp;utm_campaign=bptw2022&amp;amp;utm_content=na-wcl#paxos&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BuiltIn NYC Names Paxos a 2022 Best Place to Work&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/T_B9-TxFIVM&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Life at Paxos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h5ar-oLO1VY&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos CEO Discusses Crypto, Blockchain and the Future of Finance&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2020/10/21/paypal-launches-new-service-enabling-users-to-buy-hold-and-sell-cryptocurrency/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos &amp;amp; PayPal Bring Crypto to Millions of Users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/10/19/usdp-chosen-for-novi-pilot/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;USDP Stablecoin Chosen for Meta&#39;s Pilot of Novi Digital Wallet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/fintech/2021/#413b4e2631a6&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Forbes Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/29/paxos-raises-300-million-in-series-d-funding-at-2-4-billion-valuation/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Raises $300M in Series D Funding at 2.4B Valuation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/12/02/mercadolibre-is-creating-the-biggest-crypto-market-in-latin-america-paxos-powers-the-experience/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Mercado Libre Creating Biggest Crypto Market in LatAm through Paxos&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/23/paxos-national-trust-receives-occ-conditional-approval-for-de-novo-charter/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos National Trust Receives OCC Conditional Approval for De Novo Charter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/11/29/introducing-prex-crypto-powered-by-paxos/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Powers Prex Crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/13/paxos-supports-interactive-brokers-journey-into-crypto-markets/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Interactive Brokers&#39; Journey into Crypto Markets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/fintech-250-startups-most-promising/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CB Insights Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 250 for Crypto Category&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/30/trust-is-not-an-option-its-a-requirement-paxos-explains-its-unique-approach-to-pioneering-a-new-market/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Flourish Crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Paxos team is made up of passionate people from all over the world with different perspectives and experiences. If this opportunity excites you, but your experience doesn’t perfectly match the description…apply! Unique voices help us build a more open, trusted economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-JM1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-Remote&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com/careers/role/5711796002?gh_jid=5711796002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/215201/paxos.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxos@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c782dc3a-8644-40b8-919b-b98b0cb1b35f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxos]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crypto Research Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,400+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">About the Role</b><span style="font-size: 18px">&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div>This is a fully remote role, we will consider applicants based in North America, South America and Europe.&nbsp;Kraken is expanding its Intelligence team! This is an opportunity to join Kraken’s inhouse team of research experts focused on providing industry insights for market participants and for internal business decisions. As a member of Kraken Intelligence, you will be tasked with exploring and analyzing industry trends, producing highly impactful and original content, working internally with key stakeholders, supporting colleagues, and growing the Intelligence brand. As crypto, Kraken, and the Intelligence team grows, so will you.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>The ideal candidate for this position is a self-starter who is highly ambitious and is not afraid to approach difficult questions, collect and analyze large quantities of data, and deliver concise, actionable reports. Intellectual curiosity and a desire to learn is a must; you should be passionate about exploring all corners of crypto. Interested applicants must be capable of multi-tasking and wearing multiple hats.</div><div><br></div><div>Kraken Intelligence prides itself on being a group of open-minded individuals interested in finding answers, optimizing for the best result, and not letting one’s ego get in the way of decision making. While we are laser focused on providing value both internally and externally, we also like to have fun!</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Support the Manager of Kraken Intelligence in conducting research, unpacking industry developments, and monitoring market trends</li><li>Spearhead external research efforts and develop differentiated content based on research, analytics, and related insights</li><li>Contribute to the team’s content ideation, dissemination strategy, and brand awareness initiatives</li><li>Analyze and produce managerial reports for research KPIs</li><li>Work with other teams in a generalist capacity, as needed</li><li>Support other functions, including corporate and business development, to identify and capture additional value-enhancing opportunities</li><br/>Basic Qualifications<br/><li>Bachelor’s degree in a quantitative field and at least 2+ years of relevant work experience in equity research, investment banking, venture capital, strategy consulting, economics, computer science, or a similar capacity</li><li>Strong communication and presentation skills, and proven ability to translate data into actionable insights</li><li>Existing knowledge of the cryptoasset industry</li><li>Exceptional research and analytical skills and advanced proficiency in Excel </li><li>Detail-oriented with emphasis on quality</li><li>A team player that works well with various functions across the company and can work independently</li><br/>Preferred Qualifications<br/><li>Experience with cryptoasset or traditional market analysis</li><li>The ability to think critically under pressure, simultaneously maintain multiple workflows, and deliver against aggressive deadlines</li><li>Experience with APIs, HTML, Python, SQL, and/or Tableau (or other data visualization tools)</li><li>An understanding of smart contracts, cryptography, tokeneconomics, blockchain technology, and Web 3.0.&nbsp;</li><div>Location Tagging: #EU #US <span style="font-size: 15px">#APAC&nbsp;#LI-Remote </span>#LI-BL1</div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</b></div><div><br></div><div><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link"><b>Follow us on Twitter</b></a></div><div><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link"><b>Catch up on our blog</b></a></div><div><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link"><b>Follow us on LinkedIn</b></a></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/f5d5e6ae-756f-46ca-b478-51a82a145a8d/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Manager, Analytics]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - India]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re Coinbase. We’re the world’s most trusted way to join the crypto revolution, serving more than 73 million accounts in more than 100 countries.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our mission is to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/our-mission-strategy-and-culture-18a92a3bb0fa&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;increase economic freedom around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, and we couldn’t do this without hiring the best people. We’re a group of hard-working overachievers who are deeply focused on building the future of finance and Web 3.0 for our users across the globe, whether they’re trading, storing, staking or using crypto. Know those people who always lead the group project? That’s us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;There are a few things we look for across all hires we make at Coinbase, regardless of role or team. First, we look for candidates who will thrive in a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/culture-at-coinbase-f0e1c2a99aff&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;culture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; like ours, where we default to trust, embrace feedback, and disrupt ourselves. Second, we expect all employees to commit to our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.coinbase.com/coinbase-is-a-mission-focused-company-af882df8804&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;mission-focused approach&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to our work. Finally, we seek people who are excited to learn about and live crypto, because those are the folks who enjoy the intense moments in our sprint and recharge work culture.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ready to #LiveCrypto? Who you are:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve got good vibes. You’re optimistic about the future and determined to get there.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’re never tired of learning. You want to be a pro in bleeding edge tech like DeFi, NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You appreciate direct communication. You’re both an active communicator and an eager listener - because let’s face it, you can’t have one without the other. You’re cool with candid feedback and see every setback as an opportunity to grow.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You can pivot on the fly. Crypto is constantly evolving, so our priorities do, too. What you worked on last month may not be what you work on today, and that excites you. You’re not looking for a boring job.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You have a “can do” attitude. Our teams create high-quality work on quick timelines. Owning a problem doesn’t scare you, but rather empowers you to take 100% responsibility for achieving our mission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You want to be part of a winning team. We’re stronger together, and you’re a person who embraces being pushed out of your comfort zone. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase, Inc. is seeking a full time employee to be part of our Workforce Management (WFM) team.&amp;nbsp; As a Command Center Leader, you’ll build and define Coinbase’s Customer Experience analytics operations and strategy. This includes ownership of all Coinbase support reporting, while also developing a team of analysts, working closely with different stakeholders on their operational reporting needs.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll be doing (ie. job duties):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work closely with the Customer Experience (CX) team to define what are the reports and metrics needed across our operations and the best way to deliver them&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with CX Leadership and cross-functional partners to prioritize work and define impactful ways share insights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Leverage metrics to drive insights and influence business decisions in a global scale&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to frame and break down complex business problems into key components and recommend practical solutions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build a collaborative team environment that fosters efficient execution, innovation, and continuous improvement&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop and support the analytical technologies that give our team timely, flexible, and structured access to their data&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we look for in you (ie. job requirements):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passionate about delivering an excellent Customer Experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Minimum of 3 years of relevant experience in analytics with management experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Expertise in workforce management reporting&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to work with large amounts of data to identify trends and patterns.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Specialist in spreadsheet tools like Excel and Google Sheet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible and adaptable to meeting the evolving needs of a high-growth and fast paced organization.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written and verbal communication skills required&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Able to proactively collaborate with other departments, providing inputs and insights on business metrics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using BI tool such as Looker and Salesforce&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;SQL experience a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience meeting with and presenting information to senior leadership&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;PID_P33713&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Please note that for employees based in the US, Philippines, Canada or Singapore, if your role requires you to be present in a Coinbase office or if you choose to be physically present in a Coinbase office or sponsored location, participate in any in-person gathering (including offsites) or engage in business travel sponsored by Coinbase, you will be required to be fully vaccinated (as defined by applicable law).&amp;nbsp; If you receive an offer, you will receive additional information about the grounds and process for an exemption.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Commitment to Equal Opportunity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is committed to diversity in its workforce and is proud to be an Equal Opportunity Employer.&amp;nbsp; All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, gender, national origin, age, disability, veteran status, sex, gender expression or identity, sexual orientation or any other basis protected by applicable law. Coinbase will also consider for employment qualified applicants with criminal histories in a manner consistent with applicable federal, state and local law.&amp;nbsp; For US applicants, you may view &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/ofccp/pdf/pay-transp_English_unformattedESQA508c.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pay Transparency&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.dol.gov/sites/dolgov/files/WHD/legacy/files/eppac.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Rights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eeoc.gov/sites/default/files/migrated_files/employers/poster_screen_reader_optimized.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Equal Employment Opportunity is the Law&lt;/span&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;notices by clicking on their corresponding links.&amp;nbsp; Additionally, Coinbase participates in the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://static-assets.coinbase.com/e-verify.pdf&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;E-Verify program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; in certain locations, as required by law.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coinbase is also committed to providing reasonable accommodations to individuals with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation because of a disability for any part of the employment process, please send an e-mail to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;accommodations[at]coinbase.com&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and let us know the nature of your request and your contact information.&amp;nbsp; For quick access to screen reading technology compatible with this site &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/chromevox/kgejglhpjiefppelpmljglcjbhoiplfn&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;click here to download&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a free compatible screen reader &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chromevox.com/tutorial/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;(free step by step tutorial can be found here)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Global Data Privacy Notice for Job Candidates and Applicants&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Depending on your location, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) may regulate the way we manage the data of job applicants. Our full notice outlining how data will be processed as part of the application procedure for applicable locations is available &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.coinbase.com/legal/applicant_privacy_notice&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;By submitting your application, you are agreeing to our use and processing of your data as required.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iWA1eLgSmfM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.coinbase.com/careers/3830156?gh_jid=3830156&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143074/coinbase.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[coinbase@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5ca8d11e-b184-412a-9ed3-9fc9125704eb]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Coinbase]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[DRW]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://drw.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRW&lt;/strong&gt; is a technology-driven, diversified principal trading firm. We trade our own capital at our own risk, across a broad range of asset classes, instruments and strategies, in financial markets around the world. As the markets have evolved over the past 25 years, so has DRW – maximizing opportunities to include real estate, cryptoassets and venture capital. With over 1200 employees at our Chicago headquarters and offices around the world, we work together to solve complex problems, challenge consensus and deliver meaningful results. It’s a place of high expectations, deep curiosity and thoughtful collaboration.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Software Development Engineer in Test&lt;/strong&gt; provides mission critical support for our core proprietary trading systems.&amp;nbsp; As a SDET, you will partner closely with the business and with software developers to develop test&amp;nbsp;plans and test cases for various trading platforms that are used globally by trading and research teams across the firm. We are seeking a candidate with a strong background in functional testing and the ability to design and develop both manual and automated test strategies and test cases.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Core Duties:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Set up, maintain, and support testing environments for automated and manual testing for both the QA and software development environments&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide testing environment configuration support for development teams; ensure availability and provide backup QA support during overlapping times for Asia and US-based teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform certification and conformance testing with Asian exchanges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Test market data and order adapters for European exchanges&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop automated regression testing of system functionality using Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop scripts for maintaining, updating, and monitoring test system components&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Troubleshoot issues and bugs discovered in testing to help determine root cause&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide feedback on system functionality to help make improvements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work with operations team to communicate upcoming changes to software systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Help troubleshoot and resolve problems in production systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Reproduce issues discovered in production using the test environments in order to help identify issues and solutions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong programming skills obtained through a degree or equivalent experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated ability to effectively test applications independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical skills, detail orientation and excellent written and verbal communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with automated test frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with scripting languages, primarily Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2+ years of experience working with databases such as SQL or Postgres&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ year of experience working on Linux operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience in testing trading systems and strategies is a big plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For more information about DRW&#39;s processing activities and our use of job applicants&#39; data, please view our Privacy Notice at &lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;California residents, please review the&amp;nbsp;California Privacy Notice&amp;nbsp;for information about certain legal rights at&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&quot;&gt;https://drw.com/california-privacy-notice&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/MdwEImeQcx8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/drweng/jobs/3829874?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145892/drw.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[drw@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bf32acf8-cf47-410b-aa59-74974c4d6afd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[DRW]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Creative Program Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Global]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a Creative Program Manager to join our Central Marketing team. </div><div><br></div><div><b>This is a full-time remote position and can be based in any global locations. </b></div><br/>Responsibilities: <br/><li>Program Management: As part of the creative team, work closely with the Creative PM Lead to develop and implement optimal workflows, ensuring the greatest efficiency among the creative teams</li><li>Manage and optimise day-to-day creative workflow between internal stakeholders and external partners to ensure creative work quality and delivery in a timely manner</li><li>Own and manage creative team’s daily, weekly and quarterly workload reporting / dashboards and analyse data to provide regular updates and accurate overviews</li><li>Manage tools and licenses for creative development, asset libraries, and collaboration platforms</li><li>Responsible for managing new third party engagement and assessing new vendors / suppliers capability / professionalism and proposing the best possible vendors based on quality / cost</li><li>Collaborate closely with the internal creative team to ensure quality briefs, brand coherency and consistency across all creative output</li><li>Development of global Swag Management system</li><div><br></div><li>Project Management: End-to-end project management for cross-functional tasks</li><li>Develop project plans and timelines</li><li>Closely follow up, coordinate and collaborate while establishing and maintaining effective working relationships with internal and external stakeholders</li><li>Provide daily / timely project updates</li><br/>Requirements: <br/><li>At least 3-4 years of professional experience in established digital agencies, consultancies, or in-house PM roles</li><li>A clear communicator - ability to express complex ideas clearly and succinctly, while collaborating closely with teams outside of the Creative team</li><li>Ability to single handedly and independently critically assess and develop data tools required</li><li>Expertise in Google Workspace is a must</li><li>PgMP/PMI/PMP/Agile certifications is a plus&nbsp;</li><li>Knowledge and interest in the world of Binance and cryptocurrency is a plus</li><li>Proficiency in project management tool is a plus</li><li>Fluency in English required, Mandarin is a plus</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/5c4bb03b-d5a9-4757-864f-d50a01a770d4/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
