<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Operations Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">About the Role</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">This is a fully remote role.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Given our explosive growth and the incredible opportunity in front of us, we are working to innovate across all aspects of the company and execute on our highly ambitious plans.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Business Operations team works closely with all functional areas of the company to improve Kraken’s effectiveness and efficiency. The team acts as a thought partner to leadership across the company, helping them understand and improve operational processes.&nbsp;&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">On a daily basis, the team delivers actionable data-driven insights and recommendations that helps the company stay organized and coordinated.&nbsp;</span></div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Lead the execution of high-impact, cross-functional projects</li><li>Establish partnerships across functions, gaining a deep understanding of their operating models and identifying opportunities for innovation and improvement&nbsp;</li><li>Bring workflow management and automation tools to bear in order to improve process infrastructure for scaling and performance</li><li>Establish strong working relationships across functions and management levels, working collaboratively and independently to drive improvement&nbsp;</li><li>Bring stellar analytical methods to complex challenges around scale, operating models and cross-functional processes</li><li>Own initial delivery of recommendations, demonstrating proof-of-concepts and real business outcomes while spurring change&nbsp;</li><li>Cultivate a deep understanding of what makes Kraken tick and readily identify and address potential blockers to progress</li><li>Mentor team members and drive continuous improvement of our team’s ways of working</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Bachelor’s degree</li><li>5+ years experience in a similar role</li><li>Proactive communicator with excellent verbal, written and interpersonal communication skills</li><li>Passion for solving complex problems and building scalable processes</li><li>Creativity, adaptability, tenacity, a sense of urgency, and a hands-on, roll-up your sleeves work ethic</li><li>Strong interest in and familiarity with both cryptocurrency and traditional financial industries</li><li>Experience and proven track record in business process management consulting or operations roles in the financial services or technology industries</li><li>Experience navigating complex operational hurdles in hyper-growth companies</li><div>Location Tagging: #EU #US #CANADA <span style="font-size: 15px">#LI-Remote</span></div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/iG-bpAnRvqM" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/26ec25a6-0971-49c9-98c6-63cd77f4379e/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior UX Designer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Wintermute]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.wintermute-trading.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Wintermute</b></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">&nbsp; </b></div><div>Wintermute is a hyper-growth fintech startup and one of the largest players in the global digital asset markets. We provide liquidity algorithmically across most cryptocurrency exchanges and trading platforms, as well as support high profile blockchain projects and traditional financial institutions moving into crypto.</div><div><br></div><div>Culturally, we combine the best traits of both trading companies and technology startups. As a trading company, we manage hundreds of millions in assets, trade more than $5B+/day across dozens of trading platforms and are highly profitable in doing so. As a technology startup, we build, innovate and move incredibly fast, we create best-in-class liquidity products that create more efficient markets. We believe that traditional finance has to change and we are on a mission to define and build the decentralized future of finance.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Wintermute is a hyper-growth highly profitable proprietary trading business. We are backed by top tier global venture capital investors such as <a href="https://medium.com/lightspeed-venture-partners/wintermute-makes-sure-you-dont-get-ripped-off-when-you-buy-crypto-63aa96dcb983" class="postings-link">Lightspeed</a>, <a href="https://panteracapital.com/" class="postings-link">Pantera Capital</a>, <a href="https://www.sinoglobalcapital.com/" class="postings-link">Sino Global Capital</a>, <a href="http://blockchain.com/" class="postings-link">Blockchain.com</a> Ventures, Avon Ventures by <a href="https://www.fidelity.com/" class="postings-link">Fidelity Investments</a>, <a href="https://defialliance.co/" class="postings-link">DeFi Alliance</a> and others. Learn more about our team and culture on our website and Evgeny’s post <a href="https://twitter.com/EvgenyGaevoy/status/1380121973058076672" class="postings-link">here.</a></div><div><br></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">Working at Wintermute </b></div><div><br></div><div>In this role you will be driving user experience vision and execution for Wintermute’s B2B and prosumer products. You are someone who can take initiative and lead, and also loves to design. You have the big picture in mind, but also impeccable attention to detail. You’ll work alongside our very talented product managers, visual designers, engineers and traders. You will improve experience of the existing products and design new ones from scratch. You will keep learning about the dynamic space that crypto is, closely interact with the industry and the users, and enjoy being at the heart of the evolving blockchain space.</div><br/>Responsibilities <br/><li><b>Experience Strategy and Delivery</b></li><li>Develop user experience vision and make it a reality</li><li>Co-own design projects with visual design and execute on UX end-to-end, incl discovery, concept, prototypes, detailed designs and ongoing refinement.</li><li>Develop design system in partnership with visual design&nbsp;</li><div><br></div><li><b>Market &amp; User Insights</b></li><li>Conduct user research, from early discovery to user testing</li><li>Conduct market research to adopt industry best practice, while developing competitive edge</li><li>Utilise quantitative data to evaluate and steer design strategy</li><div><br></div><li><b>Collaboration</b></li><li>Work closely with visual designers, product managers and developers to deliver holistic experience for users</li><li>Embed design thinking approach to drive user-centric problem solving</li><div><br></div><li><b>Other</b></li><li>Most Importantly, all employees can shape and develop their roles. There's no limit set by the company. </li><br/>Hard Requirements <br/><li>Bachelor’s degree in UX / HCI or equivalent</li><li>5+ years experience as a UX designer working with complex financial products in B2B / prosumer space, and a corresponding portfolio</li><li>Passion for complex products and hard-to-crack problems</li><li>Experience designing holistic product frameworks, establishing design systems and principles, create product blueprints</li><li>Strong personal interest and experience in crypto</li><li>Desire to both lead the vision and be very hands-on with execution</li><br/>Preferred Requirements <br/><li>Experienced Figma user</li><li>Experience with varied research techniques</li><li>Data analytics skills, with visualisation tools or Python</li><br/>Wintermute offer <br/><li>A unique opportunity to work on very interesting projects, get the level of responsibility and ownership that would be unlikely at any other firm</li><li>Great company culture: informal, non-hierarchical, ambitious, highly professional yet collaborative and entrepreneurial&nbsp; </li><li>A cool office in central London with a sci-fi touch</li><li>We support significant flexibility in regards to working from home and working hours; however, we require hard/smart work and &gt;60% work from the office; we are unable to accept remote candidates</li><li>Weekly team events, such as team lunches, team dinners, team board games and Dota playing sessions; these are not obligatory in any sense, but this is what we like to do</li><li>Aligned incentive structure: on top of competitive pay, a significant part of your compensation is performance-based variable pay with unlimited upside</li><li>We offer standard perks too, like pension, private health insurance, free food and office gym, but that’s probably not the right reason to join us</li><li>We offer UK work permits and help in relocation</li><br/>Write to us if <br/><li>You love problem solving, and love seeing your products work</li><li>You are determined, ambitious yet humble, willing to work hard and learn on the way</li><li>You like meritocracy and being judged by what you deliver</li><li>You have an entrepreneurial mindset versus 9-to-5 mentality</li><li>You are prepared to work non-standard working hours (since we are a high-growth startup operating in the 24/7 crypto world)</li><li>You like working in the team environment (not fully remote)</li><br/>Tips for a successful application <br/><li>This is a London based role</li><li>Do some research: look at our website and social media channels</li><li>If you don't have an obviously matching experience or skills, make sure you state very clearly what you can bring or how your experience is relevant.</li><li>Prepare to be tested on your hard skills required for this job. We do not care as much about your credentials (university or prior employer), but we care a lot about your knowledge and ability to get things done.</li><li>Unfortunately, we won't be able to proceed if you simply press "submit button"; we do promise to reply to everyone who puts time and effort in making the application relevant!</li>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/wintermute-trading/58d1b81e-d0ec-46ed-979d-1d488680c032/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/637352/wintermute-trading.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[wintermute@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b33e8b5-6d52-4368-8eea-e8c0ac3382ff]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Wintermute]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Cardano DCF Content Editor]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOHK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://iohk.io]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Cardano is an open source blockchain project committed to a roadmap towards decentralized governance. As part of this journey, IO Global is looking for a Content Editor to help drive forward our Decentralized Consortium Funding program, an exciting new model to expand the developer base for Cardano’s protocol and ecosystem development.  </p> <p>In 2021, Cardano has achieved incredible success, but we are still early in this space and have a long way to go.  A big component of the continued evolution of Cardano is IO Global’s efforts to fully open source and decentralize the core development of the platform and protocol.  To do this, we will need to build a broad coalition and a consortium of highly qualified and reputable firms that can meaningfully contribute to this effort. </p> <p>As a Content Editor at IOG, you are responsible for creating, maintaining, and assessing the quality of technical documentation, working directly with product teams and SMEs to develop an understanding of specialized subject matter. As part of the Cardano DCF marketing and communications team, you are also expected to contribute to general copywriting and content work and to function as a technical intermediary, providing digestible summaries of complex topics to enable and support the broader communications team function.</p><p><strong>Your mission </strong></p><ul> <li>Work with developer teams and subject matter experts to capture core Cardano DCF information and turn it into clear, digestible user information</li> <li>Publish articles across IOG social media channels (LinkedIn, IOHK Blog, Medium) to make Cardano DCF approachable</li> <li>Publish content to showcase consortium members and highlight what unique capabilities they bring to the Cardano DCF and the development of the Cardano platform, protocol, and ecosystem as a whole</li> <li>Update existing content, and write new content about our technology, our products and our people and how the Cardano DCF helps our ecosystem evolve</li> <li>Proofread, review and organize all technical documentation by liaising with the product managers and technical team</li> <li>Create Content for Cardano DCF for different formats: Turn Cardano platform &amp; protocol development into blog posts and web content </li> <li>Produce high caliber documents that meet our standards and guidelines so that we maintain a common look and feel to all articles published</li> <li>Communicate and collaborate with team members, including members of the communication team, through information gathering, content reviews, meetings, and status reports. </li> </ul><p><strong>Your expertise</strong>  </p> <ul> <li>Minimum of 1-3 years of experience as a Technical Writer preferably with a technology company</li> <li>Thorough knowledge of editorial journalism concepts and techniques</li> <li>Solid experience working directly with developer and SMEs</li> <li>Attention to detail</li> <li>Critical thinking skills</li> <li>Ability to work independently and under pressure created by deadlines</li> <li>University degree majoring in communications and/or journalism.</li> </ul><p><strong>Location</strong></p><p>IOG is a fully distributed organization and therefore this is a remote position. Due to team distribution we are ideally searching for someone in a Central European or Pacific Standard time zone.  </p><p><strong>All Colleagues</strong></p><ul> <li>Flexible schedule</li> <li>Remote work - ability to work anywhere</li> <li>Laptop reimbursement</li> <li>New starter package to buy hardware essentials (headphones, monitor, etc)</li> <li>Learning &amp; Development opportunities</li> <li>Competitive PTO and Sick Leave plan</li> </ul><p><strong>US Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits coverage through Anthem with 100% premium cost covered by IO Global for the employee and dependents</li> <li>Health Savings Account</li> <li>Life Insurance</li> </ul><p><strong>UK Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Monthly Health Stipend to use towards any wellness or medical coverage/service</li> <li>Pension</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EM-XkuQdUq8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/io-global/j/629B6B1C35/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143583/iohk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iohk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b89f946-6d3b-434f-aa32-f0e84ecb2992]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOHK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Go to Market Manager - Freelance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[SettleMint]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://settlemint.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote job]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p dir="ltr">SettleMint eliminates complexity in Enterprise blockchain development, deployment and integration. Our low-code Blockchain Platform as a Service (BPaaS) is recognised by Gartner and Everest Group as a leading technological solution for blockchain application development globally. Using our BPaaS solution enables our customers, to rapidly integrate blockchain into their digital transformation projects, to rapidly move from a blockchain concept to a fully integrated solution.</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>About SettleMint organisation and team:</strong><br />SettleMint has offices in Belgium, UAE, India and Singapore. A culturally diverse team with deep industry experience in developing innovative and scalable blockchain developer tools. The team includes industry leading thinkers and doers who strive to extend SettleMint’s product leadership, bound together by the ambition to accelerate blockchain adoption globally. In addition to our in-house team, we work hand-in-hand with leading systems integrators active in the blockchain space to deliver end-to-end solutions to customers. We are currently a team of over 50 and are growing our engineering, solution architecture, client success and sales teams.</p>
<p dir="ltr"></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>What’s the opportunity? </strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">One of SettleMint’s flagship products is Databroker.global, a blockchain-supported decentralized data marketplace where buyers and sellers exchange data on a peer-to-peer basis. The data exchanged are put to use towards improving operational efficiencies, capturing new markets, and driving better decision making across industries and the public sector.</p>
<p dir="ltr">We are looking for an innovative, detail-oriented Go To Market Manager with strong business acumen for a 5-month mission where you will be leading the go-to-market of a data marketplace for the IOT sector.  </p>
<p dir="ltr">In this pivotal role, you will be reporting directly to the head of marketing and become a key member of the project team. Your mission will be to take ownership and be responsible for the set up and the execution of the platform strategy, which includes the design and management of online and social campaigns, the set up of an industry segmentation, the development of customer personas and the orchestration of content marketing campaigns. Also, the monitoring and reporting of the campaign, the identification and resolution of issues, as well as adhering to contract specifications will be part of your responsibilities. </p>
<p dir="ltr">To be successful in this role, you should be an experienced and versatile project manager with excellent technical skills and sound knowledge of growth hacking techniques, as well as strong interpersonal and communication skills.</p>
<p><br /></p><p><h2>Requirements:</h2></p><ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">3-5 years minimum experience in digital project management, with an expertise in go-to-market strategies, preferably in a start up environment where you had to make it happen.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">An analytical mindset, you are comfortable working with Google Analytics or other reporting tools. You know what a market segmentation is and you are able to connect qualitative and quantitative data analysis and link them into a go-to-market strategy. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Tech savvy with a knowledge of growth hacking and SEO tools (Phantombuster, Sales Navigator, Lusha, Semrush…) ideally experienced with an integrated solution like Hubspot (another one is also ok).  </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Able to work independently or as part of a team and you have a high sense of ownership. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">The ability to dream big but realize that achieving great goals often requires small operational steps that you will be happy to undertake.  </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Motivated to train yourself and curious to learn, you are eager to engage in a learning path where you will be continuously auto-challenging yourself, taking lessons from successes and failures. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">You are proficient in Word, PowerPoint and at least one CMS platform that you have used extensively in the past. Familiarity with Hubspot is a plus, but not absolutely required.  </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">An international experience in Africa is a plus.</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Interest for new technologies in general and Blockchain in particular is definitely an asset.</p></li></ul>
<p><br /></p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Language: </strong></p>
<p dir="ltr">Fluent (spoken and written) in English plus one other European language.</p>
<p dir="ltr"><strong>Employment Terms:</strong></p>
<ul><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Freelancer for 2 to 3 days a week based in Belgium</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Potential start early February 2022</p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">5 months contract to start with, potential to extend beyond if needed. </p></li><li dir="ltr"><p dir="ltr">Remote to start, reporting to Belgium HQ</p></li></ul>
<p><br /></p>
<p dir="ltr">STRICTLY NO AGENCIES</p>
<p><br /></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/CSVAjHkzW-M" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.settlemint.com/o/go-to-market-manager-freelance/c/new?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/430042/SettleMint-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[settlemint@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d53ddeff-9d6a-4af9-b60f-79aaa263e2e3]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[SettleMint]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[User Community Manager - DeFi/DApp (USA)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Los Angeles, California, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>About Crypto.com</strong></p><p>Founded in 2016, Crypto.com today serves over 10 million customers with the world’s fastest growing crypto app, along with the Crypto.com Visa Card — the world’s largest crypto card program — the Crypto.com Exchange and Crypto.com DeFi Wallet. Recently launched, Crypto.com NFT is the premier platform for collecting and trading NFTs, carefully curated from the worlds of art, design, entertainment and sports.</p><p>Crypto.com is built on a solid foundation of security, privacy and compliance and is the first cryptocurrency company in the world to have ISO/IEC 27701:2019, CCSS Level 3, ISO27001:2013 and PCI:DSS 3.2.1, Level 1 compliance, and independently assessed at Tier 4, the highest level for both NIST Cybersecurity and Privacy Frameworks.</p><p>With over 2,600 people in offices across the Americas, Europe and Asia, Crypto.com is accelerating the world’s transition to cryptocurrency. Find out more: <a href="https://crypto.com/" target="_blank" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://crypto.com</a></p><p></p><p><strong>Role summary</strong></p><p>As User community manager, you act as the advocate of the DeFi user community and you engage creatively with the user community in order to educate and empower them when it comes to adopting DeFi and GameFi Dapps.</p><p><strong>Responsibilities:</strong></p><ul> <li>You create user-related content such as tutorials, FAQ lists, and engage with the user community in order to localize content in many languages.</li> <li>You publish video tutorials and organize panel discussions on Twitter and Youtube in order to inform and educate the user community.</li> <li>You seed content and discussions in the user communities in order to keep them active and valuable.</li> <li>You are active on Discord, Telegram, Reddit, Youtube and Twitter in order to engage with users via their preferred.</li> <li>You build relationships with influencers and key voices in the community.</li> <li>You work with our Content team in order to create viral marketing campaigns on Twitter, participate in Reddit forums, facilitate conversation and events among users.</li> <li>You are part of a cross-functional team that includes the product teams, the product marketing managers, content &amp; social media teams, and developer relations in order to create and refine the user experience.</li> <li>You constantly feed the team with documented user feedback collected from user communities.</li> <li>You travel occasionally to crypto / blockchain conferences in order to network with key influencers and educate users about DeFi and DeFi Dapps.</li> </ul><ul> <li>You have 4+ years of work experience in a comparable role at a consumer software product company.</li> <li>Intricate knowledge on DeFi, blockchain, and cryptocurrencies</li> <li>You are passionate about helping end-users and find it fulfilling to help millions of them to use DeFi better.</li> <li>You have a track record of writing or producing best-in-class content for end-users.</li> <li>You are known as someone who is authentic and creative and can be funny or quirky on occasion.</li> <li>You are fluent in English and ideally at least one other language.</li> <li>Self-motivated, independent, strong team player</li> </ul><ul> <li>Attractive compensation package</li> <li>Working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing content from scratch, alongside a talented team</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/3DC0F59E8C/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Community Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Manager (NFT/Metaverse)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div>You will be responsible for the marketing strategy and product management of Binance NFT. In this role, you will work closely with the Business Development team, Tech team, Listing team, and Data team to build product and our brand. You will use your understanding of the product and knowledge of the NFT, Gaming, and collectibles markets, customers, and competitors to clearly explain the unique value the product brings. At Binance NFT, you will use your expertise to contribute to the future of NFT, cryptocurrency, and Web3.0 and help us to achieve our mission of enabling digital ownership, freedom of money and transfer of digital assets in the Metaverse.&nbsp;</div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Establish go-to-market strategy for feature launches, major gaming NFT listings, and new market entry</li><li>Partner with research teams to uncover customer insights and product gaps based on industry use cases, regulation, current trend, and sector nuances</li><li>Support and drive engagement and adoption of the Binance NFT through performance marketing, PR and Communications, community building, social media, etc.</li><li>Define and analyze metrics to guide product development&nbsp;</li><li>Communicate and coordinate proactively among Marketing, Product, Business Development, Design, Customer Support, major artist partners and games to continuously improve how we market our existing feature set</li><li>Develop an analytical framework to measure and report on the performance of product marketing initiatives</li><li>Work and coordinate with regional teams in rolling out and executing global campaigns and strategies</li><li>Develop and help create / foster our brand positioning, voice and values (website, newsletter, blog, social, forum, etc.)</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>You are an expert in bleeding edge tech NFTs, DAOs, and Web 3.0.</li><li>Bachelor's degree in marketing, product management, or related fields.&nbsp;</li><li>8+ years experience working with product or marketing teams for a consumer product or service delivered through an ecommerce channel</li><li>Having thorough knowledge and understanding of Gaming and Metaverse</li><li>Deep knowledge of the marketing strategy, channels expansions and product management in Web3.0</li><li>Strong performance in building go-to market strategies and understanding how to push product in the current market trend</li><li>Excellent written and verbal communication skills</li><li>Strong analytical skills and extreme comfort with spreadsheet-based analysis and data-analysis.&nbsp;</li><li>Ability to plan and execute on multiple projects at once&nbsp;</li><li>Deep analytical, prioritization, and problem solving skills</li><li>Thrive in collaborative cultures and working cross-functionally with product, design, BD, legal, and finance to launch successful partnerships</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/0fa7d0f8-00e1-4c20-9740-4c7b54f6b266/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Site Reliability Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.okcoin.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Who We Are&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Okcoin is one of the world’s largest and fastest growing cryptocurrency exchanges. We help millions of people buy and sell bitcoin, and over 30 other crypto assets every day — but our work is a whole lot more than that. We’re building an inclusive future of finance, one that opens new opportunities to learn financial literacy, store value, and build wealth for everyone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ready to help the next billion people experience the future of finance with us? Come on board. We have offices in San Francisco, Miami, Malta, Hong Kong, Singapore and Japan. Even though this role is listed in San Francisco, we are remote friendly and believe in you working wherever you work best. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Site Reliability Engineering is a newly created engineering discipline in the company.&amp;nbsp; Its charter is to&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Triage all production issues and devise remedies to stabilize the problem until engineering can rollout proper remediation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Devise metrics to provide baselines where engineering can work to ensure that our platform achieves 95% uptime&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build tools and infrastructure that promote early detection of production failures, leading to a stellar customer experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our work is to drive safety, health and uptime of our platform, and the ability to remedy unforeseen problems.&amp;nbsp; By removing some of the complex burdens in how to scale and maintain uptime in distributed systems, SRE allows development teams to focus on feature development instead of the nuances of achieving and maintaining service level commitments.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re looking for a creative and driven individual that can spearhead our effort to push some “outside the box” infrastructure implementations that will have a tremendous impact on our platform’s stability and scalability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Be Doing:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work closely with our stakeholders to triage and resolve our production issues quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with stakeholders to devise metrics to identify areas for improvement to reduce our mean time for issue resolution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Suggest architecture improvements that improve the reliability of our platform and maintain our market leadership&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with Product, Engineering, and DevOps to propose, develop and maintain application performance monitoring tools to forecast the next problem spot and to keep with our service level commitment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Automate internal processes and develop bots to keep our Product and Engineering focused on delivering the next technological breakthrough for our customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Look For In You:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;ul1&quot;&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years full-stack development experience with a proficiency in Java and/or JavaScript (React.js)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years experience in application performance monitor tools integration and deployment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;3+ years experience with large-scale distributed environments and high traffic volume (100 million user level)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated scripting skills in Python or similar&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good command of Linux environment and cloud platform services (AWS, GCP or other)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understand DNS, SSL/ TLS, and how traffic on IP networks establishes end-to-end security and trust&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Open for pager duty&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Self-motivated &amp;amp; self-organized, with the ability to “think outside the box”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Haves:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with administrating Linux systems and with configuration management (Ansible, Terraform, Docker)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Working understanding of TCP/IP network stack&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with AliCloud&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong passion for Bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Highlights of Perks and Benefits:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Market competitive total compensation package&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comprehensive insurance package including medical, dental, vision, disability &amp;amp; life insurance (Company pays 100% for employee/80% for dependents)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401K with company contribution&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible PTO policy, company paid holidays, and flexible hours&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;UberEats Program&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paid Parental Leave&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee Referral Bonus Program paid in BTC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Company Donation Match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;More surprises when you join!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Okcoin Statement:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Okcoin is committed to equal employment opportunities regardless of race, color, genetic information, creed, religion, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, lawful alien status, national origin, age, marital status, and non-job related physical or mental disability, or protected veteran status. Pursuant to the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance, we will consider for employment qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xAd9NClUmZY" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okcoin/jobs/4884329003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/551872/OKCoin_400x400.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okcoin@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[57e0c7fc-df31-4da2-b52b-befd9a7f36e9]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKCoin]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Customer Experience Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://uniswap.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[New York, NY]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>The Uniswap Protocol is the largest decentralized trading and automated market making protocol (often called a DEX, “Decentralized Exchange”) on Ethereum.</div><div><br></div><div>The Uniswap Labs team was a major contributor to the Uniswap Protocol and now focuses on building a suite of products to support the Uniswap ecosystem. Our team is one of the most impactful in crypto. We are based out of SoHo in New York City with the option to be partially or fully remote depending on the position.</div><div><br></div><div>Uniswap Labs is hiring a Customer Experience Lead. You will have the opportunity to build out our customer service values, function, systems and processes from scratch. We are often an early touch point for Web3 users, and receive inquires outside of our product space. You will create a way for folks to feel heard and supported externally, and also work internally to represent our users within our team and improve their experiences.</div><br/>You will:<br/><li>Help build out a world-class customer service function and over time a chance to also grow a rockstar team</li><li>The first touch point for all user issues, responsible for ensuring that every inquiry is handled in a timely and effective manner</li><li>Design, implement and operate user service processes to ensure the team meets goals</li><li>Develop and implement metrics to monitor reliability and progress against goals</li><li>Systematically communicate feedback to key stakeholders, providing guidance and input on new product features</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>2+ years experience building and leading Customer Service/User Experience teams in a high growth environment</li><li>You are motivated by helping others and are the type of person who prides themselves on turning an angry user into a 5-star rating.</li><li>At your heart, you are a player-coach. You are equally as comfortable managing others as you are executing on the ground.</li><li>You can help solve complex problems end-to-end so as to mitigate delegation as much as possible.</li><li>Experience with DeFi, knowledge of blockchains, and experience using crypto wallets is a (big) plus!</li><div>Uniswap Lab's benefits include unlimited and encouraged time off, 100% company-paid medical, dental, &amp; vision for you and your dependents, 401(k) participation, daily lunches at NY headquarters, and for remote employees: up to $2,000 USD home office setup stipend (all benefits are subject to applicable taxes and based on eligibility).</div><div><br></div><div>Uniswap Labs welcomes&nbsp;all qualified persons to apply regardless of race, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, disability, age, or veteran status. Compensation will be competitive and commensurate with experience. This is a full time role which includes health insurance and other benefits.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/Uniswap/5f5b7f55-ec1e-4c63-9edf-141de2c3eb4a/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/669325/uniswap-uni-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[uniswap@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[b488dfbb-84b8-4efa-9d5d-2ced4e25769e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Uniswap]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Customer Services ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager (Gods Unchained)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Immutable]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://immutable.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 12pt">A bit about the role:</b></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The Gods Unchained Engineering team has grown significantly in 2021 and expects to grow more in 2022. As a result, we are looking to hire a new Software Engineering Manager. This exciting role brings you the opportunity to create an immersive player experience that promotes long-term engagement. You will build compelling utility for NFTs and ERC20 tokens alike, and work on monetising on player engagement, using this digital ownership to scale, retain and reward our player base massively through creating a multi-platform experience for players!</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">It's an exciting opportunity to help shape some engineering practices and processes in a rapidly growing team filled with highly passionate and supportive people. We truly live our company values, which create a culture of experimentation, honest feedback, and dedication.</span></div><br/>You will have the opportunity to:<br/><li>Facilitate discovery and implementation of projects alongside our engineering and product teams. </li><li>Manage and mentor a team of engineers. Help define key results and deliverables that will drive the success of Gods Unchained.</li><li>Work with technical experts to identify areas of improvement and drive education initiatives across the team.</li><li>Identify gaps in our processes and implement solutions that improve the team's satisfaction and productivity.</li><li>Contribute to the technical vision and strategy, overseeing and measuring our progress towards it.</li><br/>We would love you to have:<br/><li>Strong background of technical leadership – 2yrs+</li><li>Experience as an individual contributor software engineer – 4yrs+</li><li>People management experience – 2yrs+</li><li>Experience with Agile methodologies</li><li>Substantial startup/scaleup experience</li><div>Tech Stack (As many as possible):</div><li>Go</li><li>TypeScript</li><li>Angular</li><li>AWS</li><li>Terraform</li><li>Design Systems</li><li>Blockchain / Solidity</li><br/>Some extra skills that would be awesome:<br/><li>Experience working in a distributed systems (microservices) architecture</li><li>Gaming experience</li><li>Blockchain experience</li><br/>Some of the things we can offer you:<br/><li><b>Competitive Salary and Employee Stock Options:</b> Everyone in our team contributes to the success of our game-changing products, which is why we share all our wins company-wide. As we continue to succeed, stock options and a competitive salary mean you get to enjoy the upside!</li><li><b>Flexible working life and $750 WFH set up allowance:</b> Work-life balance is important. Whether you want to work from home or come to our new, shiny, Sydney office the choice is yours. To help you get comfortable working from home we’ll assist with a $750 contribution</li><li><b>Paid Parental Leave: </b>We celebrate our growing Immutable family! New parents will receive 12 weeks (primary) and 2 weeks (secondary) paid parental leave</li><li><b>Employee Assistance Program:</b> A 24/7 service that includes unlimited counselling for you and your family</li><li><b>EOY and Birthday Leave: </b>You can enjoy 2 additional paid annual leave days at EOY and a paid day off for your birthday</li><li><b>Internet and Phone Allowance</b>: $900 annually to put towards your mobile and internet expenses</li><li><b>Learning and Development: </b>We are dedicated to your professional development. You’ll get access to thousands of online learning courses via Go1, Udemy and Naspers. Immutable will also contribute between $1500-$2000 annually for you to invest in your continued education</li><div><b>Additional Information:</b></div><div><br></div><div>Immutable is committed to building and fostering an inclusive, diverse workplace. We believe in incorporating everyone’s perspectives and experiences as this has been a significant driver in our success so far.</div><div><br></div><div>For this reason, we strongly encourage candidates of all backgrounds to get in touch. Even if you don’t meet all the requirements of a job listing, do yourself (and us) a favour by still applying! It’s highly likely you’ll bring something to the workplace that we haven’t thought of yet, and we would love to hear from you.</div><div><br></div><div><b>We are a 2021 Circle Back Initiative Employer – we commit to respond to every applicant.</b></div><div><br></div><div><b>Please note: </b>There may be a delay in our response times due to our end of year shut-down period. Our office is closed between 17th of December and 4th of January. We promise you'll hear from us soon after we return!</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/fT1YFjzry3k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/immutable/90292e23-99f9-4f0a-baf4-21c67d27b101/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/364981/Immutable.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[immutable@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f8630842-e278-44a1-80ce-2963904a6243]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Immutable]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Growth Marketing Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitmex-Duplicate]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.bitmex.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;content-intro&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BitMEX is the world’s leading cryptocurrency derivatives trading platform, which has pioneered cryptocurrency trading through relentless commitment to change, and continues to set benchmarks for innovation, liquidity, and security today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As the world&#39;s most advanced peer-to-peer crypto-products trading platform and API, BitMEX gives knowledge, confidence, and precision to hundreds of thousands of traders, transacting billions of USD a day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Purpose of the Role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Reporting directly to the Head of Engagement, the role is to set up, establish and develop marketing activities to ensure a sustainable customer growth in the area.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;• Lead a consistent marketing growth strategy in the area to grow these KPIs: number of local registered users, number of monthly active users, trading volumes of the users, web traffic share, spot monthly users, futures monthly users, fiat penetration&lt;br&gt;• Establish/Grow the community of BitMEX in the area and define KPI, moderate social media channels to interact with the community and enhance a positive engagement&lt;br&gt;• Growth affiliate network, outreach to YouTubers, Medias, Influencers&lt;br&gt;• Coordinate internal resources to leverage on local acquisition campaign&lt;br&gt;• Plan and implement marketing activities to grow the awareness of the&lt;br&gt;company and so the web traffic share&lt;br&gt;• Reach out medias directly (tier 1) while use PR agencies if necessary&lt;br&gt;• Conduct competitor analysis and study market trends in your region&lt;br&gt;• KPI and Problem/Solution Weekly Reporting to Headquarter&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;• 3+ years of experience in community building or business development of which at least 2 in the crypto industry&lt;br&gt;• Business development and start-up attitude&lt;br&gt;• Strong knowledge of social media growth techniques&lt;br&gt;• Both creative and number-driven approach&lt;br&gt;• Great interpersonal and communication skills&lt;br&gt;• Expertise in analytical tools (i.e. Google Analytics, Similar Web, Semrush)&lt;br&gt;• Critical thinker and problem-solving skills&lt;br&gt;• Good time-management skills&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Join us, as we build a thriving cryptocurrency ecosystem through strategic investments in emerging cryptocurrency technology, and create the future of digital financial services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/sSh2bM3UP04" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitmex/jobs/5798129002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141827/BitMEX-Logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitmex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[53409e8e-aabf-4e89-b4e1-8d549f5434f4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitmex-Duplicate]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Digital Artist Recruiter]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Energi Core Ltd]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.energi.world]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Global - Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Energi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energi (NRG) is a next-generation Proof of Stake (PoS) cryptocurrency, combining Ethereum-compatible smart contracts with on-chain governance, a self-funding treasury, and a layer 2 masternode network, enabling powerful DeFi applications.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a fully remote company with no fixed headquarters. The team is spread throughout the Americas, Europe, Africa, Asia, and Oceania. With more than 90 contributors, the team forms a well-linked network across a variety of locations, lifestyles, and backgrounds.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energi&#39;s culture is driven by integrity, strategic thinking, leadership, and the shared desire to perform at our peak. While our differences make us adaptable and versatile, it&#39;s our shared values that give us the strength and drive to become the cryptocurrency for world consciousness.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To learn more please visit: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.energi.world/&quot;&gt;https://www.energi.world/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What’s in It for You?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work flexible hours from anywhere and be part of a team that is driven by strong values and a clear shared vision.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Directly shape the future of a completely new model for cryptocurrency and blockchain applications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Challenge your skills and push your creative limits working with the latest blockchain technologies &amp;amp; systems.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Play an active role in one of the most significant technological innovations in human history.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receive a competitive salary paid in a combination of BTC and NRG.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we’re looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energi is launching its own NFT marketplace in 2022, and we are looking for a full-time Digital Artist Recruiter who has experience finding talent in the digital space, particularly in the NFT communities.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you will do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage the full recruiting process from sourcing, interviewing, coordinating hiring process, to offer negotiation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Act with urgency and screen candidates for the best possible employees who also fit our values&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide an outstanding candidate experience, from initial introduction to onboarding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be a true Talent Partner to each department - not just execute, but consult, advice, innovate, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work closely with the HR team and hiring managers to constantly improve the hiring process. Support HR projects and initiatives as needed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Manage recruiting databases and other HR assets in structured and timely manners&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Develop and maintain online a continually stocked pipeline of quality talent&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Essential Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5+ years recruiting experience, ideally, within top-tier tech companies or agencies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1+ years digital art recruiting experience, particularly NFT/3D artists a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience recruiting across social channels for NFT/digital talent (Twitter, Discord, Telegram)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Passionate about NFTs, metaverse, cryptocurrency, and all things digital&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent written and spoken English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Skilled with modern tech sourcing and selection techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Successful track record of delivering on aggressive hiring goals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Effective stakeholder management, relationship building skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to challenge the status quo and come up with new ideas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle multiple projects and deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of other languages&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience working with a fully remote and decentralized team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This role is not open to 3rd party organizations or agencies. Any candidates sent will be considered free of any charges&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Energi is committed to creating a diverse environment and is proud to be an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, pregnancy, disability, age, veteran status, or other characteristics.&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/8QUIHRakeHo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/energicorelimited/jobs/4277204004?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/479023/energi-core-ltd-logo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[energi@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5be3229a-46ba-477a-9178-2772ea9250e4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Energi Core Ltd]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ HR & Recruiting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Agile Delivery Lead]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Port Elizabeth]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for an &lt;strong&gt;Agile Delivery Lead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;to join our Engineering team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing. We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual, and we want to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno welcomes crypto lovers and crypto newbies. You - just like everyone in the world - are on your own unique crypto-learning journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a mission-driven &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;cryptocurrency company that is building more open and equal access to the future of money. You don’t have to know lots about crypto to be interested in joining us, you just have to feel that upgrading the world to a fairer financial system matters, and that you’d like to be part of this global change. We’re a passionate and committed team taking on a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;working together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with unusual skill, focus and determination. We need the best team on board for our mission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If that sounds like a culture you’d thrive in, then we are excited to hear from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno means moon in Esperanto, we chose the name because at night, wherever you are in the world, you look up at the same moon. We believe in the power of working together, as one team, across borders, with clear focus and shared purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our popular mobile app and website helps people around the world &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;grow and manage their money using the world&#39;s most mature cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum and USDC. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve processed over &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$21 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ver 9 million customers across 40 countries have chosen to hold their crypto wallets on Luno because we offer a delightfully simple experience and bank-grade security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re part of the Digital Currency Group, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;named in 2021 as one of TIME magazine’s 100 Most Influential Companies, in the “Disruptors” category alongside Tesla, AirBnB, SpaceX, Peloton. TIME noted that DCG is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/collection/time100-companies/5953752/digital-currency-group/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;“mainstreaming cryptocurrency”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re proud to be one of the world’s most international cryptocurrency teams, with colleagues from 43 different nationalities working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria, Australia and Singapore. Financial inclusion is part of our mission, but on a deeper level, inclusion is a way of life, and a way of work for us. It is part of who we are as a company, and a group of human individuals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How we work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our engineering team (currently ~100 engineers) is split into organisations which we call Fleets. Each Fleet focuses on a core customer journey (onboarding, security, payments, support, new business, growth and marketing etc.). Each of these fleets contains multiple smaller teams called Pods, each of which focuses on a specific aspect of the product.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pods will include a product owner, product designer, back-end engineers, Android, iOS and Web developers, who each bring a unique perspective to the problem you are all contributing towards.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re agile, use scrum, continuous integration and continuous delivery, deploying to production every single day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In your first six months, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;...start at Luno by learning our processes, meeting the wider team and starting our engineering on-boarding program. After getting comfortable with the basics. Y&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ou’ll meet the Pod(s) you’ll be working with and quickly align on the teams’ current OKRs and product roadmap. We succeed as a team, so we will provide you with regular feedback from your manager and peers and will encourage you to do the same.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your mission will involve:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Being an Agile expert, coach, and servant leader&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Guiding multiple cross-functional “pod” teams on how to use agile practices and values across product, engineering and operational teams to delight customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Inspire the team to take responsibility for their delivery process and the outcomes they deliver, focus them on delivering value or failing fast.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate or remove impediments to delivery and waste in our processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitating team ceremonies, and teaching others on how to improve theirs with a wide range of methods and techniques in your toolbox&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good skills and knowledge of servant leadership, facilitation, situational awareness, conflict resolution, continual improvement, empowerment, and increasing transparency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coaching on requirements engineering, user story usage, estimation, quality assurance practices, user experience design process, risk management, and more.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Being a role model and tenacious driving force with a strong delivery ethic&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Exhibiting ownership of delivery and issues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Using simple processes to ensure we’re well prepared for software release ahead of launch day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Appreciation for and alignment with IT Service Management and Support Engineering processes.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competency in risk identification, mitigation and management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding stakeholder engagement, progress tracking, reporting and communications.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactively managing dependencies and cross-team coordination.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Accountable for the delivery approach and status within your pods.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An Agile Delivery Lead is an expert in the end to end process of delivering valuable software. They are proactive and accountable for ensuring that the delivery approach for each epic is defined, fit for purpose, tracked, communicated, and constantly tuned as understanding of the solution emerges, while also reactively acting as a servant leader that unblocks teams when they hit a problem. They lead on constant improvement to our delivery processes so that we learn and improve our estimation, risk reduction, velocity, technical quality, and teamwork.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal candidate for this role will have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong understanding of the end to end components of the software delivery lifecycle (SDLC)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A wealth of experience in agile principles, practices, and theory across methodologies such as Scrum, Kanban, eXtreme Programming, Lean, DevOps, DSDM, and SaFE.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Solid knowledge of a ticketing tool such as JIRA a must (We use Phabricator which is similar)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be friendly, transparent, articulate and driven to succeed&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Basic knowledge of and passion for digital currencies like Bitcoin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The right to work in the UK or South Africa as we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Don’t be put off if you don’t tick all of the boxes – they’re a guide based on what we’d love to see but we appreciate that excellent software engineers have diverse backgrounds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Life at Luno&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno is a ‘remote but reachable’ company! At Luno, we trust that people can do their work effectively anywhere and provide Lunauts with the flexibility to decide where they do their best work. For some of us, that’s at home for the majority of the time, for others, that might mean joining other Lunauts in person at one of our Luno workspaces more often. Luno is built on our relationships, so we still value in-person connection and have a minimum expectation of spending time in person once a quarter.&amp;nbsp; So as long as you are based in one country with a Luno workspace, we want to hear from you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Live long and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;prosper. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve got you covered with excellent private medical insurance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;ll be able to continuously &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;up-skill&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; yourself with access to free courses on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Udemy, Coursera and Codeacademy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For the crypto fans among you (should be everyone!), &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;you&#39;ll pay 0 fees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with Luno from the day you start&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;maternity / paternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and even (yes, you are reading it correctly) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;paw-ternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for your furry friend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Apple all the way. New&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Macbook,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; mouse and keyboard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Annual Inspiration Day... for that pottery course you’ve always been meaning to do!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;diverse team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; of hardworking, ambitious and friendly people on something that will truly revolutionise the financial world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We have &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;virtual cooking, dancing, drawing and house planting classes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; hosted by our Lunauts to break up your day and work that other part of your brain. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work is important, but&lt;strong&gt; your mental health should always take priority&lt;/strong&gt;. At Luno, we do everything we can to make sure you lead a healthy and happy life. That&#39;s why Luno gives you&lt;strong&gt; free access to Headspace&lt;/strong&gt; – a full library of guided meditations, sleep stories, and music.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. You&#39;ll need to hold the legal right to work in the UK already as we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be part of the change! 🚀&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3778228?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Software Engineer - Backend]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Manchester]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Backend Software Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to join our Engineering team in &lt;strong&gt;London.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as individuals.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Together, we are upgrading the world of work to unleash the potential within and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Upgrading the entire planet to a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;new financial system&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is a challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;working together&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with unusual skill, focus and determination. We’re changing the financial landscape, and to do so, well we need the best team on board for our mission. In short, to achieve our goals, we need rockstars. As simple as that.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little about us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We make it safe and easy to buy, store and learn about cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin and Ethereum.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We currently have over&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; 7 million&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; customers across 40 countries.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re part of the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Digital Currency Group,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; a group of companies driving progress in the cryptocurrency and blockchain space that includes Grayscale, Genesis, Coindesk and Foundry Service&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;s.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our platform has processed over &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$21 billion&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; to date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’re proud to be one of the world’s most international cryptocurrency teams from 43 different nationalities — working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria and Singapore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How we work&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our engineering team (currently ~100 engineers) is split into organisations which we call Fleets. Each Fleet focuses on a core customer journey (onboarding, security, payments, support, new business, growth and marketing etc.). Each of these fleets contains multiple smaller teams called Pods, each of which focuses on a specific aspect of the product.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Pods will include a product owner, product designer, back-end engineers, Android, iOS and Web developers, who each bring a unique perspective to the problem you are all contributing towards.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re agile, use scrum, continuous integration and continuous delivery, deploying to production every single day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re building teams to help us succeed in our mission to upgrade the world to a better financial system. You’ll be joining a group of highly motivated software engineers who you’ll work collaboratively with across our pods.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a fast-growing company with offices around the world, you’ll immediately see how your contributions directly impact both our internal users and client experience. Many of the problems we are solving result in trail blazing solutions which can’t be found on Stack Overflow; so we’re looking for engineers who flourish working in a complex domain.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In your first six months, you will:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;...start at Luno by learning our processes, meeting the wider team and starting our engineering on-boarding program. After getting comfortable with the basics, you&#39;ll start learning our idiomatic patterns in a safe, easy-to-follow way - by building your own toy micro services. You&#39;ll get to practice how we do design docs, code reviews, deployments, events, logging and monitoring.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ll meet the Pod(s) you’ll be working with and quickly align on the teams’ current OKRs and product roadmap. We succeed as a team, so we will provide you with regular feedback from your manager and peers and will encourage you to do the same.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your mission will involve:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build distributed microservices that are accessed by 2.5m customers from across the globe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Design, build and maintain advanced applications services.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write testable, maintainable code for robustness and reliability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work on bug fixing and improving application performance.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Write code that directly affects users, the company and the Bitcoin ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal candidate for this role will have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A passion for blockchain and cryptocurrencies (this is a new industry so we’ll help you learn about how the blockchain works and the technicals).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A proven background in computer science in areas such as algorithms, data structures, and software design.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Extensive programming experience in at least one language such as Go, Java, C++, C#, Python, etc.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A continuous improvement mindset.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;BSc/MSc/PhD in computer science or other technical discipline, or equivalent working experience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A passion for software development, mobile technology and Bitcoin.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;To be friendly, transparent, articulate and driven to succeed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The right to work in the UK if you are not a British citizen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Don’t be put off if you don’t tick all of the boxes – they’re a guide based on what we’d love to see but we appreciate that excellent software engineers have diverse backgrounds.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Remote Life at Luno&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you’re looking to work on something truly global and disruptive with a forward-thinking and ambitious team that highly values diversity, teamwork, and the continuous quest for excellence, then this is an opportunity for you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Like the majority of the companies, Luno is currently working remotely to keep our employees safe, which means you will not be physically, but virtually onboarded for now!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Live long and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;prosper. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We’ve got you covered with excellent private medical insurance.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You&#39;ll be able to continuously &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;up-skill&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; yourself with access to free courses on &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Udemy, Coursera and Codeacademy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;For the crypto fans among you (should be everyone!), &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;you&#39;ll pay 0 fees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; with Luno from the day you start&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;maternity / paternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; and even (yes, you are reading it correctly) &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;paw-ternity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; for your furry friend.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Apple all the way. New&lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Macbook,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; mouse and keyboard.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Annual Inspiration Day... for that pottery course you’ve always been meaning to do!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work with a &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;diverse team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; of hardworking, ambitious and friendly people on something that will truly revolutionise the financial world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We have &lt;/span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;virtual cooking, dancing, drawing and house planting classes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; hosted by our Lunauts to break up your day and work that other part of your brain. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work is important, but&lt;strong&gt; your mental health should always take priority&lt;/strong&gt;. At Luno, we do everything we can to make sure you lead a healthy and happy life. That&#39;s why Luno gives you&lt;strong&gt; free access to Headspace&lt;/strong&gt; – a full library of guided meditations, sleep stories, and music.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. You&#39;ll need to hold the legal right to work in the UK already as we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be part of the change! 🚀&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;No resumé? No problem.&lt;/strong&gt; There’s an easier way to apply by taking our short time-boxed online code test! No installation required, just a laptop and an internet connection that you can access the link through.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Click on the link below to read the instructions and begin. Good luck!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hr.gs/software-engineer-backend-test&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://hr.gs/software-engineer-backend-test&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3778831?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst  (CRM, SQL, Python)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Latoken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><strong></strong>LATOKEN exchange has 2 million accounts including 900k+ users of our Android app rated 4.4 by 25+ thousands of reviews. We leverage the next tech to make account opening as easy as Instagram. The technology and our Olympic sports culture can make us the first billion users digital wallet needed to free people to manage their financial life. Today, is a great moment to join us as crypto is expanding into mainstream financial market and <a>ex CFO of JP Morgan joined</a> our advisory board and <a>2 presidents joined us</a> in Davos.<br><br>For the past 3 years we have been developing our own blockchain (called “Lachain”) and we are now building the DeFi ecosystem based on it (including DEX, dApp, IDO, NFT etc) and launched our <a>mainnet</a>. <a>Here is our backlog.</a></p><p><strong>Mission:</strong> Transparent reporting and functions of CRM and Sports table</p><p><strong>Mission description: </strong><strong>Story</strong>: Sales and LS Account Managers need automated, transparent, updated, easy-to-use CRM &amp; analytical reports to create competition amongst managers and understand which managers will be promoted or will be out to prevent a toxic culture. <br><br><strong>Key PROBLEM's</strong>:</p><ul><li>Build CRM workflow with Sales and LS Managers sport table in 30 days.</li><li>Transparent telegram chats in 0.5 a month.</li></ul><p><strong>How</strong>:</p><ul><li>Develop, control and modify the workflow of leads processing</li><li>Create and maintain analytical scripts/dashboards for Sales and LS Managers sports table.</li><li>Bot added to every telegram group chat with sales chat transparency.</li></ul><p><strong>Constraints</strong>: Scripts are 100% error-free, CRM analytics is transparent and automated, sports table show free-riders and top performers.<br><br><strong>Main performance number:</strong> Transparent listings reports<br><strong>Second performance number:</strong> CRM Health<br><strong>Third performance number:</strong> Team health<br><br><strong>Functions:</strong><br>• CRM : CRM Development and Administration.<br>• CRM efficiency : Make sure sales managers work efficiently and according to workflow and rules.<br>• Workflow : Follow the company's workflow.<br>• Bots : Create required bots and manage that they work effectively.<br>• Automated Reports : Create required automated reports and check that data showing is correct.<br><br><strong>Requirement skills and experience:</strong><br>2+ year experience in Data Analysis.Strong skills in Python (Pandas, Numpy, Requests), PostgreSQL.Experience in data visualizations is a strong plus.Experience in web application development is a strong plus.Experience in Unix OS.Experience with crypto/token analytics is a strong advantage.Problem-solving and critical reasoning skills.</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> CRM, data analyst, python, SQL, blockchain, data engineer, business development, crypto</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ikbGulIPQs0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.breezy.hr/p/44925f1165c501-senior-business-analyst-crm-sql-python/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/178323/latoken.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[latoken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[ad8a3cbd-f1ed-4400-b372-af94f5f06cb4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Latoken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Events Manager (Blockchain Events /Telegram Communities)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Latoken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>LATOKEN exchange has 2 million accounts including 900k+ users of our Android app rated 4.4 by 25+ thousands of reviews. We leverage the next tech to make account opening as easy as Instagram. The technology and our Olympic sports culture can make us the first billion users digital wallet needed to free people to manage their financial life. Today, is a great moment to join us as crypto is expanding into mainstream financial market and <a>ex CFO of JP Morgan joined</a> our advisory board and <a>2 presidents joined us</a> in Davos.<br><br>For the past 3 years we have been developing our own blockchain (called “Lachain”) and we are now building the DeFi ecosystem based on it (including DEX, dApp, IDO, NFT etc) and launched our <a>mainnet</a>. <a>Here is our backlog.</a></p><p><strong>Mission:</strong> Loyal global community with events agenda and partnerships.<br><br><strong>Mission description: Story</strong>: Global community and event managers needs local LATOKEN Crypto Calendar TG groups and partnerships with major blockchain events. So they are easy to find event and partners of their interests, including listing on LATOKEN and Marketing partnerships.<br><br><strong>Key PROBLEM's</strong>:</p><ul> <li>Ensure      80% of local events are in our local and global calendar shown on web page      and downloadable in pdf for tg groups.</li> <li>Reach      3000 Telegram Calendars members looking for local events for major      locations within 3 month.</li> <li>Partner      with events as their media partner and generate TG groups members.</li> <li>Free      passes for sales managers in all major blockchain events of Q4'21 and      Q1'22</li></ul><p><strong>How</strong>:</p><ul> <li>Creating      &amp; maintaining Telegram communities related to major industry hubs</li> <li>Update      the calendars biweekly</li> <li>Moderate      TG chats</li> <li>Distribute      screenshots with a week events and a link to a post in our TG with full      pdf agenda to collect members</li> <li>Partner      with major industry events as as a media sponsor in exchange of TG group      links on their Site and Marketing.</li> <li>Generate      leads for listings from lead form pinned in TG</li></ul><p><strong>Constraints</strong>: Leads are converted to deals after the events. <br><strong>Main performance number:</strong> N of tg chat members<br><strong>Second performance number:</strong> Leads generated from TGs<br><strong>Third performance number:</strong> Revenue from events<br><br><strong>Functions:</strong><br>• Events : Promote and attract community LATOKEN events.<br>• TG agenda : Creating &amp; maintaining Telegram communities related to major industry hubs.<br>• Planning : Budgeting and assuring expenses during the trips and events.<br>• Partnerships : Conducting partnerships with major industry events.<br>• LATOKEN Meetup : Food, drinks and setup at LATOKEN meetup (30 guests)<br><strong><br>Requirement skills and experience:<br></strong>1+ year 2 of 3: Community Management, Event Management or Partnership management.<br>Experience in crypto is an advantage.<br>Diligent, disciplined with great communication skills.</p><p><strong>Keywords:</strong> communication, community management, partnerships, blockchain, event management</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/ikbGulIPQs0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://latoken.breezy.hr/p/52e4a12fb5f401-events-manager-blockchain-events-telegram-communities/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/178323/latoken.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[latoken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[ad8a3cbd-f1ed-4400-b372-af94f5f06cb4]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Latoken]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Associate Growth Manager, Social Ads]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.network/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>.</p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xW6QWaNfysw" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://celsius.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=497&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/731816/celsius_network.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celsius@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[5fa72b05-b42d-48a9-806e-c3fdccb06776]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celsius Network]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[  ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Architect & Evangelis]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>As Blockchain Architect &amp; Evangelist, you ensure that major DeFi projects receive top-notch technical advice and support to become successful. You adopt a hands-on approach to understand their requirements and feedback, follow up with cross-functional teams in order to ensure that these requirements are acted upon, and generally act as a thought partner to these projects are they think through their next development phases.</p><p><br></p><p>Responsibilities:</p><ul> <li>Understand, evangelize and educate on the businesses value of DeFi and GameFi</li> <li>Oversee the development of technical tutorials and content.</li> <li>Serve as technical resource and subject matter expert for Web3 projects that require hands-on support, performance information, and the like.</li> <li>Meet regularly with major Web3 projects to understand their requirements, and follow-up with the product and protocol teams to deliver these requirements.</li> <li>Support Cronos blockchain and research efforts by sharing your knowledge and learning when engaging with the broader Cronos &amp; crypto communities. Build a following for your yourself and Cronos</li> <li>Organise and lead technical events (webinars, workshops etc.), support hackathons</li> <li>Problem solve ad hoc technical architecture questions that may come up as part of the evolution of the DeFi ecosystem, and prepare written analyses and recommendations in order to help other teams in their technical decisions.</li> <li>Work with cross-functional teams in order to help define the future roadmap of DeFi and GameFi protocols.</li> <li>Be an active participant in the broader blockchain communities and represent Cronos at online/offline developer events</li> <li>Research and pursue open-source growth opportunities and best practices i.e. protocol governance, bounty programs etc.</li> </ul><ul> <li>The ideal candidate is a technologist who understands the Ethereum blockchain ecosystem and is a passionate advocate for any an all improvements that will deliver a delightful experience for developers.</li> <li>You have 8+ years of work experience, including as a protocol engineer or solution architect.</li> <li>Past experience as a developer or computer science researcher, and blockchain coding skills, are a plus.</li> <li>The ideal candidate is a strong written and verbal communicator. You must be able to facilitate and run meetings.</li> <li>Breadth and depth of knowledge are expected from this role. You should be able to quickly gain, retain, and deploy technical knowledge, and mentor / develop collaborators to build technical knowledge.</li> <li>You are comfortable working remotely with a global team and a global community, across global timezones, in English and potentially in multiple other languages.</li> <li>Passion for educating and inspiring developers</li> <li>Comfortable speaking and coding in a public setting with large live audiences</li> <li>Prior experience in organizing developer events, hackathons or moderating open source communities is a strong plus</li> <li>Meaningful social presence with engaged followers is a strong plus</li> </ul><ul> <li>Attractive compensation package</li> <li>Working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing content from scratch, alongside a talented team</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/C662A97356/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[cryptodotcom@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Partner Manager]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Rarible]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://rarible.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 13.5pt">About Rarible</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Rarible is one of the largest decentralized, creator-centric multi chain NFT marketplaces for multimedia content, including but not limited to digital art, collectibles, music, videos, and more. Rarible offers a user-friendly, community-led experience for creators and collectors to come together.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Rarible has an extremely active community of followers, creators, curators and collectors who are actively shaping the future of our marketplace and the evolution of digital ownership in web 3.0.&nbsp;</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 10.5pt">Rarible has a positive, diverse, and supportive culture—we look for people who are curious, inventive, and work to learn and grow every day. In our work together we aim to be smart, humble, hardworking and, above all, collaborative. We’d love for you to join our growing team!</span></div><br/>The Role<br/><li>Rarible is looking for an NFT enthusiast to help partners make the most of the space, whether it is taking their first steps and/or building long term NFT strategies. Reporting directly to the Chief Business Development Officer, this role will have a US focus, with success based on the attraction and retention of great NFT creators and projects to the Platform. </li><br/>Key responsibilities<br/><li>Build and foster strong relationships with NFT Creators and projects.</li><li>Help make sure that drops run smoothly and successfully </li><li>Handle inbound requests in an organised and timely fashion</li><li>Handle partner account issue including problem solving, on-boarding guidance and day-to-day inbound from partners.</li><li>Track, analyze and communicate industry trends.</li><li>Create innovative and strategic programs that ladder up to company goals.</li><br/>Skills & Qualifications<br/><li>Strong knowledge and passion for the space. </li><li>Ability to work with partners on technical details, diagnosing problems and finding solutions </li><li>Proven track record in partner management</li><li>Self-motivated and experienced operating in a rapidly changing work environment and remain productive with minimal supervision</li><li>Proactive solution-oriented team player with excellent interpersonal and communication skills.</li><li>Effective presentation, written and verbal communication skills. </li><li>English required, Spanish and Russian a bonus</li><li>Ability to succeed in a global, remote environment, working cross-company successfully to drive results.</li><li>Ability to travel regionally and globally periodically</li><div><b style="font-size: 13.5pt">What do we offer</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 12pt">📍 </span><span style="font-size: 11pt">Working for a rapidly expanding global organization</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">📍 Mentorship, training and career progression plans with leadership focused on developing the teams</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">📍 Team that cares about products and working conditions</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">📍 Flexible hours</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">📍 Full-time, paid vacations&nbsp;</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">📍 Remote first with relocation packages available</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">📍 Hardware and software support</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">📍 Attractive packages with bonus programme, plus healthcare and dental benefits and 401K (country dependent)</span></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/Rarible/d6b1ab53-2e79-4fe7-8b13-7358241a77e8/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/811040/rarible-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[rarible@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3d836c10-c446-4ef5-94c0-abd3afb18693]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Rarible]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
