<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Finance System Business Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Hong Kong]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>The incumbent of this role will join our global Finance Digital Transformation team and be responsible to implement the finance transformation agenda to enhance the efficiency and effectiveness of our internal finance and accounting systems and processes. This includes but not limited to conduct system requirement workshops, develop use cases, conduct training, and implement change requests that are aligned with the long term vision of our Finance system ecosystem. A high-level cross teamwork and engagement with both internal and external stakeholders is expected.</p><p><br>In this role you will...</p><ul> <li>Lead the delivery of finance system initiatives from ideation to release </li> <li>Assist business stakeholders with the decomposition of complex business requirements into Epics and User Stories that can be delivered by the Finance squad </li> <li>Partner with IT and vendor/s to design, develop and/or enhance solution by combining system, data, process, digital and other automation tools with subject matter knowledge to address business needs</li> <li>Responsible for engagement with business and/or process subject matter experts to evaluate and propose new solutions for new finance workflows/processes</li> <li>Work across business and technology to establish effective controls, procedures and quality assurance processes</li> <li>Define and implement testing strategy and manage user acceptance testing</li> <li>Manage the Change Management process for new systems and workflows to drive user adoption and ensure smooth transition process with technology solution adopted</li> <li>Anticipate the roadblocks and capacity issues</li> <li>Proactively communicate and collaborate with external/internal parties and manage vendor/s to ensure timely and quality delivery </li> <li>Adopt a customer-centric mind-set to help ensure business requirements deliver the target business outcomes and drive customer value</li> <li>Manage stakeholder communication throughout the project lifecycle to ensure all key stakeholders are apprised of progress and issues are resolved in a timely manner</li> <li>Create and maintain Finance system documentation including process flows, user guides, testing scripts and training manuals</li> <li>Undertake risk analysis and risk reporting to proactively devise interventions to mitigate risks</li> <li>Assist in production support to ensure smooth operation of the Finance system for both finance and business users</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>Educated to graduate degree in Finance, Information Technology or related field with extensive experience from gathering to documenting requirements and conducting design solutions and change interventions </li> <li>Experience of NetSuite functional and/or technical consulting is highly advantageous </li> <li>Adequate knowledge on accounting, tax, treasury and other finance treatments (especially on financial instruments) </li> <li>Experience of FinTech startups or financial institutions is a plus</li> <li>Experience in working with cross-functional teams to gather requirements and prioritize work</li> <li>Strong interpersonal and communication skills to effectively work in multicultural environments </li> <li>Self starter who is excited about driving change and is a fast learner</li> <li>Strong ownership mindset with a proactive “can-do” attitude</li> <li>Passionate about the cryptocurrency / blockchain / trading industry</li> <li>Familiar with Agile / Scrum methodology and the use of Jira as a project documentation / collaboration tool</li> <li>Extremely detail oriented with an ability to multitask in a high growth environment</li> <li>Excellent command of spoken and written English</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech.</li> <li>Flat team. Work side by side with the co-founding team</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team</li> <li>You will get to have involvement in developing a brand new product from scratch alongside with a talented team</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/QRC93ifYGa8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/9D8BFD78A2/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[careers@crypto.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Field Technician - Dallas]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitcoindepot.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Depot&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; is seeking a &lt;strong&gt;Quality Assurance Field Technician&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;that will be responsible for routine inspections and testing of products to ensure standards are met for our BTMs. The ideal candidate will be located in our near Texas and very detailed oriented. The role requires up to 95% travel.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bitcoin Depot is one of the largest multi-cryptocurrency ATM Networks in the world offering users the ability to buy and sell Bitcoin, Litecoin, and Ethereum instantly at thousands of locations. Our mission is to provide the most secure, convenient, and fastest cryptocurrency transaction. Our vision is to bring cryptocurrency market to the masses.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are proud to be an Atlanta Journal-Constitution Top Work Place for 2021.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Preparing and implementing quality assurance policies and procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Plan, perform, and oversee routine inspections and testing of products to ensure standards are met for our BTMs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Commissioning and preparation of BTMs for installation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Physical installation of BTMs at approved and qualified sites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Installation of related signage and marketing materials at site.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ongoing maintenance of ATMs including servicing, preventative maintenance, and replenishment of BTM supplies in accordance to established company guidelines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Travel up to 95% to perform servicing, installations and repairs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Training customers and third party vendors telephonically and in-person.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conducting and collecting accurate merchant and internal information at sites as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Creating training materials and operating manuals.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Documenting quality assurance activities and creating operational and technical reports on an ongoing basis.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Responsible for reporting all problem resolutions to the operations team and the operations manager.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be able to assist other departments within the company with different items as needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Beginner knowledge of Bitcoin and Blockchain is preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years of experience within the ATM or BTM industry is required.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must possess people skills and a personal style that will establish credibility with internal and external customers alike.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Follow procedures and have a structured approach to problem-solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills, both verbally and written.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organization, Routing, and Planning skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Physical Requirements&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;This role requires bending, carrying, climbing, driving, lifting, pushing, pulling, reaching, sitting, standing and walking.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You must be able to lift a minimum of 50 lbs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;&lt;strong data-stringify-type=&quot;bold&quot;&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul class=&quot;p-rich_text_list p-rich_text_list__bullet&quot; data-stringify-type=&quot;unordered-list&quot; data-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Competitive Salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Generous PTO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Health benefits offered with a company contribution towards premiums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Wellness benefits&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;401K Matching&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Revenue Sharing Plan&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Casual dress environment when in office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Monthly company celebrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Advancement opportunities based on results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Weekly catered lunches&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-stringify-indent=&quot;0&quot;&gt;Premium coffee and tea provided by Buckhead Beans&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are an Equal Opportunity Employer that does not discriminate on the basis of actual or perceived race, creed, color, religion, alienage or national origin, ancestry, citizenship status,&amp;nbsp;age,&amp;nbsp;disability or handicap, sex, marital status, veteran status, sexual orientation, genetic information, arrest record, or any other characteristic protected by applicable federal, state or local laws. Our management team is dedicated to this policy with respect to recruitment, hiring, placement, promotion, transfer, training, compensation, benefits, employee activities, and general treatment during employment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/VuS6XCo53DU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitcoindepot/jobs/4842685003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/556151/bitcoin-depot-image-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitcoindepot@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[49753fb8-b518-4786-89b5-9d1bf0e19ac0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Program Manager, NFTs]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ripple’s Creator Fund was developed to foster innovation in tokenization, with a focus on non-fungible tokens (NFTs). The fund provides targeted support for creators, brands and marketplaces to explore new use cases for NFTs on the XRP Ledger (XRPL), leveraging its innate advantages of speed, cost and sustainability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ripple is looking to hire a Program Manager for the Creator Fund program. As a member of the RippleX team, you will engage with external developers, agencies, creators, and brands to bring a diverse set of tokenization projects to the XRP Ledger. You will own the $250M Creator Fund, leading strategy and operational execution of the fund, and ensure all participants have an excellent experience from their application to execution of NFT projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build and own the operating model for administering $250M to NFT ecosystem participants building on XRPL.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Handle pre- and post-fund administration and oversight of projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage strategy and day to day execution with marketplaces, agencies, creators, and brands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the budget, planning, and allocation of resources across projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop streamlined approval processes with relevant internal stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive and ensure regular, ongoing communication and coordination across functions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate efficient meetings to ensure information exchange and alignment across teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor, analyze, and report on the fund applicants and their progress over time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define and measure success metrics, and assist with the preparation of progress reports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work collaboratively with Legal and Finance to create effective and efficient disbursement processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Recommend and contribute to process improvements, including product enhancements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate with Marketing to promote and drive applicants to ensure the ongoing success of the Creator Fund.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We’re Looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of work experience; 2+ experience in enterprise startup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in a fast paced start-up environment is a big plus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A strong interest, curiosity and passion for digital assets / crypto markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of the NFT ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience in managing global Grant/fund programs at scale.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience in implementing policies and procedures across various internal stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to build and manage relationships with creative agencies, developers, and creators and brands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding organizational abilities and interpersonal skills to develop strong working relationships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong background in marketing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serious attention to detail and commitment to excellence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactive, energetic and relentless towards driving progress.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding verbal and written communication skills.&amp;nbsp; Strong presentation skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent problem solving skills / comfort with ambiguity. You should be able to take a problem and structure a solution or recommendation with incomplete or limited data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent time management skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice &lt;/a&gt;and our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/ca-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;California Applicant Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; for reference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3707090?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Communication Specialist]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Securitize]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://securitize.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Austin]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Securitize is a global fintech, Top 50 blockchain company, with a mission to provide investors with access to invest in and trade alternative assets, and for companies to raise capital and offer shareholder's liquidity. Securitize has pioneered a fully digital, regulatory compliant, end-to-end platform for issuing, managing and trading digital asset securities (also known as security tokens), with over 200 businesses and nearly 400,000 investors already connected, and nearly $500 million in current-value digital asset securities issued on the Securitize platform.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif;"> </span></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">We just received $70M in Series B from Wall Street &amp; venture capital funding from top investors to aggressively expand our teams across New York, Miami, San Francisco, and remote offices. We are a global team made up of top blockchain and financial industry talent based around the world, based in Tel Aviv, Buenos Aires, Tokyo, New York, and San Francisco. We’re backed by leading financial institutions and blockchain investors, including Morgan Stanley, Blockchain Capital, MUFG, Sumitomo Mitsui Trust Bank, Sony Finance, Banco Santander, and Coinbase.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">We are looking for a talented, quick-learning<span style="font-weight: bold;"> Senior Communication Specialist</span>, responsible for supporting the Head of Communications &amp; Brand in development of social media content, marketing and PR writing, and coordinating the company’s presence at events/conferences throughout the year.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">This role will support an Austin, Texas-based supervisor, however can be fully remote for the right candidate. The ideal candidate has experience in financial services or journalism, and blockchain experience is ideal.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 15px;">About the role:</span></span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">This role will principally support the Head of Communications and Brand through tactical execution of corporate communications and marketing responsibilities, particularly social media and events. Specific responsibilities include:</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Learning the business, understanding and contributing to positioning, and ensuring consistency across teams and communication channels.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Monitor social media trends to (a) have awareness for the latest winning creative direction, and (b) to thematically know what content is garnering the most engagement.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Monitoring social media for opportunities to engage in support of our goals.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Monitoring and reporting social media KPIs, competitor performance, and leveraging data to drive optimizations and improvements.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Drive a social media channel strategy to aggressively grow followers, engagement, and post visibility.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Draft creative content and obtain compliance approval of social media posts; manage an evolving, news and event-driven social media calendar.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Editorial review of articles, PR, op-eds, web and other copy developed by others for grammar, and brand tone and message consistency.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Provide creative and editorial direction to a graphic designer in producing scroll-stopping, informative and highly engaging social content.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Identify event opportunities to raise the profile and awareness of the brand, our spokespeople and to aid in contributing to new sales leads. </span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Manage an events calendar, including coordinating with executives attending each, ensuring they have necessary marketing collateral, and promoting on social media.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Lead the planning, development and execution of live branded events and webinars, preparing invitee lists, solicitifying location and format, on-site coordination, etc.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 15px;">About you:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">A combined at least four years writing or editing experience, ideally in business or in journalism.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Experience developing successful social media content and growing social media platforms. This would ideally be for a financial, technology or regulated company, though it is not necessary.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Experience in, or demonstrable curiosity about, the financial markets, including blockchain, and an ability to learn the business quickly.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Hustle. Competitive. An ownership mentality.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Able to, not just survive, but thrive in a fast-paced environment where goals must be accomplished with minimal supervision and amid rapidly-evolving circumstances.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Proud of the work you produce without pride of authorship. Willingness to be edited and ability to understand and apply why edits were made.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Comfortable with minimal process and willing to roll-up your sleeves when necessary. We are a startup, and everyone wears many hats.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Someone who enjoys working with a small team where the opportunity to make an impact is high.</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Deep experience with T<span style="font-weight: bold;">witter, Facebook, LinkedIn, Reddit, Telegram, Instagram,</span> and passion for tracking evolving trends and new social platforms.</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br><br></p>
<p><span style="font-family: Lato, sans-serif; font-weight: bold;"><span style="font-size: 15px;">Join an awesome company in a hyper-growth phase:</span></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Opportunity</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Company grant </span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Unlimited Paid Time Off</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Bonus program </span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Remote work environment</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">Company paid professional development </span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">100% Medical/dental/vision insurance</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px; font-family: Lato, sans-serif;">401K</span></li>
</ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/-7Nr4euKbfk" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://securitize.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=51&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/294965/seciritize.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[securitize@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[6fa7bf1d-9e9f-4ac1-9f2a-f1de480d8620]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Securitize]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Ecosystem Relations Lead (Assembly)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOTA Foundation]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.iota.org]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The IOTA Foundation is a not-for-profit organization established in 2017 and headquartered in Berlin, Germany. The Foundation’s mission is to drive the development and standardization of new distributed ledger technologies (DLTs) that enable permissionless innovation ecosystems. To realize this potential the IOTA Foundation is actively building a global ecosystem of developers, founders, investors, experts, private enterprises, governments, civil society, and more.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Concretely, we engage in engineering, research. and community organizing efforts around the IOTA Tangle – a feeless and scalable DLT that supports secure data and value transfers. This includes building a permissionless smart contracts network, Assembly, and other supporting tools that enable the development of future open worlds.</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Mission: </span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">As an Ecosystem Relations Lead for Assembly you will acquire and manage relationships with builders, founders, investors and experts working in crypto and Web3. You will be a bridge-builder, connecting these groups together and routing information, capital and relationships. In addition, you will help identify and bring in new members into the Assembly ecosystem.<br><br></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #091e42;">Responsibilities<br><br></span></span></p>
<p><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Discovery: scout for and onboard new individuals, organization and projects working in crypto and Web3<br><br></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Actively scan crypto and adjacent industries for potentially valuable additions to the community</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Add to, update, and coordinate with rest of the team to work through the Discovery funnel entries</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Reach out to, qualify, convert and onboard candidates<br><br></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Relationship Management: be the dedicated point of contact for Assembly community members<br><br></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Establish a relationship with community members, and develop an understanding of their needs, goals, progress, and expectations</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Build bridges for the community to help them become active contributors</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Work directly with community members and their project teams to support their needs (dedicated Discord channel, regular check-ins, etc.)</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Establish connections to subject matter experts in Web3 for more specific support</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Find and build relationships with other community members, including scheduling introductions, keeping track of participants within their domain</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Educate about Assembly’s strategy, logy, and positioning<br><br></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Knowledge Management: route information between groups and the Assembly team<br> </span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Capture and synthesize key learnings and share with the community and team<br><br><br></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;"><span style="color: #222222;">Requirements</span></span></p>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;">Your Personality</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">You enjoy working with various internal and external stakeholders</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">You feel comfortable presenting or being on a stage at events</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">You can adapt to changing circumstances with ease</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">You are proactive, self sufficient and like to take new challenges</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">You enjoy working in a remote team environment</span></li>
</ul>
<p><br></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"><span style="font-weight: bold;">Your  Expertise</span><br><br></span></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Understanding of Web3 ecosystems and crypto.</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Previous experience in other DLT communities is valued</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Technical understanding of IOTA’s technology and core principles. Existing understanding of EVM a plus</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Outstanding communication skills</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #091e42; font-size: 15px;">Flexibility to engage on several different digital platforms (eg, discord, twitter, etc.)</span></li>
<li><span style="font-size: 15px;"><span style="color: #091e42;">High level of fluency in spoken and written English, other languages are a plus</span><span style="color: #091e42;"><br><br></span></span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px; font-weight: bold;">What we offer</span></p>
<p><br></p>
<ul>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The opportunity to work with the brightest minds in the industry</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">An annual budget for personal development</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Flexible working hours and fully remote set-up</span></li>
<li><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">Culture of trust, empowerment and constructive feedback</span></li>
</ul>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;"> </span></p>
<p><span style="color: #222222; font-size: 15px;">The IOTA Foundation is an equal opportunity employer. We celebrate diversity and are committed to creating an inclusive environment for all employees.</span></p><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/LVY9DzwyzdU" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://iota.bamboohr.com/jobs/view.php?id=183&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180020/iota.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iota@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[89e42fc6-4d4d-416c-82b4-a1443bc5e101]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOTA Foundation]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[UX Designer - Lightwallet]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[IOHK]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://iohk.io]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>IO Global is searching for a User Experience Designer to join its Lightwallet team. We are looking for someone who can turn our software into easy-to-use products for our clients. As a UX Designer you will be responsible for gathering and understanding user requirements, brainstorming, and designing UX patterns. You should have experience with user research and wireframe tools. If you also have a portfolio of professional design projects including work with web/mobile applications, we’d like to meet you.</p> <p>You will create functional and appealing features that address our needs and those of our users. Ultimately, by creating frictionless user experiences, you’ll be helping us to grow our customer base.</p><p><strong>Your mission </strong></p><ul> <li>Planning and conducting user research and competitor analysis</li> <li>Interpreting data and qualitative feedback</li> <li>Creating wireframes, user journeys, and workflows</li> <li>Determining information architecture and creating sitemaps </li> <li>Collaborating on surveys and focus groups</li> <li>Conducting usability testing for software products</li> <li>Gathering and evaluating user requirements, in collaboration with product managers and engineers</li> <li>Illustrating design ideas using storyboards, process flows, and sitemaps</li> <li>Developing user interface mock-ups and prototypes that clearly illustrate how sites function and look </li> <li>Collaborating with technical and product managers to understand technical constraints of the product that will guide workflow</li> <li>Preparing and presenting drafts to internal teams and to stakeholders</li> <li>Identifying and troubleshooting UX problems such as responsiveness.</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><p><strong>Your expertise</strong>  </p> <ul> <li>Minimum of five years’ UX design experience</li> <li>Experience with mobile and web apps, and blockchain wallets</li> <li>Degree or higher in design, computer science, or relevant field</li> <li>Outstanding digital portfolio across channels, including live projects and conceptual</li> <li>Experience in information architecture such as mindmap, navigation, and sitemap</li> <li>Ability to distil complex tasks into clear, clever, and creative patterns without overloading the user</li> <li>Proficiency in up-to-date design programs such as Sketch and Figma</li> <li>Experience in prototyping and wireframe mock-up </li> <li>User research and analysis, and usability testing experience would be desirable.</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p><p><strong>Location</strong></p><p>IOG is a fully distributed organization and therefore this is a remote position. Due to team distribution we are ideally searching for someone in an EMEA timezone.  </p><p><strong>All Colleagues</strong></p><ul> <li>Flexible schedule</li> <li>Remote work - ability to work anywhere</li> <li>Laptop reimbursement</li> <li>Learning &amp; Development Opportunities</li> <li>New starter package to buy hardware essentials (headphones, monitor, etc)</li> <li>Competitive PTO and Sick Leave plan</li> </ul><p><strong>US Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Medical, Dental, and Vision benefits coverage through Anthem with 100% premium cost covered by IO Global for the employee and dependents</li> <li>Health Savings Account</li> <li>Life Insurance</li> </ul><p><strong>UK Employees</strong></p><ul> <li>Monthly Health Stipend to use towards any wellness or medical coverage/service</li> <li>Pension</li> </ul><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/EM-XkuQdUq8" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/io-global/j/A2C7F356D5/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/143583/iohk.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[iohk@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[9b89f946-6d3b-434f-aa32-f0e84ecb2992]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[IOHK]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Head of Risk and Compliance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Celo]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://celo.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 11pt">At the Celo Foundation our mission is to build a financial system that creates the conditions for prosperity for all.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Celo aims to remove the barriers for large-scale adoption of cryptocurrencies as means-of-payment. Using a novel address-based encryption algorithm, the Celo protocol makes sending money as easy as sending a text. Additionally, Celo uses stable-value tokens pegged to fiat currencies, like the US Dollar, to minimize volatility. Celo is an open protocol enabling many to participate in the system, even with a budget Android smartphone. The first application launching on the Celo platform, Valora, is a social payments and money transfer app, aimed at developing markets.</span>&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">The purpose of risk management is to continue to build out systems and programs to provide important information about potential risks across the Celo ecosystem by identifying and managing and identifying those risks.&nbsp; To collaborate with the larger ecosystem, with Alliance Members, and the Celo Foundation Board to ensure that risks are identified and considered in the development of the strategic vision, and proactively manage to balance both the risk and rewards. In overseeing&nbsp; these risks, the Head of Risk and Compliance will continue to facilitate the organization’s definition of risk appetite and tolerance, coordinate risk assessments, identify the operational and strategic risks, facilitate the prioritization of risks and identification of risk owners, and develop and communicate risk reports to management and the Board of Directors.&nbsp; The Head of Risk and Compliance will also oversee and own the Foundation’s business continuity management program and key risk and compliance policies. We are looking for that unique individual who brings experience in managing and running robust risk and compliance processes while thinking creatively about their application to decentralized cryptocurrency protocols.&nbsp; This role offers a great opportunity for growth and advancement in a vibrant startup environment.</span></div><br/>You Will:<br/><li>Maintain and continue building out Enterprise Risk Management for the Foundation&nbsp;</li><li>Undertake risk assessment and risk mitigation for all business operations and support units to ensure that all major risks are identified and mitigated.</li><li>Ensure the Foundation has proper, systematic management and compliance with established policies, practices and procedures related to risk management.&nbsp;</li><li>Maintain risk manuals and relevant documentation for audit and inspection.&nbsp;</li><li>Identify potential risk event, loss or exposures (both financial and non-financial), evaluate or analyze these risk events and provide recommendations on how to mitigate the potential impact and/or occurrence.&nbsp;</li><li>Assist in identifying improvements in current systems, policies and strategies and take actions to mitigate emerging and related risks.&nbsp;</li><li>Ensure regular and timely reporting to the management and/or the Board of Directors on then outcome of risk management activities undertaken.&nbsp;</li><li>Keep abreast with the latest risk management practices and/or standards and proactively adapt these practices and/or standards where appropriate.&nbsp;</li><li>Assist in cultivating an organization-wide culture of risk awareness and management.</li><li>Work closely and collaboratively with Partner with the Information Security function to support the design, build and execution of industry leading practices.</li><br/>You Have:<br/><li>BA/BS in relevant field or commensurate years of experience</li><li>8-10 years of compliance experience, J.D., M.B.A. or other advanced degree a plus</li><li>Fundamental understanding of anti-money laundering and sanctions regulations</li><li>Working knowledge of KYC RegTech, fiat and crypto-related transaction monitoring technology, including blockchain analytics</li><li>Experience in implementing policies, processes and controls and assessing implications of key compliance risks</li><li>Experience working with financial regulators</li><li>Working understanding of the cryptocurrency industry</li><li>Demonstrable integrity, initiative, perseverance, organizational and leadership skills</li><li>Strong communication and interpersonal skills</li><li>Ability to work independently and as part of a team and take on new tasks</li><li>Strong attention to detail</li><li>Strong personal ethics</li><li>CAMS, CFE, or equivalent certification is preferred</li><div><span>cLabs ("Celo Labs") started Celo in 2017 and is one of many contributors to the open source project Celo.&nbsp;cLabs builds financial technology to enable prosperity of all beings.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>cLabs is a Teal organization, a method of decentralized management and organizational governance. Roles are defined around the work, not people, and there is a high degree of autonomy. As such, we're all proud to hold the job title of "Partner." For more information on our culture, we encourage you to check out our blog at&nbsp;</span><a href="https://medium.com/celohq/the-future-is-teal-cc264a5d51d3" class="postings-link"><span>https://medium.com/celohq/the-future-is-teal-cc264a5d51d3</span></a><span>.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>To build technology and products that are used and loved by people and solve real-world problems, we need to build a team with many different perspectives and experiences. We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not discriminate on the basis of race, religion, color, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status. We encourage candidates from all backgrounds to apply and always consider qualified applicants with arrest and conviction records, in accordance with the San Francisco Fair Chance Ordinance.</span></div><div><br></div><div><span>Applicants in need of special assistance or accommodation during the interview process or in accessing our website may contact us by sending an email to assistance(at)</span><a href="http://celo.org" class="postings-link"><span>celo.org</span></a><span>. We will treat your request as confidentially as possible. In your email, please include your name and preferred method of contact, and we will respond as soon as possible.</span></div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/vwfHiaVzc2E" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/clabs/ad1ca5f9-bb06-4a2b-a574-2d94cfbe4847/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145322/celo.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[celo@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c6054e2e-9096-43cc-9ea8-c4a05ab9335a]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Celo]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Finance & Accounting ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Business Development - Commodities]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Paxos]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London, Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos is on a mission to enable the movement of any asset, any time, in a trustworthy way. Today’s financial infrastructure is archaic, expensive, inefficient and risky - supporting a system that leaves out more people than it lets in. So we’re rebuilding it.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a regulated blockchain infrastructure company, we use technology to tokenize, custody, trade, and settle assets for enterprise clients like PayPal, Novi, Bank of America, and Interactive Brokers. Paxos is a top-funded blockchain company, with more than $500 million in total funding from leading investors like OakHC/FT, Founders Fund, PayPal Ventures, and Declaration Partners. Together, we empower today’s financial leaders to build a more open, trusted economy.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;We need someone to join our &lt;strong&gt;Business Development team&lt;/strong&gt; to help drive growth in Commodities by establishing commercial relationships with a focus on - but not limited to - Banks and Brokers. This person will be responsible for creating sales opportunities for Commodities Settlement and Optimization products, in a network growth environment.&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As a member of our Business Development team, you&#39;ll get to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive growth in Commodities.&amp;nbsp; You will report to the Head of Growth and will be responsible for new business development.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be responsible for creating sales opportunities for Commodities Settlement and Optimization products in a network growth environment. Success is being able to convince banks and brokers to work with Paxos and to advance their settlement processes to Simultaneous settlement through our regulated Trust Company. Developing relationships and managing stakeholders to close deals, as well as being able to analyse the ROI we can offer our clients, is critical.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Show that you are a keen self starter, hungry to close business and able to use everything in your tool box to close deals.&amp;nbsp; You should thrive when thinking about opportunities and maximise your efforts through networking and connecting counterparties in order to increase value proposition.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;p-rich_text_section&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You experience should include:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of experience selling to customer base of banks and brokers with an understanding of network sales&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A track record of building customer relationships in large enterprises, while delivering on commercial goals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Aptitude and interest to learn the deeper details of how Commodities settlement works&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A demonstrated passion for driving innovation and change with little supervision&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You might also have:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Great communication skills to present our vision and win customer support&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Comfortability working in a continuous evolving business.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll love about Paxos:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos has consistently been named as a “Best Place to Work” by BuiltIn and was recently listed on the 2021 Forbes Fintech 50. All of our employees have significant ownership and impact on our business, as well as benefits like company equity, health insurance, family leave, a $500 quarterly stipend for development, a $500 stipend for home office setup and unlimited PTO. From team product demos and virtual lounge and learns to care packages and an active Slack #shoutouts channel, there are countless opportunities to connect and make your mark. Help us continue to build a new, open financial system from one of our three offices or right from your home!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/10/19/usdp-chosen-for-novi-pilot/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;USDP Stablecoin Chosen for Facebook&#39;s Pilot of Novi Digital Wallet&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/fintech/2021/#413b4e2631a6&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Forbes Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 50&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/13/paxos-supports-interactive-brokers-journey-into-crypto-markets/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Interactive Brokers&#39; Journey into Crypto Markets&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cbinsights.com/research/report/fintech-250-startups-most-promising/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;CB Insights Names Paxos to 2021 Fintech 250 for Crypto Category&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/09/30/trust-is-not-an-option-its-a-requirement-paxos-explains-its-unique-approach-to-pioneering-a-new-market/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Supports Flourish Crypto&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/23/paxos-national-trust-receives-occ-conditional-approval-for-de-novo-charter/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos National Trust Receives OCC Conditional Approval for De Novo Charter&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2021/04/29/paxos-raises-300-million-in-series-d-funding-at-2-4-billion-valuation/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos Raises $300M in Series D Funding at 2.4B Valuation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://paxos.com/2020/10/21/paypal-launches-new-service-enabling-users-to-buy-hold-and-sell-cryptocurrency/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Paxos &amp;amp; PayPal Bring Crypto to Millions of Users&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our Paxos team is made up of passionate people from all over the world with different perspectives and experiences. If this opportunity excites you, but your experience doesn’t perfectly match the description…apply! Unique voices help us build a more transparent and open economy.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/NDa8GIm_5EE" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.paxos.com/careers/role/5709289002?gh_jid=5709289002&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/215201/paxos.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[paxos@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[c782dc3a-8644-40b8-919b-b98b0cb1b35f]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Paxos]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[React Native Engineer (Remote US)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Stacked Invest]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://stackedinvest.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Chicago or Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Stacked is looking to add to its dynamic group of professionals that are dedicated to simplifying crypto investing and helping as many people as possible to take part in the greatest investment opportunity in history. </div><div><br></div><div>Based in Chicago, Stacked is a venture-funded crypto company with less than 100 employees. It provides automation technology to help investors more easily manage their cryptocurrency investments and strategies. Founded out of a personal need, Stacked has grown quickly and has facilitated tens of millions of trades, billions of dollars of volume, and helped tens of thousands of users. Visit <a href="http://www.stackedinvest.com" class="postings-link">www.stackedinvest.com</a> to learn more.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>And, while work experience and educational preparation are certainly important, we don’t hire resumes.&nbsp; We hire talented individuals based on our culture and values that can help us drive innovation and get us to the next stage of our business.</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a software engineer to help build our MVP mobile application on iOS and Android to help get us to the next stage of our company. Over the next several years we are going to be faced with some incredibly complex technical challenges and we will rely on you to help us overcome them. </div><br/>Your Core Contributions To The Team<br/><li>Actively contribute to the scrum team deliverables for each sprint&nbsp;</li><li>Lead the development for iOS and Android platforms using React Native within the team</li><li>Setup and maintain automated test suite for mobile applications</li><li>Maintain the mobile apps CI/CD infrastructure and act quickly when unexpected issues arise. </li><br/>About You<br/><li>4+ years of experience developing mobile (iOS and Android) applications using React Native.</li><li>Experienced with all phases of app development - from prototyping to publishing to the App Store or Google Play.</li><li>Experience with agile development methodologies such as SCRUM or Kanban</li><li>Ability to work collaboratively in teams and develop meaningful relationships to achieve common goals</li><li>A passion for investing and the crypto-currency space</li><div>Note: This position is only available in US time zones.</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">#LI-Remote</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">What We Provide You</b></div><div>Stacked works hard to provide benefits that make your life better. We offer a comprehensive benefit program that features:</div><div><br></div><div>- Health coverage for you and your family through medical, dental, and vision plans.</div><div>- A 401(k) plan with a company match.</div><div>- Free gym access in the Chicago office.</div><div>- A generous paid time off program.</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">All The Other Stuff</b></div><div>Stacked is proud to be an equal opportunity workplace dedicated to pursuing and hiring a diverse workforce. We are committed to building an environment of mutual respect, free of discrimination and harassment, where opportunities are available to everyone based on business needs, job requirements, and individual qualifications.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>The job functions listed above represent the primary duties and responsibilities of this job and in no way states or implies that these are the only duties to be performed by you. Other duties and responsibilities within the scope of this job may be assigned.&nbsp; You will be required to follow all instructions and to perform all duties requested by your manager; subject to reasonable accommodations and within the scope of the position.</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/stacked-invest/2146d622-001c-48c2-97e0-8c1e0a610512/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/943211/stacked_invest.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[alexander+stacked@cryptocareers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[f165af66-d59c-48cc-9832-2dc642e4bdb9]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Stacked Invest]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
