<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Marketing Manager - Tallinn or Remote in Europe]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ultra]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ultra.io/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Tallinn]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><span style="font-size: 17pt">About Ultra</span></div><div><br></div><div>Ultra is a blockchain company launching a PC games distribution platform initially and ultimately an app ecosystem.&nbsp;Ultra offers a highly integrative user experience and new business models for developers, gamers and influencers. Our goal is to unify the fragmented gaming industry around one platform.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>The combination of cutting-edge technologies we use (including blockchain) enables Ultra to aggregate all gamers’ activities in one place: from buying, playing and reselling games, to accessing live-streaming platforms, tournaments, reviews and contests, as well as interacting with communities and brands.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>The team is currently composed of 70+ full-time members, working across 5 continents. To learn more, visit our website:<a href="https://ultra.io/" class="postings-link"> https://ultra.io/</a></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 17pt">The Role</span></div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">Ultra is looking for an experienced marketing manager to lead our growing marketing team. This is an exciting role in an ambitious startup that's ready to shake up the gaming industry.</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">In this role, you will lead the development of Ultra's global and local marketing strategies. Reporting directly to Ultra's CEOs, you will think creatively and strategically about Ultra's brand development, design and implement marketing campaigns, and will have a direct impact on Ultra's growth.</span>&nbsp;&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><span style="font-size: 17pt">Your Profile</span></div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 11pt">You are an experienced gaming marketing manager with a proven track record in leading complex B2C marketing projects from design to completion.&nbsp;</b><span style="font-size: 11pt">You know how to design and execute go-to market strategies. You have experience building and maintaining a recognisable brand in your field.</span></div><div><span style="font-size: 11pt">You enjoy interacting with high-level internal and external stakeholders, and you are quickly able to build a strong network of industry partners and providers. You are proactive, creative, .&nbsp;You are a strong team-player, and a people leader. You are KPI-driven, and you know how to measure your impact and drive your and your team's efforts.</span></div><br/>Key Requirements<br/><li><b>5+ years experience leading complex B2C marketing projects from design to completion</b></li><li><b>Previous experience leading a marketing team for a gaming product</b></li><li>Experienced designing and executing products go to market strategies</li><li>Experience building and maintaining a recognisable and trusted brand</li><li>Proven track record in successful, multi-channel marketing campaigns</li><li>Excellent interpersonal skills</li><li>Able to build a strong network of industry partners and providers</li><li>Proactive, creative, self-driven with an analytical mindset and entrepreneurial spirit</li><li>High interest in gaming and crypto, with previous experience in the games industry</li><li>A strong commercial awareness and data-oriented mindset to measure and maximize performance</li><li>Fluent in English</li><br/>It's great if you also have:<br/><li>A strong personal brand / persona on social media</li><li>Previous experience in the crypto industry</li><li>Previous startup experience</li><li>Fluent in French</li><br/>What you will do<br/><li><b>Your challenges</b></li><li>Ultra is an ambitious startup in a very promising market: through marketing and brand awareness, you will have a direct impact on our growth as a company.</li><li>You will work with staff &amp; entities all around the world, and collaborating with them will be part of your daily routine, and the key to our success.</li><div><br></div><div><b>Your tasks</b></div><li>Lead the development of the Global Marketing strategy and calendar, planned in partnership with Ultra's executive team</li><li>Manage the Marketing team's performance</li><li>Think creatively and strategically about Ultra's brand development and awareness</li><li>Research and analyse industry leaders and market trends</li><li>&nbsp;Implement and project manage the campaign strategy to support our ambitious growth objectives</li><li>Maximise monthly marketing budget to reach our objectives</li><li>Coordinate post-project retrospectives to ensure evaluation against objectives and key learnings and insights</li><li>Track the relevant indicators to maximise performance and impact, report to Ultra's leadership</li><br/>What's next<br/><li>If we select your application, you will start our interview process:</li><li>Meet Mathilde, Recruiter</li><li>Meet David and Nicolas, Ultra's co-CEOs</li><li>Meet Nada and Rami, who are working on Ultra's marketing strategy</li><div><span style="font-size: 9pt">🌈 Ultra is a true international company currently spread across the globe (Estonia, Belgium, France, Portugal, Ukraine, USA, China, South Africa…). We thrive off diverse perspectives! We recognize that diversity has different aspects: gender, sexual orientation, ability, ethnic origin, social, age, lifestyle, and more! We're committed to giving equal opportunities, and fostering a culture where everyone is heard and feels a sense of belonging.</span></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/ultra/69afbcb2-6433-401c-8855-585adf4cf184/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/549658/ultra-logo-400x400.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ultra@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[01d06fb8-7df1-4a55-9ad1-eceeb24b632e]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ultra]]></employer_name>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Security Technical Project Management, Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://crypto.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Sai Wan, Hong Kong Island, Hong Kong]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>About the Role</p><p>We are looking for a full-time Security Technical Project Management Associate, who is responsible for multiple functions from both implementation projects and internal application development perspectives in the Security Team.</p><p>Responsibilities</p><ul> <li>Work in the Security Project Management team which is part of the Security IT team.</li> <li>Manage waterfall implementation projects including IT infrastructure, security solutions and Devsecops related projects.<ul> <li>Gather and elicit requirements from different stakeholders</li> <li>Define project baseline in terms of scope, cost, timeline and resource</li> <li>Report to the Sec PMO office and Steering Committee with the management </li> <li>Draft test plan and test case with QA</li> <li>Communicate with vendor for POC and implementation</li> <li>Work with end-users for project initiation till roll-out</li> </ul> </li> <li>Act as a product owner to manage internal applications development<ul> <li>Elicit user requirement and technical requirements from stakeholders</li> <li>Drive application development in an agile environment</li> <li>Able to drive discovery, define and delivery phases for product features</li> <li>Facilitate daily standup, sprint planning, release planning, roadmap, technical discussions and retrospective meetings with stakeholders</li> </ul> </li> <li>Assist to design and drive security features for our end products</li> <li>Act as a security team point of contact in terms of the collaboration with different teams.</li> <li>Take the initiative and collaborate with internal stakeholders.</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>3 years of working experience, with a minimum of 2 years of experience in project management or lead technical support role for software applications.</li> <li>Must be proactive and possess strong English communication skills (written and verbal).</li> <li>Demonstrated success in defining and launching IT projects and security-related products.</li> <li>Remote work using collaboration and IM software like Microsoft Teams, Slack, etc.</li> <li>A Bachelor’s degree.</li> <li>Technical background, with experience in the IT industry including digital solutions or infrastructure or cloud-related or application development.</li> <li>Excellent teamwork skills.</li> <li>Proven ability to influence cross-functional teams without formal authority.</li> </ul><p>Has to be proactive and passionate in a Startup environment.<br></p><p>Benefits</p><ul> <li>We offer an attractive compensation package working in a cutting-edge field of Fintech;</li> <li>Huge responsibilities from Day 1. Be the owner of your own learning curve. The possibilities are limitless and depend on you;</li> <li>You get to work in a very dynamic environment and be part of an international team;</li> <li>You will get to be involved in developing a brand-new product from scratch alongside a talented team.</li> </ul>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/crypto-dot-com/j/0D6C879358//apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/180888/cryptocom.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[careers@crypto.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[08b998fc-63af-482e-9310-d578bb3d4ffd]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Crypto.com]]></employer_name>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Product Designer (Professional Services, UK/Ireland & Europe)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Consensys]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.consensys.net]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[UK, Ireland, France, Spain, Portugal, Germany, Romania, Italy]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At ConsenSys we have a vision of a world where data sovereignty and financial well-being is accessible to every person and organization. We believe Ethereum and decentralized protocol technology is a more trustworthy and equitable foundation for how we create and share value across the web. On this trusted, open source foundation, we can accelerate the world’s transition to a universally accessible network of distributed participants where transparency, security and freedom are fundamental.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our product suite, composed of Truffle, Infura, Quorum, Codefi, MetaMask, and Diligence, serves millions of users, supports billions of blockchain-based queries for our clients, and has handled billions of dollars in digital assets. As the leading Ethereum software company, ConsenSys enables developers, enterprises, and people worldwide to build next-generation applications, launch modern financial infrastructure, and access the decentralized web. To learn more about ConsenSys, and explore our products and solutions, visit &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://consensys.net/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;http://consensys.net/&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Professional Services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Professional Services is a client-facing division of ConsenSys Software focused on delivering Ethereum empowered solutions for enterprises around the globe.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our teams are busy at work building the future of identity, financial markets, commerce, security and infrastructure, and more. If you are someone that thrives in a dynamic environment where being well-adapted, determined, and resilient are a requirement, we would love for you to join us.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What you’ll do&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work closely with the Product Design Lead or Project Manager to define features, patterns, UX and UI that provide user value&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Collaborate with engineers, product managers, business analysts and the full products team to deliver usable &amp;amp; thoughtfully designed products&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Use research &amp;amp; testing to drive and validate your design decisions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Map goals and success metrics to data points and insights&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Participate in the QA process by developing clear, specific, and testable acceptance criteria&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Designers at ConsenSys balance real passion for the technology while knowing when and how to focus the conversation on the user. ConsenSys designers enjoy an open and inclusive culture, competitive benefits and the freedom to explore and experiment. We are always iterating and improving our work, the culture, and ourselves.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Would be great if you brought this to the role&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of experience working in product and design&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proven ability to adapt and react to new information quickly&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You are self-disciplined and can work well both collaboratively and independently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellence in articulating design decisions, and presenting to clients or partners&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve built or maintained design systems&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in building and shipping applications or software&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A portfolio featuring examples of interaction design work&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bonus points for&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Visual design experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working in an Agile team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience working as part of a remote team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience participating in cryptocurrency communities&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated interest in Ethereum, smart contracts, and/or cryptoeconomics&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Front-end development experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&#39;t meet all the requirements? Don&#39;t sweat it. We’re passionate about building a diverse team of humans and as such, if you think you&#39;ve got what it takes for our chaotic-but-fun, remote-friendly, start-up environment—apply anyway. While we have a pretty good idea of what we need, we&#39;re ready for you to challenge our thinking on who needs to be in this role.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is an equal opportunity employer. We encourage people from all backgrounds to apply. We are committed to ensuring that our technology is made available and accessible to everyone. All employment decisions are made without regard to race, color, national origin, ancestry, sex, gender, gender identity or expression, sexual orientation, age, genetic information, religion, disability, medical condition, pregnancy, marital status, family status, veteran status, or any other characteristic protected by law.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;ConsenSys is aware of fraudulent recruitment practices and we encourage all applicants to review our best practices to protect yourself which can be found &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://consensys.net/careers/best-practices-to-avoid-recruitment-fraud/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;here&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;: &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;https://consensys.net/careers/best-practices-to-avoid-recruitment-fraud&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://consensys.net/open-roles/gh_jid?gh_jid=3663096&ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/341584/consensys.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[consensys@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[1036a9a0-3cf5-4e0b-bfa9-5c096c0d3a02]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Consensys]]></employer_name>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Kiva US Operations Associate]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kiva]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.kiva.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Portland, OR / U.S Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kiva (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://kiva.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;kiva.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;) &lt;/span&gt;is an international nonprofit with a mission to expand financial access to help underserved communities thrive. We run a global marketplace platform to crowdfund microloans for financially excluded entrepreneurs, farmers and students around the world. &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Through Kiva Capital, we serve as a bridge between large scale impact first investors and underserved populations. Our digital identity platform enables borrowers who don’t have a track record with traditional financial institutions to record and verify their financial history and gain access to less costly mainstream financial markets. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our organization combines the culture and technological passion of an internet start-up with the compassion and empathy of a non-profit to create impact and opportunity at global scale. &lt;/span&gt;Since 2005, we have raised more than $1.57 billion in loan capital for 3.9 million borrowers in 98 countries. Our lenders fund over $10 million in loans every month. With offices in San Francisco, Portland, New York, Nairobi, and Bangkok, Kiva&#39;s team includes 100+ employees and 400+ volunteers worldwide. Our team is growing as we pursue exciting new opportunities to create a financially inclusive world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role overview:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Kiva U.S. team provides 0%, no-fee loans of up to $15,000 to entrepreneurs and small businesses in the United States that are typically excluded from formal financing products. With no minimum credit score and an inclusive approach to underwriting, Kiva U.S. extends access to capital to small businesses across the country.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In communities and cities where there is an expressed gap in affordable financing options, Kiva offers a plug-in microlending partnership model for small business support centers, city governments, and community development financial institutions called the Kiva Hubs program. In more than 40 cities like Oakland, New York, Detroit, and Pittsburgh, partners are developing small business ecosystems and deepening their impact by making Kiva loans accessible to the entrepreneurs they serve.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is a unique role that gets to play a part in the complete lifecycle of a Kiva US borrower, from application to repayment. As a Kiva US Operations Associate, you will participate in the execution of Kiva’s innovative, social underwriting process, and support our borrowers with their repayments. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In other words, you will be performing the tasks that turn a loan application into capital in an entrepreneur’s hands and then work on ensuring they repay their loan in full so Kiva lenders can support even more borrowers!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will learn the current processes we use to vet borrowers and to manage their delinquency, as well as engage with the larger team in suggesting and executing improvements to our processes and tech infrastructure&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;. Once you’re fully onboarded, a typical day might include approving loan applications reviewed by our underwriting team, answering borrower questions, monitoring loan review and repayment through key metrics, creating repayment reports to be shared with partners, attending team problem-solving sessions on ways to improve the underwriting process and/or strategies to increase repayment, and experimenting with new solutions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If you’re highly analytical, detail oriented, mission driven, and if you’re interested in seeing a fast-growing startup expand and scale, this job is for you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At this time, we can only consider applicants with authorization to work in the United States on a permanent, full-time basis; unfortunately we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key responsibilities include:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support the US Credit Operations Manager on the underwriting process for entrepreneurs interested in receiving a loan through Kiva&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead the communications with borrowers in repayment, helping them avoid delinquency or default&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Carry out collections, delinquency, and defaulting processes for repaying borrowers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track and analyze impact and loan fundraising/repayment metrics for both reporting and strategy-informing purposes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create and support projects aimed at improving our operations and at increasing the value we provide to our borrowers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Implement innovative solutions to boost one of the most important metrics of our program: repayment rate&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bachelor’s degree&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;1-3 years of relevant academic or professional experience&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong critical thinking and process orientation&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Attention for detail and ownership of your work&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Enjoys completing processes efficiently while maintaining high quality&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Thorough and organized, responsible and reliable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Highly proactive and able to work independently&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to manage time well and prioritize across competing tasks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Tech-savvy&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Spanish is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Familiarity with Salesforce, Looker, Excel, Google Suite is a plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Passion for social impact and financial inclusion&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An opportunity to improve real lives, solve hard problems, and change the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Friendly, supportive, and adventurous environment with a team of engaged colleagues&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A comprehensive, industry-leading benefits package&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Opportunities to connect with and learn from colleagues and partners around the world&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Salary range for Colorado : $48K - $50K&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A diverse and inclusive workplace where we learn from each other is an integral part of Kiva&#39;s culture. We actively welcome people of different backgrounds, experiences, abilities and perspectives. We are an equal opportunity employer and a great place to work. Join us and help us achieve our mission!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We will only accept applications directly from candidates. Kiva will not be responsible for any recruiting agency fees, absent a formal agreement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/kivaorg/jobs/3665354?gh_jid=3665354&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194099/kiva.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kiva@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[12467ec7-a781-4b48-abdb-bfbbc2a9cc79]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kiva]]></employer_name>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[People Operations Coordinator]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Tari Labs]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.tari.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Nashville, TN (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Tari Labs, a digital assets-focused blockchain organization that believes privacy on the internet should be pervasive and available to all, was co-founded by Naveen Jain (who also founded Sparkart). And in case you’re worried about funding (stability), Yat is backed by Blockchain Capital, Pantera Capital, Multicoin Capital, Trinity Ventures, Redpoint Ventures, Canaan Partners, and Slow Ventures (as well as some of the best investors in the world).</div><div><br></div><div>Yat is the brainchild of Tari Labs. It’s really about connecting to the universal language of visual representation in a whole new way, one that celebrates individuals, community, and everyone’s right to privacy in the digital realm. We don’t want to say we’re changing the world, but yeah, we are.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We also happen to be one of the fastest-growing consumer products of all time (👑 us) and as such needs an incredibly talented team dedicated to making sure it’s continued 🚀from here on out.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a People Operations Coordinator to help Tari Labs support and build a high-performing, mission-driven People team. The People Operations Coordinator will help shape the programs and processes that help Tari create and maintain a great culture to work in. Our team cares deeply about the employee experience and we work hard to help our teams, employees, and leaders thrive.</div><div><br></div><div>If that sounds like you, join us.&nbsp;</div><br/>About You:<br/><li>You have a positive attitude (and a sense of humor) when things don’t go as planned.</li><li>You can pivot quickly in a rapidly growing startup environment with a sense of urgency and be comfortable with the unknown.</li><li>You exhibit attention to detail, especially when working on routine tasks, processes, and projects.</li><li>You can give and receive constructive feedback without hesitation and while maintaining objectivity.</li><li>You embody our core values, represent our brand as a cultural ambassador, have a service-oriented mindset, and work cross-functionally with all types of people.</li><br/>What You’ll Do:<br/><li>Recruitment Coordination</li><li>Build solid relationships with hiring managers, being a thought-partner and providing solutions around interview logistics, and keeping them informed as needed.</li><li>You will support hiring managers and the People team through recruiting coordination and partner with them to onboard new team members.&nbsp;</li><li>This includes scheduling all types of interviews (phone screens, zoom interviews, case presentations, reference calls, etc.) and sourcing candidates if needed.</li><li>Maintaining our applicant tracking system integrity and logging all appropriate information into the system to help track candidate progress from initial contact to offer.&nbsp;</li><li>Audit job descriptions, postings, and interview notes.</li><div><br></div><li>Company Administration</li><li>Assist the Head of People with general HR inquiries, including HR policies and procedures, systems administration, and tactfully managing or redirecting escalations.</li><li>Keeping employee data and reporting up to date. Maintain the accuracy of and policy updates on HR Notion and employee handbook.</li><li>Handle confidential employee information with discretion, ensuring data integrity and compliance.</li><li>Provide monthly employee reports and perform data analysis and audits as needed.</li><div><br></div><li>Employee Experience</li><li>Facilitate the onboarding process to ensure new hires have a seamless experience.</li><li>Collect feedback from our employees through regular new hire and engagement surveys.</li><li>Learn fundamental employee relations, be coached and developed to take on larger duties such as exit interviews, conducting new hire orientation, assisting in the annual performance process and talent management processes, administering the system, and interpreting and using data for strategic decisions and change management.</li><br/>Requirements:<br/><li>2+ years proven work experience as a high volume recruiting coordinator, or recruiter, with experience scheduling all types of interviews (interviews for various lines of business at a high volume)</li><li>1+ years of experience in an administrative, people ops support required, ideally in a fully remote or hybrid environment.</li><li>Technologically savvy and familiar with our tools (gSuite, Zoom, Notion, etc)</li><li>Familiarity with Applicant Tracking Systems (especially Lever)</li><li>Familiarity with PEOs (especially TriNet)</li><br/>Bonus Points:<br/><li>Experience supporting a SaaS/tech start-up</li><li>Global HR experience&nbsp;</li><br/>Benefits:<br/><li>100% Remote</li><li>Highly competitive compensation package</li><li>Comprehensive benefits, including up to 100% paid medical, dental, &amp; vision insurance coverage for you &amp; your loved one.</li><li>401k program&nbsp;</li><li>An Oculus Quest 2 - Our All Hands meetings and Engagement events are done in VR</li><li>Flexible work schedule and paid time to create your work/life harmony</li><li>An international team of highly talented and engaged people from different cultural backgrounds and locations.</li><li>The latest technology and equipment to do your best work from your home office</li><li>Be an OG in a young project that is already making 🌊</li><div>That's all to say: these job listings are approximations!&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>If you are passionate about the employee experience, you want to be challenged, and you want to work with a supportive and energetic team, then we’d love to hear from you. We are all generalists who like to dip our toes into different fields and skillsets, so if a job isn't a 100% fit, don't worry!</div><div><br></div><div>We’re proud to be an equal opportunity employer. We only care that you’re the best person for the job.</div><div><br></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/tari/e2106027-8978-4de8-81bb-f8c14f944c42/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/389046/tarilabs.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[tarilabs@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[20082bd3-12ce-46ad-8d7f-d896825fa014]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Tari Labs]]></employer_name>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Android Developer - Fresh/Junior]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Singapore]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><div><br></div><div>We are looking for a talented Android Developer to join our team.</div><div><br></div><div>This is a full-time permanent position that is based in Singapore. We are open to candidates with little to ~3 years of commercial programming experience assuming you are strong in Computer Science basics and passionate about engineering/crypto.</div><br/>Responsibilities:<br/><li>Have some experience in Android development.</li><li>Knowledge of computer system structure, algorithm, network, database and computer security.</li><li>Work together with cross-functional teams to define, design, and ship new features.</li><li>Ensure the best possible performance, quality, and responsiveness of the applications.</li><li>Help maintain code quality and organization.</li><div><br></div><br/>Requirement<br/><li>Bachelor's/Master's degree in computer science, engineering or equivalent industry experience.&nbsp;</li><li>Proficient in java/Kotlin, and familiar with Android framework.</li><li>Good familiarity with third-party libraries and APIs, such as OKHTTP, RxJava, Coroutines.</li><li>Good knowledge of the general mobile landscape, architectures, trends, and emerging technologies.</li><li>Have hybrid technology experience.</li><li>Experience in large APP development</li><li>Familiar with Flutter development</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/20c813d5-5367-4b35-8697-e790e38f1615/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[UX Writer II]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kraken]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://kraken.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div><b style="font-size: 18px">About Kraken</b></div><div><br></div><div>Our mission is to accelerate the adoption of cryptocurrency so that you and the rest of the world can achieve financial freedom and inclusion. In our first decade, Kraken has risen to become one of the largest, most successful and respected crypto exchanges on the planet.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>We are changing the way the world thinks about finance and our range of successful products are playing a critical role in the mainstream adoption of crypto assets. We continue to trail-blaze into new territory with the introduction of Kraken Bank, providing a more seamless integration between crypto and the traditional financial system. This makes us the first crypto company (ever) to be awarded a U.S. state banking charter.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Our diverse group of 2,000+ Krakenites are distributed all over the world as part of our 'remote first' culture, united by a shared passion for delighting customers, upholding crypto values and achieving our meaningful mission. We attract people who push themselves to improve, are radically transparent and think differently in order to unlock their potential.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Crypto is a rapidly evolving industry and we’re just getting started. We’re growing fast and you're invited to join the revolution!</div><div><br></div><div><b style="font-size: 18px">About this role</b></div><div><br></div><div>As a UX writer, you’re an advocate for Kraken design principles, influencing product experiences across platforms by creating useful, meaningful copy that helps our clients achieve their goals. You help define the vision and narratives across multiple trading platforms and applications. You collaborate with people in a variety of UX design-related roles including product managers, developers, marketing and customer experience teams to establish a unified voice across all of our products. You consistently use empathy, logic and data to inform content choices and thrive when challenged to solve the new and unknown.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>You’re also a content strategist, defining product vision and narratives across multiple platforms and products you will co-own with designers as the content subject matter expert. You will drive guidelines and document best practices, oversee complex omnichannel projects, and work with leadership to establish product goals.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>User experience is at the core of how we create intuitive, innovative trading experiences for Kraken clients. We strive to learn and understand their unique needs, behaviors, and emotions to gather insights that inform product strategy and design. We work together on collaborative teams, all unified under a single goal to make cryptocurrency easy and accessible to everyone.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Throughout the history of civilization, there have been a handful of moments that changed the course of how we think about wealth and equality. The discovery of gold, the creation of paper money, mortgages, ATMs. We’re at the next of those moments <b>right now</b>, and there is no more exciting place to invest your creativity than directly at this intersection of technology and adventure.&nbsp;</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Use writing and editing skills to write UX microcopy that facilitates user navigation, onboarding, error messages, instructional materials, and other pieces of the complete user experience</li><li>Drive vision for product and content across a product or subject-matter domain, and ensure cohesive product narratives by documenting your strategies with guidelines and best practices</li><li>Collaborate with designers, legal, marketing, product managers, and engineers. Influence and adapt to stakeholders and their feedback</li><li>Provide UX writing and content strategy leadership to the team throughout the product development process</li><br/>Minimum qualifications<br/><li>Bachelor's degree in English, Communications, Journalism, Technical Writing, UX or equivalent practical experience</li><li>4 years of experience in user-centered product writing such as software, web or app based products</li><li>Experience creating content for multi-disciplinary projects</li><li>A portfolio of UX writing samples</li><div><br></div><br/>Preferred qualifications<br/><li>Experience with finance, cryptocurrency and blockchain technologies</li><li>Experience with localization tools and accessibility best practices</li><li>Knowledge of online technology and related products, including web and mobile UI and tools</li><li>Familiarity with UX research principles, best practices and how to use data to drive informed user insights</li><div>Location Tagging: #EU #US <span style="font-size: 15px">#CANADA&nbsp;#APAC&nbsp;#LI-Remote </span></div><div><br></div><div>We’re powered by people from around the world with their own unique and diverse experiences. We value all Krakenites and their talents, contributions, and perspectives, regardless of their background.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>As an equal opportunity employer we don’t tolerate discrimination or harassment of any kind. Whether that’s based on race, ethnicity, age, gender identity, citizenship, religion, sexual orientation, disability, pregnancy, veteran status or any other protected characteristic as outlined by federal, state or local laws.&nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div>Check out all our open roles at&nbsp;<a href="https://www.kraken.com/careers" class="postings-link">https://www.kraken.com/careers</a>. &nbsp;</div><div><br></div><div><b><span style="font-size: 18px">Stay in the know</span></b></div><div><br></div><div><b><a href="https://twitter.com/krakenfx" class="postings-link">Follow us on Twitter</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://blog.kraken.com/" class="postings-link">Catch up on our blog</a></b></div><div><b><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/kraken-exchange/" class="postings-link">Follow us on LinkedIn</a></b></div>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/kraken/d3f2ced7-16af-4a7e-b14f-7c5ee5d9756e/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/141006/kraken_new.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kraken@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3fb432db-ca35-4833-8307-f0a44eb39242]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kraken]]></employer_name>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Financial Analyst]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://bitcoindepot.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Atlanta]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bitcoin Depot&lt;/strong&gt; is seeking an experienced and dynamic &lt;strong&gt;Senior Financial Analyst&lt;/strong&gt; who is passionate about driving finance strategy and business impact to partner with our rapidly growing business.&amp;nbsp; This position will report and work directly with the VP of Finance. The ideal candidate will contribute both at both hands-on and strategic levels. This is a full time role located in our Atlanta office.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Bitcoin Depot is one of the largest multi-cryptocurrency ATM Networks in the world offering users the ability to buy and sell Bitcoin, Litecoin, and Ethereum instantly at hundreds of locations. Our mission is to provide the most secure, convenient, and fastest cryptocurrency transaction. Our vision is to bring cryptocurrency market to the masses.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive the forecasting and reporting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Provide variance analysis on monthly results.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Partner with leadership to provide analytical support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assist in preparation of senior management financial reviews, including preparation of presentation materials&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support strategic business initiatives - assess and report their impact vs. expectations (Breakthroughs, Software, NPI, and Productivity tracking).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Continuous improvement and development of world-class FP&amp;amp;A processes through a relentless focus on leveraging &amp;amp; expanding reporting capabilities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s Degree.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-4 years of progressive finance experience.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Working Tableau knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Financial modeling experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experience with financial reporting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal &amp;amp; communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Excellent problem solving and analytical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Drive to meet commitments/deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ability to apply good judgment to business planning and annual planning processes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong business partnering/team building skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Assertive, Initiative, positive attitude, self-starter, gets-things-done attitude.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strong personal computing skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Benefits&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Competitive Salary&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;401K Matching&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generous PTO&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Health benefits offered with a company contribution towards premiums&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wellness benefits&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Casual dress environment when in office&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Monthly company celebrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Advancement opportunities based on results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/bitcoindepot/jobs/4817423003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/556151/bitcoin-depot-image-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[bitcoindepot@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[49753fb8-b518-4786-89b5-9d1bf0e19ac0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Bitcoin Depot]]></employer_name>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Director Infosec Governance Risk and Compliance]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Through our blockchain technology and rapidly growing network of financial institutions, Ripple is improving the global financial system and increasing economic inclusion for more people, in more places around the world.&amp;nbsp; Ripple is looking for a passionate Information Security leader to build a world class Information Security program.&amp;nbsp; As a leader on the Information Security team, you will help us achieve this mission by actively working to protect our staff, company, and the larger crypto communities we engage with.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In this role, you will build and lead a team of GRC professionals to deliver exceptional security solutions and processes.&amp;nbsp; You will collaborate across the business with other leaders in Engineering, Product, IT, Legal, and Compliance to ensure Ripple maintains a world class security posture.&amp;nbsp; This role reports directly to the Head of Information Security.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT YOU’LL DO:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead organizational efforts to accomplish SOC2 Type II, ISO 27001 and other certifications and attestations to demonstrate cybersecurity assurance internally and to our customers&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Scale our GRC organization to meet financial services requirements on a global scal&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Co-create and help articulate Information Security strategy across the company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Support the development and maintenance of cybersecurity policies, standards, and guidelines in alignment with applicable laws, common security frameworks and best practices&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive the closure of gaps and control improvements with internal teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Lead automated evidence collection efforts to ensure our controls are durable and consistent&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track, remediate and report on risks and guide risk reduction through the GRC system&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop consistent processes for identifying potential risk events, quantifying and documenting the probability of occurrence and impact on the business&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE’RE LOOKING FOR:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with building GRC programs at high growth companies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;8+ years of experience in the field of Cybersecurity, Cyber Risk and GRC&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Co-create and help articulate Information Security strategy across the company&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A track record of hiring talented cybersecurity professionals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proficiency with common information security frameworks including SOC2, NIST CSF, and ISO 27001&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ideal candidate has experience acquiring MTL’s on a national and international level&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Inclusive leadership and teamwork skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Results oriented, values collaboration, self-motivated&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Someone willing to adapt to change in a fast moving environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our UK/EU applicant privacy notice &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3663199?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
  </job>
</jobs>
