<jobs>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[SEO Copywriter (Russian)]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[OKEx]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[http://www.okex.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Anywhere (Remote)]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About OKEx:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKEx is a world-leading digital asset trading platform, providing advanced financial services to traders globally by using blockchain technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;OKEx provides hundreds of token &amp;amp; futures trading pairs to help traders to optimize their strategy. We are also one of the top digital asset trading platforms by trading volume, serving millions of users in over 100 countries. OKEx derivatives remains a top-notch venue globally and has a daily volume of approximately $10 billion and is widely recognized as the golden standard in the industry. We believe the blockchain technology will eliminate barriers to transactions, increase the efficiency of transactions across society, and eventually have a significant impact on the global economy. We strive to make innovative achievements that change the world and never stop to improve on our customer experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Team:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are a highly motivated and result-oriented mixture of specialists with different backgrounds. What we value the most is the ability to learn, speak up and to collaborate. We are open, curious and we love to test even the craziest ideas and share our knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About the Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a tech-savvy Russian content writer to produce and manage stellar and unique content for both Google and Yandex. As a part of the team, you will be responsible for helping define the content strategy, write SEO copy for landing pages, perform keyword and&amp;nbsp; industry research and coordinate with various internal stakeholders to collect info needed and help create successful landing pages to help our user base.&amp;nbsp; We strongly believe that SEO is a crucial lever for our growth strategy; the topic has full support from top management including funding for tools and infrastructure. To be successful you will need to gain a significant understanding about the blockchain space and come up with innovative content ideas and write engaging copy to excite the community and help translate content into landing pages. You need to be a passionate content writer and creator who can think out of the box and be able to successfully convey what&#39;s unique about our brand to both technical and non technical audiences.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Participate in building our SEO content strategy for our new landing pages&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform in depth analysis and keyword research to help unlock growth across our verticals&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Proofread and write content for blog posts, ads, press releases, articles, infographics, studies, website, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Perform basic SEO keyword research and incorporate the findings in the copy&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce ideas for new content formats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Measure content performance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Produce relevant content targeting both technical and non technical audiences&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with designers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Research industry trends to gain a good technical understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fluency in Russian (written and spoken)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Degree in Journalism or Communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 years experience as a copywriter and a portfolio with published content&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Must have minimum 3 years experience in the tech space and very good technical understanding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Blockchain &amp;amp; crypto experience is a STRONG plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2-3 years working with SEO &amp;amp; Google Analytics is a huge plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/x9kSkBMcOuo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/okex/jobs/4839070003?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/175406/okex.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[okex@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[bcbc2afc-a2fd-45d8-bba3-e7ce4b53b3d8]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[OKEx]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Social Media Lead - Global Corporate Comms]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Luno]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[London]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The world is changing. We all want something different.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Luno, we see you as an individual, and we want to unleash your potential and empower you to become the best possible version of yourself.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno welcomes crypto lovers and crypto newbies. You - just like everyone in the world - are on your own unique crypto-learning journey.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a mission-driven cryptocurrency company that is building more open and equal access to the future of money. You don&#39;t have to know lots about crypto to be interested in joining us, you just have to feel that upgrading the world to a fairer financial system matters, and that you&#39;d like to be part of this global change. We&#39;re a passionate and committed team taking on a challenge of epic proportions. Like the first moon landing, it requires a special kind of people working together with unusual skill, focus and determination. We need the best team on board for our mission.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;If that sounds like a culture you&#39;d thrive in, then we are excited to hear from you.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A little about us&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno means moon in Esperanto, we chose the name because at night, wherever you are in the world, you look up at the same moon. We believe in the power of working together, as one team, across borders, with clear focus and shared purpose.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our popular mobile app and website helps people around the world grow and manage their money using the world&#39;s most mature cryptocurrencies: Bitcoin, Ethereum and USDC. We&#39;ve processed over $ 21 billion to date.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Over 9 million customers across 40 countries have chosen to hold their crypto wallets on Luno because we offer a delightfully simple experience and bank-grade security.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re part of the Digital Currency Group, named in 2021 as one of TIME magazine&#39;s 100 Most Influential Companies, in the “Disruptors” category alongside Tesla, AirBnB, SpaceX, Peloton. TIME noted that DCG is &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://time.com/collection/time100-companies/5953752/digital-currency-group/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;“mainstreaming cryptocurrency”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; .&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We&#39;re proud to be one of the world&#39;s most international cryptocurrency teams, with colleagues from 43 different nationalities working across South Africa, Indonesia, the United Kingdom, Malaysia, Nigeria, Australia and Singapore. Financial inclusion is part of our mission, but on a deeper level, inclusion is a way of life, and a way of work for us. It is part of who we are as a company, and a group of human individuals.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The role in a nutshell&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will be a lead resource on the global team at Luno which is responsible for all social media content distribution, community management, and reporting across multiple regions and on various platforms. Your chief responsibilities will be in curating content for Luno’s corporate brand on social channels, as well as engaging as Luno on social media so as to establish the brand as a trusted thought leader and employer of choice. Whether it be industry thinkpiece content, CEO amplification, engineering and product content, or employer branding, you will need to liaise with internal stakeholders to bring this content to life. You will report to the global head of social engagement, and be a part of the global social engagement team, stationed across many continents.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;In addition to this, you will be required to take charge of the team for approximately 4 months when the head of the department will be on maternity leave. This will mean managing the regional team leads of our general social media brand presence, nurturing strong relationships with local and global stakeholders, and being answerable for the success of Luno’s social media channels during this time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your mission&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Deeply understanding the global corporate brand communication goals and using all moments of community engagement as an opportunity to further them both.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Be the voice of the Luno corporate brand across all relevant social media channels. You will be our brand’s voice on all things crypto and Luno in order to drive an increase in corporate brand awareness through thought leadership, position Luno as an employer of choice, and maintain healthy online relationships with press and news contacts.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You will respond to all incoming queries, requests and complaints on our corporate comms channels, tailor responses to each individual that is engaged with, offering two-way genuine communication, follow crisis comms procedures should an incident arise, create synergy between the content we publish and the engagement in the comments, and collaborate with your peers and across the timezones.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Partner with global and local stakeholders to help craft the content calendar for the channels in your remit, manage publishing across these channels, and compile regular and ad hoc social media reports on wins &amp;amp; misses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Share best practices across your team as a senior member of the team, exploring new tools and processes, helping to develop efficient workflow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage the social engagement team as a maternity cover, and generally serve as a team 2iC.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ideal Lunaut for this role will have&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A wealth of experience in social media management.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong people management skills and leadership competency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using social media engagement, reporting, and listening tools.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A wealth of experience and knowledge on social media best practices, trends, and post formats.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good spelling and grammar, with a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; keen eye that pays attention to detail.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent written communication skills, with an understanding of how to translate complex topics and technologies into easy to understand messaging.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Empathy and the ability to relate to others.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Good time management, knowing how to prioritise important and urgent matters to get the most out of a busy team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Initiative, knowing how to problem solve and think quickly on their feet.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The ability to work well in a team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Luno is a ‘remote but reachable’ company! At Luno, we trust that people can do their work effectively anywhere and provide Lunauts with the flexibility to decide where they do their best work. For some of us, that’s at home for the majority of the time, for others, that might mean joining other Lunauts in person at one of our Luno workspaces more often. Luno is built on our relationships, so we still value in-person connection and have a minimum expectation of spending time in person once a quarter. So as long as you are based in one country with a Luno workspace, we want to hear from you!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: center;&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are an equal opportunity employer and value diversity at our company. We do not negatively discriminate on the basis of race, religion, colour, national origin, gender, sexual orientation, age, marital status, veteran status, or disability status.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yq6lSA5uNYA" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://www.luno.com/en/careers/apply/3698248?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145517/luno.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[luno@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[d4a1d4d5-b5b6-4f82-b913-953220c869d0]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Luno]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Marketing & PR ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Blockchain Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ankr]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.ankr.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Amsterdam, North Holland, Netherlands]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Description</p><p>ABOUT ANKR</p><p>Ankr provides Web3 infrastructure for easy, accessible and affordable deployment of blockchain nodes, API’s, decentralized staking infrastructure and Layer 2 scaling solutions, designed to lower the entry barrier for everyday people, enterprises, and developers to contribute to blockchain ecosystems. Check us out at <a href="https://www.ankr.com/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">https://www.ankr.com/</a></p><p><br>Ankr was founded in 2017 in Berkeley, California. Its founding team and headquarters are based in San Francisco. Ankr’s distributed team of 50+ people operates from offices in San Francisco, Shanghai, Moscow, and Amsterdam.<br></p><p>Responsibilities:</p><ul> <li>Design, code and implement business applications</li> <li>Integrate blockchains with our platform</li> <li>Work with APIs and microservices</li> <li>Design and verify cryptographic protocols deployed on the blockchain</li> <li>Define requirements, prototype and design new features for product users</li> <li>Effectively communicate technical details via documentation and demonstration</li> </ul><p>Requirements</p><ul> <li>Proven track record of developing modern, secure, scalable complex applications</li> <li>Practical experience with crypto tokenomics, blockchain consensus protocols, P2P networks, cryptographic principles, key management, encryption algorithms</li> <li>Ability to use <a href="https://web3.foundation/about/" rel="nofollow noreferrer noopener" class="external">Web3 tech stack</a> </li> <li>Familiarity or ability to use Solidity, EVM or Polkadot Substrate</li> <li>Back-end: GoLang (Go) (or C++/Rust)</li> <li>Great listener and communicator</li> <li>Bilingual or high fluency in English</li> <li>Leadership and teamwork skills</li> <li>Able to provide open source code samples</li> </ul><p>Benefits</p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://apply.workable.com/ankr/j/F6B8ACECFD/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/746707/ankr-logo.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ankr@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3b58522a-6fba-41ac-b017-94bbed42523c]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ankr]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Crawler Development Engineer]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Binance]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.binance.com/en]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Remote - Asia]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[<div>Binance is the global blockchain company behind the world’s largest digital asset exchange by trading volume and users, serving a greater mission to accelerate cryptocurrency adoption and increase the freedom of money.</div><div><br></div><div>Are you looking to be a part of the most influential company in the blockchain industry and contribute to the crypto-currency revolution that is changing the world?</div><br/>Responsibilities<br/><li>Participate in the design and development of crawler systems, capture and analyze multi-platform information, and improve and enhance crawler efficiency.</li><li>esearch various anti-crawling strategies, quickly solve various technical problems, and monitor crawler progress and early warning processing in real time.</li><li>Collaborate with the big data team to manage, analyze, analyze, and apply results.</li><br/>Requirements<br/><li>Solid foundation in Python or Java, familiar with multi-process and multi-thread programming.</li><li>Familiar with common crawler frameworks Scrapy, Selenium, Webmagic, Puppeteer/Pyppeteer, etc., and have a strong enthusiasm for new knowledge and technology.</li><li>In-depth understanding of HTTP and various login authentication mechanisms can solve problems such as image verification code/slider/account restriction/ip restriction.</li><li>Familiar with common anti-climbing strategies, experience in JS anti-climbing, APP anti-climbing, packet capture analysis, anti-climbing strategy detection, reverse and other fields is preferred.</li><li>Have a strong sense of responsibility and teamwork spirit, clear thinking, good communication skills and technical learning skills.</li><div><b>Working at Binance</b></div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Do something meaningful; Be a part of the future of finance technology and the no.1 company in the industry</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Fast moving, challenging and unique business problems</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     International work environment and flat organisation</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Great career development opportunities in a growing company</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Possibility for relocation and international transfers mid-career</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Competitive salary</div><div><span style="font-size: 10px">•</span>     Flexible working hours, Casual work attire</div><p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/TkgHFA3fp5g" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://jobs.lever.co/binance/45a9783e-a99f-48ab-9d4a-887ddd5f1042/apply?ref=crypto-careers.com]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/145896/binance.jpg]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[binance@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[3638d60f-1c89-4146-a69f-e9b3de672b11]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Binance]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Engineering And Tech ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Program Manager, NFTs]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[projectmanagerteamlead]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Ripple]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://ripple.com/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[False]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[San Francisco, CA, United States]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ripple’s Creator Fund was developed to foster innovation in tokenization, with a focus on non-fungible tokens (NFTs). The fund provides targeted support for creators, brands and marketplaces to explore new use cases for NFTs on the XRP Ledger (XRPL), leveraging its innate advantages of speed, cost and sustainability.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ripple is looking to hire a Program Manager for the Creator Fund program. As a member of the RippleX team, you will engage with external developers, agencies, creators, and brands to bring a diverse set of tokenization projects to the XRP Ledger. You will own the $250M Creator Fund, leading strategy and operational execution of the fund, and ensure all participants have an excellent experience from their application to execution of NFT projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What You’ll Do:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Build and own the operating model for administering $250M to NFT ecosystem participants building on XRPL.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Handle pre- and post-fund administration and oversight of projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Manage strategy and day to day execution with marketplaces, agencies, creators, and brands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Own the budget, planning, and allocation of resources across projects.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop streamlined approval processes with relevant internal stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Drive and ensure regular, ongoing communication and coordination across functions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Facilitate efficient meetings to ensure information exchange and alignment across teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Monitor, analyze, and report on the fund applicants and their progress over time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Define and measure success metrics, and assist with the preparation of progress reports.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work collaboratively with Legal and Finance to create effective and efficient disbursement processes&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Recommend and contribute to process improvements, including product enhancements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Coordinate with Marketing to promote and drive applicants to ensure the ongoing success of the Creator Fund.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We’re Looking for:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5+ years of work experience; 2+ experience in enterprise startup&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience in a fast paced start-up environment is a big plus.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A strong interest, curiosity and passion for digital assets / crypto markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Understanding of the NFT ecosystem.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience in managing global Grant/fund programs at scale.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Demonstrated experience in implementing policies and procedures across various internal stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to build and manage relationships with creative agencies, developers, and creators and brands.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding organizational abilities and interpersonal skills to develop strong working relationships.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong background in marketing.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Serious attention to detail and commitment to excellence.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Proactive, energetic and relentless towards driving progress.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Outstanding verbal and written communication skills.&amp;nbsp; Strong presentation skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent problem solving skills / comfort with ambiguity. You should be able to take a problem and structure a solution or recommendation with incomplete or limited data.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Excellent time management skills.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHAT WE OFFER:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The chance to work in a fast-paced start-up environment with experienced industry leaders&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A learning environment where you can dive deep into the latest technologies and make an impact&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Competitive salary and equity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;100% paid medical and dental and 95% paid vision insurance for employees starting on your first day&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;401k (with match), commuter benefits&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Industry-leading parental leave policies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Generous wellness reimbursement and weekly onsite programs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Flexible vacation policy - work with your manager to take time off when you need it&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Employee giving match&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Modern office in San Francisco’s Financial District&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully-stocked kitchen with organic snacks, beverages, and coffee drinks&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Weekly company meeting - ask me anything style discussion with our Leadership Team&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Team outings to sports games, happy hours, game nights and more!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WHO WE ARE:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple is doing for value what the internet did for information: enabling its instant and seamless flow around the world. We call this the Internet of Value (IoV). Using blockchain and cryptocurrency technology, Ripple is dedicated to creating powerful gains in financial efficiency, equity and inclusion. In addition, Ripple is developing and enabling the future use cases that will catalyze the new digital economy for governments, businesses and consumers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ripple has offices in San Francisco (HQ), New York, London, Mumbai, Singapore, São Paulo, Reykjavík, Washington D.C. and Dubai.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ripple is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We’re committed to building a diverse and inclusive team. We do not discriminate against qualified employees or applicants because of race, color, religion, gender identity, sex, sexual preference, sexual identity, pregnancy, national origin, ancestry, citizenship, age, marital status, physical disability, mental disability, medical condition, military status, or any other characteristic protected by local law or ordinance.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please find our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/eu-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;UK/EU Applicant Privacy Notice &lt;/a&gt;and our &lt;a href=&quot;https://ripple.com/ca-applicant-privacy-notice/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;California Applicant Privacy Notice&lt;/a&gt; for reference.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/xyWiO7ioTFo" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/ripple/jobs/3707090?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144615/riple.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[ripple@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[4d3e7506-ac7d-4756-9b59-070be3efa0d6]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Ripple]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Product Management ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Senior Designer - Contract Position]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[seniorlevel]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Kiva]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.kiva.org/]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[U.S Remote]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About us:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kiva (&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://kiva.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;kiva.org&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;) &lt;/span&gt;is an international nonprofit with a mission to expand financial access to help underserved communities thrive. We run a global marketplace platform to crowdfund microloans for financially excluded entrepreneurs, farmers and students around the world. &lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Through Kiva Capital, we serve as a bridge between large scale impact first investors and underserved populations. Our digital identity platform enables borrowers who don’t have a track record with traditional financial institutions to record and verify their financial history and gain access to less costly mainstream financial markets. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Our organization combines the culture and technological passion of an internet start-up with the compassion and empathy of a non-profit to create impact and opportunity at global scale. &lt;/span&gt;Since 2005, we have raised more than $1.66 billion in loan capital for 4.1 million borrowers in 77 countries. Our lenders fund over $10 million in loans every month. With offices in San Francisco, Portland, New York, Nairobi, and Bangkok, Kiva&#39;s team includes 100+ employees and 400+ volunteers worldwide. Our team is growing as we pursue exciting new opportunities to create a financially inclusive world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Role overview:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;This is for a 4 - 6 month, remote contract position working for the Creative Studio at &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kiva.org/&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Kiva&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; (kiva.org) - starting as soon as feasible.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;As a Contract Senior Designer, you’ll partner with Kiva’s Creative Studio team. The Creative Studio designs, writes and executes marketing campaigns to drive awareness of Kiva and acquisition of new lenders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The Senior Designer/ Contractor will work directly with the Creative Director. You’ll also work closely with other designers and writers on the Studio team, as well as cross-functionally with the Marketing and Content teams.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At this time, we can only consider applicants with authorization to work in the United States on a permanent, full-time basis; unfortunately we cannot provide visa sponsorship.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key responsibilities include:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Develop concepts for, and design creative, as part of our Tentpole and Evergreen campaigns. Campaign elements include email, social media posts, web and mobile UX, landing pages, and other channels as they are needed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Bring to life the Kiva story and develop communications that engage consumers with emotive design,&amp;nbsp; while driving acquisition of new lenders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work collaboratively with other members of the creative team.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Absorb Kiva Brand style guide and design within those guidelines.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Create engaging animations for campaign elements and catalog them in Google Drive.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work within our Project Management tool to complete tasks on time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Work on multiple campaigns and deliverables at once with ease.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Regularly bring new ideas to the team, have a curious mindset, and a desire to always improve our creative.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We are a small team, the Senior Designer Contractor needs to actively look for places to help others and be willing to jump in on tasks when asked for help.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Help mentor other designers on the team, providing feedback and guidance based on your experiences.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Preferred qualifications:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;5-7 years of experience designing marketing creative at an agency or in-house creative studio.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to decipher a brief and convert that into compelling, succinct designs/ concepts.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with documentary-style/human-centric storytelling creative/ emotive design.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A clear understanding of advertising/marketing/ direct response design best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with designing a variety of channels - social, email, website, mobile, landing pages with a thorough understanding of best practices.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong proficiency in designing in Figma.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience using Google Suite.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A curious nature (ask questions and learn).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ideally 30-40 hrs/week with some flexibility.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we offer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A competitive hourly rate paid on a monthly billing cycle.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Fully remote working, anywhere within the U.S.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;An opportunity to improve real lives, solve hard problems, and change the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Friendly, supportive, and adventurous environment with a team of engaged colleagues.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Opportunities to connect with and learn from colleagues and partners around the world.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When applying:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please submit a resume or LinkedIn (or other) profile that showcases your work history and experience&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Please include samples of relevant work that you have done - samples that showcase how you would be a good fit for working on Kiva campaigns.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;A diverse and inclusive workplace where we learn from each other is an integral part of Kiva&#39;s culture. We actively welcome people of different backgrounds, experiences, abilities and perspectives. We are an equal opportunity employer and a great place to work. Join us and help us achieve our mission!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We will only accept applications directly from candidates. Kiva will not be responsible for any recruiting agency fees, absent a formal agreement.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/IEdy6XHkd9k" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/kivaorg/jobs/3714314?gh_jid=3714314&ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/194099/kiva.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[kiva@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[12467ec7-a781-4b48-abdb-bfbbc2a9cc79]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Kiva]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ UX / UI Design ]]></category>
  </job>
<job>
    <title><![CDATA[Account Executive, Public Sector, Nordics]]></title>
    <referencenumber><![CDATA[mid-level]]></referencenumber>
    <expiration_date><![CDATA[]]></expiration_date>
    <company><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></company>
    <company_url><![CDATA[https://www.chainalysis.com]]></company_url>
    <remote><![CDATA[True]]></remote>
    <location><![CDATA[Copenhagen, Denmark | Aarhus, Denmark]]></location>
    <city><![CDATA[]]></city>
    <state><![CDATA[]]></state>
    <zip/>
    <country><![CDATA[]]></country>
    <description><![CDATA[&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;The sales team responsible for our Nordic&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Law Enforcement / Central Government&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt; customers is driven by our mission to make the world a safer place by tracking and investigating activities that involve cryptocurrency like human trafficking, terrorist financing, and money-laundering. We’re experts on the “why” and the “how” with deep relationships and knowledge of navigating government sales processes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Account Executives are servant leaders who can quickly establish trust and build strong relationships with the Public Sector stakeholders, tailoring their sales approach to their needs, and evangelizing Chainalysis solutions in a compelling yet approachable way. We measure success by the attainment of assigned quota, accuracy of forecasting, and the growth of accounts in your region. They are experts at navigating complex sales cycles. and still enjoy the thrill creating a calculated account plan and then closing a deal. We measure your success by your ability to accurately forecast revenue and hit (read: exceed) quotas and the engagement of your team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In one year you’ll know you were successful if…&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve upskilled the team’s ability to drive sales wins by participating in and leading client and prospect meetings.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Stakeholders across the sales teams and rest of the company trust you and are eager to support and provide resources to your team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You’ve built transparent and valuable relationships with your team and have developed an effective and efficient strategy for recruiting, hiring, and training new Account Executives on the sales motion at Chainalysis.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your team has a reliable cadence for rhythm for forecast meetings and each team member’s forecast is accurate and documented in Salesforce.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Your team’s closure rates have increased and customer churn has decreased because of your direct coaching and mentorship.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Senior sales management can trust and rely on your forecasts and sales activity to inform the overall sales strategy across the business.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;You know the intricacies of your teams’ sales activity and track the results to inform your forecasts and individual development plans.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A background like this helps:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Recent experience managing and closing complex software sales within Public Sector customers in any of the Nordic markets.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience managing the sales cycle from mission/program manager to agency leadership&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Strong relationships in the System Integrator and Defense community&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Key industry knowledge and ability to effectively articulate the Chainalysis value proposition&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Track record of over-achieving quota (top 10-20% of company) in past positions&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Ability to negotiate pricing, terms and conditions and other concessions in complex, multi-year sales agreements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;History of scaling and coaching high-performing and diverse sales teams&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Experience with Financial Intelligence, Blockchain, Cyber Security, and/or Cryptocurrency technologies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;#LI-MJ1&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;content-conclusion&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we help government agencies, cryptocurrency businesses, and financial institutions track and investigate illicit activity on the blockchain, allowing them to engage confidently with cryptocurrency. We take care of our people with great benefits, professional development opportunities, and fun.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You belong here.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;At Chainalysis, we believe that diversity of experience and thought makes us stronger. With both customers and employees around the world, we are committed to ensuring our team reflects the unique communities around us. Some of the ways we’re ensuring we keep learning are an internal Diversity Committee, Days of Reflection throughout the year including International Women’s Day, Juneteenth, Harvey Milk Day, and International Migrant’s Day, and a commitment to continue revisiting and reevaluating our diversity culture.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;We encourage applicants across any race, ethnicity, gender/gender expression, age, spirituality, ability, experience and more. Additionally, if you need any accommodations to make our interview process more accessible to you due to a disability, don&#39;t hesitate to let us know. You can learn more &lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/Interview%20Accommodations%20Request.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. We can’t wait to meet you.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;font-weight: 400;&quot;&gt;Applying from the EU? Please review our &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.chainalysis.com/rs/503-FAP-074/images/GDPR%20Notice.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Candidate GDPR Notice.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/0ZgkZLn.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;97&quot; height=&quot;136&quot;&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.powertofly.com/best-work-from-home-companies-2649504754.html?rebelltitem=10#rebelltitem10&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/HNMvlj9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; width=&quot;187&quot; height=&quot;134&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;By submitting this application, I consent to and authorize Chainalysis to contact my former employers, and any and all other persons and organizations for information bearing upon my qualifications for employment.&amp;nbsp; I further authorize the listed employers, schools and personal references to give Chainalysis (without further notice to me) any and all information about my previous employment and education, along with other pertinent information they may have, and hereby waive any actions which I may have against either party(ies) for providing a reference.&amp;nbsp; I understand any future employment will be contingent on the Company receiving satisfactory employment references.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - USA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;2600&quot;&gt;All employees are required to have or obtain a COVID-19 vaccination as a condition of employment at Chainalysis, unless an exemption has been approved. All employees shall be required to report their vaccine status. All new employees shall be required to provide proof of their vaccination status prior to the start of their employment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - EMEA&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;As an employer, Chainalysis is obliged to ensure a healthy and safe working environment. This means that we must try to prevent the coronavirus from spreading inside the workplace and all employees are obliged to follow the local regulations issued by the relevant health authorities.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3483&quot;&gt;To help support a safe work environment, we encourage all employees in EMEA to get fully vaccinated against COVID-19.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3602&quot;&gt;Employees will not be required to attend an event or in-person customer meeting.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;3784&quot;&gt;Employees in the EU and the UK are allowed to travel internationally for internal meetings to any country deemed “green or amber” by the EU and the UK authorities. All attendees for Chainalysis in-person events or meetings will be required to adhere to the following guidelines:&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4068&quot;&gt;International travel will only be permitted if you receive approval from both your manager and Executive Leader&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4183&quot;&gt;You must familiarize yourself and comply with any screening/safety protocols imposed by the entity/individual hosting the in-person meeting or event&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4335&quot;&gt;You must comply with any and all safety guidelines and travel restrictions established by applicable law&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li data-renderer-start-pos=&quot;4445&quot;&gt;If you are in close or proximate contact with others at the event/customer site and test positive for COVID-19, you must immediately notify the People Team and avoid contact with others for 10 days&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style=&quot;text-decoration: underline;&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Chainalysis COVID-19 Policy - APAC&lt;br&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;With circumstances changing on a regular basis and parts of our APAC team going in and out of mandatory lockdown, APAC will continue to follow country legislation and guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p style=&quot;text-align: left;&quot;&gt;&lt;sub&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://imgur.com/HNMvlj9&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/sub&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;<p><figure><iframe style="width: 500px; height: 281px;" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/yNpNz-FvSYQ" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen=""></iframe></figure></p>]]></description>
    <jobtype><![CDATA[]]></jobtype>
    <compensation_min/>
    <compensation_max/>
    <compensation_currency><![CDATA[USD]]></compensation_currency>
    <compensation_interval><![CDATA[Annually]]></compensation_interval>
    <apply_url><![CDATA[https://boards.greenhouse.io/chainalysis/jobs/5742950002?ref=crypto-careers.com#app]]></apply_url>
    <logo><![CDATA[https://www.crypto-careers.com/uploads/employer/logo/144926/chainalysis.png]]></logo>
    <url><![CDATA[]]></url>
    <apply_email><![CDATA[]]></apply_email>
    <contact_email><![CDATA[chainalysis@crypto-careers.com]]></contact_email>
    <date><![CDATA[]]></date>
    <updated><![CDATA[]]></updated>
    <employer_id><![CDATA[31de1ffa-3dc5-41f3-ae72-ed4cbf977d1b]]></employer_id>
    <featured><![CDATA[False]]></featured>
    <campaign_type/>
    <reference/>
    <employer_name><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></employer_name>
    <category><![CDATA[ Sales And Business Development ]]></category>
  </job>
</jobs>
